Grauman's
Chinese theater in Hollywood,
here comes, yes,
I believe it is.
It is, it's Katharine packard.
Turning to the local news,
another dismembered body of a
Hollywood woman was discovered
in the Hollywood
hills, late yesterday.
Homicide investigators
believe she was the victim
of the same psychopathic
killer who has murdered
and dismembered a number
of middle-aged women
in the Hollywood area.
Property owners voiced
their disapproval
of the disclosed
increases in property tax.
Today, an angry
administration is adhering
to the state bill
that's happening.
Oh.
She never gets sick,
except one time, on
the flight to Detroit,
she had one of those
breaded hot dogs, you know.
Folks, this is the home
of Katharine packard,
one of the most famous stars
of the motion picture screen.
Happily retired from the glamor
of the motion picture world,
she now devotes
her days of leisure
to benevolent social work and
her pet Hollywood charities.
This home was built at a cost
of over half a million dollars,
once a scene of lavish
Hollywood parties.
But she never gets sick
unless she has apple juice.
Just as much now
that I'm gonna be a star,
again, as I did before.
Everyone in Hollywood's gonna
be, absolutely everyone,
and it wouldn't be right
without you, would it, darling?
It's a real comeback.
So you see, you simply must
come to my little party.
Yes, oh, yes, darling, Ava,
Clark, yes, oh!
Must run!
Ooh.
J Dee, Dee, Dee, dah, dum,
da-dum, Dee, yah, yah
oh, just one more
glass of personality.
What happened to you?
To my dear, loving,
loyal friends.
Ah!
Let's go!
J Dee, dum, dum,
da, la, la, la, la
oh not like a start,
like a star.
Oh boy, you came.
How wonderful of you
all to have come.
I can't tell you how happy I am.
I can't believe that
you're all here.
Every one of you, I'm
glad that I had found you.
Oh, it's so
wonderful to see you.
Dickie, you did
fly in from Europe.
Oh, she looks divine.
Thank you, all!
And to you, Felix, you
know I gave her the brush,
just for my carpet.
I'm so happy I could cry.
She looks stunning tonight.
She looks lovely.
Oh, Lee, I'm glad I
caught you before you left.
How is she?
Well, she's broken
her lower tibia.
Oh, what does that mean?
Well, she'll be in
a cast for a while,
but she'll be all right.
She was drinking?
Yes.
Now I've ordered a wheelchair
and the registry is
sending over a nurse.
We'll get her on crutches
and keep her as
active as possible.
Well, I'll see if
I can cheer her up.
Thanks, Lee.
Hello, ira.
It's cold in here.
For god's sake, why don't
you turn on some heat?
I think you should know
that Katharine... - I know.
Lee's already told me.
Well, I can't watch
her every moment.
If I may say so, I don't
think it's good for her
to stay up in her room, all
the time, like she does.
Well, let's get her some films
to see in the projection room.
Leslie, I'd be careful
about the pills.
Don't leave anything up there
that she could use
to harm herself.
I've thought of that.
There's nothing.
Well, I better
get up and see her.
Katharine, please.
Stop.
- I'm only interested in...
- Ira.
I'm tired.
I'm awfully tired.
Forgive me.
I was going to say
that I am only interested
in your, in your welfare.
I know.
You've always been so damned
interested in my welfare.
Ira!
Yes?
You're an angel for coming by.
Nick, take me
to the club, will you?
Yes?
My name is Hardy,
Laurel n. Hardy.
Are you from the registry?
Yeah.
Oh, uh, come in, Mr. Hardy.
Miss packard's secretary
will interview you.
I didn't know that Katharine
packard was still around.
Around?
Well, she's very much around.
She's got a lot
more youth about her
than all the young
people you see
in films and
television nowadays.
They're all so callow.
Callow?
Yeah, callow and disgusting.
I take it you don't like
the modern generation.
Self-centered animals.
I don't think you
like me in particular.
I'm not the one that
does the hiring and firing.
Well, cheer up, sweetheart.
I may not get the job.
Miss Blair, Mr. Hardy
is here from the registry.
Why don't you sit
down, Mr. Hardy?
I'll be right with you.
She got the name wrong.
It's valance.
Miss packard has broken her leg.
You'll have to help her
with her wheelchair.
The elevator is out of service,
so she will have to be carried
up and down the stairs.
Do you drink?
Now and then.
Is there a decent interval
between the now and then?
Well, I can steer a straight
line with the wheelchair,
if that's what you mean.
You see, miss packard
is an alcoholic.
We don't allow spirits
on the premises.
No spirits.
Please make yourself
look more presentable.
You'll have to get a haircut
and wear a proper uniform.
You mean I got the job?
Yes.
Yeah, how does anybody
have too much success?
I'm unhappy because I
haven't had enough success.
Well, we should all be
grateful for what we have.
Thanks for the advice.
I'll remember it next time
somebody hands me a bedpan.
Hey, um, what's that?
Oh, it's an egg timer.
That's miss packard.
She wants her lunch.
I'll take it.
Oh no, I don't think...
1 guess it's about time for her
to meet her babysitter, right?
Look, I don't
think miss Blair...
Uh, where do I go?
Top of the stairs.
Chop chop!
Take it easy, Greta.
Too bad, sweetheart, the
callow youth got the job.
I did not mean to imply
that you're callow, Mr. Hardy.
I never judge a person
until I know him.
Well, it won't be so bad.
A broken leg is usually only
good for a couple of months.
I'm sure we'll learn
to get along, Mr. Hardy.
You can call me Laurel.
Laurel, Laurel n. Hard...
Greta, is that you?
Mildred?
You must be the ice cream man.
That's right.
What flavor would you like?
Vodka.
Sorry, all we got
is tutti-frutti.
Get out, get out of my bedroom.
You don't like tutti-frutti.
I don't like you.
I don't you, and I
don't want to know you.
Mildred, will you
get him outta here?
You best leave, Mr.
Whatever your name is.
I'll see what other
flavors I can find, right?
It's Mildred or Greta who
serve meals to miss packard.
If you're incapable of
fitting into our routine,
we'll make other arrangements.
Any questions?
Yeah, can we get
the elevator fixed?
No, the service
charge alone is $50.
Anything else?
You could've
told me you were the nurse.
But I had my nursey
costume on, right?
Fuse.
In the mornings, I like
to sit by the pendula.
And in the afternoon, I
like to sit by the pool.
Sometimes, I sneak
in a nap after lunch,
but don't worry, I'll
ring when I want you.
There's a buzzer
in my room, right?
Oh for god's sake, why
do you end every sentence
with a question Mark?
The buzzer's in the
pantry, I think.
You mean, you ring the buzzer,
and you don't know
where it rings?
It's not my concern
where it rings,
as long as it rings.
In other words, I hang around
wherever the buzzer rings
around three, right?
You make it
sound dreadfully difficult.
You know, man,
your house is so big.
Maybe I ought to put a taxi
meter on your wheelchair,
instead of being
paid by the week.
That's up to you.
Where does that go?
To the heart of this
house, the very heart.
After my husband died, and
I came back from Europe,
I closed those rooms, and
I stopped entertaining.
You know, it's a shame,
the state these gardens
have gotten into.
We used to have a wonderful
man who did everything,
and then one day he was gone.
Perhaps you could do
something about the gardens.
Do you have a green thumb?
Yeah, I'm pretty good at grass.
You'll have to figure it out.
Oh . - Say!
I remember you from
the silent movies.
You must be fatty arbuckle.
On!
Oh, wow . - Yeah.
Actually, I picked
up those jokes
from the encyclopedia
britannica.
- Hey, it's dark in here.
- Shh!
Why don't you use the light?
Be quiet.
- Where are we going?
- Shh!
Vic, are you
sure we should go in there?
This goes to the heart of
the house, the very heart.
Hey, what if miss packard
finds out we've been here?
Don't worry about it.
I have never been in this
part of the house before.
And this is where
Katharine packard entertained
in the elegant opulence
of her Hollywood home.
It's only a dummy.
This way to the rathskeller.
Don't be afraid.
And this is where
Katharine packard did some
of her most dedicated drinking.
Hey, Vic, what is a rathskeller?
I give up.
What an interesting room.
Ah, chartreuse.
She got here ahead of us.
Imagine being perched up
here in baronial splendor
on a cloud of gin fizz and
doing exactly as you like.
Most people who do
exactly as they like die.
Aren't you a clever
little fortune cookie.
You know, Vic, I don't
know anything about you,
not really, I mean.
What do you want to know?
Well, tell me about your
past, what you've done,
what you've learned,
what you want to do.
Look, I'm not
interested in the past.
All that counts is now.
But the past is many, many now,
and you're a collection
of all those nows.
All right.
My mother was a lush.
She slept around.
She ran off with a pimp, and
they put me in a foster home.
Is that the kind
of stuff you mean?
That's a beginning.
No.
That's the end.
Turn off the lights, Victor.
Come back.
Now, Victor, lean
back next to me.
Now put your arm around me.
Now say something
just lovely to me.
Like what?
Can't stand that
horrible cacophony.
Miss packard's
looking better today.
Maybe the poor dear's
health is improving.
Katharine.
Would you care to look these
over before I send them out?
He does bring some life
perhaps noise would
be the better word.
Oh, you don't
like music, darling?
I love music.
It's noise that offends me.
What are those
papers you want me to read?
I wish you'd told me you
asked him to clean the pool.
We had quite a scene about it.
You made me look foolish.
Oh, Leslie, let's not
have any difficulties today.
It's such a lovely day.
Here, I'll take care
of that, tomorrow.
Uh, tell me, what was the name
of that publicity man,
Jerry or something?
Jerry Flynn.
Yes, Jerry Flynn, call him.
Tell him I've been in Europe,
that I want to get
in the columns again
and do a few
personal appearances.
I'll even do television.
He can put me on one
of those vile talent
shows, if he likes.
I'll even do the
Christmas parade.
You don't really mean it.
Of course I mean it.
And have a trunk sent up.
I'm going to get rid
of all my old rags.
I'm going to get a
whole new wardrobe.
Now, Saturday night, we'll
have dinner in the east wing.
Call ira and Josef
and ask Mr. valance to join us.
Mr. valance?
Well, why not?
He's staying here in the house.
It would be rude not to ask him.
Mildred will have a good
deal of cleaning to do.
Oh yes, yes, everything
must be cleaned.
I want it all cleaned, all
the cobwebs brushed away,
the silver polished, the
crystal chandelier cleaned
so that it sparkles
we'll but the
candelabra on the table,
and Vic can cut some
flowers from the garden.
Did you know the roses
are all blooming?
They're just beautiful.
J here I go again
j I hear those
trumpets blow again
j all aglow again
j takin' a chance on love
j things are mending now
j I see a rainbow blending now
j we'll have a happy ending now
j takin' a chance on love
you know, your
mother has good taste.
But if you don't
get out of here,
I'll have to call the police.
- Oh god!
- You again!
Anybody in there?
Come on in, George is back!
Did you do anything
any good over there?
You touched my masterpiece.
Well, there's a lot...
Uh, what do you call it?
"Gastronomic rhythm."
This sort of work,
George, is unquestionably...
I used to be marvelous.
Right no the nuance.
Now will you get
him out of here!
You, uh, you want a drink?
Makes me sleepy.
Here.
Try one of these.
What is it?
It's a painkiller, man.
A painkiller?
Well, what do I need
a painkiller for?
'Cause you're in pain, man.
You sure?
Come on, Vic, stop it.
No ticky, no washy, huh?
There's a place for everything.
I know where that is.
Oh, Vic, there's
more to life than sex.
- No kidding.
- Hmm.
I was dying of some
mysterious illness,
and poor George Brent
didn't know about it.
I guess I missed that one.
Mm, that feels marvelous.
Now remember the
dinner party tonight,
sit up straight and
don't slur your words.
Oh, honestly, your
manners are atrocious.
Victor!
That's too hard.
- Sorry.
- Victor,
that, that hurt awfully.
Sometimes, you forget
how very strong you are.
I didn't realize
I was hurting you.
Kiss me, Victor.
Yes, you do have the eyes
of a raven.
Now don't forget,
dinner's at eight,
cocktails, seven, of course.
I'm sure you're gonna like ira.
He's really a darling.
You know, I think he's always
been secretly in love with me,
but he's never done or
said anything to me.
Hollywood was a
glamorous place, then.
It was glamorous.
Now it is just past now.
Yes, bitter.
I am bitter.
I needed time to
direct my pictures.
Creation is like vintage wine.
First, all the
elements must be right,
and then it takes time.
That's why my grapes are sour.
Mr. valance is
interested in acting.
I tried to explain
to him it isn't easy.
But like most young people,
he has an idealistic
point of view.
Well, Hollywood
is no place for an idealist.
Better for a masochist.
Yeah, that's what
they keep telling me,
down at the unemployment office.
Well, it takes dedication
and perseverance.
As in everything, one
must know one's goal
and go after it.
I'm sure Mr. valance knows what
he wants and will persevere.
Isn't that true, Mr. valance?
I'd like to show Mr.
Valance my gallery.
That's where Katharine
keeps her mementos.
I'd love to see those old
things again, Katharine.
But, uh, I'll run
off and fix my face.
Yes, by all means do.
So you're interested
in films, Mr. valance?
Oh well, yeah.
I was in an Andy warhol
movie, the other week.
War who?
Hol, warhol.
Oh, interesting.
What part did you play?
Oh, I just sat
there in the movie.
He forgets that she
was a mere puppet,
and I was the master.
What you see is really a
product of my imagination.
Oh please leave
me something, Josef.
After all, it was my legs they
admired, not yours.
Oh, now that's the costume
I wore in "samokhan."
Oh, yeah, that was
with Ronald Fairbanks.
Ronald colman.
Right.
So vivid in my memory,
as if it were yesterday.
Thank you.
Oh, Greta, you're
an astute person.
Astute?
If an older woman
showed a great deal
of generosity and
indulgence to a younger man,
wouldn't you think they
were having an affair?
I'm afraid I don't know anything
about that kind...
Excuse me, please.
Why don't you sit down, huh?
I told you I don't want to.
What's the matter with you?
This place gives me the creeps.
What are you talkin' about?
You and Katharine.
Come on, she's old enough
to be my grandmother.
Well, that doesn't seem to
make much difference, does it?
I don't intend on pushin'
the bedpan the rest of my life.
Do it my way, and we'll
have all the bread we want.
I don't want that kind of money.
And I don't my child to
have that kind of a father.
You're pregnant.
You really are a bastard!
Greta, come back here!
Come back!
What do you think
you're doin', huh?
What's the matter with you, huh?
- Let go of me!
- Look, there's nothing
to worry about.
These things can be fixed.
Let go of me, no!
Greta, I meant all
those promises I made.
You're just upset.
Gimme some time and we'll
get outta this dump.
Greta, come back here!
No, no.
Ah!
Greta, what is it?
Miss Blair, I'm
afraid I must go.
Go?
Why?
Well, I'd rather not discuss it.
It's just that I can't stay
in this house another day.
It's Mr. valance, isn't it?
Yes.
It hasn't been very
pleasant for any of us.
I'm packing.
I'll be leaving in the morning.
Before you go, tomorrow,
won't you come upstairs
with me and tell miss
packard why you're leaving?
- Well, I...
- Please.
It could solve all the
problems in this house.
It's best miss packard know
what kind of man Mr. valance is.
Yes.
Yes, I will.
Good.
Vic.
Vic!
Vic, are you there?
Listen to me, Vic.
I think I understand now.
Vic, you've got to
understand yourself.
Things between you and
miss packard could,
could only go badly, Vic.
She could never give you the
things that you've never had.
Vic?
Vic, I know you're there.
No!
Get out!
Get out.
Well, are you
burying your conscience
or trying to turn
over a new leaf?
Meaning what?
I'm talking about Greta.
It seems that Greta is
leaving us, this morning,
because of you.
Oh, it was, uh, just a few
kisses behind the bushes.
You might not find it so amusing
when she tells miss
packard why she's leaving.
Well, I'm sorry to ruin
your day, miss Blair,
but Greta has left.
Sleep well?
No, horribly.
You didn't ring for breakfast.
I didn't want any.
You know, a little
food might make you feel
a little better, you know.
I feel all right.
You know it's past 10 o'clock?
Where'd that watch come from?
Well, you bought
it for me, Katharine.
I did not.
Look, I told you
I needed a watch.
You said I could charge
one to you at Tiffany's.
What else have you bought?
What else have you
bought and charged to me?
Katharine, you said
I could have a watch.
Where's Leslie?
I never seem to
see Leslie anymore.
Tell her I feel she neglects me.
Of course, darling.
Maybe, uh, you should get
a little fresh air, huh?
We'll go for a drive,
this afternoon.
We could stop... - No.
No, I don't want
to go for a drive.
Oh, listen, we could
go down to Malibu.
And we could stop and have a
little drink on the way home.
How 'bout a little drink?
Go slowly, Vic.
It's so long since
I've been on the strip,
I want to see things.
I guess it's changed.
Oh yes, it has.
It was so glamorous once.
Say, how would you
like to go to a party?
A party, I'd love it.
I haven't been to
a party for ages.
Atwater Kent used
to have such lovely
Sunday afternoon parties,
oh, with the most interesting
people, strolling violins.
Oh such a tacky thing,
tacky New York fairy.
J go back-back, go back-back
j go back
isn't that Katharine packard?
Who's Katharine packard?
Oh, thank you.
Katharine packard, I
have a painting of you.
Thank you very much.
Hey!
I remember you.
You look divine, darling.
Oh.
My son saw you
in the Philippines
when you entertained the troops.
Oh, your son was in
the Spanish-American war?
Want coke, lady?
I'd much prefer a
deep-dish Martini.
No, I got coke, speed,
smack, grass and acid.
No, thank you.
The only trips I
take are to Europe.
I'll get you a vodka
Martini, miss packard.
Thanks.
Wow, I'm Katharine
packard's pusher.
Where'd you find
old Sarah heartburn?
In the classifieds, baby.
Under business opportunities?
Detergent.
Hey, my man!
Where you been
keepin' yourself, huh?
You mean, who has
been keeping yourself?
You know, I'm not in the
habit of crashing parties.
But I must say,
this whole thing is absolutely
fascinating to me.
Oh, here comes my sweet Saint
Bernard with my antifreeze.
Ah.
J come to mama-do
mm.
Yeah!
You're mine now!
Hey, dig this!
Woo! - It will make you crazy!
Woo!
It's heaven.
It's Louis xvi.
Oh, it's Louis v. Bear!
J love by you, by you
j but nobody else but you
I want this one to
go on and on and on
and on and on and on and on!
Oh, look at them,
aren't they wonderful?
- And agreeing with them.
- Take my love.
Take my love.
Take my love. - You are kind.
Take my beard!
You can have my beard.
Oh, look at you!
You look just the
same as you did
in "the bride of Frankenstein."
Thank you.
Vic?
Victor!
Where are you?
This is my room.
And you have no
right to be here.
What right do you have
to bring those horrible
people into this house?
They're Katharine's friends.
She invited them.
Mr. valance, you
have taken advantage
of a vulnerable woman, and I
am going to use every means
in my power to see to it
that you leave this house
and never come back.
But, Leslie, she really,
she really needs me now.
She'll never send me away again.
This time, it will be different.
What do you mean?
I always knew she'd need me.
I amuse her.
[, uh, help her
with her wheelchair.
[, uh, serve her her meals.
She'll never listen to you.
I service all her
corpulent needs.
Why, les,
I do believe you're jealous.
Oh, thank you!
Thank you.
Queen, yes, I'm a queen.
I'm the queen of the may.
No, I'm the queen of the
Christmas parade.
Merry Christmas, everyone,
and all is well, well,
well, well.
Merry Christmas and
a happy new year!
Yo, ho, ho, ho!
See, he heard that.
Happy new year!
Now ladies and
gentlemen, boys and girls,
here's that moment we've
all been waiting for.
Here he is, all the way
from the north pole,
it's Santa claus
and the queen of the
Santa clause Lane parade.
Ah, I wonder who the queen is.
The one with the beard, silly.
And here, ladies and
gentlemen, a face familiar
to Hollywood, the queen of
the Santa clause Lane parade,
miss Katharine packard.
Yes.
Uh, well, it's so wonderful.
It's, it's simply wonderful,
all, all these wonderful people.
1, 1, I'm sure this is
reminiscent of other evenings
for you on Hollywood boulevard.
Yes, I've had
glorious nights here.
Sid grauman, poor old sid,
he was a good friend
of mine, you know.
We always had our premiere's
at grauman's Chinese.
But the boulevard has
changed since then,
all these hoodlums
and queers, oh!
The boulevard has gone downhill.
It's gone downhill!
- Boo!
- I'm tellin' you the truth.
Thank you, thank you,
yes, uh, uh, and there,
ladies and gentlemen,
you have miss Katharine packard,
a great actress, a great star.
Katharine, Jerry Flynn called.
Do you want to talk to him?
No, how did you
like my performance,
last night, on television?
It was obvious
that you were drunk.
Leslie!
I'm not one to lie
to you, Katharine.
Well, at least I didn't
fall off the float.
Now please go, I don't
want to see you or anyone.
You've been a great
star, Katharine.
You're an exceptional
human being.
But now don't destroy the past
by making a fool of yourself
over that Mr. valance.
Let's face him for what he
is, a vulgar opportunist.
Please, please, Leslie,
just leave me alone.
Will you?
I'll thank you to wipe
your feet before coming in.
You're welcome, Mildred.
And it's miss Leslie
that goes through the mail.
Things change.
They certainly do, Mr. valance.
I hope you haven't been
disturbing Katharine.
She's feeling ill.
Yes, quite ill.
Oh, miss Leslie, there's
been so many problems
since that young man arrived.
Don't worry, Mildred.
I think our problems are solved.
Why, Victor,
where have you been?
I've been waiting for you.
1, uh...
Come over here
and sit close to me.
You know, all afternoon, I've
been thinking and planning.
We'll go away, soon, won't we?
Oh yeah, sure, we'll go away.
Well, I was thinking,
you'll need some summer clothes.
Yeah, yes, I will.
And a car.
Car?
Well, we can't take the rolls.
You'll need a smaller car,
something you can run about in.
You mean something
like a Maserati?
Yes, something like that.
Oh.
Do you know, Victor,
that's the first time
you've ever kissed me
without my asking you to?
Was it the Maserati
or the clothes?
What do you mean?
I must've been a very
lonely, miserable woman not
to have imagined what
an opportunist you are.
I must've been very lonely.
Now, for god's sake, please
just get out of my house.
What's the matter with you?
Get out!
Get out of my house!
Oh god.
You're not to disturb Katharine.
I don't intend to disturb her.
She's sleeping, and
you're not to come up here.
Oh, well, I'll
come back later then.
Ah!
No.
Leslie!
Les!
Victor.
Victor, where are you?
Vic!
Vic, I know you're here.
Operator, operator,
operator, I need help.
I need...
Oh somebody, somebody
help me, help me, help me.
Oh god, oh dear god, help me!
Help me, help, help, help!
Ah!
Miss Blair.
Yes, Mr. valance?
I suppose you want
your paycheck.
I haven't made it out yet.
I seem to forget that
you're an employee here.
Katharine doesn't
want to be disturbed.
She suggests that you
take the afternoon off.
Katharine doesn't know
that I have some bookkeeping
to do this afternoon,
which I'm sure she
will find of interest.
Oh, Vic, how nice.
Well, what time is it?
You know, I think I'm hungry.
Has, has Greta fixed dinner?
Greta's gone.
Gone?
You made her go.
No, no, I didn't.
Where's Leslie?
I want to see Leslie.
She's not here.
Vic, I'm, I'm frightened.
I'm frightened!
Your nerves are bad.
Maybe a little drink
will help, uh...
No!
No, I, I, I don't.
Drink!
Listen, my mother was a lush.
She couldn't help herself.
No, I don't, I don't want...
Drink!
And we'll, uh, we'll
make a little toast, hmm?
Here's to lonely,
rich, old bags.
= take it, please, take it.
Now, uh, why don't you sing
me your little song, huh?
I can't.
I couldn't.
I can't... - Sing!
J here I go again
j those rainbows blow again
oh, no, no, no, that isn't it.
That's wrong.
[, I can't, I can't remember it.
Maybe a little drink will
help you remember, huh?
Now sing.
J here I go again
j here I go again
louder, louder.
J I hear those
trumpets blow again
louder!
J all aglow again
j takin' a chance on love
j here I slide again
j about to take that ride again
j all aglow again
j all aglow again, aglow again
Don't be stingy, Mildred.
Thank you, love.
His royal highness is
having Brandy and cigars.
Mildred, where's the egg timer?
Humpty dumpty?
It disappeared mysteriously
along with Greta.
What do you mean?
I can't find it anywhere.
I mean about Greta.
You said mysteriously
disappeared.
Oh, that's what
she did, didn't she?
Mildred, I notice you haven't
been polishing the silver.
Tarnished silverware
is so depressing.
This is a big
house, Mr. valance.
There's too much to do
for one housekeeper.
Yes, I understand.
It must be quite difficult
for a woman of your age.
Perhaps a younger woman
could handle it better.
Oh Mildred, would you
tell Leslie I want
to speak to her
about the screening?
But I do wish
you'd come by, ira.
She doesn't seem to
listen to me anymore.
Oh, I don't think things
can be as bad as all that.
Hold on a minute.
Leslie thinks it's important
that I talk to Katharine.
Apparently, there's some
difficulty with that young man.
If you think I'm gonna let
that woman ruin our holiday
again, you're mistaken.
Leslie, we're going out
of town tomorrow, but I'll,
I'll drop by at the
end of next week.
Yes, ira, good night.
Vic, yes, you had
nothing, remember?
You came here, and you had
nothing, and I helped you.
And I loved you, a little,
I think.
I have to watch you
like a hawk, don't I?
No, no, no.
Did you think I was
somebody you could buy
with your little handouts?
Was I to be another one
of those mo-mentos
for your collection?
- No.
- You'd like me stuffed
and put in a glass case
for all your dinner guests
to admire, wouldn't you?
No, no, Victor, why
are you doing this to me?
You were gonna throw me out.
No, listen, listen to me.
Victor, Victor, listen to me.
I'll give you anything you want.
My money, I've lots
and lots of money,
and my jewelry, all my jewelry.
On, I'll, I'l, I'l, I'm
give you everything I've got.
Too late for that!
You're going to hurt me.
Oh no, Victor, please.
Oh no, please, don't hurt me.
No, please don't hurt me!
Victor, don't kill
me, don't kill me.
Victor, don't kill me.
Victor, please, don't kill me!
Oh, I don't want to die!
I don't want to diel
Katharine.
Why, Mr. valance,
are you leaving?
Miss packard
wanted me to put some
of her stuff in the basement.
See that you don't
Mark the floors.
Miss packard would
like her breakfast.
She's feeling
better, this morning.
Oh, Mr. valance,
you frightened me.
Your nerves are bad, miss Blair.
You look pale.
My nerves are quite
good, thank you.
Tell Mildred that miss packard
will have her eggs soft
boiled, this morning.
And I'll have my
breakfast in the sunroom.
Yes.
I'll take it up when it's ready.
Apparently, the poor
dear's feeling better.
Yes.
The other night, I
thought I heard her scream.
Scream?
Yes, I was asleep,
and it woke me.
Perhaps I was
having a nightmare.
Haven't been sleeping well.
This house just isn't the same.
Mr. jaffee will be back soon.
Perhaps he'll be
able to do something.
You know, I think
she's drinking again.
Why, what makes you think that?
She stays up in her room
there now all the time.
Yes.
Yes, perhaps you're right.
Well, I see miss packard
didn't want cream after all.
What do you mean?
I forgot to give her cream.
I thought you'd be down for it.
As a matter of fact,
I drank the coffee.
She didn't want any.
You know, I shouldn't
have to ask for my check.
Perhaps you'd like
me to mail it to you.
You can put it
under my bedroom door.
That'll be fine.
Which bedroom door?
Oh, just a moment, Mr. valance.
Would you have miss packard
approve and sign these papers?
I would like them
returned in the morning.
They happen to be
your charge accounts.
I don't think I could send out
checks in such large amounts
without miss packard's approval.
Katharine, don't be
alarmed, it's me.
We must be very quiet.
Oh, thank god you're all right.
I've been so worried.
He wouldn't let
me come upstairs.
We've got to get out
of this house, tonight.
That man is dangerous.
I'm awfully frightened.
Oh, oh no!
No, oh no, no, no!
Oh no, no, no!
No!
Miss Leslie!
Leslie thought you
were in the trunk.
She didn't know you were in
the flowerbed with Greta.
But you told her, didn't ya?
Didn't you?
You know what happened
the last time you talked
to Leslie about me.
Are you awake?
I love you.
I know you love me.
That's why I came back
after all those years.
I knew you'd need me, one day.
I feel I can trust
you now, can't I?
Get out, get out!
You know, what you
need is some air.
Just ring if you need me.
Good morning, Mildred.
She's not feeling
well, this morning.
An omelet and some orange juice.
Yes, sir.
I'll take it up when it's ready.
Mildred, are you ill?
=?
Of course I'm not ill.
I've never been sick
a day in my life.
I'll thank you not
to imply I'm ill.
You know, uh, I think you
could do with a holiday.
Why don't you, uh,
take some time off?
Why, I don't know
what I'd do with myself.
Mildred, when Leslie
returns from town,
tell her I want to see her.
Miss Leslie?
I was just another
one of your crusades.
You have people up that think
anything great about you.
You know, it's true
you never loved me.
You know what?
I think you thought
you had me fooled, huh,
you and your righteous friends?
And how do you think I'm suffering
about this, all the time,
cozying up with your
stupid friends, huh?
I know better now.
The truth is you only had
time for those drunk friends
of yours you slept around with.
You never really wanted me,
and so you thought you
could order me around.
You, oh yeah, tell
me how to behave,
tell me how to dress,
tell me about my manners,
tell me about how to speak, huh?
You thought you could
tell me what to do.
And then you thought you
could throw me out, huh!
Mr. valance!
Good evening, miss packard.
I brought your tray.
I think it'd be nice if
you had it over here,
at the fireplace.
And [I'll light the fire.
My goodness,
listen to that rain.
You'll catch your death.
You should have
something around you.
I'll get your shawl.
Folks, this is the home
of Katharine packard,
one of the most famous stars
of the motion picture screen.
Happily retired from the glamor
of the motion picture world,
she now devotes
her days of leisure
to benevolent social work
and her pet Hollywood charities.
This home was built at a cost...