Put that away.
Well done.
Not as good as last time, but good.
Colleen ...
- Don't forget, those of you who
haven't completed your tally charts.
Moron.
Quiet!
- Anna Madden, out!
- But it wasn't me.
- Out!
- Sharon took my exercise book.
- Liar!
- Out now or you're on detention.
- But it was Sharon.
- Out!
No.
- Right, I'll see you after school.
And wait where I can see you.
Nigel, did I tell you to stand up?
No, so get back in your seat.
Now, we all know how many degress there
are in a circle, don't we Nigel.
Quit! The next person
to laugh joins her.
Right, we're starting something
new today. Another way of showing
basic statistics.
Pie charts.
Now a pie chart is just another way of
showing information.
Take for example the information we
took last week.
Now what was the most common number of
letters in all your surnames?
Seven.
About half of you have seven letters
in your surnames. So ...
what portion of the pie do
those people have?
Half.
180-degree slice of the pie.
Now I'm going to make up
a different pie chart
with a different set of information.
How we spend our day.
I'll do an example for you based
on my average weekday
then I want you to make up a pie chart
based on your average Saturday.
First, I write down my information.
What are the things I do?
Getting dressed and undressed.
Eating.
Travelling.
School.
Meeting friends.
What?
- I feel dizzy.
- She's lying!
- I want to go home.
- She's lying, Miss!
I'm not!
-Well you don't sound ill to me.
If you disturb us again you're going
straight to Mr. Murphy. Understand?
But it's my birthday.
Well you should have thought
of that before.
Quiet.
And you can wipe that look off
your face, Sharon Davis.
Where were we?
Sleeping. Right.
I spend one hour dressing
and undressing.
About two and a half hours eating.
About 8 hours at school.
She passed out.
- Is she gonna die?
- Trisham, go get matron.
Thanks.
Hi.
How are you feeling?
- Terrible, mum.
- That bad, eh?
Worse.
- Oh, but I'm sure it's nothing serious.
- I wish they hadn't called you.
- I could have gone home by myself.
- Don't worry.
Things were so busy at work that it
was really nice to get out of there.
Listen, this'll cheer you up.
It came after you left.
Guess who it's from?
- Dad.
- Yeah.
Happy 11th birthday.
Lots of love, Dad.
Well, that's not all. There's something
very special fixed up for you.
- What?
- No, it's a surprise.
Riding lessons?
Yeah, some surprise.
Where's Mogadishu? -I think it's a
port on the east coast of Africa.
Well they spelled my name wrong.
-Did they?
Oh ... it's just a mistake.
- Maybe I could send a reply.
- That's a nice idea.
- I wish dad was here.
- So do I.
- When's he coming back?
- Soon.
How are you feeling now?
- No worse. When is the riding lesson?
- It was meant to be after school today.
Meant to be?
Let's see what
Dr. Nicols says first.
Do we have to? I'm sure if I just lay
down in front of the telly I'll be OK.
Doctor first.
No arguing, okay?
Stop!
Stop it!
- I was pretending.
- Pretending?
Sharon Davis stole my book.
Then I pushed her off the chair and
Miss Vanstone put me on detention.
I can't be on detention on my
birthday, can I? So I faked it.
You faked it?
So you're not ill?
- Where are we going?
- Back.
- I can't go back.
- Oh, you're going back.
- I'll look stupid.
- Well you do already.
Stupid cow.
Just because it's your birthday don't
think you can talk to me like that.
You should be pleased
there's nothing wrong with me.
You're telling too many lies, Anna,
and it is going to stop.
- What about my riding lesson?
- Oh, don't ask.
We'll see.
- What does that mean?
- It means we'll see.
I hate you.
Karen.
Come here.
- I was wondering where you got to.
- Shh ...
Got the afternoon off.
I'm having a really
miserable birthday.
- You been using the sunlamp again?
- No, my skin just tans very fast ...
naturally.
I don't get brown;
I get sunstroke.
Last year I fell asleep in a
deck chair on my dad's oil rig,
and when I woke up I was
burnt to a frazzle.
- Why's your mum so angry with you?
- 'Cause she's a cow.
What was Gary's
party like then?
Lots of snogging. Not much
else I can remember, really.
- You had a nice time then?
- I suppose you could call it that.
First I was upstairs with Nigel,
then on the sofa with Ronnie ...
then Vaughn Hancock, pissed out of
his head, got me on the thick pile.
You're lucky you haven't
started that yet.
What's snogging like then?
Well, like kissing a vacuum cleaner.
This looks a real skill
place to play hide-and-seek.
- I'm too old for that kind of thing.
- Bet you 50p you can't find me.
- A quid.
- You're on.
Close your eyes, count to 100,
and don't peek.
1, 2, 3, 4 ...
86, 87, 88 ...
99, 100. I'm coming!
Is anybody there?
Karen!
It's her.
Anna.
Don't ever do that to me again.
Never! What has got into you?
Mum, I don't feel very well.
Now open wide.
My throat hurts ...
like I've swallowed dust.
Gritty ... and it aches,
but that's all.
You sure that's all?
No fainting fits?
No dizziness?
And this ache,
is it just in your throat?
You've obviously had quite
an eventful birthday.
- I suppose you could call it that.
- Sorry to drag you out like this ...
but I was worried.
I don't blame you.
Look, I'm sure there's
nothing to worry about.
She should have a
couple of days rest.
What I don't understand is
what happened in the tunnel?
Anna.
What happened
in the tunnel?
Fell asleep and lost track
of time. You know....
- That doesn't sound like you.
- I'll have that throat swab analyzed.
And you're obviously running
quite a temperature.
- And I think a day or two in bed ...
- When it goes down can I go riding?
- You must rest for a couple of days.
- I'm not staying in bed.
Don't.
Well, think of it this way:
if you rest now you'll get better
sooner. You rush around, who
knows how long it might take.
How long exactly do
I have to stay in bed?
I'll come and see you again
at the end of the week.
- The end of the week?
- Count yourself lucky.
I've got a patient a little bit older
than you whose been in bed for a year.
I'd rather die than that.
You and he would get on well.
No we wouldn't: I hate boys.
- I'll see you on Friday then.
- Goodnight Sarah
Here Sarah, I'll show you out.
Is there someone who can come and look
after Anna whilst you're at work?
No.
- I'll have to take some time off.
- You okay?
Yeah. I could do with
a break, that's all.
Tired?
Yeah.
It's always difficult when
John's away, and I just ...
I don't know....
Too sad.
Is anybody there?
Can I come in?
I can't hear you.
- I said go away.
- No, you let me in, then I'll go away.
- I can't do that.
- Why not?
'Cause there aren't
any stairs.
- How did you get up there then?
- I don't know. I'm just here.
Can't you tell someone else to let
me in? -There isn't anyone else.
Look, just stop mucking
around and let me in.
Go away, don't you understand,
it's dangerous around here, dangerous.
It's real.
There are stairs.
- You were wrong about the stairs.
- Must have come since.
Since I drew them.
You shouldn't be here.
I knew I should've
made you more cheerful.
I drew you, this house,
the stairs, everything.
Come and have a look, come on.
I can't walk.
Of course, I didn't draw you any legs.
I'm not a drawing!
I'm sorry, I just drew someone
at the window, that's all.
It's alright.
My name's Mark, what's yours?
Mark!
Mum?
And one, and two, and three...
- Mum?
- What?
- Go away please.
- What's wrong mum?
Nothing, I just don't
want you ruining this print.
- Feeling better?
- No, worse.
What photo are you doing?
The one you took on
the beach last summer.
I'm having dreams mum, but
they're real, I know they are.
Dreams can't be real sweetie.
It's dad!
They might frighten you
but they can never hurt you.
- How do you know? - Because if
they could they wouldn't be dreams.
- No, leave it, I like the
clouds dark. - Alright, darling.
Oh that's too much.
Come on, we're gonna get you to bed.
- No, i'll be alright if I stay awake.
- No, come on, come on right now.
On the other side of
the hill is the sea.
It shines out for miles and
miles and everyone can see it.
It looks like glandular fever.
I lied to you about the fainting,
it's happened several times.
I guessed you weren't
telling the truth.
That's all though,
you didn't need to come.
- I'm getting much better.
- Your mother was right to call me.
- Is it bad? - Well, it'll
knock you out for a few weeks.
Your pulse is right up.
So are these glands.
- What have you been upto in here?
- Nothing.
- When did you last faint.
- After I saw you, yesterday.
I see.
Sarah?
- You know this boy you see?
- Yes.
When's he going to be able to get up?
Well, he can get up, he just doesn't
want to most of the time, that's all.
He's getting better though?
You're really interested
in my other patients Anna?
- Doesn't he want to get better?
- Well of course he does.
Then why doesn't he get out of bed?
As long as he gets enough books to
read he's content to stay in bed.
That's terrible, I
can't stand staying in bed.
If you told me I could
get up tomorrow i'd be up.
Well it isn't just a question
of getting up, it's just that...
Exercise is too much
bother and pain for Mark.
- Mark, can't walk?
- No.
What wrong Anna?
We're just opposites
me and him, aren't we?
He's got to do exercise
and doesn't want to...
and i've got to stay in
bed and I don't want to.
It's a pity you
can't mix us up a bit.
Well I dare say you two are
each better off as you are.
I'll have a word with
Kate on my way out.
Bye Anna.
Now he'll walk.
Mark!
Mark?
Oh, no cones.
Hi.
Whoever left this
should've left some instructions.
It seems to be based on the
Apple design, it's a bit crude.
I'll fix that tomorrow.
I suppose you'll tell me you drew it,
that would explain why it's so mental.
You've been moving things around.
My name's Anna.
- I drew you walking but it went wrong.
- I don't undertstand you.
- You like reading don't you?
- Yeah.
- Then you are Mark?
- Well i'm not a drawing, I know that.
I've got the same doctor
as you, Dr Nichols.
Not me.
- I mean... when you're not here.
- Look, i'm always here.
- They left me here.
- Who left you here?
It's great, isn't it?
Do you want some fruit?
It's really good for you.
Ok.
Behind you!
Very funny.
Very funny, I could've broken
my leg, you're so stupid.
There was this boy...
about my age...
he had a bike, a blue one...
it was in perfect nick.
Although he loved this bike,
he couldn't ride it.
He'd just watch it every day and having
it there made all the difference.
But one day he'd ride it and that
was all that ever mattered to him.
Why are you here Mark?
I did something wrong,
I expect that's why you're here too.
- I haven't done anything wrong.
- Oh I bet!
But I haven't done anything wrong.
Maybe all this stuff's here for you
and you're to stay here like me.
No chance, this is a dream.
That's what I thought.
Do you think whoever brought you
here will come back again?
I hope not.
If my dad was here
he could carry you...
and you could run away
with us, then you'd be safe.
And you wouldn't be afraid any more.
He looks like a madman.
Hello darling.
- What's that?
- A radio.
- It doesn't look like a radio,
it's too big. - It's a radio.
Who's that?
That's dad, that's good.
I think he looks drunk,
I hate it when he's drunk.
He stopped drinking years ago.
He was drunk when
I took that picture.
- Why don't you have your soup.
- He was, wasn't he?
Let me see.
Well, a bit, maybe.
You could rub it out and try again.
- I can't.
- It's almost right, it's just...
His head's a bit too big
and he looks sort of angry.
What is it?
Why don't you go back to work, I
don't like you hanging around here.
- I'll be alright. - Listen,
it's good, it's really good.
- It's total rubbish!
- It's only a drawing Anna, come on.
That's right, it's only a drawing.
I think it's good, I really do.
It's just that i'm
having those dreams again...
and i'm frightened dad's going to come
into those dreams looking like that.
Listen, if dad came into your
dreams that would be nice.
And no drawing is going
to make any difference.
- Have I done anything wrong?
- Do you ever do anything right?
I must've done something really bad.
It's nothing you've done,
that's silly, don't think that.
- Then why don't you believe me?
- Believe what?
That my dreams are frightening me.
- I do believe you.
- No you don't.
Listen...
I know it's hard for you with
dad away all the time but...
It's hard for me too, we've
got to try to get on better.
- Will you promise me something?
- What?
You've got to be honest with me about
when you pass out and when you...
see things that maybe
I don't see, you understand?
It's really important
Anna, you have to promise.
I always tell you the truth.
A nice hot bath and then to bed.
Mum!
- I don't feel well. - I know, I know,
you try and get some sleep, ok?
- My head hurts. - I know
but I have to dry your hair.
There, just a bit more.
Ok.
- Will you set my alarm for me? - Why,
are you going somewhere special tomorrow?
- Set it for 7.
- Ok.
I'll just get your teddy.
Stay with me until I get to sleep,
I don't wanna be on my own.
Sure.
I'll just be a second, I just have
to get something from my room.
No dreams.
- That was quick.
- I'm late.
Is something the matter?
I'm very busy this morning,
I should be at the hospital.
Well perhaps I should've
got worse yesterday.
- Is anything wrong?
- No.
- You're miserable today. - Well even
doctors get miserable sometimes Anna.
- Is it something I did?
- Don't think so.
- Bye.
I've given you some
mild sleeping pills...
keep a very close eye
on her temperature...
and let me know immediately
if she seems delirious.
It's not very likely,
she seems stable now.
Sarah, are you sure you're
alright, you look worried.
It's just a young boy I thought
was ok had a relapse yesterday.
What's wrong with him?
He has muscular dystrophy,
he's got a chest infection.
- Oh no.
- It's dangerous.
Anna, what are you doing?
Mum, last night you
cleared up my bedroom...
I threw something away,
where's the rubbish?
I've got to find it.
I leave you alone for 5 minutes and
you work yourself up into a frenzy.
But I threw something away
and i've got to find it.
- What is it.
- A drawing.
- A drawing? Can't you do another one?
- No!
Alright, i'll go and look, but only if
you promise to take 2 of these pills.
Yeah!
- Yes, yes, just find it. - Ok, ok,
here, stop it, stop, here, Anna!
God, well if it's not there
there's nothing I can do, ok?
- No that's not ok.
- Well, i'll find it alright.
Anna!
Wait! Don't!
Anna! Anna!
Come back! Anna!
Wait! Anna!
Wait!
Come on love, out of the way.
No, I have to find something,
I threw it away by mistake.
- To bed now, come on!
-  No!
You're going to be sick,
really sick unless you calm down.
You've gotta help me
find it mum, please.
Can you help?
- What type of bag was it?
Black!
Ok boys, we're looking for a black bag!
Please, let me check them.
Open them mum, open them.
- You missed one.
- I'm doing my best.
It could be any of these.
- Look, you've lost the drawing
Anna, just accept it. - No!
- That's your lot.
- You didn't check that one.
If we checked every one
we'd be here all day.
It's no good Anna, stop it now.
There!
You're going to be alright
now darling, you must sleep.
Mark?
Fooled you!
Your face.
Sorry Anna.
- How you feeling?
- Fine.
You did all this then, eh?
I don't understand you.
Mark, do you remember
anything about the real world?
But this is the real world.
I suppose so.
When i'm not here I know where
I am... and you're there too.
- What's wrong with me?
- You're in hospital.
I wish you weren't, sorry.
Well you're right about
one thing... I am ill.
I'm tired, like i've just run
a marathon but all the time.
And the big joke is I have to crawl
to move from this lump of wood.
- That must be really uncomfortable.
- And cold.
Instead of making a mess out of
this place... why don't you help me?
I think I should wake up now.
- I can't wake up.
- I told you so.
- They've come for us.
- Who?
- It's dad!
- No, don't let him in.
- Rubbish, i'll go and fetch him.
- No!
Dad!
Dad, come in, it's getting dark.
- Anna, is that you?
- Yes.
I'm blind!
No locks.
Anna, he's moving,
he's got a hammer.
- Anna!
- Go away.
Anna.
Are you ok?
Let me in Anna.
- Behind the hills is a sea,
we have to go there. - You go.
- Listen, we can ride the bike.
- How can I ride a bike, be realistic.
You ride and i'll push.
- You're mad.
- Anna!
Please Mark, you have to try.
Anna, i'm not going away so
you might aswell let me in.
Let me in Anna!
Open this door now!
- You'll never get
me up on this. - Try.
Anna.
- Don't leave me.
- Of course I won't.
- Of course I won't leave you.
- I'm scared.
- Don't be scared.
There.
You've had a really bad fever darling
but I think this is the worst of it.
When you're better
we'll go to the seaside.
You like the sea.
We'll go there, all 3 of us, and
we'll have a big, long rest, ok.
To the sea, to the sea,
to the beautiful sea.
Let me see, let me see it.
You're temperature's going down,
it's normal, you're getting better.
- Don't.
- What.
- Who are you?
- Anna?
I don't talk to strangers, go away.
- Go away.
- It's mummy, you're alright now.
Go away!
Anna!
What are you doing? Darling?
Anna! Look at me, look at me!
Anna, please, don't!
Anna!
Mark?
He must've taken him.
Anna?
You're going to be alright.
Just stay where you are.
Daddy's here.
Anna!
Alright...
if you want to play games...
One, two, three...
four, five, six...
seven, eight, twelve,
thirteen, fourteen, fifteen...
It's you he's after not me,
you should've never come back.
I thought that he'd taken you.
Listen. it won't take
him long to find us...
You've gotta wake up and change
your stupid drawing, get rid of him.
I've tried.
No, rip him out of the
paper, it's the only way.
- I drew a lighthouse, we can go
there then we'll be safe. - Ok.
Look, just wake up, we're not going
to get anywhere with him around.
I can't.
- Wake up! - I can't.
Thirty-one, thirty-two, thirty-three...
Thirty-four, thirty-five, thirty-six...
I've got an idea.
Lie down like you're in bed... do it!
Reach out to where the drawing is.
Pick up the drawing Anna.
Careful!
- Dad's on the left, by the rocks.
- Put your finger on him.
Eighty-seven, eighty-eight, eighty-nine...
Now rip him out!
Ninety-nine, one hundred.
I'm coming.
Run Anna, leave me.
Anna!
Mark, Mark!
Mark!
Get off me!
Who are you?
- What is your name?
- Please, dad, please.
Do you know me?
Do you recognise me?
The sea.
Anna?
- Anna.
- It's alright love, it's just the tube.
There's a brave girl.
You'll be alright, you'll be alright.
Anna?
It hurts when I breathe.
That's just your ribs,
they're a bit bruised.
The ambulance man had
to give you a heart massage.
- He saved your life.
- I know but it still hurts.
You'll be out of here in a few days.
I've been here long enough.
How's Mark?
- How's Mark?
- He's ok.
Don't lie to me.
We sent him home, he'll
be more comfortable there.
He's dying isn't he?
- They've stopped.
- What's stopped.
My dreams.
If I tell you something,
will you keep it a secret?
- I know Mark, I know him
from my dreams. - Anna...
I drew a house on paper,
Mark's there too.
It was me who made Mark ill and
me who helped him get better again.
Then we had to escape and we
did but now I can't even dream.
You have to believe me.
When you're ill the
mind plays funny tricks.
It's not a trick...
Mark's eyes are blue...
His left leg is
stronger than his right...
He's got a bicycle,
a blue one, he just looks at it.
- How do you know all this?
- It's true isn't it?
You have to get me my pencils
and drawings, you have to.
- But...
- Just do it!
And as soon as you're better...
I'm going to take us all down
to Devon for a little holiday.
Hey, are you listening to me?
Look at me darling.
That's better, I was beginning
to think I was invisible.
You don't have to be
invisible to disappear, dad.
Anna, you said you wanted
to go to the seaside, no?
Sounds wonderful mum.
Hey and don't forget
your riding lessons.
I've taken time off,
we can go together if you like.
And then you'll go away again.
I don't know what you want
these for but here they are.
She shouldn't have told you,
I told Sarah to keep it a secret.
- Can I see?
- No.
I wouldn't want to live if he died.
Now if there's anything
we need we'll be alright.
Mark, Mark.
Anna.
Wait there.
How's that then eh?
I thought you weren't ever coming back.
Come on, there's lots to show you...
You've really kitted out
the place good this time.
- Hey, what's the matter?
- Nothing, just pleased to see you.
Come on,
let's walk along the cliffs.
Here, I want to show you something.
- Can you do rollovers?
- Yeah.
You haven't done them properly
until you've done them here, my way.
What do you mean "your way"?
Sit in front of me.
Keep your head well in and
imagine you're half of a wheel.
Now pull me.
Again!
How am I getting on
in your world?
You're recovering
but not as fast as here.
- So i'm different here?
- Don't know.
I don't care what happens to me there,
as long as I can be here with you.
You see, your world doesn't
matter any more, we can live here.
Have you ever kissed anyone?
Me neither.
Is this snogging?
I've walked as far as I can along
these cliffs but there's no way down.
- We should draw a ladder then.
- There's not one long enough...
And even if there was I wouldn't
go down there, would you?
I know i'm getting better
but that's just stupidity.
- You suggest something then?
- Helicopter?
- I don't think I can draw that.
- I can.
I brought it with me this time.
You draw the helicopter.
- Are you sure?
- Positive.
- Do you think it'll work for me?
- Don't know.
- Where are you going?
- I'm going back to draw.
Wait.
You can't go yet.
Well you wait down here
and keep a look out for it.
I can see better from up there.
To be honest i'd rather draw by myself,
I don't like people watching me.
- And I never saw you draw did I?
- I suppose not.
- You wait down here then.
- Ok.
Don't go without me.
Please don't go without me.
I've got some good news...
They've given me a job at head office
so I don't have to go away anymore.
That's good isn't it?
We can all be together
like a proper family.
Things aren't the same between you
and me since I got back, are they?
I missed you when I was away but now
I feel as if i'm missing you even more.
I'm worried.
- I went to see your doctor.
- Why?
Mum said you were having bad
dreams about me, is that true?
Do you want to see
someone about the dreams?
- I don't have them anymore.
- Maybe because i'm back.
No, it's nothing to do with you.
What did Dr Nichols say?
She said you knew a
patient of hers who died.
What's the matter?
Mark's dead.
Didn't you know?
- I'm sorry.
- No, don't be sorry...
I knew, it's just when I last saw
him I sort of hoped he'd get better.
Was he a close friend?
- Dr Nichols didn't tell me
the whole story. - Obviously.
Mark would hate
anybody being sorry.
Come on Anna.
Did you seen those boats there?
- Good morning.
- Good morning, Mr Madden.
Hello, is everything ok?
That's good.
After lunch we'll go for
a walk down to the front.
- Here.
- Thanks.
Don't lose it.
Dad.
I'm sorry.
- What on earth for?
- Being so miserable.
Don't be stupid.
It was the illness, when I was
ill I thought I saw funny things.
I want to go to the pier...
to get Karen some rock.
- Well we'll go after we've eaten.
- Good.
- Shall I open your curtains.
- Whatever you like.
Be careful you don't
get sunstroke.
Mark, i'm back.
Mark.
Mark, let me in.
Let me in.
I don't want to go without you but the
helicopter's been hovering all day.
I think i'm meant to go.
Wait for me here, i'll come
back for you, love Mark.
Mark, Mark, Mark!
Anna!
Move back from the
edge, it's dangerous.
- I can't reach.
Move back from the
edge Anna, it's dangerous.
- Anna, move away!
- I can't reach.
Mark, I can't reach,
don't leave me.
- Anna, it's dangerous.
- I can't reach.
- Move away from the edge.
- Don't leave me.
- Bye Anna.
- No!
He's alright now mum,
I know he is.