All right, haul away.
Come on. Come on.
Damn it.
- Go on!
- Any time!
Go on!
It's no bloody good!
Turn it off!
Yeah. Go on.
All creatures
Of our God and king
Lift up your voice
And with us sing
Alleluia
Thou burning sun
With golden beam
Thou silver moon
With softer gleam
Oh, praise Him
Alleluia
It's not goin' to move, Garron.
Dennis is right. Give up.
Maybe.
Doesn't look too healthy.
Well, I'd better be gettin' back.
Me dinner's on the table.
Thanks anyway.
Are you comin', Mitch?
Yeah. Good luck.
May the same dinner choke ya.
Hey, Dad.
Smile.
Dad!
What's the problem?
Mom says it's gonna rain. Why don't you
stop taking the damn photographs?
- Damn photographs?
- Just quoting.
Oh. Just quoting.
I see.
Well, what would you say?
I'd say I'm hungry.
What an entirely new response from you.
All right, listen, tell her...
- Tell her about ten minutes. Okay?
- She's mad with you.
All right. Tell her five.
I have to see somebody about this site.
Then can we go home? I'm bored.
Robbie, how can you be bored? This is
the land of your forefathers. Remember?
Yeah, and they left.
Tell her five minutes.
Tell her I really mean it.
Bastard.
Alleluia
Hi.
- We should get you home.
- I don't know what came over me.
Shall we make a dash for it?
I felt like I was burning.
Come on.
Can I help you?
Yeah, I hope so.
I'm looking for a Reverend Coot.
Am I saying that right? Coot?
That's right. But I'm not your man.
I'm the verger.
Oh. Hi. I'm Howard Hallenbeck.
Declan O'Brien.
Tell me something. This Coot,
he wouldn't happen to be old, would he?
Sorry.
I talked to him a couple weeks ago.
He said that I might look at the church.
I see.
You see, it's for a book I'm writing.
He said I might take some photographs,
maybe even look at the parish records.
Then you'd probably find him
in the rectory.
Which is where?
Out the door.
Turn right,
and it's straight ahead of you.
Right, then straight.
Thanks.
All right.
One, two, three.
Rawhead.
- Come in. Come in.
- Thank you. Thank you.
Look at this. A striking collection.
Well, it passes the time.
- Here. Let me take your coat.
- Thank you very much.
This is very nice.
Well, now, how can I help?
Well, when we spoke on the phone
I think I mentioned
that the book that I'm writing
is about the persistence of sacred sites
in this part of the country.
I'm sorry. Persistence?
Yeah, see,
a lot of churches are built on sites
that have been considered sacred
for, well, some considerable time.
Pre-Christian, you mean.
Pre-Roman, even.
Although that doesn't apply
here in Ireland.
What I'm after are neolithic sites.
Fertility cults of one sort or the other.
Here?
It's very possible, yeah.
Intriguing.
What I'd like to do is photograph
the interior of your church,
particularly those stained glass windows.
Very interesting designs.
Of course. It's always open.
How about your parish records?
Could I have a look at those?
I'm sure it can be arranged.
I'll have Declan look out
whatever stuff we've got.
Ah, yes, the verger.
Perhaps I'd better come back to you
when he's sorted it all out.
That'd be much appreciated.
Where are you staying?
At your pub.
The Tall Man?
The Tall Man.
Once upon a time there was a little boy
called Treehorn.
He just noticed that...
Shut up!
Watch it!
I'm trying to read my comic!
- Watch it.
- You're a pig, Robbie.
Oh, yeah, sure.
Two more days of this, I'll go nuts.
What are you talking about?
We just checked in here.
We've been here two months.
Well, we've been in Ireland
a month and a half, actually... not quite.
We may not have to be here that long.
I've gotta see the records of this church.
This is the most interesting site
I've seen.
- And then?
- Then we can go to Dublin.
It's about half a day's drive.
Come on, get it. Just get it!
- I want my doll!
- Well, you're not getting it.
I will. I'll go bananas.
All right, quiet down!
This is a working trip for me.
Remember?
You know, you also got a family.
That's who those kids belong to.
I was wondering.
I thought you'd feel at home here.
- "At home."
- Irish forebearers and all that.
It's a vicious rumor put out by my mother.
Your mother is a vicious rumor.
One more day?
- Dennis.
- What?
Dear, the door's not shut.
- I locked it.
- Well, it's open now.
Damn. I could have sworn
that I bolted it.
Who's there?
I said, who's there?
Dennis! Dennis!
No. No!
No! Get away!
Dennis! Oh, Dennis!
- Did you hear that?
- You're changing the subject.
Listen.
It's just more thunder, I think.
Why did we have to come here
in the monsoon season?
I like this place. I think I could
live here. It's quiet, it's charming.
And dead.
What do you expect from a historian?
I prefer dead things.
Oh. I'll bear that in mind.
With one or two exceptions.
Name one.
What's the other?
You haven't kissed me like that
in a long time.
You have very dirty eyes.
Anybody ever tell you that?
Practically everybody.
She'll certainly know us next time.
- Strange.
- Yeah.
The way she looked.
What do you mean?
She reminds me of something.
Somebody.
Maybe she's a relation of yours.
- You're right. You're going bananas.
- Thanks.
- Now, about that hotel.
- Yeah?
What the hell?
Dennis. Jenny.
Are you there?
Dennis.
Dennis!
Dennis. Jenny?
Jen, what happened here?
Would you take over here?
I'm wanted. All right?
Just a moment.
Could I have a word?
Travel with her in the ambulance.
Take down anything she says.
You understand? It's very important.
Any little mumbled phrase.
Anything at all.
I went into the kitchen.
There wasn't a mark on Jenny.
Which leaves the husband.
Dennis.
Did they have any visitors
staying with them?
I don't think so.
I could check.
What amazes me is
how the woman survived.
Clearly, she hid herself.
A wardrobe, perhaps. The attic.
I don't think Conroy
knows what hit him.
They probably haven't had
a murder round here before.
You're assuming Nicholson's dead.
The state of the house. The blood.
Yes, I think so.
I think we're talking about
some kind of revenge killing.
Doesn't seem to go with the territory.
I don't know.
Resentments can fester anywhere.
We're looking for several individuals
to have caused this kind of damage.
- Howard?
- Yeah, I'm right here. I'm here.
- Something wrong?
- No, it's just...
- You didn't hear the sirens?
- Sirens?
Just an accident of some sort
up in the hills.
Come back to bed.
I'm gonna take a walk, get some air.
Help me go to sleep.
You know, you were talking in your sleep.
Was I?
Who the hell is Big Jake?
Wouldn't you like to know.
Keep it warm, okay?
I'll be back.
Big Jake.
Hey, take your coat.
It's cold out there.
- Why don't you watch the film?
- Seen it.
- Well, then change the channel.
- I've seen them all.
- You're just being selfish.
- Don't, Andy.
You're a selfish little brat.
Come on. Come on.
He can watch the telly.
You'll be sorry for this.
I'm gonna get you back, dickhead.
You and whose army?
You little pig.
Just you wait.
It's not very warm.
You're a little bastard.
- Hey! Give me that!
- No, you don't! Get lost!
- Come on.
- Andy.
I have to talk to you.
Sure.
No, I mean seriously.
I can talk seriously, you know.
Come on. We'll walk.
Let me out, you pig!
Come on.
Andy!
Pig! The bloody pig!
I tell you what. I'm gonna kill
the little brat one of these days.
- I don't think this was such a good idea.
- Why not? There's nobody around.
- Are you feeling a bit cold?
- Yeah.
Come on. I'll warm ya up.
No, Andy.
Oh, come on, Katrina.
You said we could talk.
Did you hear that?
No.
Oh, God.
My God. Neil. Sean?
Sean!
Sean! It's little Neil.
Damn.
My God. What's happened?
- What's wrong, sweetheart?
- What is it, son?
Speak up. What is it?
What's happened?
There's somebody here, Andy.
Hey, listen.
Stop playing hard-to-get, will ya?
- I wanna go back to the caravan.
- We'll go back in a minute.
God!
I said I want to go back.
Shit.
What the hell's goin' on?
God knows.
- The boy just appeared on the doorstep.
- He won't say a word.
Hey, Katrina.
Katrina, hang on, will ya?
Here. Listen, I'm sorry.
- Hey, you're not upset, are ya?
- I'm not. It's just...
I'm just feeling chilly. That's all.
You poor little baby.
- I'll keep you warm.
- Andy.
There. You getting warmer?
Good.
Run! Come on!
I can't... I can't go...
Come on!
- What is it?
- Something... I don't...
- What is it, for God's sake?
- I don't...
Andy!
- Don't get too far apart.
- No.
And stay in sight of each other.
Let's go see.
He'll be back in a second.
Okay.
- What's happening out there?
- Something going on up in the hills.
We were worried.
Is that why you're still up?
Is it an accident?
- I don't know.
- Was there any blood?
I didn't see, so I don't know.
All right, pumpkin.
All the excitement's over.
- Time for bed.
- Yep.
Now you see Daddy's okay.
Time for beddy-bye.
Okay.
Oh, my God!
- Who is it?
- What the...
Did someone fetch the police?
I'll go back and check.
Who is it?
It's not the Johnson boy.
God knows.
Over here!
Where's his head?
Jesus Christ! It's a bloody massacre!
- There's that no-good brother of yours.
- Boring.
No more comics, Robbie.
- They rot the brain.
- Yeah?
Down to bed, okay?
- Okay.
- And here's Icky.
Thank you.
Night-night. Sleep tight.
And don't let the bedbugs bite.
- Off we went to have our dinner.
- Just hang on there, gentlemen.
The officer in charge of the case
is arriving just now.
- He'd like to ask you a few questions.
- That's all right.
How long's he been dead?
I'd estimate under 24 hours.
Apparently he was trying
to move this stone.
Witnesses?
Two local men.
They've been helping him clear the field.
When they left here, he was fine.
This is number three.
Do you know what I mean?
- Morning.
- Who's that?
Excuse me. I'd like to report
something I saw last night.
- Who do I speak to?
- Just go in. Last door on the right.
- On the right?
- Yeah. That's right.
Any statement's going to be
pure conjecture.
Somebody wants to speak
to the man in charge.
- He'll have to wait.
- Yes, of course.
Would you mind waiting a moment, sir?
I'll get right back to you.
Yes. Promptly, sir.
- Somebody to...
- I heard. Come in.
This is Mr....
Hallenbeck.
Howard Hallenbeck.
Inspector Gissing.
What can I do for you?
Well, I heard about
the murders last night,
and I think maybe I saw something.
- Oh?
- But I'm not exactly sure what.
We're looking for more than
one perpetrator, Mr. Hallenbeck.
What I saw wasn't human.
I beg your pardon.
At least I don't think it was.
It was very tall.
Much too big to be a man.
How big?
Eight foot, nine foot.
- I really don't have time to...
- I saw this.
Just let me speak. Okay?
I saw it.
And what's more, it saw me.
This... thing...
was watching me.
It fixed me with these
mean, burning red eyes.
All right, I know how this sounds.
Believe me, I know.
But I saw it.
Was this on the road?
No, no. I was in a road.
It was up a field.
Cattle then. You saw cattle.
I know what cattle look like.
For Christ's sake!
Darkness can be deceptive.
All right, I came here
to tell you something.
I saw something.
I don't know what it is.
But it was there.
And it's out there right now.
So what do you want to do?
Well, if you want to give a statement
to Officer Conroy here...
Forget it. Just forget it.
Sir, maybe we ought to
look at what he's saying.
Tea?
No, none for me. I was wondering
about the parish records.
Yes, a curious thing, that. They appear to
have been removed from the premises.
What do you mean? Stolen?
Well, so it seems.
Though I frankly can't see why.
Again, I'm sorry I can't be more helpful.
Thanks anyway.
- Bye-bye.
All right, there it is.
Strangest thing.
All right, handsome. Smile.
Death...
walks...
Fearing what?
Death walks...
Death goes in... Fear...
Itself...
never became.
Death goes in fear...
of what it cannot be.
Goes in fear...
Sorry. I'm sorry.
Oh, dear.
- What did you do that for?
- Get the fuck outta here.
There's nothing here for you.
You fucking...
Yeah, I'll get the fuck out of here,
and you be very fucking glad.
That's a little present for you,
you goddamn maniac.
Finally.
God, it took you long enough.
Well, checking out
is always a major adventure.
All right.
Now, let's see where we're going.
Okay. Where to, my lady?
Well, I's having trouble
reading the map.
How surprising. Your mother's
having trouble reading a map.
I see. Daddy's being rude again.
- Rude?
- Rude.
- Truthful.
Accurate.
Dublin, oh, Dublin
Yeah.
- Icky.
- Have they got a McDonald's in Dublin?
Probably.
Are we almost there?
No, for the 15th time.
I'm hungry.
You're a bottomless pit, Robbie.
What's a bottomless pit?
My God.
What? What is it?
There's something there
back in the field.
Do you wanna go back and see?
Okay.
What's a bottomless pit?
Why are we going back?
Your mother thinks she saw something.
It's a scarecrow.
- Yes.
- What did you think it was?
I don't know. It's this bloody place.
Bloody place, huh?
You're sounding more Irish every day.
It's time we move on.
Drive, madam?
Please.
You guys ready to go?
Yeah.
Your enthusiasm overwhelms me.
Sir.
- What?
- We've got something.
The Nicholson woman.
No, sir.
She's still refusing to speak.
There's some kind of trauma apparently.
- What then?
- It's the boy, sir.
Neil Johnson?
- He's talked?
- Not talked exactly.
What then?
Down at the hospital,
Conroy was left to look after him
while we spoke with the parents.
The kid wouldn't say a word.
Not a word.
So Conroy gave him some stuff
to play with. Paper, pens.
And?
And the kid started drawing.
God almighty.
Maybe the Yank was right.
Maybe there is something out there.
We have to stop.
Why, honey?
I gotta pee.
Well, we're not going back.
But I have to.
You should have thought
of that before we left.
I forgot.
How can you forget?
That's stupid.
Robbie.
Okay, it's too far to the next town,
so we're just gonna stop right here.
Okay, wanna go with her?
She's okay on her own.
Go on, Minty.
- Where?
- In the field.
Nobody will see you.
Come on, sweetheart.
We haven't got all day.
I'm gonna go with her.
- She's okay.
- I know, I know.
She's got to grow up
sometime, you know.
But not till I'm good and ready.
You see that big green bush?
You go right behind there, okay?
Hurry up, sweetheart.
- You mustn't look.
- I won't look.
Now, go ahead. Hurry up.
Just go on. Go on.
That's right. Go on.
Minty!
- It's all over now.
- Oh, my God.
- What happened?
- It's just a rabbit there. It scared her.
All right, you go to Mommy now, okay?
Oh, little baby.
- God, that's ugly.
- Feel all right now?
- Really disgusting.
- You feeling better?
- How's Mommy? Mommy okay now?
- Mommy's okay.
No, it's okay.
Crows are very bad things.
Poor little bunny.
- It's gone to heaven.
- Yeah.
You wanna go back to the car?
Robbie.
Give me a kiss.
Dad! Dad!
Robbie. No. No.
Robbie!
Look, please.
- I have a job to do.
- We all have a job to do.
- Give us a break.
- Fine, okay.
- Just one or two shots, right?
- Here he is now.
Let's get the whole situation.
- Is it true the army's been moved in?
- I have no comment.
Is there any connection
between the murders?
Yes. They're all dead.
Is the army being moved in?
Why don't you all
get the hell out of here.
What have you got up there, Detective?
Animal, vegetable or mineral?
Go ahead. Answer the man.
What have you got?
- Look, mister...
- Animal, vegetable or mineral?
- We're doing all we can.
- Too late.
Too goddamn late.
Obviously, we'd appreciate
your assistance.
I've given your man here everything.
Every sickening detail.
We've done maps. We've done drawings.
It's the same as what the boy saw, sir.
What in God's name is it?
Of course darkness can be deceptive.
I was wrong. I'll grant you that.
- Thanks.
- Believe me.
We're going to find your son's killer.
The valley's being searched
by armed officers. We'll find it.
I bet it has hiding places you couldn't
even guess at. You wanna know why?
Enlighten me.
I think it belongs here.
This is its home.
- From way back.
- Then we've got it, haven't we?
If this is his territory, it'll come back,
sooner or later.
All we have to do is wait.
Wait? Wait for what?
More of your mistakes?
More slaughter?
Look, Mr. Hallenbeck,
we understand how you feel.
You have no idea how I feel!
Your goddamn stupidity
is the reason my son is dead.
Now, do you understand that?
Get the goddamn thing myself.
- Look, Hallenbeck...
- Go to hell!
Just go right to hell!
I'm sorry.
- I have to go out. I'll be back.
- Okay.
They buried him alive.
- What?
- The devil.
They put him in the earth, deep down.
They thought he'd die, you see.
Thought they could forget about him.
But the dark ones come back.
They always do.
- This window...
- Useless to fight.
- What does it represent?
- Nothing!
- The devil's won.
- Wait a minute.
Declan.
See?
You've nothing left to fight with.
I've just heard about your son.
My condolences.
These windows.
When were these put in?
You can think of windows
at a time like this?
When were the windows put in?
Well, they were made
and remade several times.
The church was badly damaged
in the 1860s.
A lot of the glass was lost or replaced.
It's a bit of a jigsaw puzzle.
It wasn't a very good job.
Some of the fragments were...
This is not just academic interest, is it?
You're damn right it isn't.
That thing killed my son.
I stood there and watched him do it.
It's not human, that thing.
If I was your friend Declan,
I'd say that was the devil.
- But you don't believe in the devil.
- No, I don't believe in the devil.
But something started the rumor.
I knew it. That's it. It just didn't fit.
What?
That's the missing piece.
Look. This image doesn't fit there.
But look at this.
There's one hand,
and there's the other one.
So?
I think this guy in the picture,
I think he beat the creature once before.
This is paganism.
Just look at it. It's as plain
as the nose on your face.
That is what I saw.
That is what killed my son.
And that is out there right now,
ready and waiting.
Please, you're distraught.
Goddamn it, don't you humor me!
Mr. Hallenbeck, this is Christ's house.
It wasn't always His, was it?
We couldn't see much, of course,
even with the torches,
but I had a pretty good idea
what was going on.
- Why was that?
- Smelled the blood.
Really?
Certainly.
It had a coppery smell about it.
You couldn't miss it.
- Jesus, what was that?
- Go on.
Then, of course, we found the body.
What's going on?
All right, keep calm. Keep calm.
- Felt like an earthquake.
- Where's the door?
Kick it out.
Get out here.
What is it, Tom?
Somebody get the police!
Get the police!
Here, you bastard!
Oh, God, no! Mary!
Shoot it. Shoot it.
- Well?
- Yes, we've got it, sir.
- Where?
- The caravan park.
- Get the cars around the front.
- On my way.
We'll be right there.
It's territorial. I told you so.
- Where do you think you're going?
- With you.
- No, you're not.
- You can't stop me.
- Conroy, hold this man.
- Mr. Hallenbeck...
- Get your hands off me.
- Howard, please.
Just stay here with us.
God almighty.
It went over there, towards the village.
- Get ambulances.
- Right.
Move.
You wanna go back to the hotel?
Elaine?
No.
- You'd be more comfortable there.
- Only if you come.
- No, I'm gonna talk to Gissing.
- Let him do his job.
I want him to make
house-to-house inquiries.
They know something, these people.
What are you talking about?
He's been here before,
this... this thing.
In Rathmorne.
And these people, they beat him.
Look at this.
This is a stained glass window
in their church.
Do you see? He's being done in
by whatever the hooded figure's holding.
It looks like a tablet,
but it's a missing piece of glass.
That's the missing piece.
I think there's other missing pieces too.
It's like the handle
of a knife or a sword or...
something.
But it's a weapon.
- Weapon?
- Yeah.
If I can find it...
I can do that goddamn thing in.
Stop the car.
- Where is he?
- We probably passed him.
He'd never have gone this far on foot.
- Damn him!
- What shall I do?
- Turn around. Let's go back.
- Yes, sir.
Holy Jesus! Christ!
No! No! No!
Yes.
For you.
Mr. Hallenbeck?
- Gissing here yet?
- He's very busy at the moment.
It's very important that I talk to him.
Mr. Hallenbeck, you've already
made your feelings perfectly clear.
The inspector will see you
as soon as he can.
In the meantime,
can I get you a cup of tea?
Go fuck yourself.
- I'll pass that suggestion along.
- You do that.
You came!
Quickly!
I can't hear a word you're saying.
Who is this?
Get over here quickly!
Who is this? Reverend, is that you?
Well, where are you?
The church, damn you!
Control to Inspector Gissing.
Is Inspector Gissing there?
There's no escape!
Keep your voice down.
He's in the rectory.
You think I don't know?
I see what he sees.
He wants you, you know.
Wants to baptize you.
- You're out of your mind.
- No!
I simply saw the light.
Declan, you are one of God's teachers.
God?
He is God!
The parish records.
He was here before Christ,
before civilization.
He was king here.
No. Gissing went after it.
We're trying to organize...
I just got a call from the reverend.
It's down at the church.
The church.
Yeah, we're on our way.
Rawhead.
That's what they called him.
Rawhead!
You stay here.
No. No, no, no, Declan.
Wait. Wait. Declan, wait.
Think. Think.
It doesn't care about you.
When it's finished with you,
what will it do with you?
Kill me, I hope!
Declan, for the love of God.
Get upstairs, fuck-face.
I can't keep God waiting.
You did this?
I'm going to destroy it all.
He wants me to take it apart
piece by piece.
You wouldn't dare.
He's not scared!
Why doesn't he come in
and do it personally?
I think your God is afraid, Declan.
- No.
- Yes.
Afraid to set foot in Christ's house.
No!
Your pathetic little shepherd
has no hold on him.
Or me!
I know my real master when I see him.
And so will you!
Get back.
Will we rush the church, sir?
No. Just stand by.
This is holy ground.
God's ground.
Oh, Jesus.
What was that?
Keep them back, out of the line of fire!
Come on. Back.
Come on. Out the way now. Stay back!
- Stay back here!
- Target!
Hold your fire. Hold your fire!
He's got the vicar.
Kill the murdering bastard!
Oh, no! The poor soul!
Can we shoot the bastard, sir?
We may hit the old man.
He's dead already. Look at him.
No, he's still moving.
Jesus, have mercy on his soul!
No!
Ready!
Fire!
For you! For you!
I can't just stay here.
I have to do something.
Howard, no!
Oh, Jesus.
Oh, my God.
Hallenbeck, over here!
Get some help.
He's bleeding to death.
Jesus. Dear God.
Stay in the church.
- What's he saying?
- Shut up.
The altar.
It... afraid.
Something...
in the altar.
You go back to the station.
My wife and my daughter are there.
I'll look after them.
Oh, Jesus. Oh, Jesus Christ.
What the fuck do you want?
Get the fuck out of here.
Get the fuck out of here!
It's afraid of something.
What? What is it afraid of?
He got into the altar.
I couldn't stop him.
But you can kill him.
There he is.
There!
Okay, sweetheart, let's do it.
Okay, do it.
Come on.
Do it.
Kill the fucker! Now!
Take me. Yes.
Oh, my God.
Elaine, get out of here. Get out!
Howard!
A woman.
It had to be a woman.
No!
It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
We can go home now.
It's all over now.
It's all over.