That's a first down.
Husky ball at the 35-yard line.
Hut!
Touchdown! Paul Taylor.
17-yard pass from Terry Stokes.
Paul, look at her, man. Look at her!
I think she wants your body.
You got to ask her out, Paul.
Isn't she dating Pulver?
Yeah, but that's going nowhere.
Take a shot, for Christ's sake.
Hey, I'm going to ask her out.
Bullshit!
When, when, when?
- When the time is right.
- Yeah, right.
Timing's everything.
Hit him! Hit him!
Yeah! All right!
Wildcat fumble.
Husky ball. First and ten.
7-yard pass complete to Paul Taylor.
Meg, you have any plans this evening?
Go!
Looks like the game
put you out of business.
Don't worry.
When they're through screaming...
...they'll be in here like a flood.
More iced tea?
Please.
It's good that this town's got up
on its hindlegs about something.
It takes people's minds off their troubles.
It's been a lean year for most folk.
The ski season is about to start.
There will be tourists.
You know, there's a new band
out at the Tin Palace tonight.
Is that right?
Supposed to be pretty good.
That's nice.
You like country music?
Herb, are you asking me out?
Yeah, well, I guess I am.
I don't know.
I'm kind of stuck here.
You know, I've got to earn a living.
Yeah, it must be tough trying to get away.
Shoot!
George, here they come.
Is that my check?
If you do get any free time to yourself...
...that's my number there
down at the station.
Okay.
Okay. One at a time.
Flagg. Congratulations.
For what?
I hear you have a birthday coming up.
No more juvie hall, right?
Yeah, right.
You mess up now and you're in the majors.
I'll see you around, Flagg.
Moss, what's happening?
You look like hell.
It's a fashion statement, man.
The only statement those clothes
have got to make is, "I look like hell."
My bike's broken down at Elkin's Grove.
I was thinking...
...maybe I could borrow your ratchet set?
The Summit's got me overhauling
six damn Skidoos, three Cats...
...and two flatbed snowmakers, by Monday.
What's the hurry?
It must be 70 degrees out there.
It's Indian summer, boy.
Very soon winter will be tear-arseing
through this town...
...with no apologies.
Come on. It barely pissed snow
the last couple of years.
This whole town's ready to fold.
This year's going to be different.
Is that right?
Take my word.
You'll wish your piece of shit excuse
for a motorcycle...
...was one of these sweet little rigs.
So how about the ratchet?
All right. Maybe I'll put in
a couple of hours over the weekend.
Maybe that'll lighten things up a bit.
There are twelve sockets in that set.
Twelve.
They better all be there when I get it back.
You got it, buddy. You got it.
Thanks a lot, Moss.
I owe you one.
You owe me too damn many.
Holy cow!
Lend me $5 just until tomorrow, okay?
What for?
You know, you're not the only one
with a date tonight.
I'm going to score with Vicki tonight.
I want to invest in some protection.
Let's go. It's closing time.
All right, here.
Make it quick.
Look, pal. Give me a pack of Trojans,
and a Binaca spray.
Scott Jeskey.
Reverend.
Good game today.
Thanks. Thanks, Reverend.
How are you?
The hay fever's acting up a little bit,
but I'll live.
Haven't seen you
at the Sunday services lately.
You want the ribbed, or the regular?
Ribbed, I guess.
They're not for me, you know.
They're for my friend.
There's this sort of naive girl
that he's planning on...
Well, you know.
I insisted that he take precautions.
Why doesn't he pay for them?
I had to drag him down here as it is.
The guy is totally irresponsible.
Come on, Scott. What's the hold up?
I can't keep this girl waiting.
The boy doesn't need condoms.
He needs a muzzle.
Kevin! Don't eat with your face.
Mum, we're in a hurry.
We're going bowling with Anthony.
And then to the movies.
What movie?
Garden Tool Massacre.
It's your basic slice-and-dice.
Your basic what?
This guy in a hockey mask,
he chops up a few teenagers.
But don't worry,
there's no sex or anything bad.
They won't let you kids
into a movie like that.
No problem. My brother's an usher.
No. Absolutely not.
Mum, come on!
Kevin! I will not have you seeing
that kind of trash, and that's final.
Do you understand?
Yes, ma'am.
Mum, have you seen my pink sweater?
It's on the hamper, honey.
I meant to talk to you about that.
- Why did you do that?
- What did I do?
We had a little accident.
What happened?
It got mixed up in the wash.
Interesting look.
Why don't you wear
my cashmere sweater?
- Are you serious?
- Sure.
Oh, my God! That's him.
What do you want?
Hi. I'm here to see Meg.
What for?
Just to see her.
- ls she home?
- Just a minute.
I'm terribly sorry.
You must be Paul. I'm Meg's mother.
Nice to meet you, ma'am.
Come on in. Meg will be right down.
Where are you going?
- I'm sleeping over at Eddie's, remember?
- Right.
But you're not going anywhere
without your jacket.
Mum, it's boiling out.
It's October. It's night-time.
You're wearing your jacket.
- Stupid coat.
- No, here, let me.
Bye, honey. Enjoy yourself.
Bye, Mum.
Bye, Eddie.
Oh, yeah.
Won't you sit down?
Excuse me.
Hi, Paul.
Are you surviving my family so far?
- Yeah. You look great.
- Thank you.
You want to go?
I just want you to meet my dad.
It'll just take a second.
Sure.
Daddy, I'd like you to meet my friend, Paul.
Ribbed.
Hey!
I'm really sorry about my dad.
I've never seen him like that before.
That's okay.
It was just a misunderstanding.
I've made better first impressions.
That's for sure.
No harm done, I guess.
No, wrong.
Scott Jeskey is going to die.
Paul, watch out!
Flagg! Jesus Christ.
What did you do to him?
I'm not the one
who bounced him off my car, pal!
- You ran him into the road!
- Stop it! Let's get him to a doctor.
Watch out. He's got some kind of
corrosive shit on his hands.
Come on. Take it easy, mister.
We'll get you some help. All right?
The sky. It fell from the sky.
What's he saying?
He's in shock. Let's just go.
Get in the car.
What for?
There'll be a lot of explaining to do,
and you're part of it.
Are you going to get in the car,
or am I going to make you get in?
What's the matter? You worried
about a little insurance claim...
...on Daddy's car?
Maybe I will come along...
...just to make sure
you don't blame it all on me.
Are you two finished?
Whenever you're ready.
- Excuse me, nurse.
- One moment, please.
How may I help you?
We've had a car accident.
This guy needs a doctor.
He has something on his hand, too.
Some kind of acid or something.
Does he have Blue Cross?
- I don't know.
- Medical insurance of any kind?
I don't believe this shit.
We don't even know who the guy is.
The doctor's with another patient
right now.
Could you put this gentleman
in Room 3, please?
You'll have to fill these out.
Okay.
Take it easy, old dude.
These guys are going to fix you right up.
Where are you going?
These people don't give a shit
about explanations.
If you need me,
you know where to find me.
I bet you've had better first dates.
I don't mind.
You want a soda?
That would be great. Something diet.
Absolutely. At this point
the prognosis is very positive.
In cases like this, the question is always
the quality of physical therapy.
The follow-up to any operation is
to a great extent...
Doctor, come in here quickly!
- I'm with a patient...
- There's a man dying in here! Hurry!
Excuse me a moment.
Is this the hand injury?
What is this?
That thing on his hand.
Nurse!
- Sheriff's Department.
- Get me the Sheriff! It's an emergency.
Paul?
Geller speaking.
Sheriff, this is Paul Taylor.
Paul, what's wrong?
I'm at the Arborville Hospital.
An old man's just been killed down here.
- You said "killed"?
- Yes, sir.
You sit tight. I'll be right down.
Who else is involved?
I'm with Meg Penny.
- And Brian Flagg was here earlier.
- Flagg?
Where is he now?
Paul?
Paul!
I did see it, Dad. It killed Paul.
Sheriff.
How about it, Herb?
Can we take her home?
You may as well, Tom.
Make sure she gets a good sleep.
We're not going to get anything
out of her tonight. She's hysterical.
I have to call Paul Taylor's folks.
They haven't heard from him.
Let's face it, Bill. They're not going to.
You get that to Sacramento tonight.
And I want the autopsy pronto...
...not next week.
Jesus wept!
Herb, you okay?
Taylor was a good kid.
I want the son of a bitch who did this.
I think we've already got him.
Scott! Cut it out. I told you.
Come on, Vicki. You're wearing my ring.
That makes you my girl.
Doesn't that count for something?
What are all those lights down there?
Isn't that the hospital?
It's probably a promotional gimmick.
They're giving away free tonsillectomies.
I think that you're about ready
for another one of my famous...
- ...cherry coolers.
- I think I've had enough.
Nonsense. You've never had enough.
My very own blend
of special imported liquors.
Okay.
It's like a steam bath in here.
Here's your drink, Vicki.
Hot as a dog out there tonight.
That's a...
That's a nice blouse.
Nice material.
It must be hot, though.
I'll just undo one of these for you.
That's better, huh?
Oh, no?
Oh, well.
I'll just...
...undo another one then.
Okay.
Oh God, Vicki!
No!
I shouldn't have let her
go out with the son of a bitch...
...in the first place.
Lower your voice.
That poor boy's probably dead.
I want to know
what happened out there tonight.
Whatever it was
that Flagg kid was behind it.
It's about time they nailed
that little psychopath.
His arse is going to fry this time.
Believe me.
Here, take this.
I don't want it.
Come on, honey.
You have to get some sleep.
That's my good girl.
Now, just let it alone.
I'm sure the police will have
this whole thing settled by the morning.
Come on.
Mum?
You don't believe me either, do you?
You're home now.
You're safe.
That's all that matters.
Look at him. He's too stupid
to know how much trouble he's in.
Why don't you wise up?
I told you everything.
I'm getting tired of hearing myself talk.
We're not boring you, are we?
A bright kid like you?
Am I under arrest?
Because if I am, I want a lawyer.
Now he wants a lawyer.
That's right. If you're not booking me,
I'd like to leave.
Either way, I want you out of my face.
Oh yeah, hard-arse?
I'm in your face to stay.
What are you going to do about it?
Go ahead, hit me!
Go ahead.
Any luck with his mama?
I can't seem to find her.
That's not unusual, is it?
She takes vacations
with Johnnie Walker Red...
...and anyone else
who happens to be around.
We could call his dad,
if anyone knew who he was.
Call a shrink. I'm a broken man.
You think this is a joke?
Turn him loose.
We got eyewitnesses
placing him at the crime scene.
We got no motive. No evidence.
He hasn't got a drop of blood on him.
- Flagg's a punk. But he's no killer.
- I think it's a mistake.
Your objection is duly noted.
Now turn him loose. We got work to do.
Go on.
Take a hike.
Brian! I need to talk to you.
What the hell are you doing here?
Look, I came down to bail you out.
What do you think they are,
Neiman-Marcus?
They don't take plastic.
Look, I appreciate the thought.
Now, go home, okay?
I need to talk to you.
I'm sorry about your boyfriend. I really am.
I'm tired and hungry, and I'm not
in the mood for conversation, okay?
George. Frannie. Que pasa?
Hey, hotshot, we're closed.
Come on. I've been dumped on all day.
Give me a break.
What's the matter, dear,
tough day at the office?
Well, grill's shut down.
How about a sandwich?
Beautiful.
You don't give up, do you?
I need your help.
For three years in school
you haven't said shit to me.
All of a sudden you need my help
and we're best friends, right?
Nobody believes me
about what happened tonight.
What did happen?
You were there. You saw.
All I saw was an old man
with a funky hand. That's all I saw.
Thanks.
Can I get you something, hon?
No, thank you.
The thing on that man's hand killed him
and then it killed Paul.
And whatever it is, it's getting bigger.
Is that what you told the cops?
Do you mind if I ask you
a personal question?
I know you're the homecoming queen type
and all, but...
...are you strung out on something,
or what?
You're just the same.
What are you talking about?
You act like you're different.
You put on this big show.
But you're just like everyone else
in this town. You're full of shit, Flagg!
Wait a second!
Calm down, all right? I'm sorry, okay?
Come on, sit down.
You okay?
You want something to eat?
Here. Go ahead, it'll make you feel better.
Unbelievable.
It's just that I've never heard
you say "shit" before.
What was that like for you?
We're coming up empty here.
Should we head to the foothills?
Negative.
I'd rather have you patrolling the streets.
We'll start that at first light,
when the state police come in.
Ten-four.
You look exhausted.
It's been a long night. Thank you.
It's going to be even longer.
That's the truth.
One deputy and six volunteers.
I feel like the one-legged man...
...in an arse-kicking contest.
You're doing all you can, Herb.
This isn't your normal, Friday night drunk.
Something wrong?
I'm just worried about a friend of mine.
I guess I'm worried
about everybody tonight.
Dessert.
Fran. That sandwich busted me.
On the house. Last two pieces.
Eat up, or I chuck it in the garbage.
Thanks.
Shit.
Here. I'll get that.
I'll get it.
- Here. Knock yourself out.
- Well, thanks.
What is this?
Don't touch him!
Fran, come on!
In the freezer!
Hear anything?
I'm okay.
I'm going to get us out of here. I promise.
Come on, answer!
Your call can not be completed as dialled.
Please check the number, and dial again.
- Sheriff's Station.
- Help me!
Get me Herb. Get Herb Geller.
He went down to the diner.
You ready?
Okay.
Great. I killed the strawberry jam.
Let's get out of here.
The front door is locked.
That's okay. I got a key.
Merciful God.
Hello?
Is anybody...
...hurt?
We need to see the Sheriff!
I don't know where he is.
Sheriff's Department. Please hold.
What about Briggs?
I can't raise anybody.
All I'm getting is static.
Sheriff's Department. Please hold.
The last I heard from the Deputy,
he was on his way up to Elkin's Grove.
Elkin's Grove.
That's where I found the old man.
Come on, let's go.
It looks like he left in a hurry.
He's got to be around here somewhere.
In the woods.
In the dark woods.
Right. We could wait here.
I never thought I'd go out of my way
to find a cop.
Hello!
I feel like fucking Hansel and Gretel here.
We should have brought bread crumbs.
Wait.
I think I hear something.
What the hell is that?
Put those weapons down.
We're here to help you.
- Name?
- Meg Penny.
- Are you a resident of Arborville, Meg?
- Yes, I am.
Have you experienced any vomiting,
nausea or diarrhoea?
Back off!
Hey, pal. You want to fill us in?
Who the hell are you people?
I'm Dr. Meddows. We're a government
sanctioned, biological containment team.
"Biological containment?"
We're microbe hunters, young lady.
Flagg?
What are you doing here, boy?
The men from Glad here are showing us
how to keep our leftovers fresh.
They're here on business.
They don't have time for bullshit. Okay?
Colonel, has the Deputy been briefed
in detail?
Yes, sir.
I'm heading to town now to get started.
Splendid.
Colonel Hargis will arrange an escort.
What is going on over there?
That's the source of our worries.
A troublesome souvenir from space.
- What?
- A meteorite.
Don't get too close.
There's danger of contamination.
I don't understand.
Let me tell you a story.
The dinosaurs ruled our planet
for millions of years...
...and yet they died out almost overnight.
Why?
The evidence suggests...
...that a meteor fell to earth bearing
an alien bacteria.
Plague? Is that what this is all about?
Prevention.
And you think this meteor brought
some kind of a killer germ?
It's something I've expected
and prepared for, all my life.
Your meteor brought something all right.
But if it's a germ...
...it's the biggest son of a bitch
you've ever seen.
What's the matter?
Isn't it awfully late
to be trimming the hedges?
Maybe this guy's a peeping Tom
or something.
So, let's give him something to peep at.
Wait a minute.
Hockey season ended months ago.
He's going to get the camp counsellor
with the hedge trimmer.
But the girl gets away.
She's going to run into the lodge and hide,
but he's going to get her anyway.
Please be quiet.
You shut up!
Hey!
You've got to shut up. If you get caught...
...your mum'll kill me.
Get your feet off the seat!
Anthony, come on.
Jerk.
What a wimp!
Check out the body on the blonde.
Wonderful.
Yeah?
It's Hobbs. It's boiling up here.
Is the air conditioning on?
It's on full blast.
It must be blocked up or something.
There's nothing wrong with it.
Come up and see for yourself.
Hobbs, are you in here?
I can't begin to thank you both.
This information is incredibly valuable.
Please, get in.
- Where are we going?
- Back to town.
Arborville is under quarantine
until we've isolated that organism...
...and checked every living soul
for signs of infection.
- ln the meantime, we're your prisoners.
- Not at all. You're my patients.
Sounds like the same thing to me.
Young man, please, step into the van.
Thanks for the offer, Doc. But my bike's
back there and we can make it back...
...on our own.
By the way, I love your tailor.
I got to get me one of those.
Get in the van.
Van ride sounds nice.
Clear.
- lt's locked.
- So what?
Brian, what is with you?
You're acting like a complete jerk.
I have a problem with authority figures.
What are you doing?
We ought to get out of here.
Take my bike and blow this town.
It's getting thick around here,
don't you think?
That's crazy.
These people are here to help us.
Come on, Meg.
We don't even know who they are.
NASA? CIA?
The Royal Canadian Mounties?
All I know is I saw a bunch
of unmarked trucks.
I think this whole thing stinks.
Well, we can't just run out.
Let's just think of it
as looking out for our best interests.
You coming?
Brian, I have to go back.
My family's there, people that I care about.
I'm going.
If you're smart, you'll come with me.
Then go. Take care of yourself.
That's the only thing you're really good at.
No one else ever volunteered for the job.
Christ, Flagg. A cheerleader.
Come on, ma'am.
There is no cause for alarm.
I repeat, there is no cause for alarm.
This is a precautionary quarantine,
due to a potential biological hazard.
Please proceed toward Town Hall
in an orderly fashion.
Mum! Dad!
Meg! Thank God you're all right!
Honey, is Kevin with you?
No. Isn't he staying at Eddie's house?
Eddie says they were staying
at your house.
Oh, God! He must've snuck off
to that damn movie.
What movie?
You didn't tell me about any movie.
Sir, my little brother is
at the movie theatre on Main Street.
We're going by sector.
We'll be there soon.
- You don't...
- We'll handle it. Back in line.
Seems you're doing nothing.
You on a break?
- Look, Mr....
- Don't "Look, Mr." me. I pay taxes.
I pay your salary.
I want you to find my son!
I know you're upset, but get in line...
...we have everything under control.
Did you know that ten years ago tonight,
there was a horrible murder in this house?
- No way! Come on.
- This man...
You'll love this.
He hot-curls her to death.
Mister, we're trying to watch a...
My zipper!
Come on! Hurry!
Your feet!
No!
Hurry!
Here!
Open it up!
Eddie!
Hurry! Go!
Go!
Come on, Meg!
Meg, come on!
- Alpha Team, do you copy?
- Affirmative.
Status report?
Highway 31 closed.
Phone lines down.
We've got this town locked up tight.
On up.
We suspected that conditions in space
would have a mutating effect on bacteria...
...but this!
Its activity threw the satellite out of orbit.
Correct. Our little experimental virus
seems to have grown up...
...into a plasmic life form
that hunts its prey.
A predator. It's fantastic.
Sir, the organism is growing
at a geometric rate.
By all accounts, it's at least
a thousand times its original mass.
This will put U.S. Defence years ahead
of the Russians.
You don't understand.
At this rate, by next week,
there may be no U.S.
Nonsense!
All we have to do is contain it.
As far as the locals are concerned...
...this is simply a medical quarantine.
Nobody gets in, or out.
Dr. Meddows, just for the record...
...I don't agree with any of this.
Those people's lives are at stake.
Don't you think I know that?
This isn't one of your textbook exercises,
Mr. Jennings.
This is an experiment in biological warfare,
or hadn't you noticed?
That organism could be the greatest
breakthrough in weapons research...
...since man split the atom.
What we do here will affect the balance
of world power!
Of course there are lives at stake.
Whole nations, in fact.
And that's far more important than
a handful of people in this small town.
And that is my cross to bear...
...Mr. Jennings.
Now, carry out your orders.
Yes, sir.
Colonel!
Colonel, we've got a sighting.
Hargis here.
An eyewitness saw the organism
pursue civilians...
- ...into the sewers.
- lt's got Kevin, Eddie and Meg down there.
You've got to do something.
Excellent!
We need a schematic of the sewers.
We'll contain it down there.
I want that organism alive.
What about the civilians?
They're expendable.
Get up.
Stop him!
Attention!
We have an infected civilian
trying to escape.
Stop him before he reaches
a populated area!
Halt, or we'll open fire!
I repeat: Halt, or we'll open fire!
Turn!
Handicapped persons,
or persons in need of special assistance...
...may report to the Blue Station,
located on the north lawn.
Dr. Sims and Dr. Divatni,
please report to Med. Unit 1.
- Are these the schematics?
- Yes, sir.
The whole town's sitting
on a system of aqueducts...
...run off from the mountains.
Can the organism be contained?
There seem to be three main junctions.
Here, here, and here.
If we close off those valves,
I think we got it.
Is it still after us?
I don't think so.
I'll be good, I swear.
I'll never see a movie, ever again.
It's going to be okay.
Let's just find a way out of here.
This way.
Baker Team,
we place you 80 metres south of Valve 2.
Come on. That's our way out of here.
Watch out for the rat.
What rat?
Run!
Get up the post. Move!
Come on, climb! Go!
No!
Get him out of there!
Come on!
I can't get through!
You can make it, Meg! Come on!
Run, Kevin! Run!
We have orders not to shoot!
Run, Kevin! Go to Town Hall!
No! But, Meg...
Do it now!
What are you doing?
Hang on!
Brian!
- You all right?
- Yeah.
Forget about it, Brian.
Let's go. Forget about it!
It got them. Bigelow and Wilson.
How do we get out of here?
They were trying to scream.
Inside it. Trying to scream...
Listen to me! How do we get out of here?
Brian, he's hurt!
I think...
...we'd better go now.
Baker Team, Baker Team,
what the hell's going on down there?
We're coming up!
Close the manhole.
That's my man down there!
We've got to contain that thing.
Now, close it off! That's an order!
Do it.
Hey!
No!
You son of a bitch!
Colonel, you can't!
That thing's down here with us!
Meddows!
Do you hear me, Meddows?
Talk to me, man!
Meddows!
The water's rising.
It's coming for us.
I thought you were going to take care
of yourself.
I guess I blew it.
I'm sorry, Meg.
I really am.
This thing work?
- Does this thing work?
- It won't do any good.
Not against that thing.
All right, Meddows.
If you won't listen to me...
...listen to this.
Shit!
Fire in Sector 2!
Charlie Squad to Sector 2!
All right, people, please stay
where you are! Stay out of the street!
Mobile weapon units to Sector 2!
We got a man down in Sector 2.
On the double!
Flagg!
Drop it!
Stay back.
It's a lie!
All of it!
I said, put it down!
I'll blow you out of your shoes, boy.
Shoot him.
Freeze, mister!
All right, hold on.
Everybody...
...just lower your weapons.
Hold your positions.
Don't come any closer.
He's infected! Contagious!
He'll spread a plague through this place...
...and kill all of you!
Listen to me, Briggs. Think for a minute.
Do you think an army of guys,
in plastic suits, show up every time...
...a meteor falls?
Shoot him. That's a direct order!
How do you think they got here so quick?
- How did they know when to come?
- Shoot! Damn it, shoot!
I'll tell you how! That meteor is manmade!
Some kind of a germ warfare test
they fucked up!
Don't try it!
Let's scrag that son of a bitch!
Satchel charge! Short fuse!
Chew on that, slime ball.
What's happening?
I think you pissed it off.
Go!
My God...
- ...the day has come.
- Reverend, come on!
You don't understand.
This has all been prophesied.
Move! Get out, everybody!
Everybody, back!
He ran for it, Meg. Let's go! Move!
Come on.
Reverend!
Meg, look out!
It's the cold. It can't stand the cold!
Hurry!
Barricade all the entrances!
Get some more CO2 over here!
Look out! Coming through.
It's empty, Meg! Get back!
Stay here!
And the great voice spoke
to the seven angels and said: "Go your..."
There! Right there!
It's out!
Find some more!
Help me.
Come on! You can do better than that!
Come on, you son of a bitch.
What a rush.
Hey, man...
...I told you we'd get snow.
You got to have faith.
I wonder if I'm covered
for this sort of thing.
Dave, bring in the dump truck.
We better get this thing
to the icehouse before dawn.
The will of God is written in the sky
in fingers of flame.
Wormwood falls from Heaven...
...consuming sinner and saint alike!
Who shall be lifted up to rapture...
...when the judgement trumpet blows?
None but the faithful...
...brothers and sisters!
None but the faithful.
When, Reverend?
Ma'am?
The day of reckoning, how far off?
Soon, madam. Soon.
The Lord will give me a sign.
Subtitles by ARAVIND B
[by_agentsmith@yahoo.com]