I told you to
keep an eye on her!
I was. It came on so suddenly.
Get some towels
and another pillow.
There may still be a chance.
Get her ready.
She's the last one.
Where's my baby?
I'm sorry, Mrs. Slater.
No.
No!
Does anybody have a hairbrush?
I can't find it anywhere!
I just hope there are enough
bags to carry all this.
Well, we moved it on
here in the same bags, Mom.
Does anyone ever
clean that pool?
Hardly.
Mrs. Slater says she's not paying
anyone to clean it if we never use it.
How are we supposed to use it
if it's always dirty?
Yeah. It sounds like
Mrs. Slater, all right.
Well, we've just had the
pool man over,
so you can swim all summer
while you're at home.
I'm not moving back home, Mom.
This has nothing
to do with you.
I just have a lot
to think about.
Like what I'm going to do
with the rest of my life.
Well, don't you think
after four years of college
you'd have a start
in those decisions?
Katie, stop packing!
Hi, Mrs. Rose,
how you doing?
Katie, come here a second.
I just want you to stay till
Friday to help set things up.
How about it?
By Friday, we're going to have
this place looking outrageous!
Come on, yes or no?
All six of us are staying.
Ok.
Great!
By the way, don't worry
about a date for Friday night.
-I went ahead and fixed you up!
-You what?
No need to
thank me! Ciao!
Yes?
Thank you. You can send
her right in.
They're just
asking for talks.
You've got to reconsider.
My mind
is made up.
I intend to spend this summer as
I've spent all the rest.
But the environment
here is so much more helpful.
I told you,
there'll be no one at the house.
It was closed for
three months today.
I understand, but
anything might happen.
At least here, we're
prepared to handle it.
His condition is getting worse.
You know it as well as I do.
We both knew the risks.
For 20 years, you've been
blaming me for what happened.
Don't you see?
You're living in
a fantasy world.
You've got to
forget the past.
Live with what
you have today.
You have done a good
job of forgetting.
Well, I never will.
If you try to stop me from
living as I please,
I'll see that what you
did is remembered.
I've had a
new tag made.
This must be worn
at all times,
just in case there
are any problems.
There'll be no problems.
Good day.
Vicki, where
you taking me?
Just wait.
Holy shit, look
at this place.
Is it deserted
enough for ya?
Come on, let me try it.
Do like I told you,
though, all right?
Yeah, yeah,
I will, I will.
Aim it at that
sack over there.
Ok.
Will you get off me?
Go on, pull the trigger. Just...
All right, all right.
Come on, come on up front,
I'll start this time.
-Ok.
-A toast to law school.
May it be the three shortest
years of my life.
I hope so!
Ok, ok.
Here is to reaching
my fullest capacity.
Bout a quart and a half!
Here's to Pan Am,
my new employer.
May they never find out
I'm scared of flying!
To my mother,
who never let me forget I was born
with a silver spoon in my mouth.
Mama, you were wrong...
It's up my nose!
Come on, Katie.
Ok.
I wanna thank you all.
Noo, no
No, I'm serious.
I wanna thank you all for
helping me become what I am today.
Wasted!
Morgan, it's your turn.
We realize this takes a
lot of thinking, Morgan.
Ok.
A toast to... to...
God, I'm... excuse me!
God!
What are you girls doing here?
Who, us?
The house is closed.
What are you girls doing here?
Well...
You tell her, Diane.
It's all very
simple, Mrs. Slater.
We had to move the graduation
party from the Silver Bear.
Move it?
Insufficient funds.
So, we...
We're having the party here.
Really?
We're only staying a
couple of extra days
to set it up.
And whose idea was all this?
Well, Vicki thought the house would be
the perfect place, and we all agreed.
Vicki.
Where is she?
We haven't seen her.
I'll speak to her later.
As for you girls,
how could you even think of
having a drunken spree in my house?
There'll be no party here.
The house is closed.
I want you all out by tomorrow.
Good night.
Sheesh.
The wicked witch of the
west strikes again.
She can't kick us out, can she?
No way. The bylaws
say we can stay.
Like always, she's just
flapping her wings.
Why does she always close
the house on June 19th?
Every other house stays
open through the weekend.
Who knows?
-She's retiring, anyways.
-Nuh-who said?
-I heard talk about it.
-I can't believe it!
-She's an institution around here.
-She's the sorority mascot.
Yeah, the house jackass.
Well, maybe this place'll
finally get a normal house mother.
The kind who sits in her
room and drinks tea.
She is different.
Just a shame she's
gotten so weird.
She used to lend a little tradition
to the house, you know?
Slater is the last
of her breed.
When she goes, the
species'll be extinct.
Let's propose a toast.
To Mrs. Slater.
The house mother to end
all house mothers.
Yeah, that's for sure.
Wait a
minute. Not here.
Why not?
We always do it here.
Not tonight.
Count to 20, I'll
meet you upstairs.
-What?
-Count to 20, Rick.
Vicki?
Look what daddy bought
his little girl.
You filth!
Trash like you doesn't
belong in my house.
Slater, I'm
going to kill you!
You bitch!
I'll get back at you if
it's the last thing I do!
You hear me, goddamn it!
-Vicki, what are you doing?
-Bitch!
Vicki, what
are you doing?
We can't swim
the damn thing, anyway,
what's the difference?
Jesus.
How was that romantic
little skinny-dip last night?
You shut up.
-Chill out.
-My water bed got slashed to pieces,
and all I should
is joke about it?
I'm telling you guys,
she tried to kill me!
Come on, Vicki,
you deserved it.
Can't you fuck anywhere else?
Mrs. Slater really flipped.
She's never gone
that crazy before.
Wait till the party.
God, when she sees the liquor,
she'll have a stroke.
To hell with her.
Sick of worrying about
what Slater thinks.
We run this house!
For four years, we've had to
put up with her and her shit!
She's right, that lady's
been a royal pain in the ass.
Yeah, well there's
been a million times
that bitch has
screwed us all over.
We can't let her get away
with this time, right?
Do you have something in mind, or are
you just exercising your mouth again?
Yeah, I do have
something in mind.
Slater wants things to be
as they used to be, right?
Ok.
Well, how about if we give her a
good old-fashioned sorority prank?
Yeah.
That's a good idea.
What, are you kidding?
-Like what?
-Wait a minute. Let me think.
How about we
T.P. her room?
No, no, no.
How about the old dog shit
in a paper bag routine?
No, we did that
freshman year, no.
How about a bucket
of water over her door?
So when she comes
in, she gets it?
Tomorrow morning, we
could short-sheet her bed?
No, no, no, no.
I got a great one.
Let's spread glue on
her toilet seat!
I got it!
It's perfect!
Well, are you interested or not?
This is silly.
I mean, we're supposed to be
mature adults by now, right?
One more fling won't
set us back any.
Ok.
We'll do it on Friday, right
before our party starts?
Ok, sounds great.
Evaluation as follows,
Condition clearly stems
from Mrs. Slater's
extremely difficult and
traumatic delivery.
Since that point, the
slow progression towards
a psychotic break
has been evident.
X-rays taken after
an errant cephalogram
reveal the cortex undergoing
a process of decay.
Patient's advanced age is
aggravating the condition.
My recommendation is for
immediate advanced treatment.
The next three months must be spent
under complete clinical supervision.
Allowed to live in an
uncontrolled environment,
there's a good chance that any traumatic
episode could act as a stimulus
for the patient's
latent violence.
Vicki, where'd you
get this thing?
I have my sources.
-Is it loaded?
-Of course not.
Go ahead, it's not
going to bite you.
Bam!
That's not funny.
Vicki, this is crazy.
I mean, a joke is one
thing, but a gun?
Trust me, Katie, have
I ever been wrong?
Right before
the party starts,
Slater's going to be in for
one very big surprise.
Hold it,
hold it up here.
Well, it's heavy.
Ok.
I think we're going
to have to go up.
Ready?
-You got it?
-Ok, don't drop it on me.
Take all that junk down!
It's a disgrace!
I want all of you to
pack your belongings
and leave this
house at once.
Do you hear?
What if we don't?
You have a lot to learn
about this world, young lady.
Mrs. Slater, you seem to
be missing something.
Where is it?
Go check out by the pool.
Go ahead, take a swim.
You like getting
people wet, right?
I should teach you
a lesson or two.
Are you threatening me?
If that gun is real,
you are all in serious trouble.
We thought you might need
a little persuading.
What's wrong with a swim?
Come on, it's not much to ask for four
years of putting up with your shit.
Now, go on.
-Get out of my way.
-Go on!
Vicki...
What the hell
are you doing?
I know exactly
what I'm doing!
Vicki, it's not
funny any more!
Shut up, Liz!
You all want this
as much as me.
Someone's gonna hurt.
Give me that gun!
She's all right.
Ok, Slater.
Move it!
-Vicki, you don't want to do this!
-Come on!
Shut up! Go on!
-Vicki, Vicki, give me the gun.
-All the way in.
Vicki, I don't
think you wanna do this.
Vicki, what
are you doing?
No! Stop!
Vicki, don't!
Vicki, no!
You
didn't really think...
-You're wonderful!
-You don't believe us?
My God.
Get a blanket, somebody!
Quick, quick!
Get her out!
All right, all right, easy, easy.
Watch her head, watch her head.
God, come on.
Where is the blanket? Come on!
Put her on a blanket!
Ok, ok, who knows
what to do?
Stevie, know what to do?
Roll her over!
-This is impossible!
-Watch her head!
-Shut up, Vicki!
-I don't think she's breathing, Stevie!
She's not breathing!
Try and get an
ambulance, move it!
Wait a minute.
What good's an
ambulance gonna do now?
There might still
be a chance, hurry!
Don't you realize
what we've done?
-It was an accident!
-That doesn't matter!
We killed her.
My God,
the band's here.
Vicki?
Morgan, run to the
door and stall the band!
-Hurry!
-Ok.
Ok, shit.
She doesn't have any relatives.
We either hide the body,
or face the police.
I am calling an ambulance.
Katie! Katie!
If you call now,
it's over for all of us!
Please, Katie,
please do what she says.
I don't wanna get in trouble.
Katherine, listen to Vicki.
You've got to!
Come on, Vicki!
What are we gonna do with her?
Come on, let's hurry!
Let's hide
her in the house.
No, no,
someone'll find her.
The pool.
It's perfect for now. We can
get her out tomorrow morning.
She's gonna float!
Won't she float?
-Stevie, won't she float?
-How the hell should I know?
I have an idea. Diane, run
to the porch and get as many
towels as you can find,
something to sink her with.
Stevie, go to the pool house, get a
rope, and something to cut it with.
Hurry up!
-Help me!
-Ok!
Got it.
Katie, you, too, come on!
Jesus.
Put it underneath her!
I can't reach over...
-Lift her head.
-I can't!
-Just move her!
-Yes, you can. Lift it up a bit.
Goddamn it, give it to me.
-What about that down there?
-Put it through here.
Tie this all through.
-Make sure she's not gonna get out.
-It's ok.
God!
Get out of here.
Zeta, Eta, Theta,
lota Lambda, Moo, Nu...
-You forgot Kappa.
-Zeta...
Yeah,
I heard Finzer failed.
What?
What do you care?
I thought you hated him.
I do, but I copied
all his answers.
Are you in a frat?
Yeah, I'm a Beta.
Really? You don't look
like a Greek.
-Kata, Omicron, Pi.
-Hey, look at him.
Yeah.
He is cute.
Bobby?
It's over this way.
It's over here.
My favorite tree in
the whole world.
You gotta watch out for squirrels here,
cause they can jump real high.
Here, you can use this one.
Bobby?
Vicki, where's Katherine?
Peter... Katie's upstairs.
Hi.
You must be Katherine.
I'm Peter, hi.
-Hello.
-Vicki told me... are you ok?
Yeah. I'm ok.
Would you like to
be left alone?
No, it's just... its nothing.
Damn it.
Look, blind dates
are silly, anyway.
Why don't I just go?
Wait...
I'm all right, really.
Are you sure?
You
wanna go downstairs?
Great, great.
I bought this for you.
It was very sweet.
Thank you.
Do you wanna dance?
Not now.
How about a drink?
Maybe later.
I could use one.
I'll be right back, ok?
Get the... help me!
One... two...
-There's a wet t-shirt contest!
-Really?
Yeah, yeah.
Nice try!
That one was good.
-Are you ok?
-Get her out of there. My God.
Diane, here give me...
Careful.
Shit, the pool lights.
What is somebody
turns them on?
No, no, please.
No, please, no!
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
We've come to a special part
of the evening tonight,
I think one you've all
been waiting for.
Will you, just clear the
dance floor here please?
Get everybody to back
off a little bit.
That's good.
Let's get our graduating
ladies out front here.
Give em a big hand!
Let's get em all
out front here.
Ok, quiet down, quiet down
out there, quiet down.
Where's Stevie?
She's upstairs polishing
her tennis shoes.
Ok, we're gonna the snowball off
with these six ladies up here.
You all can join
in after while.
Vicki?
Where's my gun?
Upstairs.
Hey, how'd your
little prank go?
Just fine.
This is really gross.
When's the last time
they cleaned this pool?
Looks ok to me.
Where is Stevie?
I can't believe a
house mother like
Mrs. Slater would let
all this happen.
Just the way
I like it.
Well, go ahead,
pig, jump in!
Wait a minute,
I gotta prepare.
You know, I'm really
glad this is working out.
I'm really having a
nice time. Are you?
I'm a sea pig!
My God!
I'm a sea pig.
She's alive.
We put her back in the pool,
and she was still alive!
You and Stevie are the ones
to blame for that.
You said she was dead, not me!
Who's to blame for shooting her!
How was I supposed to know
there's another bullet in the gun!
It doesn't matter now.
Where is Stevie?
I've looked all over for her.
She must have left before
she could turn off the...
It's a good thing she didn't.
We would have never known
Mrs. Slater is still alive.
How do we know she is alive?
What do you think she
floated out of that pool?
Or, maybe she got
sucked down the drain?
Do you believe this?
Look what we're talking about!
Jeanie, stop.
Morgan may be right.
Mrs. Slater could have
collapsed somewhere
just after getting
out of the pool.
We have got to find her,
before somebody else does.
I cannot believe you, Vicki.
You'd sacrifice anything
to save yourself.
Even Mrs. Slater's life?
And what about
the rest of you?
I am calling the police,
I cannot live with this anymore.
Listen to me!
If she were alive, wouldn't
the police be here by now?
She's right, she would
have called hours ago.
What if she can't?
What if she's lying on the
ground bleeding to death?
If she were alive, she
would have reached a telephone.
Face it, Katie.
Mrs. Slater is dead.
She won't call.
But what do we do?
Well, Mrs. Slater couldn't
have gotten far.
Let's check around the
outside of the house.
Morgan, go unpack Slater's clothes,
so it looks like she's left.
We can find her, but we're
gonna have to hurry.
-Don't do that, Diane!
-I'm sorry.
-Have you seen anything?
-No, have you?
No. Come on.
Water?
Give me something stronger.
She's all right.
How'd she ever get up
in the attic like that?
Why would she struggle all
that way, just to get up there?
God, who knows?
Where's her cane?
I don't know! Must be in the
attic, I didn't see it in the pool.
Don't have time to worry about
that now! We gotta get rid of her!
-Ok.
-What about the old cemetery?
Nobody would ever
find her there.
Get
away from her!
Morgan!
-God.
-Let her go!
We haven't got time to
waste pampering her!
She's a baby.
Her and Stevie, leaving
us to do this ourselves.
For Christ's sakes,
we're in this together.
After this is over...
Cowards.
You're all a bunch
of goddamn cowards.
Morgan?
Have you guys seen Morgan?
Morgan, it's me.
Are you in there?
Morgan?
We're not carrying
her all the way, are we?
Nope.
Hey, hey, where did you get those?
Those are mine!
-We're using your car, Liz.
-No, wait! I just got it!
Goddamn it, Liz, yours is the
only car that isn't blocked in.
Forget it,
we're not using it!
Diane, you take them.
Wait, it's too crowded in
the front of the house.
We'll meet you at
the old garage.
Hurry!
God, we gotta find
something to put her in.
What we are gonna use?
Vicki?
That's perfect.
Watch the feet, Liz,
be... shit. Come on.
Ouch.
Come on.
God!
What are you
doing up here?
I'm not really sure.
Well, I saw you
go up the steps,
and I was just
wondering what you...
Look at all this stuff.
This is a neat room.
You know what?
Why don't you go downstairs?
This used to be
one of my favorite things.
Peter, why don't you go downstairs
and get yourself another drink?
-My God.
-What is it?
-Peter, go, go downstairs.
-But...
Go on!
Is that you guys?
Jeanie?
Vicki?
Liz?
We just have to get to the
garage, and we're home free.
What is someone sees us?
Stop
worrying, just push!
Almost there.
You guys, my dress...
Hurry, get out of here.
Come here.
Come here!
657 to dispatch.
657, go ahead.
Yeah, I got a
fender bender here.
Send car 412 down here
on campus on my 1020.
Ten-four, acknowledged.
Yeah, and
also be advised
I got two female suspects here.
Ten-four.
Please keep us advised.
Hell of a time to be
taking out the trash.
We always take the trash
out on Friday night.
Yeah.
At 1:43
in the morning?
Sororities.
What you got in there?
Nothing, officer.
We had a large party tonight,
there's a lot of people
who had a lot of...
We had an awful lot of
garbage to get rid of.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
657, go ahead.
1019 to station.
I'll be right there.
Look, turn this thing around
and get it back up to house.
And don't let me catch you around
here anymore, you understand?
-We'll see, thank you, officer.
-Good night.
Jeanie!
Jeanie, what happened?
Did somebody do this to you?
Who?
Where did it happen?
-Gate.
-Gate?
Jeanie, I'm gonna
have to get help.
I'm gonna get somebody,
we'll take you to the hospital.
Cane.
Ok, Jeanie, it's gonna be all right,
ok? I promise. I'll be right back, ok?
Come on.
Bye, meet me down
at the bar, ok?
Jeanie!?
Katherine, what are you, what is
wrong? Why won't you just tell me?
Something's happened to them.
What are
you talking about?
Three of my
friends are missing.
I'm calling the police.
Are you sure about this?
Couldn't they have
just left the party?
Nobody saw them leave,
and Jeanie was in
no condition to go
anyplace by herself.
Should I get
your house mother?
They're gonna wanna
speak to her.
Sheriff's department.
This is Sgt. Palmer.
Hello?
What are you doing?
Katherine?
You're probably right, that they
just must have left the party.
It's late, I think you
better be leaving.
I'm sorry, Peter.
She isn't here!
What?
Diane?
Diane? The keys are
here. Where is she?
This is
really unbelievable.
Why am I always
saving everyone's ass?
Forget it, let's just
get this over with.
I'm sorry to be calling so
late, but I found this necklace.
Who is this?
My name's Katherine Rose,
you don't know me.
I found this medical alert tag, and I
called the number, they connected me.
What's
the name on the tag?
-Slater.
-Dorothy Slater?
Yes, she's our house
mother at the sorority.
That's where I'm calling from.
Yes I know the house.
is something wrong?
Well, during our party here,
one of the girls was...
attacked...
that's where I found the tag.
Where's
the girl now?
I don't know.
She's disappeared.
Two other girls have also.
Where's Mrs. Slater?
She's not here.
Now,
listen to me carefully.
I doubt anything's happened
to your friends.
But I think I'd
better come over.
Stay in the house
until I arrive.
I don't see any.
Wait!
There's one over there.
Ok.
We'll dig it a couple of
feet deeper and we're set.
-All right.
-Come on.
-Dr. Beck?
-Yes, Katherine?
-Yes, please come in.
-Thank you.
I found this in the room of one
of the girls who disappeared.
A few nights ago I heard
music coming from up here.
Mrs. Slater must have spent
a lot of time in this room.
What else
have you found?
We have to find Mrs. Slater.
Do you know where she is?
Why did she wear this?
24 years ago,
she came to me.
She heard about my work with other
women, unable to bear children.
As risky as it was, and knowing
the odds were against her,
she went through with
the experimental procedure.
All she ever wanted in life
was to have a child.
What happened?
It was a bitter disappointment
for her, as much as for me.
The delivery
was terribly traumatic.
Ever since then, she's been
in a world of her own.
Who's Eric?
Where did you hear that name?
It's on the card, right there.
Every June 19th she
celebrates his birthday,
as if she had a normal,
loving son.
So that's why she always closed
the house before June 19th.
Katherine, we've got
to find Mrs. Slater.
Where is she?
That tag, I found it in the same
spot where Jeanie was attacked.
Could Mrs. Slater have done...
You think Mrs. Slater has something
to do with your missing friend?
I don't know!
There's something you're
not telling me.
-What is it?
-My god.
All right, all right.
All right, Katherine.
All right, all right,
all right, all right.
No!
Three girls
at 413 Danfair Road.
That's on the Sorority Row.
Yes, Dr. Nelson Beck!
Wait a minute.
One second,
officer. What is it?
Cemetery.
Vicki and Liz must still be
there. It's less than a mile away.
Mrs. Slater could
have followed them.
What cemetery?
Parkview, on Perry Street.
Hello, officer?
We think she may have headed for the
Parkview Cemetery on Perry Street.
Two girls are there now.
Yes! I'll meet you there!
Is it deep enough yet?
Yeah, that
oughta do it.
Why don't you go pull
the van around?
Liz, what
are you doing?!
Liz?
Liz!
Shit! What are you doing?
The gun went off again.
She fell back in the water.
I wanted to call an ambulance,
but we were so scared.
We thought that she
was dead.
The body we found must
have been Stevie's.
He's alive.
Please, get back in the car.
Please.
Come.
What happened to the police?
They're not coming.
Yes they are, they
said they were!
What are you doing?
Just a mild sedative.
Please, get out of the car.
Come on.
Stay there.
Come on, come on, come on.
Get up, get up, get up.
Stay there.
It's all right.
Relax, Katherine.
Mrs. Slater was the last
one I used the drug on.
Like the others, Eric was born
with certain abnormalities.
I warned her, it's what we
expected would happen.
Eric spent every summer away
from the clinic in the attic.
I told Mrs. Slater that his
condition was worsening.
She wouldn't listen.
He must have seen everything
from the attic window.
Do you understand?
I must find him.
You're the last one of
your friends alive.
You're the bait.
No.
Don't move, or make a sound.
How are you, Katherine?
Peter, no!
Katherine, the only way
to get Eric is to trap him.
That boy downstairs
is only tranquilized.
I don't wanna hurt anybody.
I've got to find him.
No one must know about him.
I'd be ruined if anyone
knew what I did.
I beg you.
You've got to help me.
I must bring Eric back!
Katherine...
No, no!
Mom...
Ok.
Ok, ok.
Katie, it's all Vicki's fault.
Katie, why did you
call the police?
Katie, it's your turn.
-We're waiting for you.
-Katie, come on.
We're waiting. Come on.
Katie, come on.
We won't go away, Katie.