Stop Right There!
Stop Right There
And Surrender Your Weapon.
Now You'll See--
[Groans]
[People Chattering]
Ladies And Gentlemen,
That Concludes The Film Portion
Of Our Presentation.
I'm Sure You All
Have Questions.
So Let Me Introduce You
To The Head Of Development
For Secure-Tronics
Unlimited--
Dr. Stan Simon.
Thank You Very Much.
Before I Open The Floor,
I'd Like You All To Meet
Your Brand-New Security Team--
The Protector 101
Series Robots.
One Week From Tonight
At Closing,
The Protectors Will Begin
Their Patrol Of The Mall.
Paul, They Look Like
The Three Stooges.
Each Assigned To One Of
The Three Upper Shopping Levels.
I Don't Know, Mary,
The One In The Middle Has
An Unpleasantly Ethnic Quality.
Now, Are There
Any Questions?
Yes, Dr. Carrington.
So What Do Your Machines There
Do Besides Kill Criminals?
First Of All,
The Protectors Do Not Kill.
I Wonder If They
Kill Cockroaches.
They Could Probably
Be Programmed To.
And Merely Detain Intruders
Until The Computer,
Located On The Roof,
Can Patch Into
The Mall Phone System
And Send The Alarm
To The Police.
I Don't Know.
That Guy Looked
Awfully Dead To Me.
Just Neutralized.
Protectors Can Achieve
This Function
In A Number Of Ways.
At Close Range, Sleep Darts
Fired From Here And Here
Can Knock A Man Out
In Less Than 30 Seconds.
However, The Likelihood
Of An Intruder Gaining Entry
Is Greatly Minimized
By The Steel Security Doors
Which Are Time-Locked
From Midnight 'til Dawn.
Um, They Seem So Violent.
If They're Called Protectors,
What Do They Protect?
Plenty. For Starters,
As Seen In The Film,
The Protectors Do Their Work
In The Mall Proper,
Not In The Stores Themselves.
Maybe We Could Use One
At The Restaurant--
Get Rid Of People
We Don't Like.
For Instance, Lasers
Positioned Here
Can Cut Through
Any Sort Of Debris.
Well, That's All Very Well
And Good, But What About
Those Who Work Late?
How Can Your... Things There
Distinguish Between The Good
Guys And The Bad Guys?
That's Very Simple.
Watch.
This Is Simon.
Bring Number One On-Line.
[Whirrs]
Whoa!
Wow!
[Murmuring]
May I See Your
Identification Badge, Please?
It's Scanning.
They Remind Me Of Your Mother.
It's The Laser Eyes.
[Robot]
Thank You.
Have A Nice Day.
Same To You.
There. You See?
The System Is
Absolutely Foolproof.
Now, Everyone Connected
With The Mall Has Been
Issued An I.D. Badge
So That When The Mechanism
Goes On-Line,
The Protectors Will Make
Park Plaza The Safest Mall
In The State.
Trust Me.
Absolutely Nothing
Can Go Wrong.
Ow!
Are You All Right?
Coffee?
Come On, Sweetheart!
Give It To Me!
What Do You Got?
Andiamo!
Can I Get Two
Uncle Luigi Bellybusters,
A Double Anchovy Pizza
And An Order
Of Garlic Logs?
Gross. What Mojave
Brain Ordered That?
Guy Over There.
Oh, God. I Should've Known.
That Orca Beaches
Here Every Night.
Always Trying To Snag Some Skin.
Play It Safe, Alison.
Serve At Arm's Length,
If You Get My Drift.
Thanks For The Advice.
Yeah.
[Screams]
Shit!
Oh, Honey, You
Breakin' My Heart.
[Speaking Italian]
Look, Alison, In About
An Hour And A Half...
We Bail This Barbecue And
It's Good Times To The Max.
You've Got To Show.
Suzie, You've Got
A One-Track Mind.
I Already Told You,
I Don't Know Anybody.
Yeah, But You Will
After Tonight.
That's What I'm Afraid Of.
Would I Set You Up With
A Slime Dog Or Something?
No Way, "Babe."
[Together]
It Is Babe, Isn't It?
Come On, Come On!
Take It While It's Hot.
Girls, Come On!
Yeah, All Right,
All Right.
Waitress, More Butter.
[Loud Thunderclap]
[Alarm Blaring]
[Alarm Stops]
[Groans]
[Man Over P.A.]
Attention, Shoppers.
In The Next Half Hour,
Everything In
Our Drapery Department
Will Be Marked Down
30 Percent.
Your Attention, Please.
We Have A Lost Child
In Lingerie Answering
To The Name Of Steve.
If My Uncle Finds Out
I Let You Do This, I'm Dead.
Don't Tell Me, Freddie.
Are You Going Chicken-Shit
On Us Again?
We Already Agreed.
He Trusts Me To Take Care
Of The Store While He's Gone.
He Ain't Gonna Know Diddly
Unless You Tell Him.
You Ain't Gonna
Tell Him, Are Ya?
Don't Force Me
To Pull Rank.
Oh, I'm Shaking.
You Know, Brennan, You're
Becoming A Real Candidate
For Prickhood.
What?
Look, Guys,
This Party Is Gonna Happen,
But We Need A Little Teamwork.
Besides, If The Place
Looks Like Shit On Monday,
It's All Our Asses.
You Got The Beer?
Correct.
Come On. Dude!
The Fridge Is Packed.
Good. Rick And Linda
Are Bringing The Food.
Clean Sheets Are
Definitely Waiting.
And, Uh, Suzie--
[Chuckles]
[Chuckles] Suzie Has
A Surprise For You.
[Gibbering]
I Don't Know, Guys.
Come On, Ferdy.
Forget About Your Uncle Awhile.
This Is Gonna Work, Okay?
Ferdy, You Can't
Back Out On Us Now.
Okay, Okay, Let's Party.
All Right.
First I Gotta Find
Mrs. Flanagan's Fuchsia
You Find
Mrs. Flanagan's Fuchsia.
You, You Hold Down
The Fort.
I Will.
I'm Gonna Go Find Leslie.
[Chuckles]
I'm Sure You Will.
Quack, Quack.
Greg, I--
Ferdy,
Don't Worry.
I Can't Find The Fuchsia.
Ah, Fuck The Fuchsia.
It's Friday.
Tell The Old Bag To Wait.
[Loud Thunderclap]
Okay. Give It A Try.
[Engine Grinding]
Strike Three, Walden.
You're Out.
My Turn.
It's Okay.
I Got It, I Got It.
You Know The Rules, Buster.
Into The Cab.
Okay, Butch.
You Know I Can't Resist It
When You Get Tough.
Yeah, Yeah, Yeah.
Just Crank It When I Tell Ya.
Well? We're Waiting.
Just A Sec, Huh?
All Right. Hit It.
[Engine Starts]
Always The First Time.
I Don't Want To Hear It,
Not Another Word.
Me? No Way.
I Covered This Whole Deal
When I Said, "For Better
Or Worse," Remember?
Of Course I Remember.
Who Could Forget
That 40-Weight Stain
Right There On Your Chest?
Should've Been
"For Better Or Weird."
And Speaking About Weird,
What About This
Furniture Store--
Come On, Walden.
Indulge Me.
We Haven't Had Any Fun Since
We Sunk All Our Wedding Money
Into The Business.
Besides, Suzie's
Counting On Us.
Honey, I Don't Care About--
Okay. Okay, Okay.
I Guess I Won't
Be Needing This.
Or, Um,
Will I?
[Tires Squealing]
[Man Over P.A.]
Attention, Shoppers.
Park Plaza Will Be Closed
In 20 Minutes.
The Mall Will Be Closing
The Lower Parking Levels
Will Be Closed At 10:00.
Attention, Please.
Mr. Brad Trevoy To
The Information Kiosk.
[Gasps]
You Horny Bastard.
[Chuckling]
Can't You Wait?
No. No, I Can't.
[Chuckles]
[Giggles]
What Can't You
Wait For, Michael?
Mr. Todd.
Uh, Well, I--
Uh, I Was Just Telling
Leslie Here That, Uh,
Uh,
Well, That, Uh--
Daddy.
He Was Just Telling Me How
He Couldn't Wait To Take Me
To Suzie's House Tonight
For Her, Um,
Birthday Party.
I See.
Well, I'm Running Late.
You Lock Up?
Sure, I'll Take Care
Of Everything.
Yes.
I'm Sure You Will.
Okay, Daddy.
I Love You Too. Bye.
[Shower Running]
So, What He Say?
He Said, "Go Out
And Have A Good Time.
All Right!
That Is Bitchin'.
I Wish I Had It That Easy.
My Parents Still Think
I'm A Kid.
Why Do I Have The Feeling
I'm Gonna Regret This
In The Morning?
Look, Alison,
You've Had Yourself
A Very Rough First Week.
You Owe Yourself
A Little Blowout.
Come On.
It'll Be Fun.
Okay, Just So Long
As I Don't Have To
Look At Any More Pizza.
You Won't.
I Promise. Oh, Great!
This Is Gonna Be Wonderful.
You Won't Regret This.
I Bet.
[Man Over P.A.]
Attention, Shoppers.
Park Plaza Will Be Closing
In 10 Minutes.
I Am So Nervous.
Hairspray, My Lovely.
I Really Hate Blind Dates.
Oh, Yeah! Audacious!
Lipstick.
Suzie--
Oh, No.
This Is A Terrible Color.
Give Me Another Color.
What If He's Not My Type?
Oh, Yeah, That's It--
Luscious Lust.
Are You Listening?
What Are We Gonna Do
All Night?
Will You Stop Worrying?
Like I Said, He's Got--
[Together]
A Great Personality!
That's Right!
He Does.
You're Going To Love Him.
Trust Me On This.
Hey, Babe.
It Is "Babe," Isn't It?
[Laughing]
Let Me See. Okay.
What? What, What?
You Look Good. Yeah.
Are You Sure?
Really?
Yeah!
[Loud Thunderclap]
Marty, I'm Sorry I'm Late,
But It Was All-You-Can-Eat
Night Down At The Pit,
And I Couldn't Resist
The Opportunity To Pig Out.
Marty?
Yo, Marty!
Hi, You Guys.
The Least He Could Do
Was Clean Up.
Waste Not, Want Not.
You Know What I Mean?
No, I, Uh--
I Guess You Wouldn't.
[Sniffles]
[Whirring]
[Clanks]
[Phone Ringing]
Hello.
What Do You Mean,
"Who Is This"?
You Called Me.
No, Marty's Not Here Right--
Jerk.
[Woman]
♪ Street Walkin' ♪
♪ It's A Crazy World
Street Walkin' ♪
Happy Motoring.
You're So Sentimental.
♪ Street Walkin' ♪
♪ [Continues, Faint]
Shoot.
[Sighs]
♪ I'm Standing On The Corner ♪
♪ Night After Night
♪ Waiting For A Lonely Man
♪ [Continues, Indistinct]
[Exhaling]
[Spraying]
♪ He's Just Another Customer ♪
♪ Lookin' For A Thrill
Street Walkin' ♪
♪ It's A Crazy World ♪
♪ Street Walkin' ♪
♪ You Get It
Through The Night ♪
♪ Street Walkin' ♪
♪ There's Nothing
That I Can't Do ♪
♪ Street Walkin' ♪
♪ I'm Lonely Without You ♪
Come On, You Guys.
I Got A Lot Of Bookkeeping
To Catch Up On.
Tonight You Are Going To Shake
That Ultra-Wally Image Of Yours
Once And For All.
But I Like My Image.
I Don't Wanna Shake It.
You Guys Have Fun.
Look, This
Is Not A Democracy.
You Have No Choice.
But I Got A Lot Of
Bookkeeping To Catch Up On.
But Nothing!
Ferdy Meisel,
Meet Alison Parks.
Hi.
[Whispering]
Oh, Hello.
Protector 1 Going
On-Line, Level 1.
[Chattering, Shouting]
[Squealing]
Protector 2 Going
On-Line, Level 2.
Protector 3 Going
On-Line, Level 3.
Lady, You, Uh, Got
A License For That Outfit?
Why, Uh, No, Officer.
I Guess You're Just
Gonna Have To Take Me In.
[Laughing]
You Smell Like Pepperoni.
Well, If That's
The Way You Feel.
Wait A Minute.
What?
I Like Pepperoni.
[Chuckles]
Oh.
In That Case--
♪ [Humming]
Michael.
What Now?
You Know I Don't
Allow That.
You Allowed It
Last Week, Didn't You?
Huh?
What Are You Do--
Michael.
I Seem To Recall It
From Last Week.
[Giggling]
[Gasps]
Oh!
[Laughs] I Don't Know
Why I Watch These Things.
I Scare So Easily.
I'm Sorry.
I Should've Told You About That.
I've Seen This A Few Times.
Can I Get You
Some More Wine?
Ferdy, Are You Trying
To Get Me Drunk?
No, No. I Just Figured
Maybe You Might Be Thirsty.
Part Of The Reason Why Greg
Fixed Me Up Here Tonight
Was So I Wouldn't
Squeal To My Uncle.
I Never Thought That, Uh--
What?
[Sighs]
I Never Thought
It Would Be So, Uh,
You Know, Nice.
It's Been Nice
For Me Too, Ferdy.
[Leslie]
Oh, God! Oh, God!
You're The King!
[Laughs]
Chalk One Up For
The Furniture King.
They're Having A Nice Time.
Yeah.
It's Getting Kind Of Late.
I Was Going To Seal Up
In About An Hour.
What Do You Say
I Take You Home?
That's Real Sweet, Ferdy,
But If It's
All Right With You,
We Can Stay
A Little While Longer.
Nice Shot.
[Electrical Buzzing On Tv]
He Gave His Life.
I Know.
[Laughing]
[Laughter Continues]
Yo, Walter.
You Havin' A Good Time?
Ty, You Know Paisley.
He Loves A Challenge.
Go Ahead And Laugh,
But If I Ever Find
The Bastards That Did This,
They're Dead Meat.
Right, Walter. Right.
You Better Hustle.
You Don't Wanna Get Locked Up
In Here Again, Do You?
Rub It In All You Like.
I'll Be Out Of Here In
10 Minutes. You'll See.
[Laughing]
Creeps.
Bastards. Bastards.
Bastards.
You Clumsy Son Of A Bitch!
Look What You Did.
I Ought To Turn You Into
Scrap Metal For This.
May I See Your
Identification Badge, Please?
Identification Badge?
Do Not Make
Any Sudden Moves.
Sudden Move?
I'll Give You A Sudden Move
Upside The Head.
What The Hell Is That?
What Is This, You Worthless
Pile Of Junk, Huh?
Hey, Look, I'm
Like You, You Know?
I Work Here.
See? Huh? See That?
Ah, Shit. I Knew You Bastards
Were Gonna Be Trouble When They
First Brought You Here.
[Yelling]
Thank You.
Have A Nice Day.
[Michael]
Hey, Smoking's Bad
For Your Health.
I Have To Have A Cigarette,
And I Have To Have One Now.
Are You For Real?
Can't You Think Of
Anything You'd Rather Have
Besides A Smoke?
No.
Okay. Okay.
Uh, I Think Singleton
Left A Pack Of Camels
Under The Register.
Camels? No Way.
You Know I Only Smoke
Virgin Lights.
What Do You Expect Me To Do?
Go Out In The Mall
And Buy A Pack?
There's A Machine
Right Down By The Phones.
You Always Get Your Way,
Don't You?
When I'm Happy,
Everybody's Happy.
That's For Sure.
Hand Me My Badge, Will You?
What's The Magic Word?
Hand Me My Badge, Please.
Thank You.
Oh, Mike?
What, What, What, What?
Hurry Back.
Count On It.
Mmm!
[Zipping]
[Coins Jingling]
A Buck And A Quarter?
[Door Closes]
Leslie.
[Phone Ringing]
Yeah?
No, Jamal, There Haven't Been
Any Messages For You.
[Exhaling]
May I See Your
Identification Badge, Please?
Geez, You Little Bastards
Are Quiet.
Here.
Clatto Verata Nicto, Ok?
Hey.
[Door Rattling]
No.
[Muttering]
Mike?
Brennan, You Ass.
I'm Not In The Mood For Games.
[Angry Muttering On Tv]
What Is It With
Those Two Anyway?
Personally, I Can't
Figure It Out. All They
Do Is Have Sex And Fight.
Like Most Couples.
Yeah.
Look, We've Got About 15 Minutes
Before The Whole Place Locks Up.
Ferdy.
Yeah?
Thanks.
Mike?
Damn You!
Brennan, 'You Don't
Come Out Now, Don't Bother.
All Right, Wake Up.
Wake Up!
I Said Wake Up!
That's It! I Don't
Need This Crap!
[Screaming]
[Screaming, Shouting]
Oh, My--
[Screaming]
Oh, My God!
Oh!
[Screaming]
[Whirring]
Thank You. Have A Nice Day.
Protector 1, Arming.
Engage Intruder.
Oh, My God,
There's Another One!
Protector 2, Arming.
Assist Protector 1.
The Storeroom,
Quick, Let's Go.
Let's Go!
[Screaming]
Go, Go, Go, Go.
[All Screaming]
Here's A Box.
Good. All Right.
[Greg]
This Isn't Gonna
Hold Them Very Long.
You Got Any Better Ideas?
What About The Fire Exit?
[Greg] All That's Gonna Do
Is Put Us Back In The Middle
Of Those Machines.
Beats Being Trapped In Here.
Who Knows What They're
Planning Right Now?
Linda's Right. We've
Gotta Get Out Somewhere We
Can Run And Get Some Weapons.
[Mechanical Doors
Slamming Shut]
What Was That?
That's The Sound Of Us Being
Locked In Here All Night.
The Security Doors
Don't Open 'Til 6:00.
Oh, No! We're Never
Gonna Get Out Of Here!
Yes, We Are.
The Phone's Dead.
The Computer Must
Have Taken Control.
[Whimpering]
Hey, What About That?
The Air Duct.
We Take It Down
To The Parking Levels,
We're Outta Here.
Let's Go For It!
[Whimpering]
Go, Baby!
[Whirring Noises]
[Screaming]
What Was That?
Go, Suzie. Go.
I'm Right Behind You.
As Usual.
Prepare For Detonation.
Proceeding To Alternate Access.
Come On, Alison, You're Next.
Come On, Keep Going.
Keep Going!
[Yelling And Screaming]
I Thought This Was
An Air Conditioning Duct.
Except The Heat's
Been Turned On.
In The Middle Of Summer?
They Know We're In Here.
They're Trying To French-Fry Us.
Come On, Suze.
You Know Who Gives You Twice
As Much Heat At The Restaurant.
[Grunting]
[Panting]
Damn!
Wrap Whatever You Can
Around Your Hands.
[Whimpering]
I Can't Stand This Anymore.
I Gotta Get Outta Here.
I Gotta Get Outta Here!
[Sobbing]
Come On, Suze.
Hang In There.
[Sobbing Continues]
What Now?
Find Some Way Outta Here.
We're Gonna Have To Defend
Ourselves. This Place Got
A Sporting Goods Store?
[Together]
Peckinpah's.
Let's Go.
How Are We Gonna Get In?
Don't Worry.
I Got The Keys.
Jesus.
Ferdy, Propane Tanks.
Grab The Biggest.
All Right.
Let's See.
What About Shells?
Twelve Gauge.
Here.
Great. Thanks.
And Some 223's.
Let's Go Send Those Fuckers
A Rambo-Gram.
You Sure You Know
How To Shoot That?
Yeah. I Saw
Dirty Harry 24 Times.
All Set?
Yeah.
Good.
One Of Them Ought
To Have Heard That.
Dead Man Could've Heard That.
Hey, Fellas,
We Got Company.
That Didn't Take Very Long.
Steady. Go For It.
Ferdy, Now!
[Whimpering]
I Gotta Find Greg.
He Needs Me.
Let Me Outta Here!
Suzie, Please.
The Guys Told Us To Go Down
To The Parking Levels.
[Whirring]
Come On, Kiddo.
Greg Wouldn't Want You
To Give Up Now.
Oh, Go To Hell, Linda!
You Do What You Want,
But I'm Getting Out Of Here.
Suzie, Stop It! Please.
Greg Needs Me.
I Know He Does.
[Burbling]
Jesus.
What's That?
Robot Blood.
Not Too Shabby, Huh?
We're Not Finished Yet.
We Still Got
Two More Of These Suckers
Around Here Someplace.
We Gotta Get More Tanks.
What Are You Thinking?
I Got An Idea.
Really, This Is
Not A Good Idea.
Bullshit!
Greg Could Be Hurt.
They All Could.
I'm Gonna Find Them.
I've Got To.
What Do You Think?
Well,
If We Gotta Go,
Let's Not Go Empty-Handed.
[Loud Whirring]
Shit. I Didn't Think
They'd Work.
Never Hurts To Try.
I Guess Not.
Give Me A Hand.
Let's Pry This Baby Open.
Come On.
You Know, I Gotta Worry.
Report From The Front:
Ferdy's Gotta Worry.
Yeah. What If These Things
Can Read Our Minds?
They're Gonna Be Awful Mad
When They Get To Me.
All Right.
Come On. Let's Go.
Give Me The Gun.
Right.
Take The Cap Off
And Stuff The Cloth In.
That's It?
That's It.
Light It And Throw It.
You Sound Like
You've Done This Before.
Regular Or Unleaded,
It Gets The Job Done.
[Whirring]
Protector 1 Back On-Line.
Hey, Guys, How's It Goin'?
Almost Done, Ferdy.
You Think Mike
Got Out All Right?
For His Sake, I Hope So.
Right Now, I'm More
Concerned About The Girls.
You And Me Both.
Hey, I Almost Forgot.
How Much Do I Owe You
For The Beer?
Forget It, Man.
If We Get Out Of Here,
You Owe Me A Six-Pack.
Just Make Sure That Those
Cords Are Good And Tight.
Are You Sure
This Is Gonna Work?
With Those Things,
I'm Not Sure Of Anything.
Ferdy, How's
The Panel Coming?
The Doors Work.
I Bypassed The Circuit.
But Forget About Going Up
Or Down. It's Controlled
By The Computer.
Do You Hear
Anything Unusual?
Only My Heart Beat.
[Screaming Continues]
[Screaming]
No!
It's Not Stopping!
Come On!
[Screaming]
Help Me.
Help Me Up!
Suzie!
[Screaming]
Help Me!
We've Gotta Help Her!
Thank You,
And Have A Nice Day.
[Suzie Screaming]
[Screaming]
Oh, God.
Come On!
You Fucking Bastard.
Get 'Em To Safety!
It's No Use!
Go! Take It!
Now!
Rick!
Nice Shot.
Dad's A Marine.
According
To My Calculations--
Provided We Survive
The Night, Of Course--
We're Gonna Be
In Hock To This Place
For The Next 85 Years.
How Many Tune-Ups
Is That?
Just A Sec.
2,900,431.
Maybe We Should Raise
Our Rates.
Hey, Dead-Eye.
Yo.
Nice Shootin'.
Thanks.
Tell Me One Thing,
Though, Huh?
Why Did You Leave
The Air Shaft?
I Mean, You Were
Safe There.
You Were Safe.
Suzie Thought
You Were In Trouble.
She Just Wanted To Help.
I'm Telling You
You Should've Kept Her There.
She Told You What Happened.
Why Don't You Just
Leave Her Alone?
Shut Up.
You Just Shut The Fuck Up!
Hey.
Do You Guys Mind
Keeping It Down?
There's Another One
Of Those Things Out There,
And You're Gonna
Bring It Right To Us.
There's Another One?
Why Haven't We Seen It?
Why?
I'll Tell You Why.
'Cause The Fucker's
Out There Waiting For Us.
He's Waiting To Pick
Us Off One By One!
But I Got News For You.
He Ain't Getting Me.
Greg, You're
Not Thinking, Man.
We Got Destroyed
By Staying Together.
And A Lot Of Good
That Did Suzie, Right?
Wait. Wait.
I Got An Idea.
The Master Computer Is
Somewhere On The Third Level.
We Shut It Down,
It Shuts The Robots Down.
Well?
[Panting]
It's Worth A Try.
Computer, Huh?
Let's Go Trash The Fucker.
Come On, Guys!
Let's Take It!
Wait! Slow Down!
Greg, Will You Wait!
Man, He's Losin' It!
We're Lucky He Doesn't
Get Us All Killed.
Greg, Stop!
Greg, Wait!
Greg, Please!
Stop!
Come On, Guys!
The Coast Is Clear!
Greg, No! Greg!
[Yelling]
Greg!
[Screaming]
[Shrieks]
[Body Thuds]
Thank You.
Have A Nice Day.
The First One.
He Didn't Kill It. Go!
Protector 3 To Level 2.
Engage Intruders.
Protector 1 To Level 2.
It's Stuck.
Let's Get It Unstuck,
And Fast.
Come On!
There's No Time.
We're Not Gonna Make It.
[Grunting]
Come On!
Go.
[Groans]
Alison! Come On.
Alison, Are You
All Right?
I Think So.
Where To?
Escalator, Third Level.
What About The Doors?
We Can't Lock Them.
They'll Get Through.
Maybe So.
Maybe Not.
Let's Go!
Instructions:
Attempt Entry, Level 3.
Affirmative.
[Beeping]
Hold It.
This Way.
Up Here.
Protector 3, Level 3.
Search Proceeding.
Hold It, Ferdy.
They Could Be Out There.
At Least We're Safe Here
For The Moment.
Yeah, For The Moment.
Those Things Can Go
Anywhere They Want.
Maybe We'll All Stand
A Better Chance If We Split Up.
Are You Kidding?
The Moment Any One Of Us
Go Out There, We're Dead Meat,
Yesterday's News.
Damn It, Ferdy,
Will You Stop It!
Will You Just Stop It!
Linda.
Linda, I'M Sorry.
I Didn't Mean To Upset You.
I--
It's All Right.
It's Not You, Ferdy.
[Sighs]
I Guess I'M Just Not Used
To Being Chased Around A Mall
In The Middle Of The Night
By Killer Robots.
[Gasps]
It's In!
Yeah, And It Won't Be Long
Before It Comes Our Way.
We've Gotta Get Outta Here.
Not So Fast. One Of Them
Could've Doubled Back. We Could
Get Picked Off Out There.
Look, If Those Things
Want Some Target Practice,
Why Don't We Give 'Em
Some Targets?
[Metal Door Rattling]
Get Out Of Here!
Ferdy, Now!
Rick, Get Out!
[Screams]
Linda!
You Son Of A Bitch!
Rick, No!
[Yells]
[Groaning]
Let's Go Find
That Computer.
Where The Hell Is It?
Probably Up One
Of These Service Corridors.
There's A Million Doors.
We'll Never Find It.
Okay, You Try Over There,
And I'll Try Over Here.
I Don't Want To Split Up.
What Can Happen?
You Want A List?
We're Wasting Time.
Look, If You See Anything
Or Hear Anything--
You'll Hear Me.
Okay.
[Gasps]
[Loud Clanking]
[Screaming]
[Sighing]
[Banging]
[Loud Mechanical Whirring]
[Screaming]
Ferdy! Ferdy!
Ferdy!
[Screaming]
Help!
Alison, Move!
Get Out!
Laser Malfunction.
Engage Intruder.
Engage Intruder!
Laser Malfunction!
Please Wait, Intruder.
Stop Right There.
Ferdy!
Alison, Get The Hell
Out Of Here!
[Gasps]
Oh.
Thank You.
Have A Nice Day.
[Dogs Barking]
[Barking Continues]
[Gasps]
[Whimpering]
[Dogs Barking]
[Animal Howling]
[Screams]
[Dogs Barking,
Birds Chirping]
[Gasps]
[Screaming]
Come On, You Little Bastard!
Hey!
Have A Nice Day!
Nice Shot.
Thank You.
Have A Nice Day.