Okay, game point. 15-14.
This team serves.
Let's go. Service!
Come on! Come on!
Keep it up! Let's go!
Teamwork! Keep playing!
- Hit it to Carrie! She'll blow it!
- Don't blow it, Carrie! Hit it!
- Carrie...!
- She blew it again!
- We almost had the game!
- We can't win with her on the team.
Help me! Help me!
Help me!
Aah!
Help me! Help me!
Have a Tampax!
Help me!
Help me! Help me!
Gross! Gross!
Carrie! Here! Plug it up! Plug it up!
Plug it up! Plug it up!
What's happening?
- Sue! What are you doing?!
- Carrie... she just got her period!
- Who's got her period?
- Carrie.
What are you doing?!
Plug it up! Plug it up!
Carrie! Come on, Carrie!
Carrie, quit it! Come on!
Stop it! Now relax! Calm down.
Listen to me.
It's okay. It's okay. Just stand up
and take care of yourself. Come on.
Grow up. Stand up and take care
of yourself. Come on, do it. Do it.
- Do it!
- Aah!
Did you see that?
No...!
Get out of here. Go on. Right now. Move!
Carrie...
Carrie, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I didn't know, okay? I'm sorry.
Baby, come on, now. Don't you know?
I'm gonna talk to you about it.
Now just calm down. Just relax.
See? They're all gone. They're all gone.
It's gonna be okay.
- Isn't she a bit old for her, uh...
- Her first period.
Um... yes.
Morty, until a half-hour ago, I don't even
think she knew there was such a thing.
It's really... hard to believe
a girl in high school
wouldn't know something.
Uh, facts...
Well, she didn't.
But I don't know why that should
surprise us, knowing that mother of hers.
- We can't interfere with people's beliefs.
- I know, I know.
- As for the girls...
- Carrie's always been their scapegoat.
- You've got to do something.
- I will.
But see, the thing is, Morty, that, um...
I knew how they felt.
The whole thing just made me
wanna take her and shake her, too.
- It was just her period, for God sake!
- Well, we'll send her home.
Miss Finch,
will you send in Cassie Wright?
It's Carrie White.
Come in, Cassie.
Carrie.
Miss Finch, would you
bring in a dismissal slip?
I thought you might take
the rest of the day
and go home,
take care of yourself, Cassie.
We're all very sorry about this incident.
It's Carrie.
Thank you.
- Would you like to go to the infirmary?
- I think Carrie can go home.
Would you like a ride?
We could call you a cab.
I'm sure she can walk home.
And, Carrie, you're dismissed from gym
for a week. Just take study hall instead.
We're all sorry about this, Cassie.
It's Carrie!
Creepy Carrie! Creepy Carrie! Ha-ha!
Ohh!
Ohh! Ohh...
Were you in Chicago two years ago?
Chicago?
Yes, Bill. Chicago.
Why, yes, I was living in Chicago.
- You knew that. I told you that, didn't l?
- No, you didn't. I found out.
You're looking at me so, uh, strangely...
Oh, Mrs White.
- How have you been, Mrs Snell?
- Fine.
- And the doctor?
- And your daughter?
- Sue is fine.
- Won't you come in, Mrs White?
- Oh, how kind of you.
- Carrie is in some of Sue's classes.
- Yes.
- Perhaps sometime she might like to visit.
- I'm here on the Lord's work, Mrs Snell.
Spreadin' the gospel of God's salvation
through Christ's blood.
Yes, of course.
I have something here I know is gonna
interest the doctor and you.
The teenager's path to salvation
through the cross of Jesus.
I don't think Sue would be very interested.
The children are wandering through the
wilderness of sin these days, Mrs Snell.
My Sue is a good girl.
These are godless times, Mrs Snell.
I'll drink to that!
We'll... all read these.
Excuse me. Please sit down, Mrs White.
Hello?
Betty, can I call you back?
Margaret White is here.
Are you accusing me...
White.
Just let me get rid of her
and I'll call you back.
And now... I'm going to kill you!
I have something here, Mrs Snell,
that I think you might profit from.
- Look, Mrs White, I'd like to contribute 5...
- Exodus.
$10.
I see.
I pray you find Jesus.
- Wasn't that Carrie White's mother?
- Hey, I didn't hear you come in.
What did she want?
Yes?
Thank you.
I know you're listening.
Come on downstairs.
Mama?
Who was that? Who called?
You're a woman now.
Why didn't you tell me, Mama?
Aah!
And God made Eve
from the rib of Adam
and Eve was weak and
loosed the raven on the world.
And the raven was called sin. Say it.
Why didn't you tell me, Mama?
- Say it.
- No.
The raven was called sin.
No, Mama... And the raven was called sin!
And the first sin was intercourse.
First sin was intercourse.
I didn't sin, Mama.
- Say it!
- I didn't sin, Mama!
The first sin was intercourse.
First sin was intercourse.
And the first sin was intercourse!
I was so scared, I thought I was dyin'.
The girls, they all laughed at me, Mama.
- And Eve was weak. Say it.
- No, Mama!
- Eve was weak.
- No!
- Eve was weak. Say it, woman.
- No, Mama!
Say it!
Eve was weak!
And the Lord visited Eve with a curse.
And the curse was the curse of blood!
You should have told me, Mama!
You should have told me!
O Lord!
Help the sinning woman
see the sin of her days and ways.
Show her that if she had remained sinless
the curse of blood would not be on her.
She may be tempted by the Antichrist.
She may have had lustful thoughts...
No, Mama!
Don't lie, Carrietta!
Don't you know I can see inside you?
I can see the sin as surely as God can!
- Let me go, Mama.
- We'll pray!
- We'll pray, woman!
- No!
Pray to Jesus for all the lustful,
sinning souls.
No!
God visited Eve with the curse.
And the curse was the curse of blood.
No, Mama!
And he visited Eve with the second curse.
And this was the curse of childbearing.
And Eve brought forth Cain
in sweat and blood.
Genesis 3:16!
Mama! Let me out!
Mama, please! Let me out!
Mama, please!
Let me out, Mama! God...!
Our Father, who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom...
Thank you, Mama.
You can go to bed now.
There is power, power,
wonder-working power in the blood
of the lamb...
Carrie?
Open the door.
It's open, Mama.
What was that noise?
What noise?
Go to bed.
Yes, ma'am. Saying my prayers...
"What are you going to leave
for us, you people in your big cars,
spewing pollution into the air?"
"You people with heavy feet,
trampling down the wilderness."
"You people who peer into
the back seats of our cars,
hours after you come out
of the back doors of your motels."
"Soon all we will have is each other."
"And that could be enough."
"If you will let us have room enough
and air enough
and peace enough
to love each other
as you never could."
Hm.
I... I really must say... I must confess
this poem displays
the most extraordinary talent.
Talent extraordinary for you,
Tommy Ross.
You know, Tommy,
this is slightly different from running
touchdowns and hitting home runs.
Class,
any criticisms?
Anyone?
It's beautiful.
Carrie White!
Beautiful.
Beautiful!
"Oh, beautiful for spacious skies,
for amber waves of grain" !
Is that the beautiful you mean?
Is it, Carrie, hmm?
Well, Carrie, this is hardly a criticism.
You suck.
Tommy, did you say something, Tommy?
- Who, me?
- Yes, you.
I said "Aw, shucks."
Roll call: Blake.
Present.
- Borne.
- Here.
- Gogin.
- Present.
- Grace.
- Here.
- Hargenson.
- Litton.
- Yeah.
- MacDermit.
- Present.
- O'Shea.
- Pollock.
- Here.
- Shires.
- Present.
- Snell.
- Here.
- Watson.
- Present.
- And the Wilsons.
- We're here.
Okay, line up.
Line up!
Move it!
On your feet right now! Two lines!
Alice and Mary, eyes front.
Katie...
You, too, Chris.
And spit out that gum.
- Where'll I put it, Miss Collins?
- You can choke on it for all I care.
Just get it out of your mouth.
Wipe that smirk off your face, Norma.
Okay. Now I want you all to know that
you did a really shitty thing yesterday,
a really shitty thing.
Did any of you ever stop to think
that Carrie White has feelings?
Do any of you ever stop to think?
No, I guess you're too busy
thinking about your dates
and the prom.
I guess you can take your pick, Chris.
Who's the lucky guy?
Billy Nolan.
- Who?
- Billy Nolan.
- I'm sorry, could you speak up?
Well, isn't he the lucky one!
What about you, Sue?
Who's taking you?
Tommy Ross.
Right.
Now, my idea for this little trick you pulled
was three days' suspension
and refusal of your prom tickets.
Oh!
What...?
God!
That'd get you where you live, wouldn't it?
And you deserve it.
I don't think any of you have any idea
of just how nasty what you did really was.
But the office has decided
you're to have one week's detention.
Still, there's one little catch.
It's to be my detention.
That's 50 minutes
every day
starting today
on the athletic field.
Get the picture?
I'm not coming.
That's up to you, Chris.
That's up to all of you.
Punishment for skipping detention
is three days' suspension
and refusal of your prom tickets.
Any other thoughts?
Good. Now change up.
Where are you going?
- Where you going?
- Gotta go.
- I'm not coming.
- You're really not gonna come?
- You're gonna miss the prom.
Fuck!
And... 1 , 2, 3, 4.
2, 2, 3, 4.
3, 2, 3, 4.
4, 2, 3, 4.
5, 2...
Energy, Norma! Come on!
8, 2, 3, 4.
1 , 2, 3, 4.
2, 2, 3, 4.
3, 2, 3, 4.
Stretch, 2, 3, 4.
Stretch, Norma, stretch!
1 , 2,
bend, up.
Bend, up.
1 , 2.
Faster.
And 1 , 2.
1 , 2.
1 , 2, 1 ,
and 2
and 3
Uhh!
..and 4
and 5
and 6
and 7
and 8
and 9
and 10
and 11
and 12
and 13
and 14
and 15.
1, 2, 1 , 2, 1 , 2, 1 , 2,
1, 2, 1 , 2,
1, 2, 1 , 2.
Get your knees up!
1, 2, 1 , 2,
1, 2, 1 , 2.
Come on, you hotshots!
She can't get away with this.
I'm gonna get her.
Let it go, Chris.
Like hell I will.
1 , 2, 1 , 2, 1 , 2.
The period's not up, Hargenson.
- It is for me.
- Keep running!
There are 10 minutes left.
Stick 'em up your...
You can't hit us!
You'll get canned for this,
you bitch!
One more word and I'll knock you down!
She can't get away with this
if we all stick together, Norma!
Helen?
Sue?!
Shut up, Chris.
Just shut up.
This isn't over.
This isn't over by a long shot!
You're out of the prom, Hargenson.
Okay, the show's over.
In place, run!
1 , 2, 1 , 2, 1 , 2.
Hang 'em high! Hang 'em low!
Come on, Bates, let's go!
- Give me a B!
- B!
- Give me an A!
- A!
- Give me a T!
- T!
- Give me an E!
- E!
- Give me an S!
- S!
Bates! Bates! Yeah!
- Guess who's entering the nationals?
- Are you kidding?
Hey, terrific!
What's up?
Can I talk to you?
- Right now?
- It's real important.
All right.
Tommy, if I asked you to do something
very special for me,
would you do it?
Yeah.
I want you to take Carrie White
to the prom.
How's it looking there?
Ha ha ha!
Freddy!
Wanna go over to Minsky's
for some hard stuff?
No.
- Huh?
- Some other time, huh?
- You pussy!
- Gimme one of them beers!
- Suck on this, huh?
- All right!
Yee-hoo!
- Hey, man!
- Oh, man, those stripes!
Ooh!
Aah!
Yes!
Oh, shit.
Watch it, you stupid shit!
Don't call me that, huh?
Well, look what you did!
Stupid shit.
- I told you not to call me that.
- Look out!
Dumb punk!
- What, are you scared?
- What, do you want to get us killed?
Dumb shit.
You fuck!
Okay, I'll do it.
Take the streets!
Hi, friend! What's up?
Don't be in such a hurry.
Oh.
Come on...
"Don't be in such a hurry."
- I'm hurrying away from you.
- No, you're not.
- Pain right in the ass.
- You don't mean that.
I don't mean that.
You're crazier than a son of a bitch.
Give me everything
Oh,
sweet sigh
Come here.
Oh, shit.
Ooh!
Mmm...
Mm!
Jesus Christ, what's wrong with you!
- Can't you wait a minute?
- Well, what for? We do this all the time.
You're so ignorant.
Yeah, but... that's what
you like about me, right?
I know that.
Shit.
No?
I know what you like about me.
This.
Touch it.
No!
Dumb shit!
I told you never to call me that!
You are totally fucked up! You really are.
I'm convinced.
Billy...
Come here.
Billy... Come on.
Come on.
I want you to do something...
Something important.
Mm-hm?
Billy...
Oh, Billy...
Oh, Billy... Billy... Oh, Billy...
Oh, Billy, I hate Carrie White.
Who?
Hi, Carrie.
Hi.
- How are you?
- Okay.
Good. Uh...
What are you doing?
Reading.
Yeah? What are you reading?
It's about, uh
sewing.
Sewing. That's good.
Um...
If you don't have a date for the prom
next Friday,
would you like to go with me?
To the prom? It's next Friday. I know
this is late notice, but, uh... Carrie?
Carrie, let...
You guys go on. Practise those drills
from yesterday. I'll be right there.
Carrie?
Carrie.
Carrie, what's the matter?
- What happened?
- Nothin'.
Was it one of the girls?
Did one of the girls do something to you?
No.
Well, what is it, then?
You can trust me. You know that?
Would you tell me?
I got invited to the prom.
That's great! That's fantastic!
So what are you moping around for?
Tommy Ross asked me.
That's even better.
- He's really cute, huh?
- I know who he goes around with.
They're just trying
to trick me again, I know.
Maybe not.
I mean... maybe he really meant it.
Let's think about this, now.
It might be terrific.
You might have a really good time.
Carrie?
Carrie, I wanna talk about this attitude
you have about yourself.
You're always walking around
with your hair down, all moping around.
Carrie?
Come here, you big silly.
I want you to look at yourself.
Would you look at that?
Come on.
Now that's a pretty girl.
Look at your eyes!
Little mascara to bring it out? Little?
Your lips. Try some lipstick.
You have nice, pretty lips.
And your cheekbones.
Look at your hair. It's beautiful hair. You
could just put it up a little, add a little curl.
What do you think?
Yeah!
Well?
Well, what do you wanna know?
Why Tommy asked her to the prom.
Well?
I asked him to.
Why?
What for?
What could you possibly
have had in mind?
I thought it would be a good thing for
Carrie, to join in and be with people...
- Make her a part of things?
- Right.
Come on, Sue.
We're not that stupid.
- Neither is Carrie.
- That means... I don't know.
You mean you're not gonna go.
Stay home and miss your own prom?
Come in.
- What is it?
- The attendance sheets, Miss Collins.
You know you can't go without a date.
Is there anything else, Norma?
- No, Miss Collins.
- Thank you, Norma.
Which brings us to you.
- I have to get to practice.
- Well, that's too bad.
- If you don't mind, it's between Sue and l.
- But I do mind... unless, of course,
you'd like to continue this little
discussion in Mr Morton's office.
What is the big deal?!
Because it is a very big deal
for Carrie White, and you know it.
She already said no, anyway.
- Yeah, well, you can change that.
- Don't count your chickens.
- Just don't try...
- Fine. I won't try.
Wait a second! It's not fine!
You can't order someone
not to take someone to the prom!
I can make sure you don't hurt
Carrie White any more.
We're not trying to hurt her, Miss Collins.
We're trying to help her!
How?!
Hey, Tommy, um... Don't you think
you'll look a little ridiculous
when you walk in the prom
with Carrie White?
We don't care how we look.
Do we?
What?
I...
- Hi, Carrie.
- Hi.
So this is where you live, huh?
- What are you doing here?
- You gonna ask me in?
Why not?
Mama's resting.
- What do you want?
- God, right to the point. Um...
- About the prom...
- I already told you.
- But you can change your mind.
- Why are you doing this?
- Cos I want to.
- No, you're not.
I don't do anything I don't want.
- I can't.
- Yes, you can!
Carrie!
- You'd better go.
- Not till you say yes.
- No. I can't.
- Yes, you can.
I said I can't.
Carrie!
Yes, you can.
- Will you please go?
- Not till you say yes.
Why is this so important to you?
I don't know.
Maybe because, um... you liked my poem.
Carrie!
- Okay, okay, I'll go.
- Good. I'll pick you up at 8 o'clock.
Okay.
What's the matter, Willie?
We gonna wake up the little piggies?
Oink, oink!
You know, this is a hell of a risk for a joke.
- You want out?
- No, no. It's a good joke. It's a good joke.
Look at this!
- What?
- All these pigs!
What are you talking about?
These painted pigs!
Lauren Hanky's nitwit cousin
painted them.
Shh!
I went out with the girl that posed for 'em.
She was a real pig!
- Will you shut up?!
- Will you let me up there?
You're gonna kill that pig, right?
Piggy!
Here, piggy!
I'm gonna bash your little heads in,
and you don't have to worry
about the bomb no more.
Come here, little piggy!
Come here, you little sucker!
- Will you shut up and do it!
- We gotta give it a chance to burn!
- Oh, yeah?
- Come here, piggy!
You can't do it standin' out here.
Get 'er done, man, get 'er done.
- I can't. I can't. You.
- Oh, I knew this would happen!
- Just... hold it there, you pig. You fuck-up!
- Do it, Billy!
- And you shut up!
- Just do it!
All right, move it out, move it out!
That's it! Come on! Move it out!
Yeah, that's my baby! Yeah!
Do it!
Carrie, you haven't touched
your apple cake.
Gives me pimples, Mama.
Pimples are the Lord's way
of chastising you.
- Mama?
- Yeah?
Mama, please see that I've gotta
try and get along with people.
What are you going on about, Carrie?
I've been invited to the prom.
The prom?
Yeah, the senior prom. Everybody's goin'.
It's that teacher that called... wasn't it?
Please say I'm not like you, Mama.
I'm funny. All the kids think I'm funny.
I wanna be normal.
I wanna try and be a whole person
before it's too late for...
His name is Tommy Ross.
- He's a very nice boy.
- No.
- He promised to stop in and meet you.
- I said no.
- Mama, I've accepted. I've accepted.
- I said no. No, no, no!
I've accepted!
- Come to your closet.
- No.
- After all you've been taught...
- Everyone isn't bad!
Everything isn't a sin!
Come to your closet and pray.
Ask to be forgiven.
He's a nice boy, Mama. You'll like him.
You'll really like him, Mama.
"Boy."
The boys! The boys! Yes, the boys...
After the blood come the boys....
- Mama...
- Like sniffing dogs,
grinning and slobbering and trying
to find out where that smell comes from.
I know where they take them
cos I've seen it all!
- Well, you're not going.
- Already said I would.
Tell that boy you're not going,
or we're gonna move from here!
No.
We'll move and never see that boy again!
- Mama, please say that Tommy and me...
- I'm gonna close the window.
Mama, please sit and talk to me!
I'm goin', Mama.
And things are gonna change
around here.
Witch.
Got Satan's power.
It's nothin' to do with Satan, Mama.
It's me. Me.
If I concentrate hard enough,
I can move things.
- Satan is clever.
- No, Mama.
I'm not the only one.
Other people can do it. I read about it.
You poor child. He doesn't let you know
he's working through you.
Mama... I know.
He entered your father
and carried him off!
- He ran away, Mama.
- The devil tempted him!
He ran away with a woman, Mama.
Everybody knows that.
You must renounce this power.
You must give it up. Never use it.
I'm goin', Mama.
You can't stop me.
And I don't wanna talk about it any more.
- Keep that damn light straight.
- Hurry up!
Watch it, you stupid shit!
You're getting blood all over the place!
Who you calling a stupid shit?
I mean, you can't even keep
that fuckin' light straight.
Just hurry up.
Yes, ma'am! We's doin' the bes' we can!
We really are, boss!
Hurry up. I wanna go home.
Just... ..keep your tits, huh?
And I'll let you pull the rope
when the time comes.
I plan to.
I know.
Ernest, tonight's prom night.
Everything all right?
- I didn't know you were interested.
- I'm a student here, amn't I?
- I don't know. Are you?
- Sure I am.
I wanna be on the committee.
You're a little late.
I could've used you a week ago.
I'm not late. I'm right on time.
I wanna collect the ballots
for the king and queen and the voting.
- Think we could arrange that?
- Okay. Can you be here at 6.30?
No. No, I can't be here at 6.30.
I'll be here at 8. How's 8?
- Yeah, that'll do.
- See you then.
- Take it easy.
- I'll take it any way I can get it, pal.
Hey, Helen.
Helen!
- What?
- Did you hear about Tommy Ross?
- He's taking Carrie White to the prom.
- No!
- Yeah!
- He can't do that! Where's Sue?
- Yes, he can. He asked her.
- What's she gonna wear?
- Who, Carrie?
A sackcloth?!
- Sweetie, keep those stars coming faster.
- They're coming.
What's this I hear about Tommy
taking Carrie to the prom?
Whatever you've heard, it's true.
Why is he doing it?
Everybody is talking about it.
I asked him to
cos I thought I owed it to Carrie.
- Where's that put everybody else?
- They gotta deal with it in their own way.
- What do you mean?
- Oh... just something.
- Well, you're not going to the prom.
- Oh, I'll be here.
You'll be here?
What, you're going to the prom?
I will tell you later.
You're gonna be in on it.
I'm gonna be in on it? What?
I'm telling you later!
- I want to know now, Chris.
- Just wait.
I won't tell anybody, I promise. I won't say
a word. I'm your best friend. Come on.
Okay.
- You gotta rent a tuxedo for the prom.
- I only got 10 bucks, though.
You can rent a tuxedo!
You don't have to look great!
Hey.
Does this look nice?
He looks beautiful. Make a good
impression for once in your life.
- Would you go out with me?
- Not with ruffles.
You don't have to get ruffles for yourself.
- I don't like ruffles...
- You don't have to get ruffles!
Don't I look sharp?
It looks good on you,
but I don't look right in a tuxedo.
- Have you ever put on a tuxedo?
- I don't have a tuxedo body.
- I know they have tuxedos here for you.
- But I wouldn't look right.
I know just the tuxedo for him.
- Well, what do you think?
- I like it. I think it's terrific.
Look at that. No ruffles at all!
Red. I might've known it would be red.
It's pink, Mama.
Look what Tommy gave me, Mama.
Aren't they beautiful?
I can see your dirty pillows.
Everyone will.
Breasts, Mama.
They're called breasts.
And every woman has them.
Take off that dress.
No.
- We'll burn it and pray for forgiveness.
- No, Mama.
Well, he's not coming.
He is coming, Mama.
Now stop it. I'm nervous enough.
No, he's not coming.
He's not gonna come.
Go away!
Stop it, Mama!
- Stop hurting yourself, Mama!
- I'm not!
He's gonna laugh at you!
They're all gonna laugh at you!
- They're not gonna laugh at me!
- Stay here with me.
I don't wanna stay with you, Mama!
I'll tell him you're sick!
- I'll say you changed your mind!
- Be quiet.
Sit down! Be quiet!
I'll tell him you changed your mind!
Sit down!
Just sit there, Mama,
and don't say a word until I'm gone.
I'll be home early.
I love you, Mama.
Thou shalt not suffer a witch to live.
Tommy,
could we wait here just a minute?
Are you scared?
Mm-hm.
Maybe this was a mistake.
Oh, no. It's not gonna be that bad.
They're a good crowd. Really.
Really.
Don't be so nervous.
Besides, I'd look awfully stupid
dancing by myself, wouldn't l?
Now come on.
When I look back on my younger days
I really was a maniac,
blowing up the john
with a cherry bomb,
giving the janitor a cardiac.
Well, the teacher could say
they should lock you away
and throw away all the keys
if you please.
He's outta control.
The devil's got a hold of his soul.
Oh!
Man, you wanted the time
so my buddies and I
choked upon a cigarette.
Too tired to jog
and you could barely walk,
swearin' for the hell of it.
Then when it's your right to see
the president's daughter,
the daughter's been so outta sight.
Right.
Dancin' till dawn,
my parents were clear uptown.
Yeah!
High school.
Pre-school.
No, 12 long years
of the education blues.
Teachers.
Preachers.
Don't know how
I ever made it through.
Oh, yeah!
Come on.
Ross, if I knew you'd look this sharp,
I would've taken you instead of, uh...
What's her name?
Don't bother about them.
If they self-destruct,
I'll dance with you.
Hey, where did you buy that dress?
I love it!
- Oh, I made it.
- Made it?!
- The decorations... don't they look great?
- Yeah...
- I'm so nervous.
- It's okay. You can sit with us.
- Hey, what time is it?
- 8 o'clock.
Gotta go.
- Where are you going?
- Just out.
See you later.
Sue!
- Would you like to dance?
- Could we just sit here for a minute?
Sure.
Sure. Anything you want.
Carrie.
Hi, Miss Collins.
You look so pretty!
You, too. You look beautiful.
Thank you! I know I don't, not really,
but thank you, anyway.
May I sit down?
- Yeah. Chair...
- Thank you.
I'm gonna go and talk to some people.
I remember my prom.
I had a date with the, uh
the captain of the basketball team.
And he was 6ft 7in tall, so
I bought a pair of 3-inch spike heels
so that our kiss goodnight would be, um
Less awkward.
Anyway, we went in his pick-up truck,
which of course broke down, and we
had to walk the last half-mile to the prom.
By the time I got there, my feet were
so blistered that all I could do was
just sit there. I couldn't dance.
So we just sat there and, uh... just talked.
And, uh
it was... magic. Is it like that for you?
It's, um...
it's nice.
- Just nice?
- No...! It's...
It's like, uh...
- It's like being on Mars.
- You'll never forget it.
I don't think I will.
Thank you.
Hey, what's goin' on here?
What are you doing with my date?
- Oh, we're just talking.
- Yeah?
Have a lovely time, okay?
And you, too!
Bye.
Don't let me catch you
hugging any guys like that.
I won't.
Better not.
Do you really have to be home so early?
Yeah, I promised.
Okay.
- Sorry.
- That's all right.
Some of the kids are going
over to Nolston's after the prom.
That's okay.
What?
If you wanna go with your friends,
I don't wanna spoil anything.
Would you let me finish?
What I was gonna say is that,
if you'd like to,
we could stop in at The Beehive.
I've never been there.
No?
Good! Well, then, let's go!
- Okay.
- Okay?
For sure. Great.
Are you ready to dance?
Tommy, l...
Come on.
I don't know how. I can't, Tommy. I can't.
Sure you can.
I'm not sure
but the more that it's real
the more it's right.
Ooh, one night...
It's as though we've been lovers
all of our lives.
There must be a God.
Could it be that he's heard me at last?
Because you look at me
as the one beautiful...
Yeah, you can. Come on.
Give me your hand. Just put it there.
- Like that?
- Yeah. Put this on your shoulder.
That's right.
Okay, just relax. All right?
Okay. Just listen to the music.
That's right.
See, you got it? That's good.
You're as good as anyone else out here.
Got it?
- I'm sorry.
- That's all right.
- It's just...
No harm...
No foul.
- I can't do anything.
- Yeah, you can.
I can't dance. I can't even... I don't know.
- Tommy?
- Yeah?
Why...
- Why what?
- Why am I here?
Because it's the prom.
Why am I here with you?
Because I asked you.
Why'd you ask me?
Because I wanted to.
Why'd you want to?
Because you liked my poem.
Only, I didn't write it. Somebody else did.
Oh.
Carrie, we're here
and we're together
and I like it.
I do, I like it!
Where there are other girls
but tonight there's only me.
I never dreamed someone like you
could love someone like me.
All right, ladies and gentlemen!
Ladies and gentlemen...
And you two behave yourselves, okay?
Take your seats, please. We've gotta vote
for the king and the queen.
Tommy,
we are here.
I know.
Do you wanna decline?
Do you?
Hell, no. If you win, all they do is put you
up there for a school song and a dance.
Then they take your picture
for the yearbook,
so everyone can see
we look like a couple of idiots.
Anyway, it's the last year. Why not?
It's so beautiful!
Hey...
You're beautiful.
Well, who should we vote for?
They're more your crowd than mine.
I don't even have a crowd.
Let's vote for ourselves.
No.
Why not?
Please don't vote for ourselves.
Carrie...
Come on. To the devil with false modesty.
The devil!
Billy! Shh!
Will you close that a little bit?
Jesus, you wanna get caught?
- That Carrie White, she sure is cute.
- Shut up.
- Thought you said they were gonna win.
- They will. Won't even be close.
I called in a few favours.
Can I have your ballot, please?
Hello, guys. Thank you.
Can I have your ballots, please?
- Thank you.
- Thanks, there.
Thank you.
Thank you, there.
Ballots, please. Thank you.
Thank you.
Freddy, hurry up, please.
Ballots...
Good, good. Thanks a lot there, Vic.
Get all of them?
They're right in back of you,
so start kicking.
- See you.
- Good luck.
More ballots? Thank you.
I have some more ballots for you.
Thank you.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I've got the winners.
All right!
I give you Tommy Ross and Carrie White!
They're all gonna laugh at you!
- Plug it up! Plug it up!
- They're all gonna laugh at you!
We're all sorry, Cassie.
- We're all sorry, Cassie.
Trust me, Carrie. You can trust me.
Come on, let's go, Billy!
- They're all gonna laugh at you!
- We're sorry, Cassie.
They're all gonna laugh at you!
We're sorry, Cassie.
- Trust me, Carrie. You can trust me.
- They're all gonna laugh at you!
We're sorry, Cassie.
They're all gonna laugh at you!
Trust me, Carrie.
Somebody open this door!
Open this door now!
Help! Help!
Look at him!
Have these students calm down!
Mr Fromm! Mr Fromm!
Carrie!
Carrie...!
Mama?
Mama? Mama, it was bad, Mama.
They laughed at me.
Mama, hold me.
Mama, please, hold me.
Hold me, Mama.
Please, hold me!
I should have killed myself
when he put it in me.
After the first time,
before we were married.
Ralph promised never again.
He promised, and I believed him.
But sin never dies.
Sin never dies.
At first it was all right.
We lived sinlessly.
We slept in the same bed,
but we never did it.
And then, that night,
I saw him looking down at me that way.
We got down on our knees
to pray for strength.
I smelled the whisky on his breath.
And he took me... He took me.
With the stink of the filthy
roadhouse whisky on his breath.
And I liked it.
I liked it!
Well, all that dirty touching in his hands
and coming all over me...
I should have given you to God
when you were born.
But I was weak and backsliding.
But now the devil has come home.
Oh!
We'll pray.
Yes.
For the last time,
we'll pray.
Our Father, who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come, thy will be done...
Aghh!
Ohh!
Aaghhh...!
Hello?
Oh, Betty, thank God it's you.
I don't think I could have handled
one more reporter.
Yeah, well, we're all a little edgy.
She's better. Well, uh,
sleeping too much, I guess,
but Dr Schnieder said that's to be
expected after all she's been through.
Well, he said that she's young enough,
so that she'll forget about it in time.
No. I wouldn't let her go to the funerals,
with Tommy and all the others gone.
It's best we just go away for a while.
It's all right!
It's all right. I know. It's all right.
It's all right. I'm here.