THE VISITORS
Wow, what an incredible
sound this thing puts out!
It cost a little more, but it was worth it.
There's no distortion.
Give me back my chocolate!
Careful, kids.
This is a brand new car.
Peter, look at your face!
Come over here so I can clean you off.
What are they up to now?
He's making a mess of the
upholstery! Stop it, Peter!
- Stop it right now, you hear?
- Will you take care of this?
Behave yourself, or you'll
get a good spanking!
- Now hold still.
- Jesus, you're driving me crazy!
Are you mad at us?
Mad? I wish you two
would learn to behave.
This is not a joke.
See what you did?
Sit still, Lotta.
There it is!
See it?
Smell that air. Fresh and clean.
Amazing...
- Do you like it?
- Frank, it's fantastic.
What do you think, kiddo?
I have chocolate on my shirt.
Yeah, well...
Give me the keys, Sara.
Don't you have them?
Why would I have them?
You had them when we packed this morning.
Yes it was.
Damn... Oh here they are.
No problem.
How would you guys manage without me?
I don't want chocolate on my shirt.
Stupid, you're the one who put
it there in the first place.
We'll wash it.
- Now, wash it now.
- Be quiet, you big cry-baby.
I'm stunned, look how
they fixed up the place.
- Surprised, are you?
- Yeah.
Lucky we didn't have to do it ourselves.
Really.
That's what happens when you're a bigshot.
Sure... Don't forget you still
have work to do upstairs.
That's just a little wallpaper.
I'll have it up in 15 minutes.
- How do you feel?
- Perfect.
- Then why do you look so worried?
- I'm not, I'm very composed.
Yeah, sure you are...
Stop worrying.
Watch, by next week I'll
have that campaign locked up.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
If I didn't believe in my ideas,
we wouldn't be here.
You'll see, money will flow in.
- You promise?
- Very soon, I give you my word.
So let's enjoy our weekend and
on Monday I'll get started, okay?
Okay.
- All is good then?
- Yes, it is.
Where is our room?
It's upstairs.
What's Peter doing?
He's unpacking his toys.
Oh, god.
What do you think of the house, princess?
It's big.
Are we the only ones
who are gonna live here?
I certainly hope so.
Hello there.
- Here's your mail.
- Oh, thanks.
Great service you provide here.
One time only.
You have to put a box near the front gate.
You mean all the way down by the road?
You know, I'm a journalist and usually
get a lot of mail every day...
Would you do us a favour
and bring it up here?
I guess... But wait...
You'll have to put a mailbox
so I can drive right up to it.
- I won't get out of the car.
- No, no, you won't have to.
That's very sweet of you.
Hey, no problem.
(Silly accent) Wallpaper paste!
Don't do that daddy...
First you climb the ladder then you
push the wallpaper like this...
Damn you kids, laughing at me like that...
You just put it up like this... damn... shit!
- How's it going?
- Damn well, can't you see?
Yeees, it looks amazing... not a single
crooked wallpaper.
Well... aren't you cocky.
Just watch this professional in action.
First you take the wallpaper like this...
...then to prepare the wallpaper you
put it on your head.
Make a little hole like this...
Strike a pose like this, keep moving...
Then just lean back and enjoy the...
eh... brush like this...
What, you're laughing at me?
I fell on my ass and you're laughing?
Don't laugh at the greatest
painter in the world!
No... no, Frank!
Seriously, isn't it nice?
Who was that at the door?
At the door? Oh, the mailman, he
wanted us to get a mailbox.
Did we get anything interesting?
Yes...
- Bills... electricity, telephone, water...
- All right, that's enough.
- When's your appointment tomorrow?
- 9 A.M.
- Didn't you forget anything?
- No.
You sure?
Oh, those...
- Good luck, baby.
- In the bag.
What's all that?
Oh, dear...
Frank, can you buy a mailbox?
Yeah, but he doesn't have to
throw the mail on the ground, the idiot.
See you tonight.
Don't forget the mailbox!
Mommy, mommy!
Something happened upstairs.
- Come and see.
- What is it?
Daddy's gonna be mad when he see this.
Hello!
Hi!
- Where's the booze?
- On the bookshelf.
- Why the hell is it over here?
- You put it there yourself.
No luck, huh?
No.
They didn't think my
ideas were original enough.
- I knew it, I just knew it.
- Oh, you did, did you?
When did you become a psychic?
Don't be so sarcastic.
How are we gonna pay for all this?
- The car, the house...
- Stop it.
I haven't finished yet.
They're giving me another chance.
I have until friday to come up with
some new ideas.
I'm just not sure where to start.
You never know where to start.
Mommy?
We're hungry.
I'm sorry for what I said before.
You'll come up with something.
You always do.
If we talk about it a little,
maybe you'll get an idea.
You can tell me some more about it.
I only know that it's a
campaign for that insurance company.
Stay at home this week and think about it.
You need some place quiet.
Without any more pressure.
Your secretary can take your calls.
Mommy, we saw a program about
peacocks on TV today.
Did you know the peacock's
tail feathers are 80 inches long?
Really? You don't say.
Yes, the male spreads his tail
for the female so they can mate.
In this house we say, "Fuck!"
Is that what we say?
Where did you learn that?
I'm glad you're staying home so you
can fix the wallpaper in our room.
What?
It all fell down.
Frank?
Are you hurt?
You scared the shit out of me!
What were you doing down there?
I heard something scratching in the wall.
Thought it was a rat.
In the wall?
Yeah, in the pipes.
I read about a lady who had a
rat this big crawl right out of her toilet.
Frank, I doubt we have
any rats in our pipes.
Come to bed. You'll think more
clearly in the morning.
That paper should stick now.
I used twice as much glue.
That's good.
I can't seem to come up with a new idea.
My head is completely empty.
We need that damn contract.
Our future depends on it.
You should have thought about that before.
Cut it out.
You wanted to move here as much as me.
But I thought we should wait
a while, you know that.
Oh, right, here it comes.
Suddenly it's all my fault.
You didn't object when we were planning it.
And that was a mistake.
I should have protested, but
I never have a say around here.
Now that's a lot of bull and you know it.
Come on, you have a mouth.
You can say anything you want.
It doesn't help if you won't listen.
So now I'm a son of a bitch.
No, you're not...
But sometimes it's a bit much
when everything is all about you.
It's always your home, your car,
your job, your ideas...
There are others around here.
That's why I'm doing this,
for you and the kids.
You don't understand.
I guess I'm just too stupid.
What the hell, it's always my fault.
I was trying to talk about this
and we end up arguing.
Thanks so much for your damn support!
Thank you very much!
Sara?
What on earth?
What the hell is this?
Did you try glue?
Very funny.
It smells like something metallic or...
electrical, I think.
Where's it coming from?
Maybe you used too much glue.
Listen, I know what I'm doing.
Well, if that's so...
Let me do what I do,
go away and do what you're doing.
So lay off and I'll put
up the damn paper again!
Why the hell did you call for me then?
Fucking wallpaper!
Frank?
- Sorry.
- Why did you turn on the light?
Never mind, it's nothing.
Want a cigarette?
No.
Do you have to smoke in here?
Want something to drink?
I'm trying to sleep.
Right, sorry.
Fuck!
What are you doing?
That's great, Frank.
You spilled beer all over me!
There's something weird going on.
You got that right.
It's called Frank.
Turn off the light.
But... every time I walk past...
Frank, I'm trying to sleep.
Please turn out the light.
Sara?
Maybe it's haunted.
Go to sleep.
Move over to your side, Peter.
I wanna sit behind daddy.
- Watch it!
- What the hell are you doing?
- What?
- Why did you throw the mail on the ground?
You have no box!
Don't just drop it in the dirt
because of that, you dumb fuck!
You have no box!
You expect your mail to be
delivered in bed?
Get a mailbox.
What kind of idiots work at
the post office nowadays?
I'll get a mailbox.
But until then,
stop throwing the mail in the dirt.
- Suppose it...
- You should be grateful
I'm even willing to drive up here.
Suppose it rains?
Well?
Then I'll bring it in to you.
Bravo, you're finally getting the message.
Do the same when the sun is out
and I'll buy your damn mailbox.
Asshole.
Jerk.
- Peter?
- I want this one.
- No, no, no... No toys today.
- Please, daddy.
No, I said. Daddy can't
afford that, put it back.
But I want it!
No, I said. Another time.
That's what you always say.
- Allright, take it then.
- Thank you, daddy!
$30 bucks for that, it's ridiculus.
No, you'll have to put it back.
- But you promised I could have it.
- $30 dollars is too much.
Let's go.
- Take the car then.
- I don't want it anymore.
Don't start. I'm saying you can have the car.
We were supposed to buy
a magazine for mommy as well.
Wait here then.
Excuse me.
Thanks.
Don't forget to pay for that.
EXCLUSIVE INTERVIEW
GHOST HUNTER
THE OCCULT
Frank?
Yeah.
Come here a minute.
What is it?
Why did you buy so much milk?
I thought it was a good idea to have extra.
Half of it will go bad
before we can drink it.
Well sorry then!
I'll just have to drink it all myself.
- Did you buy a mailbox?
- Damn, I knew I forgot something.
Right, but you can buy a toy for Peter.
What the hell am I supposed to do when he
makes a scene in the middle of the store.
I thought we agreed
not to bend the rules
every time he throws a fit.
Right...
By the way...
do we have any wire hangers?
Yes.
What about it?
Just wondering.
What are you doing, daddy?
What's that?
What do you think it looks like?
An old man.
Yeah, I guess it does look like an old man.
My father used to make these
for me when I was a kid.
Grandpa? But he's dead!
- Who's that?
- He was my father.
You never met him.
I did... His hair was white.
Yes it was, but not when I was little.
He looked a lot like me back then.
Well, let's not talk about that anymore.
Here's a present from daddy.
You can teach this old man
how to drive your car.
Thank you, daddy.
Can I have a look, daddy?
Lotta, come help me set the table.
Go help mommy.
Sara!
- What is it?
- Sara come here!
- What's happening?
- Get up here quick!
What is it?
What happened? What is it?
- Why won't you answer me?
- There! What's that?
What's what?
Have you lost your mind?
They disappeared.
What?
Footprints.
There were wet footprints
all over the floor!
Frank, calm down.
Something was here!
Don't tell me to calm down!
There were marks! Something left
slimy footprints in my attic!
Frank, come on.
Wait a minute!
- Not in front of the kids.
- Why don't you believe me?
Come on, it's nothing.
- Why is daddy so mad?
- Mommy, tell me!
It's nothing. Let's go eat.
- Are you coming?
- Later.
- Dinner's ready now, Frank.
- Listen, I'm not hungry.
- Occult Magazine.
- Yes, my name is...
I'd like to speak to someone named...
Allan Svensson.
It's regarding an article he wrote.
Thanks.
- Allan Svensson.
- Yes, hi...
My name is Frank Eriksson.
I read your article on wire hangers
and cold spots pinpointing spirits.
- That one. Listen...
- Can you speak up a bit?
I really can't right now.
What about the article?
Did you like it?
Yes, very good.
In fact, I'm calling about...
I'm sure this will sound ridiculous,
but my family and I just moved into a new
house and some strange things
have been happening around here.
Really? Such as?
Well, there's this room that
keeps rejecting wallpaper.
Is that right?
Are you putting it up properly?
Yes, but there's been a lot of
other bizarre things going on.
Listen, Frank... Maybe I
should drive out to see you?
Yeah?
- Come here?
- Would that be a problem?
No, I guess not...
See you tomorrow.
Frank?
Everything seems to be going wrong.
What worries me most is you.
Me?
You've never been like this.
Well, it's not so strange when you consider
what's going on here at night.
Where is this obsession
of yours coming from?
- It's like you've forgotten...
- What do you mean forgotten?
- I haven't forgotten a thing.
- Calm down.
I am calm.
But there are things...
Frank, you get yourself all
worked up over nothing.
I know how you feel.
Everything's spinning out of
control and you can't concentrate.
Listen...
How about tomorrow we take the kids
for a nice long walk in the woods
and we can talk this over
and clear the air.
It would really help.
It'll be like a new beginning.
How about it?
Then you have to promise you'll
stop talking about weird noises
and strange sights.
Now, go to sleep so you'll have
some energy in the morning.
Hello?
It's me...
The mailman.
This is pissing me off...
Hi.
I thought I heard someone in here.
I can hardly wait.
Have you located them yet?
Well, they're not here.
Oh? Then where are they?
How the hell should I know?
Why, have they disappeared?
I don't know where they are,
for chrissakes.
You think I follow them around?
I don't give a shit about what they do.
Mostly, they fight.
What was that?
They argue?
Yeah... about the mailbox.
The mailbox?
Oh, is that where they've moved?
Am I missing something here?
They haven't even bought one.
One of them screamed like crazy
at me yesterday.
What did you say?
You mean you can see them move around?
They just wander throughout the whole area?
Well, I have to be going.
No, no, no, wait.
Don't run off.
We have to sort this out.
You're saying they moved.
I'm sure they'll be back.
We can't let this chance slip away.
I've got equipment in the car to trap them!
Once we have them trapped,
we'll examine them. I'll take photos!
Then we'll zap them with a
blast of electricity! Bzzzt!
Are you joking?
Of course not... I don't joke.
Everybody thinks I'm joking.
I have no idea why!
I can't begin to understand this.
It's very simple.
We have to get them
before they come after us.
Who knows?
They might be listening
to us right this minute.
Wait, what the hell are you talking about?
Those cold spots of yours, of course.
Hey you!
There's a freak in here!
I think he's nuts.
Oh!
Hi.
Who are you?
Allan.
You know, from "Occult Magazine"?
Oh, you're the one.
We spoke on the phone.
- I'm Frank.
- Sure, hi.
So, you found your way here.
No, only my spirit.
I'm still at home in bed.
Glad you two seem to be hitting it off.
Now...
you still don't have a mailbox.
The weather looked bad,
so I put the mail on your table.
Whoops!
Have a nice day...
if possible.
So, now that I'm here,
let's go check the wallpaper.
Oh, sure.
Oh, right, this is my wife, Sara.
- Hi... Allan.
- Sara.
Well, I might as well bring in
the equipment.
I left it outside.
Gimme a hand, will ya?
- Sure.
- My god, Frank, did you hire a painter?
- How do you expect us to pay him?
- Wait a minute, he isn't a paint...
- Can you handle this one?
- Sure.
- Where is the room?
- Upstairs.
Whoops!
You sure don't travel light
in your business.
Right, let's see...
What are these machines for?
These, my friends, register energy.
Energy?
Life.
Frank, come.
- What is it?
- Who is that man?
- It's silly, he wanted to come.
- Who is he?
- He's some kind of researcher.
- What kind?
- A ghost researcher.
- Well, everything's working.
Now we'll just have to wait and
see if anything turns up.
Oh, and it's important that we
stay out of the room
so nobody triggers the equipment.
Come on, kids.
Now, where can I put my overnight bag?
You think it'll take that long?
Well, if you want proper
readings, it certainly will.
Yeah, so...
where do we put the kids?
Put them where you sleep.
Most people don't realize
how little we know about...
ghosts and the supernatural.
The only time most of them get
a chance to find out about it
is after death.
Have you ever experienced
this kind of stuff yourself?
Oh, several times.
But a friend of mine
had a very nasty experience once.
What happened?
Demons.
Demons?
He decided to spend an evening
in one of those really old haunted houses.
The family who lived there
had mysteriously disappeared.
But the house was still left
just like they still lived there.
The same night they disappeared
a horrible scream was heard.
Coming from that house.
So he sat there, in the middle of the night,
with nothing but a burning candle.
But suddenly,
a mysterious wind blew
through the room and the candle went out.
He's trying to find it in
the dark but it is gone.
Suddenly he hears a sound...
coming from somewhere in the house.
It sounded
...big. Heavy.
It is moving closer to the
room he's sitting in.
He turns around towards the door
he can see it slowly, slowly, slowly...
starting to open.
What the hell was that?
Don't know.
Something triggered the equipment.
But what?
What the hell could have done it?
That's what we're going find out.
What's that?
- Where?
- Behind the door.
I don't know, it's locked.
Wait! Why are you running?
That thing went crazy!
I just hit the wrong button!
- Well, why did you run?
- Me? I followed you!
Anyway, this machine
isn't gonna be much help.
Really? No kidding!
I'm interested in seeing
what's behind that door.
Do you have a key?
- Let's just forget about this!
- No way!
Can't we just break the lock?
Just have a quick peek!
Come on, it's your house!
You should know what's up there!
- I'll get some tools!
- Hold on!
Damn it!
- Do you mind if I break the door?
- Great, break the door...
Hey, I need the light!
Take it easy, you'll wake up
my whole family!
If they didn't wake up before
they won't now either.
Come here.
Listen to this. November 16th:
My research into the origins
of the previous house owners
has not yielded any results,
but the manifestations I've
seen over the last few days
have me convinced beyond a doubt.
November 17th:
I know I'm not alone.
Something is here.
Something evil.
November 18th:
My visitors are on their way.
I can hear them coming.
Wait, wait! Don't panic!
We have to get out of here!
Let's wake up the others and go!
No-no-no, stop!
What do you mean no-no-no?
This is my family and house!
- We don't even know what it is!
- I'm know and I'm leaving!
Calm down!
How will you explain this?
- Give me time to study it.
- What are you gonna do?
Go upstairs and say, I'm Allan!
Any demons hiding around here?
- We're not sure there are demons.
- I'm sure, very sure.
- What else could it be? I'm going!
- Wait! Wait!
There's one way to prove it.
If you help me, I can do it
very quickly! Come on!
Help with what?
What the hell are you up to now?
Help me with this.
- What is it?
- Grab it.
Grab it? What the hell is this thing?
What's in the box?
You'll see, don't be so damn curious!
This here is a real machine.
It registers energy
just like the other ones.
But this one can also transmit high energy.
Close it.
- High energy?
- Yep, spirits and cold spots
are just collected energy
and if you give them a high voltage shock,
BZZZT! They disappear.
Get me the cable from the car.
- The cable?
- Yeah, we have to ground this thing too.
Hurry up.
Frank, this baby will take care of everything.
First, we activate the generator
and build up high voltage power.
That will stimulate any energy
fields you might have around here.
After that, we just wait for
something to appear.
Then I push this little button...
and to hell with them.
Now, watch out.
That thing looks deadly.
Are you sure you know what you're doing?
Hell yes, I've built it myself!
Something's happening.
What the hell!
Pull the plug!
You should have your head
examined, you lunatic!
The ground!
I forgot to ground the machine!
Come back here!
Allan!
Stop right now, damn it!
There's nothing to worry about.
Allan!
So...
it will say, in my report,
that ghosts took the life of Mr. Svensson.
Demons.
That's about all we can accomplish...
for now.
We'll be in touch as soon
as we get the autopsy report.
About Mr. Svensson's equipment...
It has been packed in his car.
His car is locked.
We'll come by for it.
It's been sealed and I expect
it to remain that way
until we can remove it.
Sara, listen...
Frank, this is the craziest
thing I've ever experienced.
I don't understand why you had to
drag that man here to begin with.
Shit.
Would you stop swearing?
Alright, but I didn't drag him
here, he wanted to come.
Oh, is he the one who made
the first phone call?
Thanks to your absurd imagination he's dead.
Do you get it, Frank?
He's gone!
You're right on the edge here.
What was that about?
You, of course.
What did you both decide?
I should be committed?
Who knows, it might help.
Did you forget your appointment
with your clients this evening?
I have no intention of going.
- What did you say?
- You heard me.
Listen, Frank, don't make
this a test of wills.
What are you talking about?
You've already got me committed.
Sara, don't you get it?
We have to pack up and move.
- What are you saying?
- We have to go, Sara.
We have to pack up and
leave here immediately.
We'll be risking our lives
if we stay one more night.
Frank, we're not going anywhere,
you hear me?
So go to that meeting and explain
to them that you need more time.
Forget it, you have no idea
what's going on.
Forget it, you say?
A man is dead, Frank!
We have no money and you're
chasing ghosts! It's almost comical!
Then why aren't you laughing?!
Christ, just stop this!
Why are you doing this to me?
I don't care about work, Sara!
And I sure as hell don't care about
this damn house! Understood?
The only this I want is for us to leave, now!
Then I'm leaving, Frank.
I mean it, if you don't stop this...
it's over.
Peter? Lotta?
Sara, wait!
Wait!
You can't leave without us!
Stop the car, Sara!
You can't leave us here!
Yes I can!
Stop the car and act like an adult!
Get away from me!
Let go!
Stop it, Sara!
Stop the damn car, Sara!
Never!
Stop, Sara!
Let go, Frank!
Mom's just gone on an errand,
she'll be right back.
You two wait on the porch
while daddy calls a taxi.
Come with daddy.
Damn it!
Please, daddy, can we go inside?
Daddy will be there in a minute.
Why is daddy acting so crazy?
He's not crazy.
He's just mad at mommy.
They fight all the time because he's crazy.
How come you and mommy always fight?
We don't always fight, sweetheart.
Then why did she go away?
I don't know why.
Please, daddy...
will you read us a story?
Sure.
Yeah, a scary one!
Yeah, with a monster!
Come and sit down.
Yes, ma'am, you can dial
direct from your room.
Thanks.
Daddy?
Daddy, something bad...
We're sorry, the line is not working.
Please try your call later...
- Where's mommy?
- Now just calm down, honey.
- Mommy's coming soon.
- I want mommy.
Don't worry.
Daddy's here.
Stay calm.
Daddy?
Shit!
Crazy fool!
Damn it!
Don't be afraid.
Wait here for Daddy.
Peter!
Lotta! Check the wire!
Is it plugged in?
It came out!
Lotta!
You have to plug it in!
Plug it in as fast as you can!
Lotta!
Plug it in!
Mommy!
Help us!
Frank!
Mommy, help!
- Open the door, Lotta!
- We can't, mommy!
It's blocked!
- Where's daddy?
- In the attic!
Open your eyes!
Look at me! Look at me!
We're gonna get you out!
Don't worry!
Hurry! Run!
Run! Run!
Sara!
Think we can make it to town?