Sixty-eight... sixty-nine...
seventy... seventy-one...
Come on, will you?
Shut up!
You'll make me lose the count.
Seventy-two...
Seventy-three.
Close enough. It's a hundred.
Let's go.
No, wait!
Hey, Alice! Alice, wake up!
Jesus.
And as adults, we must
now prepare for a new life...
outside
this wonderful environment...
known as Springwood High.
So let's blow this pop stand!
Alice! Yvonne!
Girl, what's wrong?
Let's see a smile.
I had kind of a long night.
Dan keeping you up again?
Girl, you better put a lock
on that window.
The Dan part was nice.
These things are wild.
What do you think?
You look like a nun.
Dying to break her vows.
Find me a man!
Fabulous.
Maybe I should
spell it out for you.
Maybe God's trying to tell you
something.
When are you gonna
run away with me?
Next life. What's that?
My undying love. Have some.
Mark, give it up.
It's hopeless.
I think I'm starting
to wear her down.
Have a taste anyway.
Greta! That's not what
a cover girl puts in her body!
Shit!
She read you.
Ladies,
where's the party tonight?
Why don't we go to Alice's?
No. My dad's got this thing
about drinking in the house.
We gotta do something.
Guys, I got swimming practice
until six-thirty.
So?
They're gonna give me the key,
so I can lock up after I'm done.
Pool party!
Oh, damn, I gotta work tonight!
Hey, Mark! Picture time!
Come get immortalized...
parents and brats.
Greta! Photo opportunity, dear!
Damn it, they caught me.
I have to go gnash my teeth
for the paparazzi.
You guys go on.
I'll catch up with you later.
-Hey, beautiful.
-Oh, Jesus, don't do that!
Sorry. I got a present for you.
You got the tickets?
Yeah. They're coach seats...
but this plane stops in Paris.
It's gonna be a great summer.
Yeah, I know.
Hey... what's the matter?
Nothing. It's just...
I didn't see my dad
at the ceremony.
Well, he'll show up.
Hey, come on.
What's really wrong?
I had one of those dreams
last night.
About him?
Well, not exactly.
It's that I just felt like
I wasn't in control...
for the first time
since all that.
Look, if you don't dream him up,
he can't hurt you or us.
Remember?
You're right.
There you go. Love you.
-I love you.
-Hey, Danny! Dan!
You look sweet today.
Hello, darling.
Dan, this is Coach Ostrow.
He's interviewing next week.
Finest quarterback in the state.
You know what they say...
this boy
feels the need for speed.
So I've heard.
Dad, could we
get into this later?
Summer's just starting.
Dan, we're talking about
your future here.
Excuse us, dear.
-Listen.
-It's OK, Dan.
We take care of our boys.
Say "cheese. "
'Congratulations, Alice.
'You looked beautiful
up there. "
'I'm so proud of you.
'Gee, thanks, Dad. "
You do look beautiful.
I was afraid you weren't coming.
I watched
from behind the stands.
I didn't want to embarrass you.
'The drunk showed up. "
That kind of thing.
That's in the past.
Unless you've stopped going
to your meetings.
No. A deal's a deal.
Come on.
Where are we going?
Oh... to take a picture.
I don't take good pictures.
Call me
when your shift ends, OK?
Good-bye, sir.
Don't worry.
I'll have her home by August.
Just kidding.
See you later.
Thanks for everything, Dad.
You sure you don't want
a ride to work?
No. It's just across the park.
Have fun tonight.
Oh, sorry!
Freddy's coming for you
Three, four
Better lock your door
Five, six
Grab your crucifix
Seven, eight
Better stay up late
Better stay awake
Nine, ten
He's back again
Wait!
Let me go! Let me go!
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Just do exactly what I say.
Help me!
Why is this happening again?
Oh, please don't let him
do this!
Don't panic, Amanda.
We have a breech birth here.
It's backward!
We're going to have
to turn it around.
Take a deep breath.
I'm going to need you to push.
Now push!
Holy shit.
What is it?
Careful!
Sister,
this is one of God's creatures.
Take solace in that.
That is no creature of God!
Stop it! Give it to me!
Don't let it get away!
Where are you?
No! Not again!
It's a boy!
You can't come back!
I locked the door on you.
Well, I found the key!
Your birth was a curse
on the whole of humanity.
I will not allow it
to happen again.
You brought me back
to give you life...
but now I must take yours.
We'll see, bitch.
We'll just see.
I must be released
from my earthly prison.
How?
Look for me in the tower.
You'll never find her.
Anne.
Oh, God, I'm glad it's you.
-It was terrible.
-What happened?
I was in the dream...
and I don't know how,
but now he's back.
I thought you were dead.
You're four hours late.
Four hours?
I wish I had a prescription
for whatever it is you're on.
What?
Listen, thanks a lot, Alice,
for nada.
Bombs away!
What'd your dad say about
you and Alice going to Europe?
Nothing, really.
Just screamed a lot...
and tried to convince me
that I'm throwing my life away.
Who's throwing their life away?
Dan, and he's taking Alice
with him.
Pretty good dive, Yvonne.
You've been practicing.
That's right. Two hours a day,
six days a week.
Have another one.
I think you need it.
No. I got a shift
in a couple of hours.
Aren't you going in?
No. My mom's got this asshole
photographer coming over...
and I'm not supposed
to mess up my hair.
Aren't you sick of your mom
trying to run your life?
Don't let 'em.
Sure, no problem.
You know, he's right.
Sometimes I feel like I'm living
with Melicertes.
-Who?
-Melicertes.
He's this ancient guy
I read about, right?
Who, like, killed his kids...
because he didn't like the way
they were running the kingdom.
You're really weird,
you know that?
Screw 'em!
Open the champagne!
Let's have a party!
-All right!
That's for Alice and me later.
Sorry.
-Ow, are you OK?
-Oh, my God.
I could have gone all night
without looking at that.
I think it's very strange
how you draw all your comics...
loaded with blood and guts.
That freaks you out.
Yeah,
it's just a little blood, guy.
I know what it is,
you big, dumb jock.
Dan, telephone. Come on.
I'll be right back.
Don't touch this, OK?
OK, we'll guard it
with our lives.
-Dan, it was Krueger.
-What?
It happened while I was awake.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
Now, wait a second. How could...
He must have dreamt himself up.
I don't know.
Jesus, Dan, I'm scared.
All right. Stay right there.
I'm on my way.
OK, I will.
Just hurry, OK?
Shit.
What happened? Somebody die?
Nah. I got to go.
Alice beckons.
Hey, Romeo,
forgot the secret ingredient.
There he goes,
the fastest man on three legs.
The sounds of Springwood.
It's a beautiful evening
here in downtown Springwood...
and we'll be back
with the music in just a moment.
Right now,
we're open for your calls.
I'm calling about
my wayward ex-son Daniel...
who's been acting
like an ungrateful dickweed...
ever since he was seduced
by that bimbo slut whore Alice!
Mom?
If I were you, lady...
I'd kill the ungrateful piggy.
Put your pedal
to the metal, Dan!
Bad year, Dan!
Better buckle up, dear!
This boy
feels the need for speed.
Gotcha!
Fuel injection!
Power drive!
Fast lane!
Hey, Danny,
better not dream and drive.
Coffee, please?
He just came fucking
flying out of nowhere!
It was some kind
of a frigging jet!
I didn't even see him!
Want to make babies?
You're all right.
It's OK, honey, I'm right here.
Dan's been in an accident.
It was no accident.
It was Krueger.
He used to come in through
my dreams and not anymore.
He found some other way.
I'm sorry.
It was no dream.
Dan's dead.
Not Dan.
Honey.
I'm so sorry.
Daddy, it wasn't an accident.
Krueger killed Dan.
Calm down. Take it easy.
You're in shock.
The police found fragments
of a champagne bottle.
Dan didn't drink. You know that.
I mean, it was probably for me
to celebrate our trip!
We gotta do something!
Dan's already dead.
Don't you see?
It's starting again.
These sorts of outbursts
aren't entirely uncommon.
Many women
have them at the beginning.
Especially if they've suffered
a traumatic shock.
Don't worry, young lady.
You're gonna be fine.
What do you mean?
What's he talking about?
What's wrong with me?
Nothing.
You're just a little pregnant.
The doctor
wants to keep you overnight.
Just for routine observation...
to make sure you're
as comfortable as possible.
You're gonna be fine, honey.
Everything's gonna be OK.
What's your name?
Jacob.
Really?
I've always loved that name.
Shouldn't you be in your room,
Jacob?
It's lonely there.
Well, my name is...
I'm sorry your boyfriend
got killed.
How did you know that?
I could tell you were sad.
I just wanted to see
if you were all right.
Jacob, wait. Don't go.
Greta, dear...
it's time
to get your beauty sleep.
We don't want circles
under those beautiful eyes.
Have you visited that little boy
on my floor?
You know, Jacob?
He has kind of sad eyes.
There aren't
any little boys on your floor.
He must have wandered in
from the children's ward.
I was just wondering
what's wrong with him.
We don't have a children's ward.
He was wearing a hospital robe.
I don't know what to tell you.
Did you call everyone?
Yup. Listen...
let's keep this dream stuff
between you and me, OK?
Amanda Krueger
was part of a religious order...
that ran that asylum
in the 1940s.
She was raped by the lunatics
and had the baby there.
That baby grew up to be
Freddy Krueger...
who murdered
twenty or thirty kids...
right here on Elm Street.
He got caught...
but the courts cut him loose
on a technicality.
So, the parents
of the murdered kids...
got together and killed him.
Torched him.
But that was just the beginning.
He keeps on killing...
but he kills people
in their dreams...
their nightmares.
He uses my dreams
to bring him his victims.
It's my fault that Dan's dead.
Stop saying that.
That's bullshit.
Let's talk about the baby.
Yeah, congratulations.
I guess.
That's not what we're here for.
Look, Dan's parents
were really pushing him hard.
He was bitching about it
last night at the party.
He was under
a lot of pressure. We all are.
Pushy parents
can drive you nuts.
What does that
have to do with it?
When Dan died,
you weren't even asleep.
You even said so. End of story.
He must have found
some other way.
Listen to me!
This isn't some kind of joke!
He gets in
through my dreams somehow...
and I thought
I could control it...
but something's changed...
and I don't know
what he'll do next.
Look, Alice,
we all know you're upset.
The bottom line, Alice...
if anybody's
trying to hurt you...
supernatural or not...
they're going to have
to go through us first.
All of us. Right?
That's what I'm afraid of.
How was the meeting?
-Sobering.
-Very funny.
When did you become
such a smart shopper?
Ever since my little girl
became a mom.
You disappointed in me?
No, I'm not.
I sort of hope it's a boy.
It'd be nice to hear a boy
playing in the house again.
Just don't make a habit of it.
It's true.
People are always mistaking us
for sisters.
Greta certainly has
the perfect body for modeling.
You know,
Eileen Ford is a friend of mine.
I told her about you.
She's very interested.
Greta, you're being offered
the opportunity of a lifetime.
I think you should show
a little gratitude.
One of my friends
died yesterday, Mother.
Do you mind if I take
a few hours off to remember him?
But we're having a party, dear.
I read about him.
Drunk or something, wasn't he?
Oh, he was just a friend
of Greta's.
Not someone special.
Not someone she was seeing.
You understand.
No, thank you. I'm not hungry.
Aren't you eating?
I really don't feel up to it.
Really, dear,
you ought to try something.
You're the one
who's always slapping my hand...
about my weight, Mother.
That's why we diet, dear...
so we can eat at social events
and not upset the other guests.
Tell you what.
Why don't I just eat
the whole goddamn tray...
go throw up, and come back
for seconds, all right?
Madam, if I may.
Bon appétit, bitch.
Filet de Barbie.
Nothing but the best for Greta.
Open wide!
Second helping!
Don't talk
with your mouth full, dear!
You are what you eat!
Poor baby.
There.
Dad!
Dad, help!
Honey? How's dinner coming?
I can't believe
this shit is happening.
Just hang in there, Yvonne.
Man, I know Mark
is gonna be wigging out.
We just got to keep tight.
We'll get through, OK?
I know he's back here somewhere,
girls.
I think he's pretty upset.
Mark, you OK?
Fine. Just aces.
I want to talk to you guys
about Greta.
I'm terribly sorry,
but Greta's dead today.
Perhaps we could interest you
in someone else.
Look, it was an accident,
just like Dan's.
No accident.
I tried to warn all of you
about Krueger.
Alice, please.
I thought about that.
She must have fallen asleep
while she was at the table.
This is getting
a little sick, guys.
Too bad.
I don't understand
what's happening.
Krueger has to use my dreams...
but he got to Dan and Greta
while I was awake.
How's he doing it?
Why don't you two
stick to reality?
Why don't you shut up
and let her talk?
Two of us have died
in the past two days.
Does that just strike you
as particularly normal?
I'm not finished.
I loved Greta, a lot.
And if maybe, just maybe...
someone or something
killed her...
I'd like to hear about it.
-I'm not gonna listen to this.
-Then get out!
Come on.
Yvonne, wait a minute.
I'm... sorry.
I'm an asshole, OK?
I know I'm not dealing with this
very well...
but it's not your fault, and...
I'm sorry.
It's OK.
You stick around for a while?
I wish I could, but...
I got a shift tonight.
I got to get going.
I'll stay with you for a while,
if you want.
Bye, you guys.
See you.
Do you think I'm an idiot
for being in love with her?
Nobody thinks that.
I know I didn't stand a chance
in hell, but...
She cared a lot about you.
Maybe it was her mother
who killed her...
with all that
Polly-Perfect shit.
It wasn't her mother.
We have these scumbags
here on "The Hot Seat" tonight.
The Phantom Prowler
wouldn't have been afraid...
to tell her how he felt.
If I only had a tenth
of his guts.
Jesus, he's not even real...
and he's more of a human being
than I am.
This guy isn't one of your
comic book characters, Mark.
He's not the Phantom Prowler.
He's for real.
Tell me more
about this Krueger guy.
You look tired.
Why don't I make some coffee?
There's a lot to tell.
Help!
Mark, take my hand!
Take it!
We got to get out of here.
Mark, come on.
Oh, shit.
You don't look very well.
Are you feeling all right?
Been having bad dreams.
Is this where you live, Jacob?
Just waiting for someone.
It's sad about Greta.
Is that who you're waiting for?
I don't think this is
a very nice place for you to be.
Maybe we should go look
for your mom.
She doesn't want me around.
Oh, I'm sure that's not true.
I'll bet she's very worried
about you.
I would be.
No, you're not! You don't even
care about being a mom.
How come you
don't think about me?
-Who said I... What?
-I like you.
I want to stay with you.
How come you don't like me?
Who said I don't like you?
My friend with the funny hand.
Come on, honey.
We're gonna get out of here.
No, I have to go now.
He's calling me.
Jacob, wait!
Holy shit.
He's really real, isn't he?
Are you OK?
He's doing something to my baby.
I know it.
He's trying to hurt Jacob.
Who's Jacob?
My baby.
What, you named him already?
I guess so.
I got to get away from here.
Someplace where Krueger
can't find him.
Slow down.
Now, how you gonna hide
from a guy like that, huh?
Leave the planet?
I don't know.
Look...
if you're worried
about your baby...
call Yvonne and have the doctor
check him out.
I'm gonna go see what else
I can find out about Krueger.
You had me scared on the phone.
What's wrong with the baby?
I think Krueger's
trying to do something to him.
Alice! Honey, no.
I love you, but you're gonna
have to get a hold of yourself.
Mark knows I'm not crazy.
Ask him to show you his hands.
I think you just need
to calm down, OK?
I can't figure out how
he's getting in when I'm awake.
Do unborn babies dream?
They do.
But do us both a favor.
Don't mention any of this
to Dr. Moore.
I can't believe you had me
drag Dr. Moore down here...
on a Sunday morning for this.
I'm sorry, Yvonne.
I thought
it was something serious.
If this isn't serious,
I don't know what is.
Don't dare say a word.
You're gonna get me fired.
Dr. Moore,
do unborn babies dream?
As the fetus develops...
it can spend up to
seventy percent of its day...
in a dream state.
More as it matures.
Will I be able to sense them?
Is that why you're here?
To see if your baby's
having nightmares?
We're here to find out
everything we can, aren't we?
Frankly, I have found
nothing about you...
that would indicate
the necessity of ultrasound...
at this stage
of your pregnancy.
I just want to make sure
my baby's all right.
Well, the heart seems strong.
Let's hear it.
There's your baby.
Get her file.
See any family resemblance?
Feeding time.
Soul food for my boy.
Don't touch him!
What's he doing to my baby?
Please, young lady,
try to keep calm.
Your baby is perfectly healthy.
A little large
for so early on...
but as normal
as I've ever seen.
He's taking their souls,
their spirits...
and making the baby like him.
Look, sweetie, you're tired.
You'll feel much better
after I take you home...
and get some rest, OK?
Come on, let's go.
Come on.
Greta and Dan were there.
Krueger killed them.
Now he was...
feeding them to Jacob.
Alice,
stop and listen to yourself.
Do you know what you sound like?
Completely insane, but I'm not.
And if you're my friend,
you would believe me a little.
I am your friend,
and I'm worried sick about you.
It's time to leave the Twilight
Zone and face reality.
-Krueger is reality.
-So is your baby.
You got more to think about
than yourself.
What do you think I'm doing?
Look...
whether you believe it or not,
Krueger is back.
He's after my baby...
and if I don't try to do
something about it, who will?
All I know is you're not doing
you or your baby any good...
by acting like a crazy woman.
Why don't you take off?
Leave Springwood.
Cool off for a while.
God damn it, you don't run away
from this guy!
He finds you in your dreams!
He found a lot of other people
before he found us.
-You, too?
-He invited me to his house.
Look, we're all tired...
and we haven't had any sleep
since Friday night.
That's the only reason
you're alive.
No, it's not!
Look through this stuff,
will you?
She's not crazy!
You OK?
I know what's happening.
Krueger's using Jacob's dreams.
We gotta stop him.
Well, there is...
one way.
Have you thought about
not having the baby?
I mean, no baby...
no baby's dreams.
No, I can't do that.
I saw him inside of me, growing.
He's part of me and Dan.
I want to keep him.
OK, then we'll find another way.
I've seen her.
Alice, can you come down
a minute?
Mr. Jordan and I wanted to see
how you're feeling.
Well, come sit down.
This really isn't a good time.
Maybe you could come back.
Frankly, we wondered what
you intend to do with your baby.
What I what?
Well, I've thought about it,
and I plan to keep him.
We were concerned
that all this...
might be a little bit too much
for you.
I mean,
being single and everything.
What Mr. Jordan means is that
we're aware of the burden...
that raising a child
would place on you.
We want to help.
We want to adopt it and raise it
as though it were our own.
Look, I appreciate
what you're offering...
but, no.
He's my responsibility.
And ours.
It's our grandchild.
Now, Doris, maybe
this wasn't such a good idea.
Alice, we're worried that
in your present condition...
that you don't have
the ability...
to take care of a child.
What are you talking about,
"my condition"?
We got a call from Dr. Moore.
He said that
Alice was hysterical...
and that she was having
paranoid delusions.
You don't understand.
We know you've been through
a lot...
but there is more at stake here
than just your feelings.
You're not taking my baby.
Well, the courts
might not agree with you.
But I do.
I've heard enough of this crap.
You think you can just
walk into my house...
and threaten my daughter?
Please, we have
a legitimate claim to it.
He's not a thing.
He's part of me...
and I'm not giving him to you
or anyone else!
They think I'm nuts.
That's their problem.
No, it's our problem.
If I don't deal with this...
they really might try
to take Jacob.
You said she committed suicide.
Yeah, that's what
the papers thought.
She spent the rest of her life
in the asylum.
After Krueger's trial,
she flipped out...
and hung herself...
so they thought.
Meaning?
Meaning...
they couldn't prove it.
No body.
But I've seen her grave.
Ah, empty plot.
A memorial stone.
Vacant.
They never put her under.
Cool, huh?
I don't understand.
If she killed herself,
her soul's gonna be in torment.
Where'd you hear that?
Right here, somewhere.
Yeah. "Transmigration...
'Soul of a sinner... "
Yeah. "Trapped
in its earthly resting place. "
In the dream,
she was trying to stop him.
She started to tell me how,
then the door slammed.
He must have done it.
We have to find where she died
to release her soul.
I want you to stay awake
and watch me, OK?
No problem.
Hey, you missed practice.
What happened? You fall in love?
Don't ask.
You don't even want to know.
Pool still open?
I think, if you hurry.
Let's rock...
and roll!
Where are you going, piglet?
The party's just starting.
I know
exactly what you're up to.
I thought I was up to Yvonne!
Why don't you just shut up?
What happened?
He's scared to come in
because of Amanda.
Hey, are you all right?
Oh, God.
You're not crazy.
We have to find Amanda.
She's the key.
Come on. Come on.
Jesus.
Mark, help me, please!
Is she delicious, or am I crazy?
You leave her alone!
Time to die,
you scar-faced limp-dick!
Faster than a bastard maniac!
More powerful
than a loco-madman!
It's... Super Freddy!
Told you comic books
was bad for ya!
Oh, God! Oh, shit!
Damn it!
Nothing in that room
was up to code.
It's a miracle
they both weren't killed.
No! He won't hurt me.
He needs me alive.
Who? What's she talking about?
No, she's just very upset.
Maybe both of you
should come down to the station.
What's going on? Where's Mark?
Mark fell asleep.
Krueger got him.
No! God!
Hey, come on!
I need you to be strong now!
Listen, we have to get
to Krueger...
before he gets to Jacob again.
How do we stop him?
Through Amanda.
So... we have to find her?
Just don't ask me to take
a Jacuzzi with that guy again.
You know...
I was in the tower
when he used you to distract me.
What are we gonna do?
I want you
to go to the asylum...
the one I told you about,
where all of this started...
and find her!
Alice,
you're coming home with me.
No, Dad,
I've got something to do.
Alice,
you're coming with me right now.
Find Amanda! And hurry!
Come on out, Krueger!
The game's over!
I was stronger than you!
So you picked on Jacob!
You bastard!
You're trying to make him
like you...
so you can live
through his dreams!
Well, I won't let you!
You hear me, Krueger?
OK, if you won't talk to me...
maybe you'd like to talk
to Amanda!
Come on, you fucking coward!
Good night, asshole!
I'm your real friend, Jacob.
Just like a daddy.
I gotcha! I gotcha!
Mommy, meet my friend.
Nice try, Alice.
Thanks, babe.
It's my new look. Like it?
Come downstairs.
He won't hurt you.
He needs us both.
I've got you both.
Come on, Jacob.
It's time to go home.
Jacob, run!
Come on! Come on!
Come to Papa!
It's all right, son.
Now come with me.
Jacob, he's not your father!
Kids.
Always a disappointment.
Where is he?
Inside you... where he hides.
What do you mean?
Where he hides out. Inside.
That's how he found me.
But how?
He says it's easy
because he knows you so well.
All right, Krueger...
this time it's for keeps!
Come on, Alice...
now we can really get to know
each other.
Sister Amanda?
Thank you.
Jacob! Alice will not triumph!
Only you can help her now.
Hey, leave her!
Let's go!
I want to learn stuff from you.
She's no fun anymore.
Teach me?
Now, Jacob.
Unleash the power
he has given you.
School's out, Krueger.
Stay back!
Take your baby and leave!
Let me out!
You do good work, Alice.
So did Dan.
Is he still keeping you up
at night?
Oh, it's OK.
He has the rest of his life
to catch up on his sleep.
Hi, honey.
Sweet dreams, Jacob Daniel.
Hey, sugar.
How's my little grandson, huh?
Look.
Hungry?
Mm-hmm. We all are.
Hey, sweetie.