(GASPS)
(SCREAMING)
MAN OVER RADIO:
It's 47 degrees right now at 7:17.
Sports news coming up
at twenty-five after the hour.
Jack Walters will be having that
exclusive interview with Billy Martin,
and you know that could be fireworks.
The best bet for you folks
coming in from Jersey,
do whatever you got to do
to use the Holland
rather than the Lincoln Tunnel.
The backup there, at the Lincoln,
is already a nightmare.
Looking forward to some bright blue
skies all day today, with sunshine
and the highs this afternoon
somewhere in the upper 50s.
Especially in the city,
it could get up near 60.
Enjoy it while you can, my friend.
Old Man Winter is going to be blowing
on your neck any day now.
Lows tonight in the upper 30s
with frost in some of the usually
colder regions upstate.
You're listening to Willie Craig
on PRM-FM 93.
And if your clock radio
is set to go off at 7:18,
it should be doing that right about now.
- Start every day with music on PRM.
- (SHOWER RUNNING)
This is a cut from the new Pandemonium
album, "Lady Stevie."
(MACHINE BEEPING)
Peter, you're supposed to be ready
in half an hour.
Ready for what?
We're going to the museum today,
and then you and Mike and I...
Mom, I can't go. I need the rest
of the vacation to finish this thing.
We made these plans
a week ago, remember?
I know. But I'm way behind my schedule.
I'm sorry.
Peter, have you been up all night again?
Mom, the City Science Championships
are next week.
(MACHINE CLICKING)
Turn that thing off.
Put that down and look at me.
(BUZZING)
(CLICKING STOPS)
We made a little deal, didn't we?
You know I'm very proud and excited
about your project,
but I don't want
you working all night on it.
I know. I'm sorry.
Mom, this is the most incredible thing
that I've ever built.
I mean, this carries.
It carries? Carries what?
Binary numbers.
It can hold up to a 20-digit figure.
Now wait a second. You said
it can carry, and it holds, too?
Both. It does both.
That's the whole point.
I mean, there isn't a circuit like this
in any of my books.
I've invented it.
Well, that's great.
That's great, Peter.
What are you going to call it?
I don't know.
Well, come on.
Everybody knows that when you invent
or discover something,
you get to name it, like... a napoleon.
- A what?
- You know, the French pastry.
It was named after Napoleon.
Napoleon invented pastry?
I thought he was a general.
Well, you can't fight battles
all the time.
He baked as a kind of relaxation.
Are you OK, Mom?
Listen. No more all-nighters, OK?
OK.
What is this called, anyway?
It's a peter, of course.
That is, if I ever get it finished.
OK, I'll let you skip it this time,
but only if you promise
not to work all night.
OK, I promise.
I promise. All right?
Grandma's going to be very disappointed.
But it's all right. I'll explain
that you're working on your peter.
(MACHINE BEEPING)
(BELL RINGS)
(DOOR BUZZING)
There's someone at the front door. Yes.
Between 11:00 and 12:00,
Thursday, right?
OK, fine. Bye.
Kate, good to see you.
Mary is on vacation,
so I have to be my own receptionist.
How am I doing?
I hope you won't keep me waiting today.
I want to get to the museum early.
I have to be at lunch by 12:30
with Mike and his mother.
No waiting, go right in.
The doctor will be with you shortly.
So, what's happening?
My mother's driving me crazy as usual.
Did you talk to her?
Mm-hm.
She's hinting around
about surprising me for my birthday.
She's going to come up from Florida,
is she?
That's her surprise.
How do you feel about seeing her?
Well, I feel...
...I should want to see her.
It's been six months
since we've been down there,
but... she'll just ruin my birthday.
And it's my day, not hers.
Well, now, think.
What are our options?
I could make up an excuse
and tell her not to come.
Mm-hm.
No, I can't do that.
And let's not forget,
it's supposed to be a surprise.
Anyway, it's not her.
It's just...
I don't feel up to it,
or her or anything.
How are things going with Mike?
- Fine.
- Good.
No, they're not fine.
What a dumb word that is.
He gave me one of his wham-bang
specials this morning,
and I'm mad at him.
Isn't that right? Shouldn't I be mad?
Yeah. Did you tell him?
- What?
- That you were mad at him.
Of course not.
I moaned with pleasure at his touch.
Isn’t that what every man wants?
I don't know. Is it?
Don't start that stuff with me.
Don't you think you'd feel better
if you snapped at Mike instead of me?
Think about where your anger is going.
I'm sorry.
Stop apologizing
and tell Mike he makes you mad.
Tell him he stinks in bed?
Does he?
- Yes.
- Then tell him.
Maybe there's something wrong with me.
There's nothing wrong with you.
Do you find me attractive?
Of course.
Would you want to sleep with me?
Yes.
Then why don't you?
Because I love my wife,
and sleeping with you isn't worth
jeopardizing my marriage.
Is it worth it to you
to jeopardize yours?
I don't know.
(WOMAN GIGGLING)
WOMAN: Come on, look at the pictures.
[MAN] This is so boring. Come on.
[WOMAN] Look at the pictures.
That's what we came here for.
Hi.
First time here?
[WOMAN] Stop it.
Cut it out.
GIRL: Mommy.
Mommy.
Now you stop that. I told you
to stand and be still and I meant it.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have been
so rude. Thank you for picking up...
(MOANING)
(KATE SCREAMING)
(HORN HONKING)
(PHONE RINGING)
(COMMENTATOR CHATTERING ON TV)
Hello?
Who is this?
(WHISPERING) It's not polite to stare.
(GASPS)
(KATE SCREAMING)
No.
No. No.
(KATE SCREAMING)
So you really think Auditron's going up?
Well, I got it from a very good source.
(KATE SCREAMING)
- Double, huh?
- You didn't hear it from me.
You know what? I'm going to give
my broker a little call.
- Jesus.
- Well, what about...?
(MOUTHING WORDS) Oh, my...
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
No, wait! Help!
Please, you don't understand!
Please, call the police! Wait!
Please, call the police!
Call the police!
Somebody call the police!
(ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPS)
Dr. Elliott, this is Lou Freeman.
I'm still in Chicago.
I won't be back in time
for our appointment on Friday.
I'll give you a call on Monday, OK?
(ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPS)
Robert, call George.
I'll be home over the weekend.
(ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPS)
(MAN WHISPERING) This is Bobbi.
You won't see me anymore,
so I'm going to have a little session
with your machine.
Doctor, I'm so unhappy.
I'm a girl inside this man's body,
and you're not helping me to get out.
So I got a new shrink.
Levy's his name,
and he's going to sign the papers
so I can get my operation.
I borrowed your razor and...
Well, you'll read all about it.
Some blonde bitch saw me,
but I'll get her.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Remember, if he calls you...
...you better tell Levy I'm OK.
- Don't make me be a bad girl again.
- (PHONE CLICKS)
(ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPS)
WOMAN: Yes, Dr. Elliott,
this is Mrs. Peters.
I just wanted to confirm our appointment
for tomorrow. Two o'clock, right?
MAN: This is Detective Marino
from the 13th Precinct.
One of your patients, Kate Miller,
was killed tonight.
I wonder if you'd stop down
at the precinct and ask for me.
I got some questions
I think you can help me with.
Are you sure?
Mm-hm.
OK.
Positive ID.
Hey, Eddie. Listen, I want
you to take this over to the lab
- and get some pictures made of it.
- Yeah.
- Keep an eye on her.
- Right.
- Detective Marino?
- OK.
- Yeah.
- I'm Dr. Elliott.
Oh, Doctor.
Listen, would you have a seat outside
my office in the corner over there.
- I'll be right with you.
- All right.
So give me three copies...
Why don't you let go of me, will you?
Are you Kate Miller's son?
I'm Dr. Elliott, your mother's doctor.
Why do you have to be here?
I made Mike bring me.
He's identifying the...
My mom wouldn't be dead
if I had gone with her.
You shouldn't feel responsible
for your mother's death.
If you talk about it,
I might be able to help.
Do you know who killed her?
- No.
- Then you can't help, can you?
Not now maybe.
But later, if you want someone
to talk to about all this.
- Ask your father to call...
- No, he's not my father.
My father was killed in Vietnam.
Take this.
You can call me any time.
I'm always there all day long.
I'm usually there...
OK, Doctor, let's talk in here.
Call me.
MARINO: She was picked up by Lockman
at the museum.
She spent the afternoon at his place
and was chopped up in the elevator
on the way out.
That girl out there saw the murderer.
ELLIOTT: That's terrible.
- Do you know who it is?
- Some broad.
- A woman?
- Yeah.
Miss Blake didn't get
a great look at her face
because she had on these big sunglasses.
Is there anything I can do to help?
Yeah. When you spoke with Mrs. Miller...
...did she say
she was going to meet anybody?
No.
Did she leave your office
with anybody?
No.
What was she seeing you for?
Nothing too serious. She had
some problems with her marriage,
and I was helping her work them out.
What kind of problems?
Are you married, Detective Marino?
- Yeah.
- Children?
Two sons.
When was the last time
you had intercourse with your wife?
Now what the fuck is it to you?
That's exactly how I feel about
your questions concerning Mrs. Miller.
Hey, look, Doctor,
we got a brutally murdered woman here,
who passed the point
of being embarrassed
by anything you might tell me.
I guess you're right.
I'm sorry,
but I'm not used to discussing
a patient's case with outsiders.
I'm not an outsider. I'm a cop.
Now, let's make it easy for you.
Was she looking to get killed?
- You mean, was she suicidal?
- Yeah.
- No.
So why did she pick up
this Lockman character?
- He could've been a killer.
- But he wasn't.
Yeah, but the next guy might have been.
You know, if at first you don't succeed.
Do you think she wanted to get killed?
Don't you? Look.
We got some hot-pants broad
cruising around for some action.
The guy she picked up went down on her
in a cab, for Christ's sake.
I got a blow-by-blow description
from the cabby.
After she finishes with him,
she comes on to some weirdo
in the elevator?
Hey. There's all kinds of ways
to get killed in this city,
if you're looking for it.
Well... Yes, she did have a problem
about her sexual worth.
And this morning she asked me
if I was attracted to her.
Yeah, but you're not a psycho.
You do know something, though,
don't you, Doc?
Yes, of course.
I do some work at Bellevue.
Could she have met one of these nuts
at your office?
I mean, some kind of weirdo she could've
turned on that might have followed her?
The term we use, Detective Marino,
is not "weirdo,"
but a person
suffering from emotional dysfunction
and a problem of maladaption.
And they never come to my office.
Are you sure?
How about a new patient?
I mean, how do you know
how nuts they are until you see them?
That's possible,
but it's hardly likely...
Doctor.
You're not protecting
one of your patients now, are you?
Absolutely not.
Well, Doc,
you've got to look at it my way.
See, we got no leads,
except a witness out there
who maybe should take a look
at all your patients
that were around that morning.
And that way, I can be absolutely sure
that my weirdo isn't your
"person suffering
from emotional dysfunctions
and problems of maladaption."
MIKE: Peter, come on, let's go home.
MARINO: Excuse me.
OK, Doctor.
I'm sorry you're not more cooperative,
which means that
I'm just going to have to waste some
time in getting a court order
to check out your appointment book.
I'm sorry, too.
But I feel I must protect
the confidentiality of my patients.
Of course, we're just two professionals
doing our job.
It's too bad we can't work together.
Come on.
Thank you very much for your help.
I'll be in touch.
WOMAN: Yes, thank you for waiting.
This is the answering service.
- Would you care to leave a message?
- Yes, I would.
- This is Dr. Elliott.
- How do you spell that?
E-L-L-I-O-T-T.
What is the message?
Would you please say
that I would very much like to see her,
and could she call me at my office.
So, Miss Blake.
Are you still living
at 93 Nassau Street?
That's right.
Tell me, how did you happen to be
in that building
that Mrs. Miller was killed in?
I was visiting a friend.
And who was that?
Well... it's sort of embarrassing.
I'd really rather not say.
Why?
He's married.
What kind of building is this?
Everybody's getting laid after lunch.
I didn't say I was "getting laid,"
to use your expression.
What's the matter?
- I'm a little crude for you?
- That's right.
Look, Miss Blake, let's cut this shit.
I got all the dope on you right here.
Does this look familiar? Let me see.
March 5th. Charge: disorderly conduct,
solicitation
for the purpose of prostitution.
Arresting Officer: Duram.
Apprehended at the Park Avenue Hotel.
Classy arrest.
- Thank you.
- Let's face it, you're a whore.
A Park Avenue whore,
but you're still a whore.
Now, who were you fucking?
Fuck you.
No, fuck you.
You're no witness.
You're a suspect.
What are you talking about?
We got a murder weapon
with your prints on it.
That's bullshit.
Why would I want to kill her?
You were there with the razor.
You tell me.
I told you. There was a blonde woman
in the elevator...
Yeah, except nobody else saw
this blonde woman
enter or leave the building.
You didn't notice
if she had wings, did you?
She was in the elevator. I saw her.
So, what were you doing there?
- I had a job.
- Who?
You want me to get in trouble,
don't you?
- You are in trouble.
- Hey, I didn't kill her.
So who were you fucking?
Ted, I didn't get his last name.
He's from out of town.
Well, that's great.
Yeah, Ted from out of town.
That's almost as good
as the blonde from the elevator.
It's true.
He was standing right behind me.
He saw the elevator doors open
and that...
...woman inside all cut up and bleeding.
I know all about Mrs. Miller.
We got her downstairs.
But what about this blonde?
Did he see her, too?
I don't know.
Well, look, Miss... Miss Blake.
You're going to save me a lot of trouble
by finding this Ted from out of town
and getting him in town
and downtown and in here
to sign this statement as to exactly
what he saw and when he saw it.
How the hell am I supposed to know
where he is?
Well, if you can't find him,
I sure can't.
And anyway, you got a lot better
motivation than I do: your ass.
Now, get the hell out of here.
I'm giving you 48 hours.
And don't try to blow town.
I'll be keeping tabs on you.
Norma? Liz.
Where the hell have you been?
I've been trying to get you all day.
Ted was terrific.
That's why I'm calling.
I'd like to see him again.
When's he coming back?
Two weeks?
That's no good.
Do you have a number for him?
I'd like to give him a call.
What do you mean, your escort service
doesn't give out numbers?
I want to talk to him.
Trouble? No, I'm not in any trouble.
I just want to talk to the guy.
OK.
OK, thanks!
Thanks for nothing.
BOBBI: You're just never in.
I've been out myself,
running down that nosy bitch.
I found out where she lives,
so I'm just going to wait right here
until she shows her face.
And then I'm going to cut
those spying eyes out.
What were you calling me about, anyway?
It wouldn't be about that murder
I read about in the papers.
Hell of a way to lose a patient.
But you shouldn't try to fuck them, Doc.
Hi, Max. It's Liz.
Look, I want to buy 60 shares
of Auditron. What does it sell for?
BOBBI: I'm glad I took care
of that cock-teaser.
$15.60 a share?
You would've done
the same thing yourself.
- That's $936... Hold it a minute, Max.
- (PHONE RINGING)
I guess that's why I used your razor.
- Hello.
- But don't worry about it, Doc.
- Hi, Norma.
- Just call the police...
- I'm sorry about yesterday.
- ...lost-and-found department.
Yes, I know, I was a bad girl.
Remember, if Levy calls...
Tonight?
- ...tell him I'm OK.
- No, I really can't.
Norma, hold on just a minute.
I'm talking to my mother.
- Max, when do you need money?
- That's funny.
- No, I don't want to sell anything.
- Isn’t it?
Hold it, Max.
Norma, do you think this guy
might go for $500?
Great.
Hold on just a minute.
I'm going to say goodbye to my mother.
OK, Max, I got the money.
I'll have it for you tomorrow.
OK. OK.
Hi, Norma.
Do you think you could put together
a coffee break and a hot lunch,
for tomorrow?
Yeah, I need $1, 000
for my mother's operation.
No, it's nothing serious.
I'm sure she'll be fine.
- Great. Now, what time tonight?
- DONAHUE ON TV: It's been three
to four years since your surgery.
- 8:30. Where?
- I want to show a picture, prior to...
- OK, anything special?
- WOMAN ON TV: Where'd you find that?
DONAHUE: Actually we stole it from
People magazine, which has an article.
Thank God straight fucks
are still in style.
This is Nancy Hart, the transsexual.
- Just in from Cleveland.
- Isn’t that something?
- I'll be there.
- You were a war correspondent?
Among other things.
And a foreign correspondent
in the Middle East. And...
...I did a lot of police reporting,
and I dove on Spanish treasure wrecks.
DONAHUE: You did a lot
of macho things, then?
This is very common among transsexuals.
You find...
When I speak of transsexuals,
I tend to speak of male to female
because there are a whole lot of more
of them than going the other way.
And an awful lot of them
have real macho backgrounds.
I know a police captain, a West Pointer,
a couple of fighter pilots.
They all, you know,
most of them tried real hard.
You were married twice?
You are also the father
of three children.
So, you enjoyed a...
I don't want to say normal, I guess
that's a prejudicial way to put it,
but you enjoyed the traditional role
of father.
You fathered three children,
and you have engaged in
at least two heterosexual relationships.
More than that.
I've always been a devout heterosexual.
Cleveland?
Excuse me?
Room 331,
you're the guy from Cleveland, right?
Three-thirty-one. I'm from Cleveland.
Well, hi.
I'm Liz from the escort service.
You're kidding?
- It's me.
- Well, hi.
Yeah, I'm glad to meet you.
Well, are you going to pump me dry here
or invite me in?
I'm sorry, come in.
You know, could I get you anything...?
93 Nassau Street.
Well, come on, let's go.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Look, forget that address
I just gave you.
Drop me at Columbus Circle.
Could you help me out?
Someone's following me.
This is Dr. Elliott again.
Did Bobbi pick up my messages yet?
- WOMAN: Yes, she has.
- She did?
- Yes, she did.
- When?
I'm sorry. I wouldn't know.
Could you give her
another message, please?
- Yes. Go ahead.
- Yeah.
It is urgent that I see her.
I will be in my office all tonight
and after 5:00 tomorrow.
What's the going rate on running lights?
(CAR HORN HONKING)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
Did I lose her?
You're doing swell, just swell.
But she's still coming.
Look, I didn't deliver, so why don't you
let me take you to dinner instead?
- All right, you got a date.
- OK.
- Look, I gotta go.
- OK. Listen, I'll give you a call.
Yeah, call me.
Excuse me.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
- (HORN HONKING)
- Get out of the way!
It's a free country!
He nearly clipped me!
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ON BOOMBOX)
Keeps pushing me.
Do you know her?
Hey, lady, what you looking for?
A train.
They still stop here, don't they?
Yeah, they stop here.
They stop down there, too.
Am I bothering you?
- No, you ain't bothering me.
- Good.
But you're bothering me.
She's bothering you, Sonny?
Yeah, that's right,
this bitch is bothering me.
- What are you going to do about it?
- I'm going to break her fucking ass.
MAN: Hey, why break it
when we can fuck it first?
Hey, lady, where you going?
I don't want to crowd you guys.
Why are you down here
if you didn't want to crowd us?
Give me a break.
Hey, man, don't let her get away!
Get after her!
Come on, man.
Come on, catch her, man.
Shit! Get out of the way!
Take it easy, lady,
this ain't the rush hour.
Where the fuck are you guys
when somebody needs you?
I was almost attacked.
- When?
- Right here, now, by those punks.
I don't see nothing.
Well, they were right here.
I thought you said you were attacked...
There are, but there's this blonde
that's been following...
Oh, forget it.
(SHOUTING)
(SCREAMING)
Let's get the fuck out of here!
The blonde must be
one of Elliott's patients.
I was unloading my camera
when I saw her come out of his office
and I followed her to you.
What was that stuff you sprayed on her?
It's a kind of Mace I made at home.
It's a pretty simple compound
of sodium...
Save the Mr. Wizard lecture,
I wouldn't know sodium from Adam.
It sure worked.
It's temporary blindness.
It only lasts about ten seconds.
Saved my life.
I know.
I wish I had saved Mom's.
You liked your mom a lot, didn't you?
Yeah.
I miss her.
You want some more Coke?
Yeah. Yeah, thank you.
How do you like my painting?
It's... very nice.
I bought it a couple of years ago
for $500.
It's really a great investment.
I mean, ten years from now,
it could be worth... a million dollars.
More if the artist dies, of course.
- Good luck with it.
- Thanks.
Doesn't your father wonder
where you are?
He's not my father. He's my stepfather.
I told him I am staying at my friend
Paul's, and he'll cover for me.
I'll take you home tomorrow.
I don't want to go home.
Miss Blake, I've got some pictures...
Call me Liz, OK?
Liz, I've got some pictures
of that blonde
from a camera I hid
outside Elliott's office.
Now, we gotta get in, get Elliott's
appointment book, and get her name.
That's what the police are for.
Come on, let's talk to Marino.
Fine, you talk to Marino.
I'm going to find out the blonde's name.
Who do you think you are, Superman?
You're just a kid, for God's sake.
Yeah, I'm the kid that saved your life.
All right, look,
let me talk to Marino.
If he cops out, then I'll help you.
OK, but you can't mention my name.
Mike would kill me.
I'm supposed to be...
studying for a French exam.
Well, your friend's covering
for you tonight, right?
Well, I'm your friend, too,
and I'll be the best cover you ever had.
OK.
You sure you going to be OK here?
Fine.
Well... Here you go.
- Good night.
Hey, Marino, I gotta talk to you.
- Mr. Out-of-Town turn up?
- No.
Then you better send
for your overnight bags.
Hey, come on,
you know I didn't kill that woman.
You're still my best bet.
For your information,
she tried to kill me last night.
Really?
Is that supposed to be concern
in your voice?
I take a professional interest
in our citizens knocking each other off.
Where did this happen?
She followed me from the Sheraton
into the subway.
I thought I lost her,
but she was waiting when I got home.
- She tried to slash me.
- Any witnesses to this one?
- Yes.
- Who?
- I can't tell you.
- Out of town again?
No, I just promised
I wouldn't say anything.
You know, this has
a familiar ring to it.
Look, Marino, I'm not interested
in your wiseass remarks.
Someone's trying to kill me,
and I need help.
I'll help you. I got a nice cell.
You'll be very safe in it.
Hey, Eddie.
Hey, wait a minute. Look.
I know the murderer is
one of Elliott's patients.
- How do you know that?
- Because she came out of his office.
Did you see her?
Well, no, not exactly.
But I know she came out.
You got to get in there,
get his appointment book.
Her name's got to be in it.
I hope you make a better hooker
than you do a detective.
I thought about Elliott's appointment
book a long time ago.
- So?
- So...
You can’t just walk into some shrink's
joint and start going through his books.
You need a search warrant.
And judges take a long time
before they let you start snooping
around some shrink's office.
Of course, that wouldn't prevent
a paranoid murder suspect
from breaking in.
You know, searching for some evidence
to defend her case.
Oh, I get it.
You want me to break in for you.
I don't want you to do anything illegal.
You can quote me on that.
But I'm booking you tomorrow.
You got it? Tomorrow.
I'm Dr. Levy.
How do you do? I'm Dr. Elliott.
What can I do for you, Dr. Elliott?
You're seeing a patient of mine.
That's right.
I believe she's dangerous.
Really? In what way?
She's causing me trouble
because I wouldn't approve
her sex-change operation.
What kind of trouble has she caused you?
She's threatened me several times
over the phone.
- She also stole my razor.
- Why would she do that?
Doctor, did you read about the woman
who was slashed to death in an elevator?
It was on the front page,
I could hardly miss...
Kate Miller, the victim, was my patient.
You don't think that Bobbi
had anything to do with that?
My razor's gone.
Kate Miller was killed with a razor.
Nobody else could have taken it?
Doctor, I am not paranoid.
Bobbi has threatened me over the phone.
She said she was going to hurt me.
My patient was slashed to death,
and my razor's gone.
Now you don't have to be a detective
to figure it out, do you?
Come with me, and...
we'll talk to the police.
I've already been to the police.
But I didn't tell them about Bobbi.
I wanted to talk to her first.
I wanted to be absolutely sure
that it was her.
But she wouldn't return my calls.
I was hoping you'd be able to help.
Yes, I'll help.
I'll talk to her.
If I agree with your diagnosis,
we'll go to the police.
Thank you.
Please let me know what happens.
Do you know why Bobbi came to see me
in the first place?
No.
Why don't we go to my office,
and we'll try to get in touch with her.
I am late for an appointment now.
Why don't you call me at my office
when you've reached her.
All right.
You sure you'll be at your office?
Yes, I'm sure.
I'll call you there.
Peter Miller, I left some Super-8 film.
There's four dollars there.
PETER: I timed Elliott's patients
coming out of his office,
and the fastest was eight seconds.
So I set my camera to go off
every four seconds
so I'd be sure to get a good shot
of everybody.
- That's her.
- LIZ: She must be his last appointment.
We got to get a look in that book.
Yeah, I know. Marino wants it, too.
Only, I can get it for him faster.
No legal red tape, just my ass.
Look, I'll get it, nobody cares about
my ass. I'm just a grief-struck kid.
Yeah, but what a kid.
Okay, I got an idea.
It was very nice of you to see...
It was nice of you to see me so soon.
I try to keep my nights open
for returning phone calls
or in case a patient
needs some extra help.
I was worried about you.
You've had a terrible experience.
I know.
I didn't realize...
But I've been having
these terrible nightmares.
What were they about?
Well...
I have to get a cigarette.
I'm in this house that I've never
been to before, visiting a friend.
He's not there.
I'm watching TV...
and the doorbell rings.
It's a man.
He's big, dark.
He says his car broke down,
and he needs to use the phone.
I believe him and let him in...
...although I know something's wrong.
He closes the door, locks it,
and takes out a razor.
He says he's not going to hurt me.
Then he tells me...
what he's going to do to me...
...and how much I'm going to like it.
All the time he's talking,
I can see the bulge in his pants.
He orders me to strip.
I do it,
keeping one eye on the razor.
He drops his pants...
...forces me down, on my stomach.
He spreads my legs,
kneels down behind me...
...and rests the cold blade.
Forcing it.
I'm sorry.
What's the matter?
It's just so dirty.
Why do you say that?
Look, I know what dirty is,
and this is dirty.
Well, why don't you just talk about it?
I'm sure it's not as bad as you think.
It's very bad.
And you're talking to an expert on bad.
Oh, really?
Now what makes you such an expert?
Because I'm a hooker.
Ah.
And I have done most of the bad things
you just read about.
Do you like doing these things?
- Sometimes.
- What do you like about it?
I like to turn men on.
I must do a pretty good job
because they pay me a lot.
Do you ever have any sex
that's not paid for?
Is that a proposal?
No. It...
It's what we psychiatrists call
a question.
Yes.
"Yes" what?
Yes, I do. For men that turn me on.
What sort of men turn you on?
Mature, doctorly type.
Like you.
Are you sexually attracted to me?
Yes. Are you?
- Attracted to you?
- Mm-hm.
Yes.
But then,
this isn't a social visit, is it?
You've come here for help and my job
is to offer you emotional assistance.
How about some sexual assistance?
Do you want to fuck me?
- Oh, yes.
- Well, why don't you?
- Because I'm a doctor and...
- Fucked a lot of doctors.
- And I'm married.
- Fucked a lot of them, too.
Don't you think
we're getting off the point?
Do you mind if I take off my coat?
No.
(PANTS)
And the rest, too?
Now, why would you want to do
a thing like that?
Well, because of the size of that cock
in your pants.
I don't think you're so married.
Well?
What do you think?
I think you're a very attractive woman.
Would you like to touch me?
Yes and no. Yes, because I'm...
Well, why don't you?
I told you why.
That's right. You're a married doctor.
I remember now.
- I think you're full of shit.
- You do?
Just because I happen to have
personal and professional ethics?
Look, Doc, I think you're kind of shy.
So... I'm going to go powder my nose
and when I come back,
I hope to find your clothes
right next to mine.
And if not, we can just get back
to the mind-fuck.
(GRUNTS)
Dr. Elliott?
You really are shy, aren't you?
- Liz!
- (BANGING)
(PETER SHOUTING)
Behind you, Liz!
(GUNSHOT)
(SOBBING)
So you had me followed?
That's right.
You've met Betty Luce, one of our best
young police... persons.
When I told you I was attacked
on the subway, you thought I was nuts.
Well, Detective Luce told me
she lost you at Columbus Circle.
I didn't figure there was another blonde
following you. I mean, who would?
Yeah, and you wrote me off as a girl
with an overactive imagination.
Yeah, something like that.
- And she followed me to Elliott's.
- That's right.
Thank God.
What's wrong with that guy, anyway?
- He was a transsexual.
- What?
A transsexual.
About to make the final step, but his
male side couldn't let him do it.
MARINO: Male side?
There was Dr. Elliott,
and there was Bobbi.
Bobbi came to me
to get psychiatric approval
for a sex-reassignment operation.
I thought he was unstable,
and Elliott confirmed my diagnosis.
Opposite sexes inhabiting the same body.
The sex-change operation
was to resolve the conflict.
But as much as Bobbi tried to get it,
Elliott blocked it.
So Bobbi got even.
MARINO: By killing Mrs. Miller.
Yes, she aroused Elliott,
just as you did, Miss Blake.
You mean, when Elliott got turned on,
Bobbi took over?
Yes. It was like Bobbi's red alert.
Elliott's penis became erect
and Bobbi took control,
trying to kill anyone
that made Elliott masculinely sexual.
When Elliott came to my office,
it was the first time
I saw Bobbi's masculine self.
When he told me that he thought
Bobbi had killed Mrs. Miller,
he was confessing himself.
I immediately called Detective Marino.
So why the hell didn't you stop me
from going to Elliott's?
Why? Because I was at a football game
with my kids, that's why.
By the time I spoke with Dr. Levy,
you were already over there.
So you never really thought
I killed Mrs. Miller?
No. But I had to get into Elliott's
office to find out which weirdo did,
so I pressed you into service.
Are you kidding?
So I had Miss Luce there tailing you
to make sure
you didn't get into too much trouble.
Thanks.
Well, it's always wonderful
to be of some assistance to the police.
Are you kidding?
So what's going to happen to Elliott?
Well?
There's some men and women who think
they're born in the wrong body.
They're called transsexuals.
And all they want to do
is have their sex changed.
How do you do that?
Well, if you're a man
that wants to become a woman,
you take female hormones.
What do they do?
Well, your skin softens, you grow
breasts, and you don't get hard anymore.
Great.
You sure you want to know about this?
Yeah. It's giving me some wonderful
new ideas for a science project.
Instead of building a computer,
I could build a woman... out of me.
Great idea. In that case,
I'll give you all the details.
The next step is surgery.
Let me see if I can remember
the exact word that Levy told me.
Oh, yeah, a penectomy.
What's that?
You know, when they take your penis
and slice it down the middle.
Yeah, that's what I thought it was.
Then...
...castration...
...plastic reconstruction and
the formation of an artificial vagina.
A vaginoplasty, to those in the know.
And I thought Elliott
just put on a dress.
He did. And a wig, too.
But you see, that's no good in bed,
when you gotta take everything off.
What's going to happen to him now?
Well, first he has to recover
from the gun wound,
and then if he's ever sane enough
to get out of Bellevue, they'll try him.
And guess who's the star witness.
You.
Right. Something
I'm really looking forward to.
Well, I think I'm going to stick
to my computer.
That sounds like a very good idea.
Look, Liz...
I gotta get home and get to work.
I'm going to miss having you on my tail.
It made me feel kind of safe.
Look, you want to come home with me?
I'd love the company.
Wouldn't Mike mind?
Well, Mike's out of town
on a business trip.
We got plenty of room.
Great. I could sure use the vacation.
Good. I'll get the check.
(NURSE'S SHOES SQUEAKING)
(GASPS)
(ALL CHEERING)
(HEAVY BREATHING)
(SHOES SQUEAKING)
(MACHINE BEEPING)
(DOOR CREAKING)
(SHOE SQUEAKS)
(SHOES SQUEAKING)
(GASPS)
(SCREAMING)