- Taylor!
- Tangina.
Over here!
I think we finally found the core.
We dug under the swimming pool.
This is directly below the old graveyard.
There's a presence.
There's something terrible.
Too much power.
I've seen it in dreams.
What is it?
Where's the family now?
- Did you make that?
- Wait a second.
- Inch and a half. I'll try this against her arm.
- It's too hot on the kids.
Okay.
Ready.
You'd be lucky
if your teeth don't fall out from that.
Did you think that sandwich up
all by yourself?
- No. Grandma helped.
- What a fib!
Grab me the red yarn out of my basket,
will you, honey?
- E. Buzz!
- That's disgusting.
Stop!
E. Buzz, down!
Maybe E. Buzz wants some mustard, Robbie.
E. Buzz, get down.
I'll say "down,"
and then he'll get down. Down!
He really listens to you.
Honey, now could you get me
the yellow yarn?
Rob, very nice to share with E. Buzz.
E. Buzz knows how to share with Robbie.
E. Buzz, get down.
Thank you, angel.
- Come on, Guerrero! Hit it out of the park!
- Yeah, hit it!
... and has struck out...
Dad, can't we get a TV like everybody else?
We can't get a TV.
Great, I'll just have to grow up retarded.
Come on, Rob, kids don't grow up retardo
because of lack of television.
No, Dad. I didn't see it.
You got to use your imagination, son.
Come on. Let's test this baby out.
God!
How am I gonna sell this
to innocent housewives?
I don't know, Dad.
What are you drawing, honey?
Don't know. Stuff.
You draw very well.
Do you want to be an artist
when you grow up?
Maybe. Don't want to grow up much.
How come?
Probably not much fun.
Sure it is.
I've loved every age I've been.
They all have their blessings.
When I was your age...
I learned that I could do things
that other folks couldn't.
Like what kind of things?
I just knew things.
I didn't know how I knew, but I did.
Like what?
Once, my mother lost her bracelet...
and I knew where it was.
Two miles from our house,
in a place that I'd never been.
Now...
do you ever know things...
and can't explain why?
Yes?
Yes.
Darling...
that's a very special gift that you and I have.
It's nothing to be scared of.
Will it help me be a ballerina?
Sure it will.
Whatever you dream, you can be.
- They denied our claim again!
- What?
We shouldn't have told them
that the house vanished into thin air.
That's what I'm talking about.
They say that if the house disappeared,
then it's only missing.
Missing?
Do they think this house
is going to return, or something?
It's been a year.
The house is not coming back.
I got a gut feeling, Diane,
I'm positive about that.
I know that, Steven.
You tell them that...
No, I'm gonna fill out the fourth claim.
What are we going to claim this time?
Act of God? Housenapping?
We are almost broke.
Okay, we're broke, but we're not starving.
But I don't happen to like
having to live off my mother.
I think that we deserve a house of our own
again, someday.
Honey, gosh.
That's the difference between you and me.
I am into downward mobility.
I'm not settling for it. I'm into it.
I like getting out and meeting those...
I like selling vacuums.
I like carrying the pipes, the apparatus
and my little demo case.
Let's get the kids up,
and we'll paint the car different colors...
kind of Day-Glo, like we used to do
when we were kinda freaky.
The freaky Freelings on the road again!
You know, the family
whose house disappeared!
Watch them find it, Diane.
I'm not gonna get upset about this.
But I'm writing them back...
and when I sign that letter,
I'm signing, "Mr. President."
Steven, you are wacko!
You were never a hippie.
You were always into making money.
You only painted your van Day-Glo colors
and grew your hair long...
to impress Cookie Gurnich.
Cookie? Necki necka...
Don't tell me what Cookie can do.
I hated you then.
I always knew how to make up to you.
Didn't I?
- I don't remember.
- Sure you do.
- I do not.
- Come on.
I don't. You'd sing that stupid song.
Not in the shadow of Cookie.
Don't even try it. It's not working.
Don't sing that song.
I've never forgiven you for Cookie Gurnich.
It's...
Did Cookie really crumble?
Am I interrupting again?
Hi.
Hi, pumpkin.
Mom, I'm going to be a ballerina.
- Great.
- Not tonight, honey.
- Bedtime. Say goodnight, Mom.
- Goodnight, honey.
- Let's sleep in our own bed tonight.
- Okay.
Come on, Dodgers!
Come on, let's go.
Let's go, come on.
Robbie?
Mom, I've talked to the kittens.
They want to come home with us.
No, sweetheart, E. Buzz would get upset.
- Robbie, come on.
- Why?
He's not used to having
other pets around. Robert!
How would you like it
if I brought home a new baby?
That's even better than a kitten.
Mom, I have a great idea.
We are not buying a television set.
A present for Dad, it's a bargain.
Mom!
Mom, where are you?
Robbie!
Hi.
Are you lost, sweetheart?
Are you afraid, honey?
Why don't you come with me?
No.
All right.
I'll sing you a song...
till your mommy comes back.
- I'd like to purchase this.
- That's $10.26 plus tax.
Where's Carol Anne?
- I don't know.
- She was just here.
Carol Anne?
Baby!
Honey, what happened?
- Did you get lost?
- I don't know.
- Thank you.
- My pleasure.
Such a lovely child.
Thank you so much.
I'm sorry, honey.
We just stopped into a shop.
I thought you were right there with us.
Honey, what is it?
Mom, I want to go home.
- They're very unusual.
- They're just drawings.
Ugly.
She can see colors with her hands.
Mama, we don't want to hear
that stuff, okay?
And we don't want Carol Anne to hear.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
How do you know what we should be
afraid of? You weren't there.
Why don't you tell me?
- It might help.
- I did tell you.
- Not everything.
- I don't remember everything.
Try.
First the canary died.
And then the chairs went all funny...
and I thought it was kind of exciting.
And then...
Carol Anne was gone.
And I...
Honey, what is it?
Nothing.
I just want to get on with our lives. It's over.
Diane.
You've got to go unafraid into this life.
Don't instill fear into that child,
who is truly gifted...
- and filled with knowledge.
- I don't want her to be gifted!
- You don't mean that.
- I'm going to bed, goodnight.
I'll be there if you need me.
I'll be good.
I love you, too.
Goodnight, Grandma.
- She knew you loved her so much.
- Lf I just had one more day.
What's wrong?
Honey...
Grandma passed away last night.
Grandma died?
Come here, baby.
It's all right, Mom.
Mom.
You always made me feel so safe.
I love you so much.
Mom?
Can you put these on me,
so I can be a ballerina with wings?
Darling, you can be anything
you want to be.
Mama?
Hi. Grandma?
Do you have wings now?
My ballerina costume does.
Grammy?
Who are you?
I don't remember.
What?
Carol Anne, what's going on?
What are you doing?
Come on!
What is it?
Jesus! The kids.
- The kids!
- Kids!
Dad, Mom!
We're coming, Robbie!
Where are you?
They're back.
Don't panic!
Go, go!
- Who the hell are you?
- The name's Taylor.
Great. Good name. Come on, let's go.
Tangina Barrons sent me.
- Say hello to the magic munchkin.
- Steve, wait. Sent you for what?
There's no use running.
It'll find you.
You're better off here.
Let's go. You stay. We're gone.
Come on, kids.
You got me up at 4:00 in the morning
to tell me this?
You are a pack of trouble, girl.
Why are you messing around with that bum?
Because I like him.
Dad, are we going to have to move again?
I don't know.
- I'm going to think about it.
- Where can we go?
- Disneyland?
- Puke! Don't be such an infant!
Okay, what about Dunkin' Donuts?
Shut up, jerko.
Look. Here.
Go play the pinball machine.
Give some to your brother.
No.
Come on, I wanna play pinball.
Give the money to me.
- What are we gonna do?
- I don't know, I'm thinking.
We have to go somewhere.
We can't just drive around.
Mother, just don't you bring him
over to my house.
Waitress, check!
Listen, children,
you can't run from this thing.
It has made contact and will stop at nothing.
You've got to fight it head on.
Stay together.
Be loving.
Be brave.
Mama?
- I'm not your mother, lady.
- Elspeth, are you okay?
What happened?
You went funny.
It sounded like her. I don't understand.
Honey, you can't explain stuff like that.
It just happens.
I mean, there's no reason for it.
- What are you talking about?
- It doesn't matter, honey.
- What do you want?
- She told you the truth.
Who?
You mean, that...
Are you in cahoots with the lady in there?
I cahoot with no one.
Then why are you following us?
I came to help.
God, I mean, you don't understand.
We don't want your help.
We don't want anybody's help.
We want to be left alone!
Why did Tangina send you?
Why didn't she come herself?
It's my kind of job.
You know, maybe it's no coincidence.
This guy shows up...
things go kind of screwy. Get off my car!
Get in the car, Diane.
Get in the car, kids.
Wait a minute, let's listen to him.
Fine, you listen to him. I wanna go home.
Let's be sensible about this.
Sensible? What is sensible?
Honey, nobody can help us.
Let's just get in the car
and get the hell out of here!
And go where? It followed us here.
It'll follow us where we go.
We can't keep running.
Where are you from?
- From all over.
- This is Katrina.
Katrina?
- Hi, Katrina.
- What's that?
It's my medicine bag.
Charms.
See?
The house is okay? You're sure?
E. Buzz agrees. It's okay for now.
The dog agrees? That's terrific, isn't it?
Yes.
Your car.
Very angry.
I'll fix it.
Make it happy?
Okay.
I've read about these rain dances. I know.
I understand that.
We don't need rain.
I can't say that Steven fully trusts him yet.
You can't blame him.
Okay. Thanks, Tangina. We will.
'Bye.
Honey, she says he's okay.
I think we should give him a chance.
- Tangina says he's okay?
- Yeah.
- That's great.
- Keep an open mind.
This is bizarre.
I've got nothing against these people.
I got through most of the chapters.
I got some Indian in me, I think.
One-sixteenth, my mother
will never admit to it...
but, honey, what if this guy...
is, like, an escapee from the tribal asylum?
Mom, come look at this!
My God!
I don't believe it!
What are you doing?
Hi, Mom. I'm going to help
protect the family now.
Let me see.
- Come outside, Robbie.
- I'm a big guy now.
I'm still your mother.
Wait for me in the house.
Thanks, Mom.
He wants to be a man.
There are a lot of ways to be a man.
I'm not sure wearing claw marks
and war paint is one of them.
How would you know?
What?
You're not a man, are you?
Okay, I'm not a man.
But you're not a mother!
It is my job to do everything I can
to make my children part of a normal world.
A world of school, and friends, and lovers,
and families of their own, someday.
That's good.
Right, I know.
I hope that they'll learn
to forget all this soon.
They cannot learn by forgetting.
What would you have me do?
They're just children, for God's sake.
Children have fought wars.
They've built nations.
They are strong and have courage.
Don't treat them any less than that
because they're young.
Taylor!
Okay, Taylor.
You can stay in the house.
You can have my aura, spirits,
the ghosts, everything.
The whole cazaba,
but keep your hands off my car!
Okay? Hands off!
It's worse than it was before.
- Car's still angry?
- Angry?
That car is pissed!
Come on, Carol Anne. It's raining!
Come on! What's wrong?
Let's go.
Honey, come inside!
You're getting soaked! Come on, sweetie.
Can we help you?
Haven't I've seen you somewhere before?
That is possible!
I get around. I love getting around.
Love talking to people...
even on a rainy day.
Dog's shedding.
Hi!
Hi.
I saw you at the shopping mall.
Sure you did...
I remember your little angel, here.
Allow me to introduce myself.
Henry Kane.
Mom!
I got to tell you...
we've had enough
of door-to- door salesmen, if you don't mind.
Reverend Kane!
What I sell is free!
Mind if I come in and talk to you about it?
Mom, I don't feel well.
You know, I gotta...
Maybe we'll talk from here, all right?
Come inside, baby. I want to take
your temperature. Come on, Robert.
I'm glad we have this opportunity to talk...
with your family out of the way.
Because I believe you have a problem here.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I believe...
there's an Indian living here with you?
Taylor.
So that's what he calls himself now.
You are in danger!
What do you mean?
I'm with an organization...
whose concern is families like your own...
families in crisis...
that are preyed upon...
by charlatans and fake magic
and false solutions!
I don't expect you to believe me now...
but let me come in
and talk to you about this.
I don't know. This is crazy. This is nuts.
Please! Open your heart and your mind...
to what I'm saying.
He is dangerous!
I can see that he has a strong hold
on this family.
Who do your wife and children turn to...
with their problems?
They turn to him.
Now, don't they?
They don't trust you...
anymore.
What you fear...
is that you're not man enough...
to hold this family...
together.
How do you know?
Because...
I'm smart.
And I'm your friend.
And I know...
what you are thinking.
How?
Now...
let me in.
And let's talk about it.
Let me in!
You're my friend?
Now, before it's too late!
No.
You're gonna die in there! All of you!
You are gonna die!
Get the hell out of here!
Sorry to see...
you're still unconvinced.
A pleasure visiting with you.
You did good.
Who was that?
That was him.
Him?
What are you talking about?
He was testing your power.
He comes in many forms, but that was him.
Now you're hooked.
You're on the path of a warrior.
Hooked? Wait.
What are you talking about?
Your confrontation with him
was a drain on your power.
We don't have much time. We must prepare.
Prepare?
Oh, God.
Tequila. Ta kill ya!
You want a hit?
No. I used to drink. I had to give it up.
Bad dreams.
You see something?
No.
What are you doing?
Seeking power.
Me, too.
You feel like a leaf
at the mercy of the wind, don't you?
That's right. That's me.
Since the day you were born,
one way or another...
someone has been doing something to you.
I don't...
I don't think that's true.
They've been doing something to you
against your will.
And by now, you're feeling helpless...
like a leaf in the wind.
Taylor, it would help me out a lot
if you'd just say what's on your mind...
so I could understand you.
You understand me.
No matter how much
you like to feel sorry for yourself...
you have to change that.
I'm a warrior.
A warrior would rather be defeated and die...
than act against his nature.
That is the path you've chosen to take...
whether you know it or not.
You should assume full responsibility.
Responsibility for what?
Responsibility for everything...
everything in your world.
Come on, Robbie.
You're supposed to clean your braces
and come downstairs now.
Shut up, jerko! I'm doing it, okay?
Don't "okay" me!
You're a pest, you know that?
- Don't do that.
- I didn't do anything.
You're such an infant.
Ready? Where's Robbie?
He says he's coming.
Okay.
Kiss Katrina, too.
Goodnight, girls.
Rob, come on!
Goodnight, Daddy.
The telephone.
Hello?
Yes.
Okay. Dad, it's for you.
Maybe it's the insurance company...
with good news.
Hello?
Die!
Mom!
God!
- Stay here, baby.
- Robbie!
We're coming, Robbie!
Dad, help me!
Taylor! Help us!
Please!
Help!
Hold tight, Robbie!
The plug!
Get out!
Where the hell were you?
We're not safe here anymore,
my son almost dies, and you sit here!
I was protecting Carol Anne.
It's her he's after...
not Robbie, not you or Diane.
Carol Anne.
Why the hell won't you leave us alone?
Dad!
He's still here.
He feels she belongs to him.
But why?
I'm not sure...
but he's used to getting what he wants.
Taylor...
who is he?
What is he?
He's a man filled with a demon...
Iost in a dimension
that surrounds our world.
This entity believes
that his world and ours are the same.
Why doesn't he know he's dead?
Because he isn't.
How can that be?
Nothing really dies.
Like a caterpillar becomes a butterfly...
death only transforms us
into another state of being.
This man was evil.
His soul remains evil...
because he chooses not to see the light...
and pass on to a different consciousness.
How are we going to fight this thing?
Until we learn how to defeat him...
we do not let him win.
That's a hell of a plan. That's a lot of crap.
- I suppose you have a plan of your own.
- That's a lot of crap!
Listen. Don't come apart now.
This spirit is very clever.
He knows your strength is your love...
and he hates you for that.
He's been trying to pull this family apart...
and he will continue to try.
If he succeeds...
he will possess Carol Anne...
and destroy your spirit.
- Hi!
- Tangina!
Hi, Diane.
What are you doing here?
Sorry to come unannounced, sweetie,
but I need to speak with you.
I'm glad to see you.
Good, 'cause we're running out of time.
Below the old cemetery...
what seems to be a tomb
with many bodies in it...
directly below your house.
Who are they?
The researchers don't know
who these people were.
There are no marked graves.
There are, however,
records of a religious sect...
that mysteriously disappeared.
What happened?
Their spiritual leader was a medium...
who led his followers out to California
in the early 1800s...
to start a utopian society.
They disappeared near Cuesta Verde...
and were believed...
massacred by Indians.
This could be them.
This funny?
I love the health club, you know.
I'm just wondering
when I get the key to my locker.
Sense of humor is good.
You're going to need it.
The entity has revealed
his essence to you, his enemy.
Now that you've seen each other...
there'll be no mistakes.
Take this smoke.
Smoke...
make him one with power and knowledge.
Here is a photo of those people.
I think you should have a look at it.
I know this is hard for you, dear...
but I need your verification on something.
You see...
I don't really trust my instincts anymore.
Now, hold this one...
and tell me what you feel.
Oh, my God, I've seen him!
I thought so. Where?
Here! At the mall! At our house!
Who is he?
Just tell me what you feel.
What do you want me to do? Who is he?
I've consulted others.
They've told me things...
but they said you know more!
I don't know anything!
You do!
You traveled to a dimension
few people have ever traveled, to incarnate!
Your daughter is highly clairvoyant!
As was your mother, I suspect.
As you are as well!
Now tell me what you feel!
It is him. It's the preacher.
They're following him in death,
like they did in life.
Don't! No, please! Please don't!
It all makes sense now.
When you brought Carol Anne
back to this world...
his followers became restless...
because they had tasted
the light of her being...
her life force.
Now he wants her back.
This person is no longer human.
He is the beast.
You must take your family back
to Cuesta Verde.
What?
The evil spirit that is stalking you...
it knows who you are...
where you are, how to find you...
what your weaknesses are.
Your best bet is to confront him...
surprise him on his own ground.
But what about Diane and the kids?
They are your power...
and you are theirs.
Are things desperate?
What you see as desperate,
I see as inevitable.
I've done all I can.
I must be leaving you now.
I'll take you home.
Taylor's not here. That's all right.
We'll keep on going
just like we've been doing, as a family.
Son, you know, I've told you
about the helmet and eating...
I told you, I'm not hungry.
Miniature golf.
Tomorrow we can play some miniature golf!
We can get our putters...
How about bowling?
You like bowling, sweet pea.
Nature hike, Rob.
Brisk walk?
I know. The water slide.
We'll take E. Buzz, we'll put water wings
on him, and shove him down...
and laugh, won't we?
So, after Alice fell down the hole...
why'd she drink from that bottle?
Because it said, "Drink me" on it.
Were they going to capture her?
Take her someplace bad?
Yes, but Alice gets home
all right, remember?
Did she know why they wanted to hurt her?
I don't think so, honey.
'Cause I know.
You know what?
Why they're here.
Why, baby? Why are they here?
'Cause they don't know where else to go.
God!
God is in His holy temple
Hi, angel!
Are you okay, Dad?
Yeah.
I just want to give my little girl a hug.
Your mom and I would like to talk alone.
Go put on your nightie, honey.
What's going on, Steve?
Nothing. I just want us to be alone.
Carol Anne's upset.
Does that feel good?
I should dry her hair.
She's all right. She's safe.
Come on!
- Honey!
- Is that good?
Don't! Not now!
Why? When?
What do you mean?
I have needs, too!
It seems to me your needs
have been fulfilled by the bottle tonight!
Don't.
Are you accusing me of being drunk?
- I'm not accusing you of anything.
- You are.
- That's what you're thinking.
- I'm not!
I know you! That's what you're thinking!
Spare me.
You remember, just the other day...
when you were seven...
and you were helping your mommy
plant flowers in the garden?
You saw it clearly.
How the hell do you know that?
'Cause I am smart.
Mommy Jess... Don't cry.
- Shut up.
- Don't pout!
You think that all of our troubles...
are because of Carol Anne!
You wish Carol Anne
had never been given birth to!
You never wanted Carol Anne!
But you thought it!
You thought it, baby!
You thought about it!
You thought that? You thought it!
- Diane's had secrets!
- Don't!
Don't touch me!
I know you! I feel you!
What is wrong with you?
What is happening to you?
Why are you doing this?
Steven, stop it!
Stop it!
We want the angel!
The sweet pea!
Stop it!
I love you! Damn you!
He is in his holy temple!
Don't you know that?
I love you! Believe me, I love you!
God, leave me alone!
What is it?
What's happening to you?
- What's going on?
- Leave me alone.
What is it? What's the matter?
God!
God, what is it? What's the matter?
Oh, God!
Honey!
Wake up!
Kids, where are you?
Stay put! We'll find you!
Babies?
Oh, God!
I'll check in here. All right?
Babies, please answer me!
Are you in here?
Kids, please come!
Kids?
Robbie!
Carol Anne! Please!
Mom!
Baby, are you all right?
Diane?
- Where's Carol Anne?
- We can't find her. I don't know.
The garage!
- Carol Anne!
- Where are you?
Where are you? Honey?
Open the door, sweet pea!
Come on, honey, open the door!
Lift up the knob, sweetheart.
- Come on, honey, open the...
- What is it?
Sweetheart, that wasn't Daddy
in the bathroom. You know that.
Oh, baby!
Grab it!
Mom!
Dad, watch out!
Okay, Diane, get in the car!
Go, baby, go!
Open the door, Carol Anne.
- Steven, come on!
- Daddy, hurry!
Hurry!
Go!
Get us out! Go!
Dad, E. Buzz!
E. Buzz, get in!
Come on, E. Buzz, now get in!
Be a good boy!
Come on, E. Buzz, get in.
- Come on, Robbie!
- Close the door!
Dad, let's get out of here!
- Come on, move!
- Go.
- It won't move!
- Go!
It won't start!
Go! Please!
Look out!
Move, damn it!
Get going, Steven!
Hurry!
- Drive the car!
- Now, move!
Jesus!
We're going back
to Cuesta Verde, aren't we?
That's right.
But what about the kids?
Taylor said we go back as a family.
We go back together. That's all of us.
Do you believe him, Dad?
Honey, it was real smart of you
to hide in the car like that.
It wasn't my idea.
Taylor said it was the only safe place.
Dad, do you believe him?
I do believe him, son.
Tangina. Thank God.
I knew you'd be here,
so I had to be here, too.
We had to come.
I know.
But there are many dangers
you must consider, Steven.
- Are you okay, honey?
- Yeah, Mom. I'm okay.
Careful, honey.
Mom!
Honey, if you don't want
to go through with this...
we can leave here right now, okay?
I do want to go on.
I love you more than anything.
You always remember that, okay?
God, they're all...
They're all dying here! Oh, God!
They're all reaching out for help
that will never come.
All because they worship him.
Diane!
Carol Anne!
They are gone! They have crossed over!
Now we have to get them back,
and you know how. Please!
Taylor!
Dad!
Taylor, where are they?
I see her!
This is the way in.
The entity is with them.
They're in grave danger.
Hold on to each other.
When you find Diane and Carol Anne...
band together.
That will prevent you
from crossing over into eternity.
I'll try to bring you all back.
Join together.
The light of the family can defeat him.
This is the moment
you've been moving towards, all your life.
The entrance is through the flames.
Daddy, help!
This is an illusion! The beast lies!
Go through the flames, now!
She's gone.
It's too late.
I've lost.
Thank God!
Some battle.
Your car.
It's happy.
Not yet.
How are we going to make it happy?
It wants to come home with me.
- You asked it?
- Yes.
It's sure?
Okay, it's yours. Take it.
We thank you.
It started right up.
'Bye, Taylor!
- Dad, you gave our car away?
- Yes.
Steven, we have no... We need a ride home.
My car needs me!
Wait for us!
My car likes me!