Beware of the Blob
It creeps and leaps
And glides and slides
across the floor
Right through the door
and all around the wall
A splotch, a blotch
Be careful of the Blob
Beware of the Blob
It creeps and leaps
And glides and slides
across the floor
Right through the door
and all around the wall
A splotch, a blotch
Be careful of the Blob
Beware of the Blob
It creeps and leaps
And glides and slides
across the floor
Right through the door
and all around the wall
A splotch, a blotch
Be careful of the Blob
No.
Well, it's a shooting star.
I thought you were supposed to
wish on shooting stars.
- But I did.
- We only saw one.
- But you see a lot of'em
up here at night.
- What?
Well, I mean, there's
a lot of'em out at night.
You don't see 'em in town.
That's why I come up here.
Oh, no, that's not what I mean.
- I mean, you can see 'em
better up here--
- I know what you mean, Steve.
No, no, it's not
what you think, Janey girl.
My name is Jane.
Just Jane.
For a little while, I thought
that "shooting star" business
wasn't just part of your line.
But it's not, Janey gir--
Jane, I've never brought
anyone up here before.
Never?
Never.
Well, I may be crazy,
but... I believe you.
Well, you're not crazy.
Boy, that was close!
Come on. I want to see
if I can find it.
Shut up.
Get back inside.
- Get back in there.
Huh. Huh.
I could've sworn it landed
just over this hill.
Maybe it's like lightning. Sometimes
you think it's striking right next door,
and it's really miles away.
No, I still think it's close by.
Well, do you want to go back
and try the other road?
No. Um... um...
well, I'm sorry
about the bumpy ride.
It's all right, Steve.
Well, listen, why don't we
go back to town and I'll apologize.
I'll apologize over a sandwich.
I mean, on me.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Steve, watch out!
- What was that?
- It looked like an old man.
Where'd he go?
Hey, you okay?
Oh! Take me to a doctor!
- What's the matter?
- I can't get it off!
- Well, here, let me try.
Maybe I can get it off.
- No! You can't!
Okay. Come on.
We'll get you in the car.
- Yeah, okay, get in.
- It hurts.
Take it easy, now.
Here, better put this on.
Take it easy.
We'll get you there as fast as we can.
Boy, I hope the doctor's in.
Mrs. Porter, Dr. Hallen.
I'm leaving now.
Yes, I'll be back tomorrow
night, probably late.
No, I haven't
forgotten anything.
Ye-Yes, I'll be fine.
Look, Mrs. Porter, if you'll just keep
your eye on the house while I'm gone.
Thank you.
Good-bye.
- Come on!
- Hey, who's the cowboy?
- That's no cowboy.
That's Steve Andrews.
- What?
- Yeah, that's his container.
It's a real dog.
- Well, he can't do that to us.
Hey, Doc.
It's all right. Come on.
- Watch his hand.
Hey, Doc Hallen,
this man's been hurt.
Well, come on in.
- Wanna get the door?
In there.
What's the matter with him?
l-- I don't know.
He got something on his hand.
- What do you mean?
- Well, we ran into him
down on the Old North Road.
- Ran into him?
- No, Doc, we picked him up
out on the road.
He was screaming
about this thing on his hand.
Let's take a look.
Take it easy, old-timer.
- What is it he's got on his hand?
- I don't know, Doc.
It was kind of like-- well,
a big blister on his fingers, you know?
- Easy, now. Easy.
How are we gonna help you
if you don't let us see it?
Doc! It's gotten bigger.
It was just on his hand before.
Cover him with this, please.
I've got to give him something.
Take it easy, old-timer.
Everything's gonna be all right.
- Steve, uh, you know who he is?
- Huh?
- Do you have any idea who he is?
- Oh, no, no.
All right, take it easy.
There we are.
- Steve.
- Huh?
Could you drive out
to the place you found him?
See if you can find somebody
that knows what happened.
Right. Right.
- Steve?
- Yeah?
Would you turn out
the outside light when you go?
- I don't want to be disturbed.
- Sure, Doc. Sure.
What's up?
- Congratulations.
- Yeah? For what?
- "For what?" he says.
- Modest.
Mooch, quick, the crown.
Okay, I give up.
You just beat out
the champion, pal.
A little while ago
when you came into town.
Oh.
I get it. Well, thanks anyway,
but you can keep the crown.
No, no, no.
Wait a minute, Steve.
You just can't stop
being the champion like that.
You've gotta meet a challenger.
- You mean you?
- Me?
Did I say anything
about a race, guys?
Huh?
Not a word.
All right, look, it's been a ball,
you know? But I gotta go.
Yeah... we know how you go.
We're just not so sure
you should drive around so fast.
Now look, I just don't have time
to prove anything tonight.
Do you understand?
Well, who's asking you
to prove anything?
We can beat this kiddie car
of yours going backwards.
Oh, that's a foregone transfusion.
- Okay.
Now you're talkin', king.
And we'll do it
just like you said.
- What did I say?
- Backwards.
- Huh?
- See if you could beat this
kiddie car going backwards.
- To the light.
- Okay. You say when.
Okay.
- When!
I told you.
I got to leave now.
Steve.
All right,
what's this all about?
Hi, Dave.
Hey, what's up, huh?
I seem to be missing something.
What's going on?
We're just sitting here
waiting for the light.
Oh, you mean
that light down there.
Yeah.
And you do know you're
on the wrong side of the road?
I don't--
Would you think it was funny
if your father--
if Jane's father heard you were
booked for reckless driving?
Okay, don't bring the fathers into this.
I'll never do it again.
- Do what again?
- Huh?
Do what again?
What-Whatever you think
I'm doing, Dave.
Like driving
on the wrong side of the road?
Well... yeah, yeah.
Or maybe even
driving backwards?
Hey, Dave, that's an idea.
You know that 80 or 90 percent
of the accidents are front-end jobs.
You know, in Australia
they got airplanes...
with the seats
set in backwards...
so in case you get
a collision, they got...
no concu--
No good, huh?
Okay... lock me up.
You mean, you were dri--
Why?
What am I gonna do with you kids?
You know I don't wanna haul you in.
No more foolin' around,
Dave. No, I mean it.
l-- swe-- I promise.
Right, Jane? Huh?
- Right.
- See?
- No more horseplay.
- No more horseplay, Dave.
- No, no more fooling around.
- Get outta here.
Here they come.
Hey, what happened?
- Sergeant Bert?
- No, no, no. Dave.
- Oh, you're lucky it wasn't Bertsie.
- Yeah, you're not kidding.
- You don't know the half of it.
- What?
- Last night we seen Gig's car
parked in front of Nancy's.
- Listen to this.
So we decided we'd move it,
hide it on him.
So we're moving it down
the center of the street...
when along comes Sgt. Bert.
- So Mooch tells him we can't
get it started, you know?
He says, "I don't care. You're blocking
traffic. Move it out of the way."
So then he gets out of the car,
comes over to us...
and he's helping us move Gig's car.
Just then, Gig
comes out of the house...
and he's yelling,
"Who's stealing my car?"
- I thought Bertie would drop his teeth.
- I bet he did.
- If Gig didn't cover for us,
we would've been in trouble.
Yeah, you know, I'd sure hate
to cross Bertie again tonight.
Hey, what happened
with you and Dave?
I got a lecture.
Promised to be a good boy.
You know, Dave's a good guy.
I think we have been steaming
him up a little too much.
There's about two inches of rubber
on the street outside Doc's house.
Hey, I almost forgot.
I gotta do something for the doc.
- What?
- I gotta go up
and check on some people.
- You wanna come with me?
- Oh, no, man.
We're going to the flicks.
- At this time of night?
- Yeah, it's a midnight spook bit.
We got some rumors there'd be
some unprotected women in the balcony.
Well, listen, why don't you--
Come on, come with us.
You can go to the movies after.
It'll only take a half hour.
- Come on!
- It's okay with me.
- All right, man, lead the way.
- Okay.
Groverton 4771 .
5296.
Hello.
Is Dr. Gilpen there?
Dr. Hallen.
Oh, he has?
No, no message.
Thanks. Good-bye.
Hello?
Kate? Dr. Hallen.
I'm still at the office.
Something's come up.
I'll need your help right away.
No, you've got to come back.
There's a man here with some
sort of a parasite on his arm.
It's assimilating his flesh
at a frightening speed.
I may have to get ahead of it
and amputate.
No, l-- I don't know what it is
or where it came from.
Man, look at that, will you?
- What is it?
- Wow, I don't know.
Tony, look.
- Hey, what landed here?
- We must be getting close
to the front line.
Hey, why would anybody
leave a lantern here?
- I don't know.
- What is it, Steve?
- It's hot.
- Watch it.
- A shooting star?
- Hey, we saw that too!
A real big one,
like a skyrocket.
- Oh, yeah, about an hour ago.
- You think this is it?
- I don't know.
- Let me see.
Wow, a real piece of sky.
Here, Mooch.
You mean that this little pebble
has been out there hot-roddin'
around the universe?
Probably big as the moon
when it started.
No kiddin'!
Let me see it, Mooch.
And this is all
that's left?
Well, it's all that's here.
- I'll bet there is a house close by.
Doesn't sound like a house.
It sounds like a dog.
- Come on, Steve. Let's go look.
- Yeah, sure.
- Hey, wait a minute.
- Hey, there's a house.
- Hey, real nice.
- You think anybody's here?
Hello? Hello? Doesn't look
like there's anybody here at all.
Hey, I can't see anything
but just that little dog.
Oh, Steve, open the door
and let him out.
Okay. Come on.
- Come on. Come on.
- Come on, pal.
- Come on. Ohhh. Come on out.
- Doesn't look like anybody
was there at all.
- Come on.
I guess it's
the old man's dog.
Don't you worry, baby.
You'll be all right.
- Think this is the place?
- It sure looks like it.
This is a cozy spot. No neighbors,
no cars, no roads, no lights.
Yeah, and no movies.
Come on, you guys, let's get outta here.
- Let's go, Mooch.
- I guess there's nothing else
you can find out here, Steve.
No, no, I guess not.
Why don't you come with us to
the spooky show, huh? You'd like it.
- No, no thanks.
- Ah, you gotta stop takin'
everything so serious-like.
Gotta live a little.
You gotta go, you know?
Yeah, Steve, you gotta
hang loose, like me.
- Okay, sure, the spook show.
- Come on.
- Let's go, you guys!
- Yeah, comin'.
- Steve?
- Yeah.
- What about the dog?
- I don't know.
I mean, we can't just leave him here.
He'd starve to death.
- Yeah, that's right.
- Couldn't we take him with us?
Sure. I guess that's the least we could
do for the old man. Come on, let's go.
Oh, hello, Kate.
Thanks for coming back.
It's okay.
What do you want me to do?
You better take his pulse. But don't
touch that material on his right hand.
It absorbs flesh on contact,
like an acid.
Doctor, where is he?
What do you mean?
Kate, stand still. Don't move.
It must have absorbed
the old man completely.
I don't know what this is, but it's got
to be killed before it gets any bigger.
- Oh, Doctor, I'm afraid.
- Try to stay as far away
from it as you can.
- Kate, be calm! Now do as I say.
Behind you.
The trichloroacetic acid.
- Throw it!
- Throw it?
Yes, but for heaven's sake,
don't get any of it on your hands.
Doctor, nothing will stop it.
A gun. In my den.
I've got to go for it, Kate.
Now try to stay
absolutely still.
- Don't go. Don't leave me.
- I'll be right back.
Doctor, come back!
Come back!
- Kate, what's the matter?
Kate! Kate, what is it?
Kate!
Listen, you stay there,
and I'll go in and tell the doc.
- It doesn't look
like there's anybody here.
- Yeah.
Well, maybe he took the old man
to the hospital. Anyway, I'll check.
Okay.
Listen, I'm gonna check in the garage
and see if the doc's car is there.
Oh, okay.
Steve. Steve,
what's the matter?
- Steve, tell me what happened.
- I can't.
- Well, what happened?
- It was so--
- Steve, what is it?
- It's got the doc. It's got--
- What's the matter with him?
Just like the thing on the old man's
hand, only it was bigger.
Then it was on his whole head, and then
in just a second he disappeared.
- He disappeared?
- He was all gone. He was all gone.
- You know, he just disappeared.
- Steve, what are you talking about?
I'm sorry.
Get in the car, Jane.
Well, what are you
gonna do, Steve?
We're gonna go to the police.
They'll know what to do.
Well, we can get someone
over there tomorrow. Yeah.
- We'll have someone over there
first thing in the morning.
- Well, what's this?
Hey, watch it, Dave.
Don't mix up the pieces.
Ritchie, you old buzzard.
I didn't know you were a chess player.
It's like I've been telling you, Dave.
You're not the only thinker around here.
It's nothing.
Just a hobby, you know?
Well, wait. Wait a minute.
I think this is interesting.
Who do you play with?
Well, late at night when I'm here by
myself and things are pretty slow, l--
Well, you gotta do something.
You oughta take up chess.
Loosen up your gray matter a little.
I guess I'd better.
You'll have to teach me, Ritchie.
Sure, Dave.
Anytime.
Dave, Doc Hallen's
been killed.
- Doc Hallen? What happened?
- You gotta come now!
Wait a minute, Steve.
Tell us what happened.
I'm trying to tell you.
Now this thing, it killed the doc.
What was it?
Out with it, kid.
Well, it's
kind of like a ma--
It's kind of like a mass that
keeps getting bigger and bigger.
- Come on, Steve, make sense.
- I know, I know.
Look, Dave, you gotta see this thing
to believe what I'm telling you.
Maybe the thing you saw
was a... monster?
Yeah, maybe it was.
I don't know.
Hold on, Jim.
Now, what is it, Steve?
A little while ago it was driving
backwards, and now it's monsters.
Look, he's not
making it up, Dave. Honest.
Dave, I'm not kidding.
Come on over to the doc's.
You can see it for yourself.
You're crazy if you go.
Can't you see it's a gag?
He says Doc Hallen's dead, Jim.
We've got to check it out.
Let's go.
Ritchie, you mind the store.
Dave, listen--
East Cornwall, Downingtown H.Q
Downingtown, East Cornwall H.Q.
Q to K-2.
Do I read you right?
Q to K-2?
Roger.
K-9 to KB-5.
Shucks.
"This office will be closed
all day Saturday. Dr. Hallen."
- Wait a minute.
- What's the matter?
The thing might be in there
waiting for you.
- Well, we'll have to take
that chance, won't we?
- I'm not kidding.
Dr. Hallen?
Hmm. Seems to be
a short circuit in here.
You got your light?
[ Dave ]
Everything looks okay.
There. I think this
is the room I saw him in.
- It's locked.
- I'll see if I can find
a key that'll work.
No, the key's already here.
It's been locked from the inside.
Hello?
Who's in there?
Better go around and see
if the window's unlocked.
If it isn't, break the glass,
come in and unlock the door.
- All right.
- You're not gonna let him do that.
Now, don't worry, Steve. Sergeant Bert
knows how to handle himself.
And this is the only way
to get to the bottom of this.
- I'll see if I can find the fuse box.
- Okay.
Steve, I wonder where
the little dog is.
Yeah.
What do you think
happened to him?
I don't know.
Well, that's more like it.
This must have been
what blew the fuse.
Jim?
Wait till you get a load
of this mess!
Ohh.
What about this, Steve?
I don't know, Dave.
But I know I saw the doc.
All right, kid, cut the act.
What really happened here?
-I don't know.
-All of a sudden, your mind is a blank?
- No.
- Steve, are you sure this is the room?
Yes, I'm sure of it.
This has been fired.
But I haven't seen
any shot marks around anyplace.
Let me tell you
what happened, kid.
You and whoever else
was in on this thought you'd
put one over on the police.
- So you break in here,
you mess the place up--
- Wait a minute, Jim.
The kids couldn't have done this.
You saw for yourself.
The window was locked from the inside,
and so was the door.
They rigged it with string. It's part
of their plan to make us look silly.
I think you're doing that
pretty well by yourself, Sergeant.
Steve, was there
anybody else with you?
No.
How about when I stopped you
over on Morgan Street?
Those kids had nothing
to do with this.
- Who were they?
- Why, it was Tony and Mooch.
Those kids? Well, there's
your answer right there!
They're just the kind of kids
to pull a trick like this.
- But this time they've gone too far.
- What goes on out here?
- Land's sakes!
- What are you doing here, Mrs. Porter?
Boy oh boy oh boy! Wait till Doctor
gets back and sees this!
- Back from where?
- Lieutenant, was it burglars?
We don't know yet.
Where is Dr. Hallen?
Johnsonville.
A medical convention.
You know, I told him this would
happen one of these days,
the way he leaves
everything unlocked.
Of course, it was my fault too.
He asked me to keep an eye on the place.
But that's not true, Dave.
He never left.
I don't think I've had the pleasure.
This is Steve Andrews,
Mrs. Porter.
He seems to think the doctor
got into some trouble here tonight.
No, sir! The doctor
don't know anything about this.
He called me
just before he left.
He didn't leave. Look, Dave,
I'll bet his car is still in the garage.
Might be. Doctor sometimes
goes in somebody else's car.
Dr. Gilpen
from over in Groverton.
-Jim, call Dr. Gilpen.
- Right.
- He won't be home.
-Just checking.
Mrs. Porter, did you hear
any gunshots tonight?
I sure did!
Tonight and every other night.
The people downstairs have those
old movies on their television.
There's always
some shooting or screaming.
Whoever this thief was, he didn't have
to tear up the place like this.
I feel terrible.
Wait a minute, Mrs. Porter.
I don't want this touched.
Well, I don't want the doctor
to come back tomorrow and find
the place like this.
- It's bad enough
the window's broke and all.
- But, Mrs. Porter--
Now, you boys have your work
to do, and I have mine.
There's a criminal walking
around out there free as a bird.
You go get him.
Let me clean up here.
Mrs. Porter,
you don't understand.
We may want to check here
for fingerprints later.
Dr. Gilpen's on his way
to Johnsonville.
Did he pick up Dr. Hallen?
I spoke with Mrs. Gilpen, and she said
that Dr. Hallen had called around 11:00,
just after her husband left, but
she thought they were going together.
- Where can we reach them
in Johnsonville?
- I didn't ask her that.
St.John's Hotel.
That's where the doctor usually stays.
Well, they should be there
in a couple of hours.
We'll leave word to have him call us
when he checks in.
Can't I just dust
around the fingerprints?
Tomorrow.
Well, let's go, kids.
Dave, this is all wrong.
All right, kid, the show's over.
It was a cute act, but this time
it didn't work.
This locked door business
really hung you.
If everything happened like
you said, where's the doctor?
And where is this old man?
And where is the big, bad monster?
I don't know.
Hand me that small
hammer, will ya?
- Why don't you finish that tomorrow?
- I ain't gonna be here.
I'm goin' on a huntin' trip.
I didn't know you was a hunter.
Neither did I.
We got a little cabin
up in the south woods, the boys and me.
And I'm tellin' you, Marty boy,
we're goin' up there this weekend,
and I'm gonna get so roarin',
stinkin', no-good drunk...
I won't be able to see.
Hey, why don't you come with us?
It'll do you some good.
Oh, I don't think Martha
would figure it that way.
Do you have to tell your old woman
everything? Tell her your uncle died.
Tell her you're going away so you
can love her more when you get back.
Good night.
Boy, I'm so tired of lookin'
at the guts of secondhand cars...
I could spit grease.
You know, Marty, if I didn't get away
once in a while, I'd blow a gasket.
- When I come in on Monday,
if Mr.Johnson looks at me
funny just once--
just once-- you know what
I'm gonna do to him, Marty?
Hey, Marty!
- Look, you keep telling me
about a monster.
- All I want to do
is clear this thing up.
- All right, I agree.
- But I still don't see why
you had to call our folks.
- Dave, it's for you.
- What else could I do?
- Well, give us a chance
to find out what happened.
You know we didn't tear up Doc's house.
How long have you known me?
All right, I believe you!
But I still don't think you're
telling me all you know.
- Oh, Dave.
- Hello? Yeah.
Well, young lady, do you mind telling me
where you've been spending the evening?
- Daddy, it's all right.
- Oh, yes, everything's fine.
I always stop by the police station
to pick up my daughter.
Don't you realize
what this could do to me?
- By morning, it will be all over town.
We were just
trying to warn people.
After all, I am principal
of the high school.
Young man, this is the last time you're
ever going to take my daughter out!
Steve didn't
do anything wrong!
Mr. Andrews, can you make anything
out of all this? I can't.
Take it easy, Mr. Martin. We'll
straighten everything out. Hello, son.
- Dad, I saw something terrible tonight.
- And nobody'll believe us.
Mr. Martin, Mr. Andrews,
uh, apparently Doc Hallen's office
was broken into by vandals tonight.
And Steve and Jane
seem to know something about it.
Vandals?
My daughter?
Well, you don't think our kids
were mixed up in it, do you?
All we know is that they
told us something had happened
over at Dr. Hallen's house.
We're not accusing anyone
of what we found.
We can't be more definite until
we contact Dr. Hallen in Johnsonville.
Dad, it isn't vandalism!
Dr. Hallen is dead,
and he was killed
by some sort of a monster.
Now, I know
because I saw it, Dad.
Lieutenant, I want you to know
that Steve is not in the habit
of telling lies.
If he says he's
not mixed up in this vandalism,
you can be sure it's the truth.
Did you see this thing
too, Jane?
Well...
no, not exactly.
Well, look, folks, we'll
all know more in the morning
after we've called Johnsonville.
I think the best thing now is for all
of us to go home and get some sleep.
Maybe it's a good idea, son. We can
talk about this some more at home.
Sure, Pop.
Get out of the house as fast as you can.
I'll be over.
Maybe Bertie's right.
Maybe this is just a gag
like those school fraternities
were throwing last year.
Remember how they stitched that bathing
suit to the statue of General Hayes?
I don't think this is a gag.
Why didn't you
book the kids then?
Why make a big thing
of it tonight if we can clear
the whole thing up tomorrow?
Boy, if it was Bertie, he'd have them
strung up by the thumbs by now.
- Maybe he would.
Police department.
Hold on. It's Bertie.
- Hello?
- Dave?
- Yep.
- A couple of people thought they
heard shots, but weren't sure.
- Okay, Jim. Doc's place locked up?
- Yeah.
- Check back in, then.
- Right.
We'll get the truth out of those
kids if it takes all night.
- I sent the kids home.
- Home? Are you crazy?
Jim, we'll take care of this
whole thing tomorrow.
Yes, sir.
Is that all?
Yes, that's all.
Bertie got some idea
what this is?
I don't care
what Bertie's ideas are!
He acts like we're
still fighting the war.
Just because some kid
smacks into his wife on the turnpike...
doesn't make it a crime
to be 17 years old!
Okay, so I don't know what
the kids are up to tonight.
But I'm not gonna throw them
into a cell like a couple of vagrants.
We'll put this puzzle
together in the morning.
In the meantime, at least
we know where the kids are.
- Hey, where are you going?
- Oh, shhh, Danny.
- Shhh.
- Where are you going?
I've got something very important to do,
Danny, but it's got to be a secret.
I won't tell anybody.
I'll go with you.
No, honey,
I have to go by myself.
- Will you be back pretty soon?
- Well, I don't know.
Aren't you afraid
to go out by yourself?
Yes, I guess I am, Danny.
I'm not afraid.
I'll guard you.
Oh, no, Danny.
You've got a bigger job to do.
You've got to stay here
and guard Mommy and Daddy.
Oh, they don't need guarding.
Oh, look, Danny,
go on to beddie.
Look, if you go to bed, I might bring
you a little dog all your very own.
A dog! Honest?
Honest.
I cross my heart.
- Oh, boy!
- Now go on up to bed.
- What's his name?
- Oh, any name you want, Danny.
Can I name him William?
Oh, that's a fine name, Danny.
Now you better run on up to bed.
- Go on.
- Oh, I don't like William.
You run on to bed, honey.
Steve? Steve?
- Was he asleep?
- Yeah.
Do you think he did something wrong?
I don't know. I don't think so.
The police don't either,
or they wouldn't have sent him home.
I felt that he was keeping
something from us.
He did seem more willing to talk
when we were at the station.
Well, I think tomorrow he might talk and
we'll be able to straighten this out.
Maybe, after a good night's sleep.
Yeah. Good night.
'Night, dear.
You scared me to death.
What are you doing here?
Listen, Jane, I told you
to wait over there.
The folks went to bed, so I thought
I should just come on over.
All right, come on.
Let's go around the corner.
- Steve?
- Huh?
Oh, I'm sorry.
- At least I could've thanked you
for coming out tonight.
- You didn't need to.
I never needed to talk to anyone before,
not as much as I do now.
Well, we're in this together,
aren't we, Steve?
You know, I wish that we--
I must be getting confused.
I know we saw the old man,
I know we took him to the doc's...
and I know the doc sent us out to see
if we could find out what happened.
So?
And I know the old man
had something on his hand,
something he couldn't get off,
something that kept getting larger.
I saw that.
And then l--
I think I saw the doc.
He was standing
by the window, and he--
he was trying to get out...
and that thing
was all over him...
and then...just dissolved
while I stood there.
I think I saw this.
I believe you did.
You know, plenty of people
in their right mind thought they
saw things that didn't exist,
you know,
like flying saucers.
The light was just right,
and the angle and the imagination.
Boy, if that's what it is,
then this is just an ordinary night.
You and I are gonna go to sleep,
and tomorrow when we get up...
that sun's gonna shine,
just like yesterday.
Good old yesterday.
Steve, well, you believe
you did see it, don't you?
I don't know. l-l--
That's not true, Steve.
Well, maybe, maybe now
you don't want to believe it.
Maybe you'd like to tell
yourself it didn't happen.
But, Steve, you're not the kind
of person who can turn your back...
on something
you know is true.
I don't know.
Well, you actually did see
what happened to Dr. Hallen.
How do you know I did?
Because I know you.
Okay.
Now what do we do?
How do you get people to protect
themselves from something
they don't believe in?
Well, you keep trying
and hoping you can find...
some sort of proof
that'll convince them.
Okay.
I don't like it much,
but I guess the only way you can find
that is to go out and look for it.
I'll go get the car.
- You sure you want to go with me?
- Yes.
I wouldn't give much
for our chances...
wandering around in the middle
of the night trying to find something...
that if we found it,
it might kill us.
If we could only find
a couple of people to help us.
Hmm. Who?
Well, your friends,
Tony, Mooch and Al.
Hey, you know, that--
that's worth a try.
Yes, I am here,
the demon who
possesses your soul.
Wait a bit.
I am coming for you.
I have so much to show you.
Tony, listen,
I wanna see you outside.
Hey, what gives? I thought
you cats didn't dig spooky shows.
This is important.
Outside.
- Hey, what's up?
- Shhh.
I'll explain outside.
This is important.
You missed most of the picture.
You're not gonna get your money's worth.
None of us are,
unless somebody keeps quiet.
You're gotta come with us.
There's nobody else we can go to.
- Okay, you kids, knock it off.
- Come on!
What?
Walk out of the movie?
Let's cut out.
You cats gonna make it?
Not me. I'm part of this chair,
and I can't move.
Tsk.
Hold up, Mooch!
Hey, all right, Steve, you made us waste
our 80 cents. Now, what gives?
Yeah, what's the scoop?
What's the big idea, Steve?
Would you believe me if
I told you there was something
inside of that rock we found,
something that could wipe out
this whole town?
Knock it off!
Go ahead, Steve.
I saw this thing
kill Dr. Hallen tonight.
Kill Dr. Hallen?
- That's right.
- Well, what is it?
I don't know.
But one thing's for sure,
if it can kill Dr. Hallen,
it can kill somebody else.
What do you want us to do, Steve?
All right, we're gonna find this thing,
and we're gonna make people believe us.
Let's try Johnsonville
again, Ritchie.
- Okay.
- I just saw a strange one.
What do you mean?
On my way back here, I ran into
Mr. Connors coming outta that bar...
in the building he owns
over on Second Street.
He'd just stopped in,
and there was nobody there.
Queerest thing
I've ever seen.
TV was playin' away. The cash register
was there with the money still in it.
Nobody around.
No bartender, nobody.
I'll look in there
on the way home.
Forget it. The place
is all locked up now.
Why don't you go home
and get some shut-eye?
You can't run our shift
and yours too, you know?
Yeah, I know. I wish I knew
where those two doctors were, though.
- Any luck, Ritchie?
- Nope, they're not there.
Want me to call
the other hotels?
There's a lot of them
between here and Johnsonville.
No. I guess you're right.
I guess there's nothing here
that won't wait till morning.
Well, I'll see you guys.
- Good night.
Well, hello, kids!
Come on in!
You're just in time
for the fun.
- We came to warn you.
- Huh? How?
- We came here just to warn you--
- Oh, a warning!
Well, that's fine.
I didn't know you cared.
Hey, folks!
I want you
to meet Paul Revere,
and this is Mrs. Revere.
They've come to give us a warning
about something important.
The British are coming!
Excuse me.
We were just--
just looking for a monster.
Monsters? You must've been talking
to that guy from Second Street.
Man, I don't know
what they're serving over there,
but it sure must be great stuff.
Listen, we're trying to tell you.
We don't wanna get served.
Look, I have monsters in here
all the time, so beat it.
We don't serve kids anyway.
Where is he?
Over there, in the doorway
of your dad's store.
- Come on. Come on.
- Come on. Hey!
That's funny.
The door's not locked.
Do you think it's
been open all night?
Well, I don't know.
This is Friday.
The store closes at 10:00, and
then old Mr. Weinermeyer sweeps up...
and then he collects
all the push carts.
Huh. He works around for a couple
of hours before he locks up,
but I'm sure he'd never
be this late, not--
Hey, Mr. Weinermeyer?
Hey, Mr. Weinermeyer,
where are you?
I'm gonna turn on the light.
- Steve, what is it?
I don't know. Oh.
It's a broom and stuff
that Mr. Weinermeyer cleans up with.
It's spread all over the aisle.
What's the matter? Jane!
Here. You all right?
Yes.
Steve!
Oh, Steve, our parents!
They think we're home in bed
asleep, sound and safe.
- Steve, it's the little dog!
Now listen! Everything's gonna be
all right. Do you hear me? Now--
It's gonna be all right.
-I don't know if we can stop that thing.
- The dog, Steve.
- Take it easy, Jane.
- Oh, Steve, the little dog!
- Don't cry, Jane.
There's nothing
we can do about it.
Now, Jane, just put this on.
It'll be all right.
Oh, Steve,
what are we gonna do?
I don't know.
That thing probably isn't far away.
We've gotta get out of here
before it comes back for us.
Now, come on.
All right?
- There they are!
Hey, where you kids been?
- Hey, it's in there!
- You're kidding!
- I wish I were kidding. It's in there.
- He got the little dog.
- Oh, you mean the old man's dog.
- We just seen him
running down the street.
- Oh, Steve!
- What do we do now?
- We're gonna call the police.
They want evidence.
There's a phone at the corner!
- Hmm.
- Go on!
- You talk to him, Tony.
- Me? Why me?
I'm supposed to be home asleep.
If they think I'm loose,
they'll never believe us.
Yeah, here's a dime.
Come on. Come on.
- Hey, what'll I say?
- Ask for Dave.
And you give it to him straight. You
tell him to get out to the store quick.
Tell him to bring every
piece of hardware he can find
in the police station.
Hello. Police department.
Is-- Who's this?
Arthur who?
Is every kid in town
in on this?
I don't know who this is,
but you're going to wish
you'd never thought of this.
Hello? Hello?
Big deal!
I'd like to take that dime--
- Bert?
- Yeah.
- Wouldn't you know it?
All right, we tried to do it
the right way, now we're gonna
wake this town up ourselves.
- Yeah, yeah, but how?
- Yeah, how?
Any way we can think of.
We've got to stop being
a baby-sitting service and start
being a police department.
-Just kids, Jim.
-Just kids?
That's about he craziest
argument I've ever heard.
Every criminal in the world
was a kid once. What does it prove?
You know what I think?
I think they've got it in for me.
- You?
- Yeah.
They've heard about my war record,
and it bugs them.
They're trying to break me down,
see what makes me tick.
Anything they can try, they try.
Aw, I don't think so, Jim.
- What the--
- Sounds like New Year's Eve.
Hello?
I don't know either--
Lady?
- Police department.
Looks like everybody
in town's getting up.
What's going on here?
Why, that's an air raid!
Pull yourself together.
Oh, it's probably only--
No, maybe it's the real thing.
It isn't a drill.
Where is my civil defense helmet?
Where is it?
Here we are.
Here we go.
- Fire.
- Fire?
This has never happened before.
What am I gonna wear?
Henry, Danny's gone!
What?
And Jane too!
- Calm down, Elizabeth.
- I looked in their rooms.
They're both gone!
- Are you sure?
- Yes! Yes!
Well, maybe they're down here.
Here's Danny.
Danny!
What are you doing here?
I'm guarding you.
Guarding us?
Guarding us
against what, darling?
I don't know.
Has everyone in this
fool town gone crazy?
Danny, do you know
where Janey is?
She's just gone.
I'm going to get to the bottom
of this right now.
- Come, Elizabeth.
Hey, what's going on here?
What's the matter?
All right now, kill the ho--
Kill the horns!
All right,
knock off the noise now!
Listen to-- Listen to me!
Now listen to me, everybody!
This town is in danger.
Several people have been killed already.
Now we had to make this noise so you'd
listen to us, so we could warn you.
If we're in trouble,
where are the police?
You! Boy, this time
you've really hung yourself.
Now look-- Now look, sarge, just give
me a chance to talk to them, that's all.
I don't know what kind
of a game it is you're playing,
but whatever it is
it's gonna stop right now!
Here comes Dave.
What's going on here,
Jim? Steve!
Dave, make 'em listen to me!
There is a monster!
We saw it again in Dad's store.
Dave, it's bigger now.
Your story's gotten
bigger now, kid.
Dave, look at me!
Do I look like somebody who's
playing a practical joke?
Am I laughing...
or am I scared stiff?
- What are you gonna do?
- He's telling the truth.
Oh, wait a minute! It's one thing
to make a fool out of yourself,
but it's another thing to make a fool
out of the police department
and the town.
- He's right, Lieutenant.
- You've been wrong before.
Maybe I have! But as long as I'm
in charge of this town's police force,
I'm gonna handle this thing
the way I see fit.
And your job right now is to help me
restore some order around here.
Yes, sir.
- Okay, everybody, quiet down a minute.
Quiet down, please!
Listen, this is an emergency,
and it can affect
every one of us.
That's all I can
tell you right now.
But we're trying to get
things under control.
In order to do that, we have to
clear this area immediately.
So please go home
and stay there.
We'll keep in touch with you
through your radio station.
Now, be careful pulling
your cars out of this area.
Go home slowly and quietly.
Just keep calm.
Everything's gonna be all right.
- Anything I can do to help?
- Lieutenant, what's going on?
Ask your daughter, Mr. Martin.
She can tell you more than I can.
- Phil, can your boys give us
a hand clearing this area?
- Sure.
- Do you have any guns?
- A couple of'em.
- Get 'em.
- Say, Dave, what is this thing?
I don't know. But if it's in the
market, we'll all know in a few minutes.
Now all the images of horror,
the demons of your mind
crowd in on you to destroy you.
Phil, can you move your truck
over to the door...
and shine your big light
into the market?
- Sure, Dave.
- All right.
What the--
Hey, who's in the store?
Huh?
There's nobody in here
but us monsters.
Dave, it's at the theater!
Don't go in, Jim.
This won't do any good.
It's the most horrible thing
I've ever seen in my life.
- So what is it?
- Come on, we've gotta clear this area.
All right, step back!
Everybody step back!
Here it comes!
Danny!
No, Danny, wait!
What goes?
What happened out there?
Oh, I almost got it.
No, Danny! Danny, we can't stay here.
Come with me, Danny.
Listen, it's too late.
Let's see if we can get out the back.
Wait a minute!
What's this?
- What happened?
- It's all over us.
- What do you mean?
What's the matter?
- Take it easy!
Jim, get the telephone company. Have
them connect you with the diner, fast.
I'm not gonna stay here!
Now, wait a minute!
You open that door, and we've had it!
- You wanna die?
- What are we supposed to do?
- Hello? Yeah.
- Steve?
- That thing is all over us!
- Watch out!
I don't think it can be killed.
- We've gotta try one more thing.
- Okay.
- Is everybody all right?
- Okay, but not for long.
We can drop a power line on it.
Do you understand?
There should be enough juice in
that line to burn the thing to a crisp.
Yeah, get everyone
down in the cellar.
We'll do it
in 60 seconds, Steve.
Cellar!
Okay.
Jim, here's a rifle.
- Take the phone, Ritchie.
- All right.
Dave, this baby should do the trick.
It's all set to go.
Try not to miss, Jim.
Okay, let's have those lights!
- Fifteen seconds.
It's quiet now.
I think the upstairs is clear.
Good. Keep your ear
to that phone, Ritchie.
Okay, Jim.
It didn't work.
Why don't you do something?
Do something!
- Elizabeth.
The diner's on fire.
Can't we put it out?
Any suggestions how?
Anyway, not enough oxygen in there
to keep a fire going for ten minutes.
There's something burning.
- Listen, is there
any other way out of here?
- The windows.
Hey, now you be quiet.
Shhh.
- I'm not afraid.
- Well, I know you're not.
Hey, listen, Jane--
It'll be all right.
Honey, lay your head down
and try to go to sleep.
Everything will be
all right, Danny.
Hey, there's the fire!
I'll stop it!
Wait a minute.
Let me have that a minute.
CO2! Hey, that's it!
It's cold!
That's why it didn't come in the ice box
after us. It can't stand cold.
- You got any more
of these things? Huh?
- [ Man ] No.
This thing's running out.
The phone. Hey, Dave!
Hey, Dave! Hey, Da--
Anybody on the phone?
Hey, Dave!
Dave, can you hear me?
CO2!
Dave!
- What did he say?
- Al, what's up?
Shhh. Quiet.
CO2?
Phil! Phil, do you got
any CO2 extinguishers?
Not many.
Some soda acid.
Well, get the CO2s out here and start
hitting around those cellar windows.
- What?
-Just do it, Phil!
And check these buildings for fire
extinguishers. But only the CO2 kind.
- Bring back every one
you can get your hands on.
- All right. Okay.
Hey, maybe we can help.
Let's get some guys together.
- Lieutenant, I know where
there are 20 extinguishers
- Good. Where?
- At the high school.
Who can go with me?
- Hey, right here, Mr. Martin.
Well, what are we
waiting for? Let's go.
Okay, let's go.
Over here, Mr. Martin.
This thing's running out!
Hey, Dave! Dave?
Dave, CO2 fire extinguishers!
Dave, can you hear me?
CO2!
- Okay, come on.
- Oh, it's locked.
- Of course it's locked.
- Here comes Mr. Martin.
- Here comes the principal.
We could only find four or five
of these things, Dave.
- How many of them do you need?
- A lot more than that.
- Keep looking. It's all we can do.
- Okay.
Dave, Colonel Spaulding
got me through to Washington.
They thought I was crazy at first,
but they're getting someone now.
Hey, here come the kids!
Our power's still out, so we can't
do much in the way of refrigeration.
We think we've got it under control,
but we won't rest easy
until it's frozen solid.
Now--
No, it's too big for that,
and it's impossible to cut it.
No, sir, a bomb would spread it
all over the country.
Look, this thing has killed probably
40 or 50 people since last night.
In a few hours, we're gonna have
the sun overhead.
I think you should send us
the biggest transport plane you have...
and take this thing up to the Arctic
or somewhere where it'll never thaw out.
Oh, Daddy! Oh, Daddy!
Let me see you, son.
Let me see my boy.
- Nice work, Steve. You okay?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
Dave, listen, I wanna--
Well, I wanna thank you
for getting us out of there.
You know, for a while,
I didn't think we were gonna make it.
- That makes two of us.
- What are they gonna do
with that thing, Dave?
Well, the Air Force
is sending a Globemaster in.
They're flying it to the Arctic.
It's not dead, is it?
No, it's not.
-Just frozen.
- I don't think it can be killed.
But at least
we've got it stopped.
Yeah, as long as
the Arctic stays cold.