## [ Choir Singing ]
[ Thunderclap ]
[ Rain Falling ]
## [ Choir Continues ]
Taxi!
## [ Orchestra ]
[ Growling ]
Help!
[ Roaring ]
## [ Orchestra, Choir
Building To Crescendo ]
[ Screams ]
## [ Ends ]
[ Roaring ]
## [ Rock ]
Keep the change.
There is no change.
Uh, yeah, well,
keep it anyway.
[ Laughing ]
- Paris.
- Beware.
Hey, hey,
watch it, man.
All right. I have
the score for Spain.
Our leader with 125
daredevil points:
yours truly.
[ Laughs ]
In second place
with 95: Chris.
Whoa, whoa, hold on a second.
What about the sex points?
- No, those are separate.
- Since when? You can't
keep changing the rules.
Who said anything about sex points? Read
your shirt. It says "Daredevil Tour."
See that?
She smiled at me.
In your dreams. She's not interested
in douche bags like us.
European babes are charming and
sophisticated, especially the French.
- [ Laughs ] Hence the hairy pits.
- See what I mean?
I'll give you 20 sex points if you can
so much as get her phone number.
She's not my type.
Oh, come on!
- You-- You haven't made a move
this entire trip, Andy.
- I'm choosy.
When was the last time
you had sex?
- With another person?
- There's sex and there's love.
That what differentiates humans
from animals.
-Okay, fine. When were you last in love?
-When were you ever in love?
- Map's upside down, slick.
- [ Chuckles ]
Give him a break, Chris.
We can't let him fall too far back.
I won't need your charity
once we get to Paris.
- I'll show you guys a stunt
you'll never top.
- [ Both ] Oooh.
## [ Rock ]
# Don't you count on #
# Me ##
[ Boy ]
All clear.
Let's go.
## [ Techno ]
# Down, down, down #
# I still remember #
# You're dressed in grey #
# Working undercover #
# Well, I heard you say #
- [ Panting ] One more!
- Five minutes.
I don't know why you bothered
carrying that thing up there.
You're never gonna use it.
# Let's go down #
# To the normal time #
# Right down #
# Down, down, down #
# Down, down, down ##
[ Boy ]
Wooh-hoo-ha!
[ Yodeling ]
All right, man,
we did it!
[ Chris ]
How high do you think we are, man?
- Check this out! ls that the Louvre?
- This is intense!
Man!
[ Bottle Clinking ]
[ Chuckles ]
Check out the stars.
[ Boy ]
Andy?
Andy, what are you doin'?
Hey, Andy.
Come and have some vin.
Andy?
What are you doin'?
For God sakes!
I think we pushed him too far.
- I'm gonna go stop him.
- Relax, man. He's never
gonna go through with it.
Whoa. Slow down, chief.
Come have a drink.
It's the real stuff.
Has a cork.
No. I'm flying dry.
Look, I'm sorry about the train. We were
just busting your balls, that's all.
Andy, you've proven yourself
to us, okay? You don't have to
go through with this.
Don't worry, Brad. Nobody's forcing me.
I wanna do this. Understand?
Andy, this is madness, okay? You're
gonna get yourself killed. Now, please.
- I'm trying to talk some--
- Guys, guys, shh.
I think someone's comin'.
[ Footsteps Clanging Metal ]
Shit.
Come on! Come on!
[ Chuckles ]
[ Metal Clanging ]
- [ Brad ] Who is it?
- Or what is it?
[ Paper Rustling ]
What is she doing here?
[ Chris ]
Whoa. Check out the talent, man.
No! Don't!
Oh, Miss.
Mademoiselle.
Parlez-vous anglais?
Listen, wait, wait.
Don't, okay?
Nothing's that bad. Hold it.
No, no, no, no, no.
Please, let me help you.
Okay?
- [ Screaming ]
- Andy!
The rope!
[ Grunts ]
[ Screaming ]
Ye-ah!
Yeah!
- [ Shouting ]
- [ Metal Clangs ]
Hey.
Hey, he's comin' around.
- Thank God.
- Hey, Andy, can you hear me?
Whoa. Don't move too fast.
You might puke or somethin'.
Hey, prince,
remember dropping this?
- Where is she?
- Who, Cinderella?
It was after midnight, man.
She split.
But that rescue, dude,
nice grab.
Talk about fallin' for a girl.
[ Laughs ]
Just remember
to tie off next time.
God. You saved my life.
Yeah, and you saved hers too.
So we figured we're in
for half your points.
That girl... talk about the woman
of my dreams.
I think we're losin' him.
Nurse! What?
- I have to find her.
- No, you have to get some rest.
- But she might try it again.
- Andy, she's obviously whacked.
The kind of girl jumps off
the Eiffel Tower has issues, man--
major issues.
- I have to find her.
- Get real, Miss Marple.
- Look, all we have is a shoe.
- The note.
Did you pick up the note?
She had a note in her hand.
If it's a suicide note,
maybe we could go find out who she is!
Okay, we'll find it. Just relax,
all right? Here, take your little toy.
# It ain't no joke I'd like
to buy the world a toke #
# And teach the world to sing
in perfect harmony #
# And teach the world to snuff
the fires and the liars #
Hi.
# So don't delay, act now
Supplies are runnin' out #
# Allow if you're still alive
six to eight years to arrive #
# And if you follow
there may be a tomorrow #
# But if the offer's shun #
# You might as well
be walking on the sun #
be walking on the sun ##
[ Children Shouting,
Echoing ]
Oh.
Hey! Hello!
It's me!
You forgot this.
Oh, mon Dieu!
Pardonnez-moi.
- Man, that hurts.
- Did you see a girl?
- She's stolen my heart.
- I know the feeling.
- Andy, what happened?
- Is he all right?
Hey, the girl,
she was just here.
- Go! Go after her! Come on.
- Andy, you need to get back
into bed, man.
- Hurry up. She's gettin' away.
- Poor guy's hallucinating.
- Andy, relax, relax. Relax!
- Hey!
- Andy, look. Good news, man.
- Yeah.
Ohh.
- [ Andy ] What's her name again?
- Serafine "Pie-gid".
- Serafine.
- Serafine Pigot. It's a beautiful name.
- Are you getting cold feet?
- Just a bit nervous.
I don't wanna say
the wrong thing.
- [ Door Unlocking ]
- You're on, prince.
- [ Woman Speaks ln French ]
- Serafine?
Uh, hi.
Uh, it's the guy who, um--
- I've got your shoe.
- [ Unlatching Numerous Locks ]
Hi, I'm Andy.
We met on the Tower.
This is Chris and Brad.
And, uh--
Listen, I thought that you
would want this.
And, well, it's not my size.
[ Chuckles ]
You're very kind.
Now, go, please.
You must not stay here.
- [ Latching Numerous Locks ]
- Charming.
And sophisticated.
Forget about it.
Let's go, Andy.
- Wait! Did you see what I saw?
- What?
She had blood on her hands.
She's trying it again.
Just so we're on the same page,
who's crazier here?
[ Locks Unlatching ]
Please go,
or there will be trouble.
Uh--
No, wait, wait.
What did you do to your hand?
Do you have blood on your hand?
You're bleeding?
[ Nervous Chuckle ]
No. I, uh--
It's just paint.
I'm redecorating the cellar.
Oh. I thought, uh--
Please, go, now.
Wait. Listen. Hold it.
We can help.
- We could have that done
in no time. Right, guys?
- No, thanks.
- Thank you.
- I--
-Please, look. I just wanna talk.
-I don't think it's a good idea.
Please, just once. If you let me,
we'll never bother you again.
Okay. Uh--
Tomorrow, 4:00,
in front of the concert hall?
You mean it?
I promise.
Now, go, please.
[ Numerous Locks Latching ]
- Excellent.
- I did it.
You mean you almost blew it.
Take advice from the experts:
You got to play it cool.
First thing we're gonna do
is work on your outfit.
Now, okay.
Remember. Eighty percent
of all these French girls
really go for that macho type.
Whoa, bonin' up on the Playboy.
Excellent.
Don't show any insecurities.
It's the worst. And, uh--
- Split. She's comin'.
- Here. Be prepared.
- Wait. Come on, Chris.
It's our first date.
- Are you a nun?
Be cool, and show attitude.
Serafine.
- Hi.
- I didn't recognize you.
- Oh, yeah. Um-- Well, it's bright.
- What would you like to do?
- I don't know. Is there a cafe?
[ Laughs ]
We're in Paris.
Oh.
- Mademoiselle.
- Merci.
- Monsieur.
- Merci beaucoup.
So, do your parents
mind us, uh, meeting?
- My parents are dead.
- [ Spitting ]
- [ Coughs ]
- You okay?
- Need some water?
- No, I'm fine. I do like coffee.
[ Blowing Nose ]
Most guys who ask me on a date
are usually trying to get me into bed.
That must be really terrible
for a girl when that happens.
Why should I think
you're any different?
Isn't that why you brought
your friends along?
To witness you score?
No, that's not it at all.
Chewing gum.
It's, uh, the rage
in the States.
[ Chuckles ] They take chewing gum.
They make it look like condoms.
It's like a practical joke.
- [ Latex Squeaking ]
- Nice.
And chewy.
I want you to blow
a big bubble for me.
What?
Well, it's a custom in France.
The bigger the bubble,
the more a boy likes a girl.
[ Disgusted Sigh ]
Wow. What a rip-off.
My friends told me it was chewing gum.
I thought--
I think it's best if I go.
No, no, please, don't go.
I'm just so nervous.
And the more I like a girl,
the more nervous I get.
And if you go now
and something happens to you,
then I'd blame myself
for the rest of my life because
I'd blown my chance to help.
The moment I saw you on the Tower,
I was so moved by your sadness.
I swore to myself I would
try to help, whatever it takes.
No one as beautiful
and sensitive as you...
can possibly deserve
to be so sad.
Oh, God. I hate myself.
I am not the kind of guy you think I am.
If I go, it's nothing
to do with you.
No one can help me.
And anyone who tries is--
I hope you're not sorry
that I saved your life.
It was the sweetest,
most courageous...
and selfless thing
anyone's ever done for me.
Monsieur, is this yours?
- [ Andy ] Uh--
- [ Speaking ln French ]
- [ Speaks ln French ]
- Hey, you don't use--
- [ People Gasping ]
- Arrete!
- Huh?
- Hey, don't you lay a finger on her.
[ Groaning ]
Hey, you were
somethin' else in there!
I'm sorry.
I got carried away.
Oh, no, that guy
had it coming to him!
Uh, hey.
How did you do that?
That-- That guy, he weighed--
I don't know. Uh--
Do you--
Do you work out?
Do you want me to leave?
I guess that means yes.
Wait. Stop.
I have to go now.
You mustn't get involved.
Wait. When do I
get to see you again?
I don't think we should. Andy,
it's only because I care about you.
You have a funny way
of showing it.
[ Chris ] Relax, man.
She's just playing hard to get.
This whole mysterious
elusive thing is just a ploy
to make her more interesting.
It's not that simple. The way
she talks about her parents,
it's like she blames herself.
Yeah. She's demented enough.
Remember the blood on her hands?
That stunt at the cafe?
[ Imitating Punches ]
It's like she's
a black belt or somethin'.
Bonsoir.
- Je peux vous aider?
- Um, we're just--
- Americans?
- Yeah.
I love Americans.
- May I help?
- Uh, yeah. We're looking for Serafine.
Sure. But I'm sorry.
She's not at home.
Are you her, uh, brother?
[ Chuckles ]
Let's just say l...
Iook after her.
Okay. Sorry to bother you.
- See ya.
- Let's go, Andy.
Wait.
If you guys are not
doing anything later,
come to our charity
"Full Moon" party.
It's for a good cause.
Thanks, anyway, but--
Serafine will be there. Just tell
the man at the door Claude sent you.
A little, uh, competition,
huh, Andy?
- Is this it?
- Club de la lune.
- Club of the loonies.
- [ Chris ] She's here, all right.
## [ Slow Rock ]
Hey, mec.
Tu veux entrer faire la fete?
Is he invited?
- American.
- Yeah, born and bred there, tiny.
Friends of Claude.
- Okay.
- Thank you very much.
- Merci beaucoup.
- De rien.
[ Cracks Knuckles ]
## [ Continues ]
[ Liquid Streaming ]
- She ain't here, man.
- I can't believe she'd be
at a dump like this.
[ Scoffs ]
Yeah, she's way too centered.
[ Claude ]
Glad you could come. Enjoy the party.
- Merci.
- Think he's boinkin' her?
Thanks a lot, Brad. I'm gonna go
back to the villa, see if she's there.
- No, no, no, I'll go. You stay here
in case she shows up.
- Would you?
- Yes.
- Thanks. I appreciate it.
[ Metal Squeaking ]
Serafine?
[ Dog Barking ]
Hello?
[ Serafine ]
Go away!
Go!
- What are you doing here?
- You're askin' me?
- Please, stay away. Go now.
- Don't you wanna get outta here?
- Just leave me alone.
- Oh, is this some kind
of kinky game or something?
Where are your friends?
- They're at Claude's party
waiting for you.
- Party?
Yeah. You know,
that-- that "Iunar" thing.
Oh, my God! They're in great danger!
Get the key! Over there.
Wait, wait.
What kind of danger?
- Just leave it to me.
- No way. If there's a problem,
I'm coming with you.
- It's much too dangerous, believe me.
- Now hold on a second, hot pants.
There's no way
that I'm gonna--
- ## [ Continues ]
- Bottoms up.
- [ Roars ]
- [ Screams ]
Americans.
You can tell a mile away.
[ Laughing ]
[ Groans ]
[ Coughing ]
- [ Heart Monitor Beeping ]
- [ Heavy Breathing ]
Hello?
Could use a little help
over here?
Thanks.
[ Bicycle Squeaking ]
Wait!
I must go in!
Serafine.
Is Claude expecting you?
- Open the door, quick.
- I'm not sure I can do that.
Would you rather have me
stay out here with you?
No, of course not.
[ Men Chanting ]
No-ha!
No-ha! No-ha!
- We must get out of here quick!
- Serafine.
- What's the matter?
- Do as you're told.
He's mine, Jack.
Your buddy just scored.
[ Grunts ]
Hey. Slow down.
Depuis quand tu laisses
partir mes invites, Jacques?
Viens avec moi.
[ Heavy Breathing Continues ]
Damn!
[ Spits ]
Yes!
Through there, hurry!
- Why? Where are we going?
- [ Panting ]
- [ Shirt Ripping ]
- Whoa.
- You must go before it's too late!
- What?
Now? We just got started.
[ Groans ]
I'll never understand women.
- Run! Your life is in danger!
- Really? Why?
- Is Claude your boyfriend?
- [ Groans ] Please, go.
[ Voice Deepens ]
Go. Go.
- Damn it, run!
- Serafine, what's wrong?
- [ Roaring ]
- What are you doin'?
[ Voice Cracking ]
Run! Run for your life, Andy!
## [ Continues ]
[ Roars ]
- [ Laughing ]
- [ Roaring ]
[ Neck Muscles Crack ]
[ Roaring ]
[ Growling ]
[ Bones Crunching ]
[ Roars ]
[ People Screaming ]
- [ Electrical Sparking ]
- ## [ Industrial ]
[ Brad ]
Andy?
- [ People Screaming ln Distance ]
- ## [ Continues ]
Andy? Sounds like the party
is just gettin' started up there.
[ Screaming ]
- Open the door!
- Sorry. Members only.
No scum allowed.
[ Werewolf Growling ]
[ Beeping Continues ]
[ Heavy Breathing Continues ]
[ Low Growl ]
[ Fabric Ripping ]
[ Rapid Beeping ]
Hey. Hey, you okay in there?
[ Low Growl ]
[ Screams ]
[ Roaring ]
Andy?
[ Low Growl ]
- [ Roaring ]
- [ Screaming ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Skin Tearing ]
[ Wolf Howling ]
Brad?
Serafine?
Great. Come to Paris
and check out les drains.
[ Footsteps ]
- Hello?
- [ Low Growl ]
[ Roaring ]
[ Screeching ]
Whoa.
[ Screaming ]
[ Grunting ]
- [ Straining ]
- [ Roars ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Wolves Howling ]
[ Birds Twittering ]
[ Insect Buzzing ]
## [ Slow Rap Playing
ln The Distance ]
Serafine?
## [ Continues ]
[ Object Bangs Window ]
[ Banging ]
- Hey, what the--
- Shh! Get outta there now!
Wha-- Why?
- There's a mutant in the cellar!
- A what?
That French girl,
she's a freak!
- [ Door Opening ]
- Get outta there, man!
- [ Groans ]
- Andy.
You must rest.
Lie down.
Hey, what happened last night?
How did I get here?
Relax. Let me look
at your leg first.
I was attacked...
by this big, wild dog.
It was huge. It had grande yellow eyes,
beaucoup teeth and--
- Do you have rabies here?
- You don't have rabies.
That's healing pretty fast.
How long have I been here?
Just a few hours.
It's your new metabolism.
- Drink this. You'll feel much better.
- What is that?
- It's all natural.
- Because I hate Clamato.
It tastes... different.
[ Insect Buzzing ]
Wait, something weird
is goin' on here.
- I gotta go.
- Shh.
- My friends. [ Gasps ]
- You mustn't. Please.
This will relax you, no?
I don't get it.
Last time we met,
you threw bricks at me.
Listen.
- You're not the same as you used to be.
- Only since I met you.
Seriously.
There's something I have to tell you,
but you have to promise me
you're not gonna freak out, okay?
- No, I'm a rock.
- Okay.
Um, the injury on your leg,
it was not from a dog.
It was--
[ Sighs ] It was a werewolf.
[ Laughing ]
- Yeah.
- I'm serious.
- And now you have become one too.
- [ Boisterous Laughter ]
Great. Oh, I get it.
I get it.
Not Cinderella.
Little Red Riding Hood now.
Whatever kinky game
you want to play, I am in.
[ Howling ]
- [ Growls ]
- [ Door Opens ]
[ Howling Continues ]
[ Chuckles, Continues Howling ]
[ Baying, Growls ]
[ Low Howling ]
Andy?
Hi.
I was havin' a bad dream,
I guess.
Um--
- Are you feeling better?
- No.
I guess l--
My hangover's doing fine.
You need to relax,
n'est ce pas?
- [ Roaring ]
- [ Screaming ]
[ Gasping ]
Oh, my God!
I thought, uh--
Oh, man. What did they put
in those drinks?
You were hallucinating. It's quite
normal for the transition period.
- Just try to relax, okay?
- "Transition period"?
Mm-hmm.
Wait. Was I dreaming,
or did you say I was a werewolf?
It's not a joke.
-[ Woman ] I told you this would happen.
-[ Gasps ] Mummy!
- Mummy?
- Leave it to me, please.
You're making the same mistake again.
First Claude, now this.
Can't you be more careful?
- This is different.
Claude stole my blood.
- Hey.
Um, Mrs. Pigot? Um--
Um, I know this looks really kind of--
How do you do?
Uh, I can explain.
It's really not her fault.
Uh, Serafine, could you introduce us?
You wouldn't want to meet me.
I'm not as attractive as I used to be.
Oh, come on.
I bet you two pass for sisters.
Wait a minute.
Hold it. Didn't you say
your mother was dead?
- [ Gasps ]
- [ Mother Screams ]
- You scared her away!
- I scared her?
Ha!
[ Panting ]
That's it.
My friends were right: You're nuts.
Nurses with walking corpses
stealing hearts...
and monsters and werewolves
in the basement and the whole
thing with the thing--
- Andy, let me explain, please.
- No, no. You already did.
I don't know what you dosed me with,
but I will not be the lab rabbit...
for some
psychotic experiment.
[ Jiggling Knob ]
- All right, just stay
away from me. Let me out!
- You must drink this.
- It's the only thing
that will help you.
- Not freakin' likely.
- You should do as she says.
- [ Screaming ]
[ Screaming Continues ]
Andy, hold on!
Andy, hold on! Wait a second!
Where are you going, American?
- [ Muffled Screams ]
- Shh.
I love Americans.
[ Camera Shutter Clicking ]
Hey, vous!
Ne passes pas!
- [ Speaking ln French ]
- No.
- [ Continues ln French ]
- Please, no!
Friend of yours?
I'm lnspector Leduc.
Homicide.
Do you take drugs,
Mr. "Mucdermott"?
It's McDermott.
No, I don't take drugs.
What really happened down there?
Why does almost every corpse
have its heart missing?
Ritual sacrifices?
Are you the member of a sect?
I didn't see.
I was chased... by a big thing.
Um, some kind of wild animal.
Test this man for drugs.
Huh!
[ Bell Tolling ]
[ All Noises lncreasing
ln Decibel ]
[ Chattering ln French Loudly ]
[ Panting, Sniffing Loudly ]
[ Boat Engine Humming Loudly ]
[ Water Bubbling Loudly ]
[ Birds Squawking Loudly ]
[ Dog Panting Loudly ]
## [ Piano, Blues ]
I said rare, bloody.
You understand?
# You know I'm the wolfman #
That'll do...
while I wait.
[ Pager Beeping ]
# You know I'm the wolfman ##
## [ Drums ]
[ Sniffing ]
[ Whimpering, Barking ]
- [ Speaking ln French ]
- Oh, um--
[ Girl ] Hi. Um--
[ Speaking Broken French ]
No. La bottle.
[ Continues Speaking
Broken French ]
[ Barking ]
[ Screams ]
Whoo. Whoa. I'm sorry.
American?
Yeah.
Uh, Andy McDermott.
Amy Finch.
And that's, uh-- [ Sniffs ]
Hot Kitty you're wearing.
- Wow.
- You want some food?
[ Sucking Loudly ]
[ Sucking Loudly, Giggling ]
- [ Belches ] Excuse me.
- Gar-kon!
- [ Laughs, Hiccups ]
- Monsieur?
- Another bottle
of the "Poo Willy Fwissy".
- Pardon?
- Le hooch de jour.
- [ Amy Giggling ]
I believe it's pronounced
Pouilly Fuisse.
[ Giggles ]
Um, hello.
[ Echoing ]
Are you getting fresh on me?
I'm sorry.
I don't know what's wrong with me.
I'm not normally like this, honest.
[ Laughing, Echoing ]
Right.
No, I'm serious.
The truth is I lost
my best friend today.
[ Laughing ]
- Bon apetit.
- [ Screams ]
You're dead! I saw them
pull you out of the canal!
- No, Monsiuer, the Atlantic.
- [ Laughing ]
Whoa! Get away from me!
Pull yourself together, Andy.
We have to talk.
Talk? Talk!
Wait, you're not real!
All right, let me go!
[ Laughing ]
Did you see--
[ Panting ]
Oh! What do you want?
Oh, sh--
This is a bad dream.
Right? You're not here.
- Are you?
- Andy, you were bitten.
You're already changing.
You would've never looked twice
at that bimbo in there.
All right, I may be upset...
or screwed up right now,
but I'm not a wolf!
Andy, I'm dead serious.
[ Chuckling ]
Dead?
That's funny.
That's really funny.
"Un-dead," actually.
Cursed to walk the earth
as a restless spirit...
till the werewolf
that did me dies.
- What do you want from me?
- What I want from you can wait.
Dump the chick
and lock yourself up.
And do it quick.
The moon's rising.
You're just jealous
'cause I'm about to score.
You know, you can't just pop up
and tell me what to do.
I don't even know
why I'm listening to you.
- I know you're dead
and so do the police.
- [ Zipper Zipping ]
[ Giggling ]
Mmm.
- [ Giggling Resumes ] Ooh, come here.
- [ Bell Tolls ]
Want some? Come here. Ooh.
Hey!
[ Growling ]
The night is young.
The moon is bright.
What do you feel
like doing tonight, tiger?
- # You gave me this #
- [ Growling ]
- [ Toy Beeping ]
- # Made me give #
Hey, hey!
Attends! Attends!
Qu'est-ce qu'on fait la-bas?
C'est mon ble la-bas.!
[ Laughing ]
Are you kidding me?
I love Jim Morrison. Yes.
- # Your silver grin #
- Come on.
- [ Amy Moaning ]
- # Still stickin' it in #
# You have broken in me #
# Broken me #
# All your mental armor
drags me down #
# We can't breathe
when you come around #
- [ Gasping ]
- # All your mental armor #
- # Drags me down #
- Oh! [ Giggling ]
- # Nothing hurts #
- Oh, my God.
- # Like your mouth, mouth #
- You're an animal.
- [ Growls ]
- # Mouth, mouth #
# Your mouth, mouth, mouth #
[ Gasping ]
Oh!
Ah! You're hot.
- [ Groaning ]
- Oh, you're burning hot.
- # All your mental #
- [ Gasping ]
- # Armor #
- Hey!
- Where are you going?
- # And your mouth, mouth #
# Mouth, mouth ##
Hey, you forgot
your pants, Romeo!
Amy, what have you gotten
yourself into... again?
[ Sighing ]
Always with these-these head cases.
I mean, who do you have to sleep
with to get a decent guy into bed?
[ Growling ]
[ Dog Whimpering ]
Just maybe somebody
to sleep in the wet spot for a change?
Maybe somebody to notice my hair?
Huh? ls that too much to ask?
- Huh?
- [ Water Bubbling ]
Andy?
- [ Screaming ]
- [ Growling ]
[ Growling ]
[ Panting ]
[ Growling, Sniffing ]
[ Roaring ]
[ Hiccups ]
[ Screaming ]
Wait! Stop!
I am policeman.
- [ Gasping ] Oh, thank God.
- [ Barking ]
Oh, you cured my hiccups.
- [ Growling ]
- [ Screaming ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Dog Barking ]
[ Werewolf Growling ]
[ Dog Whimpering ]
[ Camera Shutters Clicking ]
- Hey, what's goin' on?
- McDermott, you are under arrest.
What for?
The possibilities are limitless.
Take him away.
[ Engine Starts ]
Elle est la.
- Oh, my God.
- That's not all.
- Detective Ben Bou.
I had him follow you.
- This some kind of sick joke?
Wait here a moment.
[ Door Opens, Closes ]
Thanks for a lovely evening,
douche bag.
You really know how to show a girl
a good time, don't you?
No, no, no, no!
- You're dead!
- No! I ain't so lucky. I'm "un-dead."
And as your rotting sidekick,
I am cursed to remain
a restless spirit until you die.
- Not so fast.
- [ Screams ]
If you want my buddy dead,
nut ball, you're gonna have
to wait. I need him first.
He's no use to me
as a corpse.
Spent four years on Stairmaster
to get a package like this.
You ripped it like a lamb chop.
Don't blame me, Andy.
I warned you.
Wait. You mean,
you knew this all along? Oh!
- [ Grunts ]
- Hey, keep it down out there!
A guy can't rest in pieces
around here.
- I'm losing my freaking skull.
- Come on. Pull yourself together, Andy.
You gotta get outta here.
The cops wanna put you away for life.
I've had enough of your ridiculous
theories. The man is dangerous.
Lock him up!
McDermott, you're--
I didn't choose
to become a werewolf.
I can't face eating people
the rest of my life.
Better get used to it.
Isn't there any way that
I can become human again?
Yeah, there is,
but you're not gonna like it.
Tell me. How?
First, find the werewolf
that bit you.
Then kill it.
Then eat out its heart.
What?
But that means--
Serafine?
I-- No way.
- Andy, look out!
- [ Bus Horn Honking ]
- What did you do that for?
- 'Cause I still need him.
- He's gonna help kill the guy
who did this to me.
- I feel sick.
All of this would be over right now
if you hadn't opened your fat trap.
You are the most egocentric corpse
I've ever met.
Listen, I don't know what kind
of friend this jerk is to you,
but he ate my spleen.
So, hey. You guys
are werewolves too, huh?
Super.
- Glad to know ya.
- Andy.
I don't think you have accepted the gift
that has been given to you...
or much less appreciated it.
[ Claude ] We have a mission, Andy:
to purify the world.
That's why we pick our victims
from the scum of society.
The governments of the world
spent billions on medicine,
welfare, charity.
To what effect?
It only keeps alive
the weak, the stupid, the lazy,
who breed and multiply,
weakening the human race.
All my men, I have chosen...
for their loyalty,
their dedication to the coming age.
But you--
You were not
to have been.
You were an accident,
an anomaly.
I do not wish to kill you.
I pray you will join us in our rise
to become the new mankind.
Pure, free of disease.
Free from the trappings
of technological advance.
Will you join us, Andy?
I don't know. That's, you know--
That's a big decision.
- Mm-hmm.
- I'm gonna need some time
to think about that.
Sure.
[ Gasping ]
Andy?
- Well, what's that for?
- Kill him, Andy.
[ Claude ]
Cut out his heart.
Wait. Couldn't we just--
[ Sighs ]
Release him, Andy.
Join us.
You can't ask me to do this.
- Join us.
- I'd rather die.
And so you shall.
[ Serafine ]
Andy!
Serafine!
Down there.
Keep going.
- Jump!
- But Chris--
Jump!
[ Screams ]
Follow me.
[ Pounding ]
[ Panting ]
- What?
- Did you know?
- What is it?
- Did you know what he plans to do?
- [ Sighs ] Yes, I did.
- And you did nothing to stop him?
- Andy, l--
- How in God's name could you
just stand by--
For God's sake! Stop it!
We may have a cure.
Thierry, my stepfather.
- Claude?
- No.
You?
And my mother too.
For a time, I had managed
not to harm anyone.
Even the hearts my mother smuggled
from the hospital were from the dead.
Two months ago,
he was sure he had discovered...
a serum to suppress
my lycanthropic cycle.
Only it had
the reverse effect.
I immediately transformed.
My mother heard the noise
from upstairs,
and Thierry tried to escape
through the underground.
When I came to,
I saw I had butchered
my own parents.
Now do you see why
I was trying to kill myself?
It's not your fault.
Don't worry about me.
It's Chris who has problems.
We gotta get him
out of there.
[ Gasps ]
Claude is a bastard.
[ Car Brakes Screeching ]
Oh, brother, just who I need.
## [ Rock, lndistinct ]
Check the cellar!
Leave him alone, Claude.
- Out the back! Quick!
- [ Screaming ]
I warn you.
Don't interfere again.
# I am revved up
See him fall into the trees #
# I am on my knees #
# I don't know if I can
foot this bill #
# I'm supposed to leave ##
[ Barking ]
Yoo-hoo!
He's over here!
Cut it out.
- [ Grumbles ]
- Hey, he's hiding by the car!
- Qu'est-ce qui se passe la?
- He-- He's getting away!
Fools! Get over here!
- Ah, c'est toi, le chauffeur!
- I say, steady on, old man.
I never touched your car.
[ Shouting ln French ]
[ Gasps ]
Oh, oh. Great.
- [ Speaking French ]
- [ Yelling ln French ]
## [ Rock, lndistinct ]
- [ Beeping ]
- [ Serafine Gasping ]
[ Beeping Continues ]
- Sera--
- Hurry up!
[ Beeping Continues ]
- [ Panting]
- Serafine.
[ Crying ]
The cure. If he dies, we have no hope.
Serafine, it's--
He's gone.
Let it go.
- No.
- Yes.
[ Crying ]
They killed him,
the bastards.
[ Sniffling ]
What do we do now?
Well, let me have a shot at it.
But they ruined the lab.
So many years of hard work.
Did your stepfather leave any notes?
There.
What does that represent?
A werewolf's biorhythm...
and how it's governed
by the cycles of the moon.
Thierry tried to keep me below
the transformation threshold...
by injecting me with a depressant.
And it had a reverse effect.
- Yeah.
- All right.
Just so I'm totally clear here,
with this drug,
you can induce a transformation
at any time of the month?
Oh, my God. The samples.
He left them in the cupboard.
Over there.
Mon Dieu.
Oh, brother.
## [ Rock ]
Good luck.
- [ People Chattering, Laughing ]
- [ Man ] Hey, hey, what's up?
Hey, man.
# Put me out of my misery
Give me a place where
I know I can go #
# lnto your arms
I don't think so #
## [ Continues ]
- Mm.
- Sorry, we are full.
This building is closed.
Who gave you a permit for this party?
Ask the boss... inside.
## [ Rock, Faint ]
# Wild
I should've kept you out #
## [ Continues ]
- [ Music Stops ]
- [ Crowd Moaning ]
There he is!
Arrest that man!
Listen to me!
It's important!
You're all in great danger!
You have to leave the building now!
It's a trap!
I'm serious!
Please, listen to me!
- [ Man ] No!
- Skinheads are planning a massacre!
No! Stop!
- You have to leave the building!
- [ Crowd Booing ]
- All right, all right, all right.
All right.
- [ Crowd Cheering ]
[ Chanting ]
- Hey! Hey!
- Hey! Open that door!
Welcome, Americans,
to our lndependence party!
[ Cheering ]
I love you, Americans!
What great taste you have.
[ Claude ]
Every man on the planet...
must take every opportunity
to show his gratitude.
Because you share your culture
and resolutions with the whole world,
spreading it
to all other nations,
influencing all other cultures...
and touching the hearts
of millions.
Now I wish to share something...
with you.
I dedicate this party
to all you Americans,
whose heart I wish to touch
in return.
- Let the show begin.
- [ Cheering ]
## [ Rock ]
Chris!
[ Gunshots ]
- Stop them! Stop them!
- Enough!
- Stop them!
- You are all under arrest!
The party is over!
Everybody else, go home!
Inspector!
## [ Continues ]
Come on. Come on!
Come on. Move. Move!
[ Grunting ]
Allez! Quoi?
## [ Stops ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Werewolf Panting, Growling ]
Send for reinforcements!
We got a massacre!
Stop or I'll shoot!
[ Gunfire ]
[ Engine Starts ]
[ Screaming ]
Allez-y!
[ Crowd Shouting ]
- Serafine!
- [ Growling ]
[ Shrieking ]
I'll show you.
Claude went down
that trap door.
It's true. Look.
Huge creatures covered in hair. Look.
Huh? That's impossible.
Just what I said... drugs.
[ Screams ]
Brad!
Andy, you got him.
[ Brad ]
Whoo-hoo! You shot him!
- I'm gonna miss you, Andy.
- Me too.
- I'm so sorry.
Come on. I'm over it.
Good luck, you guys.
It's that lunatic!
Stop them!
I didn't say shoot them.
Go that way.
I'll meet you on the other side.
Each take a corridor.
[ Bonnet ]
lf you need help, whistle.
[ Low Growling ]
[ Snarling ]
- [ Growling ]
- [ Gunshot, Pistol Clicks ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Footsteps Descending Stairs ]
[ Gunshot ]
[ Hitting Flashlight
Against Palm ]
[ Growling ]
- [ Growling ]
- [ Screaming ]
[ Snarling ]
[ Snarling Continues ]
- [ Clicks ]
- Merde!
[ Clicking ]
Andy!
[ Snarling ]
[ Shrieks ]
[ Growling ]
[ Shrieking ]
[ Gunshot ]
[ Werewolf Shrieking ]
Serafine.
Oh, my God! Oh!
Just hang in there, okay.
I'm gonna get you outta here.
[ Gasping ]
Oh, Andy.
- I won't make it.
- Huh? Don't quit on me now.
[ Grunting ]
Stop the pain, please.
[ Groaning ]
I can't.
[ Panting ]
Eat my heart, Andy.
Let yourself go.
Serafine, I'd rather kill myself.
For both of us then.
It hurts so much. Please.
Please.
We'll be free.
[ Gasps ]
Police!
Qui va la?
[ Gasping ]
Hurry, while you still can, please.
- He's trying to kill her.
- I love you.
- Drop the knife!
- [ Serafine ] Please.
No, I can't.
Listen, let them help you.
Everything'll be okay. I promise.
Stop, or I shoot!
I gotta get Claude!
He's the last one!
[ Gasping ]
[ Screaming ]
Oh, man.
Idiot.
[ Train Rumbling ]
[ Growling ]
- Oh, geez.
- [ Growling Continues ]
[ Brakes Squealing ]
[ Speaking ln French ]
[ Murmuring ]
[ Pressing Button ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Screaming ]
- [ Man Screaming ]
- [ Werewolf Growling ]
- [ Screaming Stops ]
- [ Growling Stops ]
- [ People Screaming ]
- [ Werewolf Growling ]
[ Crowd Murmuring ]
[ Paramedic ]
We're losing her.
- We're losing her.
- Okay. Pepsulin 190.
Eight milliliter. Hurry up.
[ Siren Wailing ]
[ Grunting ]
You!
Oh!
[ Growling ]
- [ Screaming ]
- [ Snarling ]
[ Screaming Continues ]
[ Growling ]
[ Howling ]
Andy, you're wonderful.
I love you.
Je t'aime.
My name is Bruno, actually,
but I'm easy.
- Are you sure you want
to go through with this?
- Mm-hmm.
- Are you scared?
- A little.
- Guys, someone's comin'.
- [ Serafine Sighs ] Let's do it.
Yeah.
Yeah, let's do it. Quick.
- Give me the ring.
- Oh, okay.
Okay.
- I got it.
- No, I got it!
[ Screaming ]
Yeah!
No!
Andy!
[ Both Shouting Joyfully ]
# All your mental armor
drags me down #
# We can't breathe
when you come around #
# All your mental armor
drags me down #
# Nothing hurts #
# Like your mouth #
# Mouth, mouth #
# Your mouth, mouth, mouth ##
# Whatever, whatever #
# Girl, I'll do #
# Forever and ever
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah #
# I'll see you through #
# Because I've got
to keep you pleased #
# ln every way I can #
# I'm gonna give you
all of me #
# As much as you can stand #
# I'll make love
to you right now #
# That's all I want to do #
# I know you need it, girl
and you know I need it too #
# 'Cause I found #
# What the world
is searching for #
# Here, right here
my dear #
# I don't have to look
no more #
# And all my days #
# I've hoped and I've prayed
for someone just like you #
# To make me feel
the way you do #
# Never, never
gonna give you up #
# I'm never, ever
gonna stop #
# Stop the way
I feel about you #
# Girl, I just can't
live without you #
# I'm never, ever
gonna quit #
# 'Cause quittin'
just ain't my shtick #
# Gonna stay right here
with you #
# Gonna do all the things
you want me to now ##
# Fill me up
Tear me down #
# Hear how he dropped that ball
six months now #
# They kicked me out #
# Used to pick on me #
# Now on the cover
of your magazine #
# Without a reason #
- # What has changed #
- # Changed, changed, changed #
# Don't make me laugh #
# I won't kiss your ass #
- # I will not do it #
- # I will not #
- # I wouldn't know how to do it #
- # I would not #
- # I'll make it from the start #
- # Make it from the start #
# I'll give her half my heart #
# Think about it twice as much #
# Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah #
# I'm married now #
# Since yesterday #
# You are in love
with me, girl #
# ln love with me, girl #
# Well, I won't do it #
# I think you're down
in the dirt #
# 'Cause I want nothing #
# And I won't do it
but, baby, I'll do it #
# You can get my best #
# Oh, yeah #
# It's a sick, sick love #
# It's a sick, sick love ##