Transcription Enigmatica
The Tale of the Mummy
Valley of the Kings, Egypt
August 15, 1948
The Turkel Expedition
Day 262
Allah Akbar
Sir richard..Sir Richard..
Sir Richard?
Come in, Nabil
- We discovered an entrance, it faces to the north.
- Are you certain of this?
But this is wonderful news my boy.
This is wonderful news..
- Do we have a name?
- No name..
I see.
Very well, we'll inform the others.
Here's to the lost treasures of men.
It's not about the treasure.
It's about history.
The investors don't give a whit about
history. Unless they can sell it
"Then they might be disappointed.
According to Nabil
the inscriptions make no
mention of an occupants name.
What's in a name? It what he possessed
in life that counts on the open market.
On the contrary Mr.
Young, to the ancients a
man's true essence is
contained in his name.
Removing that from the
entrance to the tomb..
Was considered a banishment
from the hereafter.
Surely the best people we know
are going to hell anyway.
There is no hell, only none-existence.
"Richard Turkel August fifteenth 1948"
Day 262
Nine months of digging and finally
an entrance has been discovered.
My hunch proved correct
Let along this secluded
stretch lie a series of tombs.
But who would be buried here?
A Pharaoh, I presume
Hidden safely from ancient thieves
Today we uncover the truth.
- I... I can't move! I'm stuck!
- Don't panic Parsons. Breath through your nose!!
Blow it out of your arse
- what? Same to ya!
The burial chamber must lie beyond.
Astonishing..
A virgin seal, unbroken.
- You mean no looters?
- It would appear not
- Lucky for us.
- Not luck, more a matter of fear.
It's the curse, isn't it?
Of course, it is a curse.
Well, what's it say?
Listen all who now have being avoid this
place, abandoned by all that is... holy
I who have slaughtered the innocent I who
have... confused terror with ...pleasure
Obviously lacking in self
esteem. Oh well, as long..
As he was rich, we won't
hold it against him.
We have a name
Talos!
Shall we begin?
History Beckons
No, no that's sacrilege! We are
archaeologists, we're not grave robbers.
Now be careful! What ever
you say "sire Richard".
Expect we'd be remembered more fondly
then the bloke on the other side
Wait!
- What the devil you suppose that was?
- I suppose it was the wind.
Impossible!
Get out of here!!
Save yourself!
What..is..happening...
O God!
Help Nabil!
Hey, pull me out. Hurry up you bastards!
Pull me up!
God forgive us..
January 1999
Day 262
Nine months of digging and finally an
entrance has been discovered.
But who would be buried here?
A Pharaoh, I presume.
Hidden safely from ancient thieves.
Today we uncover the truth
Digits. I see digits,
a series of numbers
four, four being
"January", four being,
April... April the a ..
April the twentieth
That's my granddad's birthday.
How do you do that?
Don't know. Kinda spooky really,
I just see, oh everything.
He obviously deduces it from
the inane series of questions
he's been asking, it is a
trick, it's a very old one.
Yeah, well I will give
you a hand with that...
Come here Miss, I'll give you a buckle.
Oké folks. The old coot finally
worked out all the glitches.
We go in one hour.
This is Operations
Control can you hear me?
- Professor Marcus, Is that you,
I don't believe it.
- Good afternoon mister Cortese
Claire you little minx.
Giving out my number again?
Knock it off Cortese.
This is not a god-damn field trip.
"Thank you doctor Mulrooney.
Load and clear as usual.
Getting in. Sensors on.
We got a self reading at 0.24 procent..
Professor, did you get that?
Mister Cortese would you please
adjust your image stabilizer.
Thank you!
We're in position at 24-30.
GPS Reading...
three meters down four meters...
Temperature six degrees
centigrade and dropping.
We've reached point zero.
I think it's appropriate a
Turkel does the honours.
We're through the seal!
The inner chamber.
It's at least a 100 meters wide.
- Holy shit!
- What is it? What have you found?
"Talos"
In a sarcophagus...
suspended from the ceiling.
..and bodies...
everywhere!
It's nothing like what history
thought us to expect.
Well the history books
are just been rewritten.
Whatever...
They obviously never
wanted this guy to get out.
The dead were interred with the objects
they valued most in life.
It was only proper they should entomb Talos
within his own chamber of horrors
- Professor, Can you see this?
- Yes, Samantha, yes I see it.
It's magnificent..oh..
Worship of the stars was standard
practice. The sun in particular.
Yes, but these are planets...
Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars.
Perfect alignment!
Cortese, are you al-right?"
cut you off..
Noooo
Brad?
Brad what's wrong
Stop it.....
Brad wil you slow down..
..S t o p I t...
Stop it!
!! Stop it!!
Breathe Brad!
Breathe...
Burke, what are you doing?
Have you lost your mind?
- Breathe!
- Burke, what the hell are you doing?
Burke... come back!
Remember that token of our
engagement I never got you.
..about time to do a Cartier!
Fine Burke, you made your point.
You just come down slowly.
The Wadjet eye...
Exquisite
Burke, it's not worth it
it is not worth it...
Burke, don't move!
Burke..
Here you go...
Burke, look I got it now...
just..just come back slowly
aarrgghhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!
O my!
London, seven months later
- Hi Sam.
- Hi Trouble.
Hello baby.
Are you're hungry, hmm?
In Rome religious leaders from over a dozen
nations agreed that the impending planetary
alignment directly correlates
With the biblical cleansing
known as Judgement Day
Conversely scientist in Geneva
stressed that such an event
has in fact occurred many times
in the past, under the exception
of high tides and possible tremors
should in no way be construed
as a prelude to Armageddon.
The British Museum summons you to the past
the materials presented here
were recovered form a hidden
chamber in the Valley of the Kings
the wrappings are all that
remains of the Mummy: Talos lonPey
Ladies and gentlemen, the museum is now closed
please make your way to the nearest exit
Thank you for your cooperation.
Excuse me Sir, I am afraid
we're closed for this evening.
Professor, I'm sorry.
I didn't realize it was you.
No need to apologize
for doing your job Carl.
Oh, I didn't know it was so late.
Time stands still for no-one he?
Wouldn't you agree Prince?
Uh, this way Professor. Please let
me show you to the south wing.
Carl?
My God!!
We had a break in, room 32. One man down!
Request medical assistance!
I'll open the gate.
Hold on don't move him just yet.
The Americans are sending down
one from their lot to take a look.
Very well. We do not want to
create an international incident.
He was Terence Moore, United States Senate.
Here on holiday.
I knew he had to be pretty hot
to get you out of bed..
- Jesus Christ
- Very clean.
Both eyes extracted with the
optic nerve fully intact.
- What for?
- What do you mean what for?
There is no reasonable explanation
for an act of this kind.
In the mind of the killer there was...
- And you are?
- That's detective Riley, US Embassy.
Like you said, not done
with an ice-cream scooper.
Nah, that's precision
hand at work here.
Do you know if the eyes were removed
before or after the neck got crushed?
O my God, I should hope after!
Well we can all hope.
But maybe our killer prefers to see his
victims suffer a little before they go.
Victims? Excuse me aren't we jumping
just a bit ahead of ourselves.
What'd you find on him?
Eh, credit cards, Rolex,
pretty much everything
He wasn't mugged for his money!
This wasn't a thrill kill.
- Look, I need all details.
- You'll have to wait for the post-mortal..
- Oké, why you still here?
- Let's go...
He's probably watching us right now.
Hoping we'll appreciate the effort.
SAM
PLEASE READ
..PLEASE BELIEVE
THE TRUTH
Dr. Mulrooney...
that man's been phoning all morning.
Sounds stark raving mad,
do me a favour will you,
if he calls again, tell
him I've been transferred.
Thank you..
Stoopid.. Start..
So we got two victims.
First one's eyes
couldn't be seen. Second
one looses their lungs
- What else they have in common?
- They're both foreigners..
- Right. So what does this tell you?
- They weren't chosen at random.
Good, so eh.. find out
if Grasby had any ties,
occupational whatever,
to the American, and eh..
..call the consulate, see if there's
any relatives we can talk to.
Erm..give me that..
- Ah
- What's that?
Looks like Gauze
I know that smell
that's spice...
.. cinnamon
Don't worry, I'm a little
wizard in the kitchen
Pussywhipped is what you are
Yeah, you should go out more...
Pass, me water!
Thanks.
Oh, hello Bradley. Looking
uncommonly insane these days.
I think I mentioned that you look pretty
chic yourself. And of course there's
also that bug that's crawling right up your
arse, is still alive and kicking Clair!
- Now... Why wouldn't you take my calls?
- Let go of my arm.
- Why wont you take my calls?!
- You want me to call the guard?
I tell you, you know it's started don't you?
We found it, we're responsible and we
got three days to find it again.
Take some advice, Bradley oké
Take the same three days and find
yourself a really good shrink.
Please look, if we don't find
this thing... if we don't find...
What thing? I mean
Bradley, there never was a
thing. Talos is dust, if
he ever even existed!
What about the museum.. what about the museum?
What about three deaths in one week, Claire!!
..you don't see, but I can see..
- see, I see, I see everything!
- Jesus Christ
- Listen to me, let me be your guide..
Oh you know eh, if it's all the same
to you I'll take the unguided tour.
Claire,
Thursday 10:55
If it is not stopped, it's gonna be the beginning
of the end of the world for all the time..
- Hey... you want to make a move?
- I need to take a leak first.
Sir Richard Turkel Research Foundation
Miss Turkel's office?
Thank you.
Yes?
- I am looking for a Miss Turkel
- That's me. How can I help?
If you can spare a few
minutes away from your work?
Yes, sure..
Um.. just carry on..
I just so happens that that
worthless pile of rags is priceless..
- Only to people like yourself.
- Hah, right!
Does that make me a suspect then?
Merely an expert. Mister Bradley
Cortese, you hear from him lately?
He's just fired from another job last week.
Been MIA ever since.
I see from your reaction, he's
more then just a colleague?
What's that supposed to imply?
I level with you Miss Turkel, our
suspect profile points to an
unstable individual with serous
ties with this Talos exhibit.
..You're looking in the wrong place..
Brad, has his problems, yes.
But violence is not one of them.
Were you and Cortese lovers?
I don't think that is any of your
business, one way or the other.
I am only concerned for
your safety, Miss Turkel.
Bottom-line, if our man is linked to this exhibit
- He is linked to me..
I'll be extra cautious, Detective.
My pager..
If there's anything you need.
Day or Night.
In fact there is something. My grandfather's logbook
was one of the items ceased from the museum..
When can I expect it back?
It's just that I ..um..
It means the world to me..
You have my word, you get it back
the second we're done with it.
Well, let's see if you're a man of his word.
Our victims turn three arrived at
Heathrow on September the seventh.
But they're on different airlines..
Security reported nothing unusual.
Most likely he targeted them when they landed.
..Oh for God sake!
Postal service, mister Cortese. I got a packet
that needs a signature.
Mister Cortese?
Shit!!
GUARD DIES IN BIZARRE MUSEUM THEFT
MURDER MADNESS GRIPS LONDON
EDITH BUTROS
SPIRITAL HEALING
Riley! Come look at this
It looks like, you and Cortese
are on to the same Princess.
I'll get a car over to her place.
Son of a bitch!
Barton are you're okay? Barton?
- Barton?
- Erh perfect..
Shit!!
- Detective?
- Miss Turkel.
- This couldn't be a coincidence.
- It could, but isn't.
I've found this in Cortese's flat
I could use some of your experts advise.
What?
Let's get to my office.
Good news for a change?
Business as usual, eh Doc..
- Night
- Night night
Oké, this is the ..eh.. core of the myth..
According to the inscriptions Talos had the organs
intentionally removed from his body by his own followers.
The cult believed that one day their
Prince would come back and reclaim them.
These organs were they taken
in a particular order?
The Eyes..
The lungs..
The pituitary gland..
The liver... the jaw
last but not least
the Heart..
What's it mean?
Resurrection?
- Well more accurately transmutation
- oh a scrabble word.
It's a term the alchemists used..
It means to ..um.. restore man to his
prime-ordeal condition of grace..
Strength, perfection and..
Eh.. physical immortality.
So what happens now?
He gets picked up, hopefully before
he commits his next atrocity.
- Yeah, that is if he
committed any to begin with.
For your friends sake, why don't you
tell me what you think is going on.
- Because Riley, you'd never believe me. Not in..
- 3,000 years?
Hey listen..
I have been on the Gold dig myself, and I
just happen to know a fine Irish pub
A cop named Riley knows a fine
Irish pub, you surprise me..
- Am I still wasting my time Miss Turkel?
- Why don't you call me Sam.
EDITH BUTROS
Spiritual healing 3rd Floor
- Bradley, you got to turn yourself in Oké
- Insanity!!
All they's gonna do is lock me up!
That all they's gonna do, LOCK ME UP!
Edith..., I am the worlds only saviour!
Well then it's your obligation to
tell the authorities what you saw.
Talking Gibberish..
Gone....Everyone is gone!
But you got me, you're
not gonna loose me..
Al-right?
I'm going with you..
Put the phone, putt the... putt
the phone down... Edith now!!
You need to help, Bradley
I know bloody shit Sherlock, and you Edith are it
You are not gonna deny me Edith
you're not gonna deny me!
I want you Edith to take me to
the eyes of his next victim..
I feel ashamed to admit, I gave very
little thought of Burke's death
You're defences were up?
No..
My mind was on that sarcophagus...
and the wrappings..
Heh...
the un-presence
For weeks and no one would go
near them not even the flies
They just lie there,
half buried in the sand
And madness to go to the camp... and
none of us seem to have any control over
It affected everyone..
Each in totally different ways
it was the darkness...
you could.. we could feel
You're cut off
I wasn't the only one who felt it, Riley
It had power. It was tangible
Argh, my heart's racing
That because it's not yours
it belongs to the other
Gonna bust out of my chest
Remember this isn't your vision..
- Oké, I'm ready, Edith.
- Release! Open your eyes
Where are you, Bradley?
Still in London
I'm going down some stairs
It's cold. I'm walking..
I'm walking on my hands..
I know what stop it is..
I know where he's going, Edith!
Let's go!
Get out of the way!
..get out of my way..
..out of my way..
What's happening Queeny?
What do you smell?
Al-right then, go and get your supper.
What's up girl.
What's happening?
O my god... Queeny what's the matter?
Get out of the way
get out... of the way
Queeny, Queeny come on!!
Queeny! Queeny!
What have you done to my dog?
Enough!!
Killer!
- you stupid bastard..You don't understand.
- Where's my dog?
- You don't understand.
- Where is my dog?
- Get off me!!
- You okay to go up alone?
- Yeah, yeah, I'll be fine.
Brad knows better than to show up here.
It's not Brad you're afraid of.
Go on say the name: Talos
I think Brad heard voices.
I didn't tell you first hand that he .. is dangerously
obsessed with this whole .. past lives theme.
Maybe..
But what if just this once, the voices
that somebody was hearing were real?
Night Riley..
Disgusting Bastards
Argh..
Oh shit!
- Dispatch to Riley, over.
- What's up?
Bradley Cortese has been spotted in
the vicinity of Notting Hill Gate
Shit!
No, I don't hear you...
- hello?
- Got ya!
Brad, um .. I can't
talk right now,
Don't hang up, don't hang up,
I'm gonna go crazy if ya hang up!
Brad, I'm on my way out I have a date.
O, with that cop, is that your date?
That cop that lied to me?
Where are you?
You sound scared, Sam...
I don't blame you..
- You should be.
- O god, Brad!
What are you doing here?
What happened? Whose blood is it?
- It's not mine
- Whose is it?
- It's from the one he.. eh.. got before you.
What are you talking about?
He wants what you got, Sam!
You can't let him take it..
Help me... help me by saying you understand?
Please...
Of course I understand,
I was there remember, Yeah?
- Kneel down, Sam
- wha .. what?
- Kneel down..
- What?
For what?
What are you doing?
You don't need to worry..
I will see, I will see you on the flip side.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Stop this Brad.
Don't worry, because I'm
gonna be right behind you...
Please...
Brad, stop it!
What are you doinggg?!
Brad stop!
- Brad!!
- forgive me, Sam
- Noooo!
Can't resist.
For the purpose of this interview Mr.Cortese agreed
to wave his rights to have a lawyer present.
It's not a lawyer I need, it's a undertaker.
Cause you are talking to a dead man..
Dead man talking..
Why do you want to harm Miss Turkel?
Don't wanna harm her, she's my family.
It's like a bloody sister.
What about them? Were they like
your brothers and sisters?
No...
Take a good look. Did he piss you off?
No, not him. It's just it..
.. it's what inside him
His Liver
Yes, 'officer Dibble', his
liver pissed me off!!
If you can't have a pass to piss you off,
you can't let out the anger, is that it?
Mmm, what if it blows your head back, baby?
- You smug bastard!
- Barton!
- Go get some air
See ya..
Your mate is... a tad pissed off, I can tell...
Naturally. He is convinced that we have our man.
- O, no not me, officer Dibble it's someone else.
- Then prove him wrong! ....Who?
I tell you for a fag.
You see your mystery, officer..
Started about 3,000 years ago.
And your suspect was a Greek
heretic exiled from his home land..
..for performing acts of .. sorcery..
His name was, and still is: Talos.
Five years later a man called Talos
Ionpey arrived in ancient Egypt.
He was cultured, he was charming,
he is a master of language, mathematics..
And... the dark science.
This impressed King Amenhotep, and Talos quickly
became part of the royal family inner circle..
Not long after he wed the King's
stunning daughter Nefrianna..
Ah, Nefrianna worshipped her dark Prince..
Those who opposed his particular brand of
theology were struck down with disease.
Or worse, he tortured to believe him!
They bring factions, pleaded with King Amenhotep to
put an end to this mad foreigners reign of terror
So you see... an assassination was plotted
But again the poor old King miscalculated.
He informed Nefrianna of his intended deed.
And she in return told her Dark Prince.
Talos decided if he was going to die,
it will be on his own terms..
The Kings battalion stormed the chamber.
But the Prince had come up with the perfect plan..
..to preserve his soul, for his eventual return
Mummification!!!
But for the King the worst
horror was yet to come..
For deep inside the chamber
the embalmers were discovered
Cannibalizing Prince Talos his organs..
His own daughter chewing on the heart..
Well, the King promptly put
the followers to death..
He himself impaling Nefrianna upon the spikes..
And Talos?
Talos?
Well you see, his body was never found!
Only the wrappings.
And inscribed inside the chamber
it says that his soul ..
'Kah'... awaits in purgatory
until the day of his rebirth.
Which happens to be this Thursday.
At 10:55. When the planets align?
So these four victims...
.. are all reincarnations of his followers
No, officer Riley, it's five you see.
You're forgetting the dog.
Who said you have to come
back wearing the same skin?
..You still don't get it, do ya?
Don't you see he taking back his organs?
So he can live again..
I saw Nefrianna's face in that chamber.
I saw Sam's face!
She is the final carrier. Her grandfather
was the final link in the chain!
It fed them . . the moment
that tomb was uncovered.
She is not responsible for the crimes of her
forefathers, but she is accountable for their sins!
..kill her!
Fuck off!!
God .. Someone has to destroy the heart!
Take a look, take a look and see mush
..seeing that's believing.
Believe!
Believe..
- Inspector, what's the word on Cortese?
- We're holding him till morning.
Where do you want me to stick him?
I could make a suggestion..
Eh..stick him in number 5.
Brad, not moving you until tomorrow. We can do
this the nice and easy way or the bullshit one.
- Well, the nice and easy way every time.
- That's a change..
- Shit! It's started.
- What did we just say?! No bullocks!
- Get out of here
O, hello..
I'm sorry
Jesus!
How's he doing?
He get himself a padded cell.
Double security
It's better than his victims
Hand delivered as promised.
Look for whatever reason, that tomb
brought grief to a good number of people.
.. If it means anything..
I think maybe your grandfather
had the right idea all along.
Thanks..
Coming from you, it does..
(TV) We interrupt our regular
programming to bring you this
live on the scene bulletin from
the City Police Headquarters..
Two corpses are now being
removed by medical personnel
One of the deceased is believed
to be a Detective Barton
a leading officer in the
grizzly murders that began..
Stay indoors until you hear from me, you have
round the clock protection untill he's nailed.
- Forget it, I'm coming with you..
- Sam please, I have no time to argue.
Oké Riley, on one condition, you give me your
word this is not come off until I take it off.
Is this a joke, you see what's happening out
there? - Yeah, it is a joke .. you and me?
Instant Cadaveric Spasm, it's
obvious from the discolouration..
And severe trauma to the
neck, crushed the vertebrae.
Happened just like that!
I don't imagine he suffered much.
Tea?
In Point effect is N. Rope loop, five letters.
- Noose.
- No, I meant a spot of tea
You know, like Lipton's
- O, sounds lovely.
- how are you on lemon?
- Lemon, Thank you!
Help! Someone help me!
Help!
Let me in!!
Sam, Sam what is going on?
- There's something out there..
- wha what.. No no no,
- There's something out there!!
It's Sam from 28. She's upset..
- It's Sam from 28
- There is nothing there, please no
.Help... Stop!
Please help me..
Stop!
Please....!
- Eye witnesses?
- A whole bunch.. all dead
If cats could talk, he?
Evening Standard
Only ten hours to go, read all about it
four planets unite... Eeeevening Standard.
"Edith Butros, you pleased
to make my acquaintance.
This is .. Detective Riley, I came across
your card in Brad Cortese's apartment.
- What sort of trouble is he in now?
- I'm afraid he is way past all that.
Brad's dead?
He was saying some..eh ..
Unusual things before he went..
- Too unusual to believe
- Well you believe him..
Yeah, just about..
Al-right..
I'll do what I can for you.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
Professor Marcus, I'm detective Riley.
Ah yes, yes, yes.
I came as soon as I received your message.
Any further news about Sam?
Not yet... I've spoken with Dr. Mulrooney,
and she's agreed to rendezvous.
Ah begrudgingly, I'm sure.
So you believe that this thing has gone after Sam
..to eh .. reclaim it's heart?
According to Bradley the final piece of the
puzzle resides within her bosom.
Bradley Cortese is a psychotic,
listen to yourself! This is insane!
Or it's prophecy!
We have less than five hours to find her.
Does anybody have reasonable suggestions?
Well, I have one somewhat unorthodox one.
Why am I not surprised, it
involves the spirit world no doubt.
- We need a vessel to contact her.
- Something with spiritual resonance.
You know for Sam I was willing to listen to
anything bordering on the rational, but this..
Claire please..
Doctor wait... Wait, wait, wait
Look I don't expect you to put your faith
into something I only half believe myself.
But if there's a chance, one shot in a million, that
what that woman claims she can do, will help find Sam..
I am willing to give it a try.
Look eh, I'm scared oké, I mean,
you can understand that can't you?
Yes.
Absolutely.
Al-right, you win, what do you need?
You're with "Samantha now
what is she showing you?
- Look I am sorry, but am I the only one..
- Doctor please, please..
Excuse me, but I mean
she talking to a dead body..
Death doesn't exist, it's
only a transference of energies.
And if we can tap into his before it moves on..
He's found her..
Ask her to guide you..
Have her show you where she is!
- Al-right, let's concentrate.
- Give me your hands..
Close your eyes..
Help!
- This can't be happening
- Where is she, Brad?
Tell us what she sees?
Bradley, her eyes are your eyes!
Have her tell us what she sees!
The Pyramid Hotel
What do you see?!
Bradley?
Where is she, Bradley?
- I saw that...
- Yeah, I saw that..
Bradley...!
Symbols? What do they mean?
Literal translation
Under the pyramid..
On the water.
Does it trigger anything?
No, I'm afraid not.
You know there's a construction site on the Thames?
The skeleton of one of those old super Hotels.
Ah yes, I remember. During the
initial phase... a level collapsed.
A completion was suspended..
Sound like his kind of hotel..
Yes, but if it were, I mean, how do you stop
something that hasn't died in 3000 years?
The wadjet’s eye symbolizes
the left eye of Horus..
.. Ripped out during his battle with Seth!
It possesses extraordinary powers of protection,
we must keep it with us at all times.
What you mean this is it. This is our only
weapon against this force you been describing?
Fuck!
Waterloo bridge is our best hope.
Now step on it!
We never make it through the gridlock
do you know an alternate route?
What about this one?
This is it..
Stand clear
Come on..
Watch your step..
Hurry up!
- Only 18 minutes left.. How's your ankle holding out?
- I'll be fine!
Let's Go!
I have defeated..
..the will..
..of Amon Ra!
Never before..
..have human eyes..
..feasted upon such ...splendorrr.
Rise and Kneel at the feet of Talos
Nefrianna, does not kneel
at the order of infidels..
What!!
Ah, she could be anywhere..
So why don't we split up?
That way we can cover more ground!
Yes, yes good idea.
Come, we go this way.
This way.. yes?
- Damn!
- It's OK, it's OK I got light
- I got ya...
Talos!
- Good evening Professor Marcus.
- You know my name!!
As I know your mind..
Countless hours spend at the museum
you stand there in my funerary containment..
Wondering what it would be
like to speak to a deity?
- Yes.. yes
- No!!
Fight him.. Professor, he's trying
to control your mind. Fight him!
Begone, less you feel these knives of light!
The mighty Amon Ra commands you!!
Begone!
Begone!!
Begone!!!
We did it professor.
We did it..
Be quiet Butros..
Be quiet!
On your knees in worship!
O my goodness, what have I done?
What have I done?
The light..
- We have 6 minutes!
- Oké
Look I can't wait. We are out of time!
- I know..
Here give me that!
Now go on, come on who's the doctor?
Gender: Male - Age: 35
Deliver to: Dr.Claire Mulrooney
Professor, there no time for that!
- Doctor! Where is Mr. Riley?
- O don't worry about him..
What you doing with our palm reader?
No no, not me. That thing, it came to me.
I couldn't fight it back
What thing, Marcus?
There's nothing here...
Well, you were right,
extraordinary powers of protection.
Talos!
It came to you didn't it.
What did it promise you?
Pompous arse.
Who are you to speak his name?
You created the history you teach
What are you saying?
Where is Mr. Riley?
Exactly where he is suppose to be...
At exactly the right moment!
O my Prince..
Sam?
Sam!
Riley!
- It's all real..
- I know..
Get away from her!
Now your time has come, Princess!
Don't let him win, Riley!
Don't let him win..
Do it! Do it now!
I am very sorry ..
You'll never have your princess
I've already have my princess
The female served a noble purpose.
Her bloodline led you back to me..
So fickle your Highness, falling in..
And out of love the way you do.
For three millennia I waited
Watching, guiding you through
all your incarnations
Nefrianna is alive within you.
Remember!
Remember, your Highness
No!
Noooo!!!
Your heart shall beat safely within me, my
love.
Until the day when I am
decreed worthy to return it.
This is a choice moment you Highness
I envy thee ..
I just sacrificed my life for thee..
- It looks he bringing down a retractor
- A what?
A retractor. They use it during
postmortems to separate the ribs.
Her speciality..
- And the body parts?
- Medical cadavers.
She had the access. Only thing you have to
do now is to figure out the how and the why?
In a case like this, there is no why.
In the mind of our killer there was.
Transcription Enigmatica