Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen
This is the pilot speaking
You'll notice the "fasten
seat belts" sign is on
Passing through
a little turbulence here
Unfortunately,
we can't get up over it
and we can't
get underneath it, so
just hang in there
Excuse me, miss?
Can I have
a different seat, please?
Oh, I'm afraid
we're full tonight, sir
You're gonna have to stay put
Thanks anyway
He's going to make you
help him
because you're the last
Listen
I really need
to change this seat
I'm sorry
There's nothing I can do
I'm afraid of heights
Don't be a pussy
It's not fair! I was almost out!
Shit!
I'll get you, my pretty
and your little soul, too!
One ticket
Round trip
Hurry up, boy
You don't wanna miss the bus
No screaming
while the bus in in motion
Now be a good little doggy
and go fetch!
Spencer, I wanna make sure
you understand our situation
In one week,
you walk out of here
and I expect some changes in
your behavior when you get home
I know you're hearing me
I put you in here
because you gave me no choice
Next time, I'll leave you here
Thanks for the visit, Dad
Nice job on my kid
I expected to see
some improvement
He isn't a Toyota
What a jerk
You OK?
Yeah Dad just came by
to lay down some ground rules
for when I come home...
no more running away, no more
setting his cars on fire
There are other ways
to get his attention
besides blowing up the garage
Yeah He barely even blinked
All he wants me to do now
is grow up to be him...
an exact copy
I don't feel like playing
football and date-raping coeds
One of these days, you're going
to have to face your father
Maggie
look what I found
in Spencer's room
A pipe bomb, huh?
That? Just showing the kids
survival techniques
Been confiscating stuff
like this all week
Where do they get it?
I'll put this downstairs
with the rest of the arsenal
Weren't the police supposed
to dispose of that stuff?
The police are supposed
to do a lot of things
-Get your hands off of me!
-Tracy!
-What's the problem?
-She was beating on another kid
He was hitting on me!
She doesn't like
to be touched
We have a session today, yes?
I have Doc's class
Work around him
I'm sorry, sir
You seen this junkie before?
No He's new
Beautiful Another afternoon
shot doing juvie paperwork
Screw that shit
Let's just scoop him up
and take him to the shelter
Let the bleeding hearts
do the typing
That's it Come on, Tracy
That's it
Oh, yeah She's bad
The crowd loves her!
She's getting ready
for the heavyweight champion
boxing match of the world
Hey, hey, hey Look at her go
You know, you are sexy
when you sweat
You ain't gettin' none, Carlos!
You wouldn't hit a guy
with a handicap, would you?
Oh, you call it a handicap?
I call it chicken, man!
Come on, let's spar
-No, no Forget it, Trace
-Come on...
Don't tune out Why don't you
talk back to her for once?
Oh, yeah, right Like you
talk back to your father?
Let me tell you something
I stopped talking back
when it became hazardous
to my health, you know?
So, are we set?
Yeah No problem
I gave the van driver our cash
As long as we do it before dawn,
we're home free
We're gonna be livin' large
in Cali before the week is out
You better be sure, man
Trust me, all right?
I got it all covered
I need to get outta here
even more than you do
You don't know shit
about needing to get out!
Your family's a picnic,
rich boy!
What? You think I hang around
you morons by choice?
Least your father
didn't try to set you up
with his girlfriend's
older sister
Don't talk to me about fathers
Yours come to visit, too?
Yeah...
every time I close my eyes
That did it Yep OK
They caught
one of your star pupils
beating up
on one of our kids again
Thought you said
you were making progress
I only get twenty-three minutes
a week with these kids
With that kind of attention
you're lucky
she didn't kill him
That's a good attitude
for a therapist
Tracy's got some deep trauma
buried inside of her head
Conventional therapy
is not going to work
And dream therapy is, huh?
You're such a hippie
I can reach these kids
through their dreams
You give me a chance, I can help
you with your little problem
I don't have a little problem
I just have
a little reoccurring dream
and I'm handling it fine
And you are not being paid
to be a dream doctor
I'm barely being paid
That's why I gotta do
what I think is right
This is new
You like it?
These are ancient dream demons
Supposedly they roam
the dreams of the living
till they find
the most evil, twisted
human imaginable
Then they give him
the power to cross the line
and turn our nightmares
into reality
Maggie, cops just brought in
another kid Real mess
Hasn't sleep for days,
bad case of amnesia
We need your evaluation
right away
How long have you been awake?
As far as I can remember?
I don't know About three days
Looks more like three weeks
Yeah, well,
that's the wonder of amnesia...
always keeps you guessing
Where you from?
I don't know!
All I know
is that wherever I'm from
I was the last
The last what?
Survivor
Look, do you have any
caffeine pills or coffee?
Maybe some coke?
I meant the soda
Sit down
Why do you want to stay awake?
Because if I fall asleep
I'm not waking up
Why do you think that?
I don't think it I feel it
If I fall asleep
there's gonna be trouble
Springwood
Water tower
Four thousand five hundred
and sixty-seven
Bottles of beer on the wall
Four thousand five hundred
and sixty-seven
Bottles of beer
If one of those bottles
should happen to fall
What a case of...
Hey, I'll break a bottle
over your head
if you don't shut the fuck up!
Four thousand five hundred
and sixty-six
Bottles of beer on the wall
I won't tell
Now you're it
Remember what you have to do
You got to tag me
That's it
Come to Daddy
Play with me
Tell me who I am
I won't tell
Free me, you idiot!
I'm your fucking memory!
Oh, shit
Asshole
What were you dreaming about?
A room
A house
A little girl
Something about the town
from my article
I remember a water tower
The article... do you remember
where you got it?
The little girl...
what did she look like?
Brown hair with
red ribbons
I don't like it
There's some connection between
your dreams and his dreams
and his dreams mean bad news
I know you think I'm crazy,
but I can feel it
Why can't anybody talk about
anything but dreams around here?
I'm so sick of hearing
about this bullshit!
You don't believe that
You think solving this boy's
puzzle can help with your own
I don't have a puzzle
Yes, you do
And although you think
you know everything
you may not be ready to face
what this boy will show you
I never said I wanted
to go back there
I've dealt
with amnesiacs before
Take you to Springwood,
it's gonna trigger something...
some spark to help you remember
I don't need a spark to remember
that it was a bad place
You want a spark? You go
I'll stay here,
sparkless but happy
I'll be right there with you
Don't worry
Kelly, we're gonna take
the van for awhile
I told you not to let me
fall asleep
Was that too much to ask for?
Go back
Oh, my God! Pull over!
John, wake up!
Shit Great
Funny meeting you here
Nice driving
What the hell are you guys
doing here?
Great plan, asshole
-It almost worked, all right?
-I can't believe you people
Pulling a stunt like that
Oh, my God
Look, the first thing we have
to do is find a telephone
and you call Kelly
and tell him where you are
You understand?
And then we have to figure out
how to get you home
Are you listening?
Don't scream at me!
It was your driving
that almost killed us
Two for a dollar, right here!
Get 'em, two!
Two for a dollar!
First I want you to find
a phone, call Kelly
and tell him you're all right
Then I want you
to get in that van
and drive straight back
to the shelter
Think you can handle that
or do I have to call
the police?
Get away from here You go away!
"Or do I have to call
the police?"
She ain't my mother
We want some peach cobbler
here and
-There are no kids
-What?
Town fair
and there are no kids
-So what's up, Spence?
-This phone's out of order
So is this town
You are not kidding
Oh, what beautiful,
adorable children!
Would you like to come
and live with us?
It's been so long since
we've had children in the house
So long
This time,
I swear it'll be different
This time, I'll be careful
and I'll hide you better,
so that he'll never find you
Looky, I got your nose! Looky!
Ethel!
I want my children back!
You know they bring him!
Now see what you done did?!
Jesus
-We're in Twin Peaks here
-Definitely
Have we seen enough?
-Yeah
-Good
Come on, back in the van
That's a very good idea
Now Go!
Jeez
I hope they make it
Let's see what they can tell us
at the school
-What?
-Somebody rang those bells
Lucky us
Trace, there's a map back here
Did I say I needed a map?
I can't get over the way
those people looked at us
Yeah, that was weird
Shit
Nice going
Takes talent to travel
in a complete circle
And you're making me dizzy
Jeez
Do you have to do that?
You're such a high ho,
you know that?
I don't play that shit
I need all the senses I've got
Put that fucking thing out
It's hard enough
staying awake
without you lighting up
every ten seconds
-This relaxes me
-I'll relax you
I'll just puncture your heart
mess up these seats
You need to get laid
Would you like the map now?
No, I don't need any map
No, of course not
-Why'd you stop?
-Look
Oh, great
Give me the map
Not a word
Carlos, I asked you for the map!
What is this?!
I asked you for the map
What?
Yeah, well,
the map says we're fucked
Look, you've had two chances
Now it's my turn
Dickhead
Nice
You'll all be expected
to pass
both the written
and an oral examination
Don't disturb him
You will need to study
this
Now the dates
Got to get the dates right
Got to keep them in order
If you get them out of order,
you'll get very confused
You were here
What?
Welcome
to Freddy 101
1493...
Freddy sailed across the sea
These dates, they're all
within a ten-year period
What the hell happened here?
Freddy happened here
Here was the crucial point
Anybody know
what I'm getting at?
Anybody? Hmm?
Come on, people!
We covered this!
This is where
they took away his child
What child?
Taken away
put in the town orphanage
Freddy had a kid
1494...
Freddy came back
to look
for more
There's no way out
Not with you driving
Yeah, well,
you didn't do much better
No, but at least I did it
in half the time
Come on Where are you going?
Away
Look, we're just too fried
to see straight
Let's just find Maggie
I'm not turning myself over
for any adult supervision
This girl's getting some rest
In fact, I think I see my kinda
neighborhood up ahead...
empty
You know, she's losing it
Sad thing is,
I'm starting to like her
That is sad
Come on, Trace Wait up!
This is the one
We'll have it all to ourselves
-Bet there's no heat
-No plumbing, right?
You'll survive
Come on
Where you going?
Gonna go upstairs
and find a bed Man, I'm tired
I gotta find a bathroom
This place makes the shelter
look like the Ritz
Great
Well
at least it beats the streets,
right, Carlos?
Ohh, this is good
I'm gonna get some sleep
and I will get us out of here
in the morning
Why do you think that kid
said not to fall asleep?
'Cause he's a lame-o freak
Miss Maggie's pet psycho
Where the hell are you?
Why aren't you listening
to me, Carlos?
Tracy, where are you?
Behind you
Mama?
Maybe you don't hear so good
Maybe I clean out your ears
for you
No, no Mama, please,
I've been a good boy
You don't understand
I've been good, Mama!
Don't make me deaf, Mama!
Please! I'm sorry!
I'm not
Oh, Carlos, lend me your ear
Give me my hearing back!
Where is it?
Y-you wouldn't do that,
would you, man?
No, no, no! Please!
No, man!
Nice hearing from you, Carlos
I can't find Carlos
See what's on this TV?
I'm gonna take the van
I'm gonna look for him
Give me some room!
Don't fall asleep, man!
Get out!
Spencer, get out, man!
Carlos, man
we were just looking for you
Don't fall asleep, man!
Spencer, you stupid stoner!
We shouldn't even be here
We're supposed to be
finding out about you
not some dead killer's kid
We might be talking
about the same thing
The whole town's obsessing
on this Krueger character
Don't you start
But why else
would they be afraid of me?
Why else am I still alive
when everybody else is dead?
Skip, skip, skip to my loo
Skip to my loo, my darling
Martha, no running
Everyone hold hands
Oh, you've come back
How nice
Do you remember me?
Well, of course I do, my boy
I remember
every one of my children
Especially you
What a pretty little girl
you were
And I remember you
and you
Do you remember
the Krueger child?
Of course
Who was it?
We're not permitted to disclose
a child's real identity
Oh, Melissa Melissa
You must let Bobby
have the ball
Come here That's all right
We share
I wonder who has a little
bare footie around here?
"K Krueger"
Could mean anything
from Kevin to Kyle
All it really means is there was
a child here by that name
No It's me
I'm his kid
That's why he's kept me alive
He's trying to play
some sick game with me
He is dead, all right?
He's dead,
and you're not his kid
How do you know?
She remembered me
She remembered me, too
and fifty other
imaginary friends
Let's get out of here
Let's draw a picture
We can draw pictures all day
There you go
Clippety-clop, clippety-clop
Isn't that fun?
I can't believe I found you
What are you still doing here?
I can't find Carlos
and Spencer's wasted
at this old house
We gotta get to them
before Freddy does
-Who's Freddy?
-I'll tell you on the way
Come on!
God damn it!
All right Once again
This is your brain
on drugs
Questions?
Yeah! What are you on?
Looks like a frying pan
and some eggs to me
Hey, Spence
Let's trip out
Cool
Now he's gone!
He must've fallen asleep
You two look here and upstairs
I'm gonna look downstairs
They're not here anymore
Just humor me,
will you, please, and look?
Where am I?
Jump, boy
-Dad?
-Be like me
Father knows best
Oh! Oh, stop!
I'm not like you!
I don't wanna be like you!
Be like me
Now I'm playin' with power!
All right
Super Spencer!
Great graphics
Whoa I'm here
I found Spencer!
OK, hold him down
Oh, shit
Hold on Hold on to him
-What's happening to him?
-He's stuck in a nightmare
And it's kicking
the shit out of him!
-Wake him up
-He's too wasted
-Spencer! Jesus
-It's Freddy
We've got to get him out
I'll go into his dream
I'll try and bring him out
before he gets killed
That's crazy
What do you call that, rational?
Right, left
Right, left, right, left Pow!
He's getting trashed
I have to go in
What about Freddy?
Freddy won't hurt me
I'm family
OK, so how are you gonna go in?
Well
you're gonna have to lay me out
What? What is th...
-Just fucking lay me out!
-Wait a second!
-Doc told me a different way
-No time to talk! Just do it!
Jesus Christ
I told you I knew an easier way
Concentration meditation
That's what Doc always says
This place is incredible
Pow! Bam! Splat!
Is that him?
Jump, boy
Ow! Stop!
Oh, shit! Spencer!
Come on, John! Let go of me!
Get out of here! Now, Tracy!
Hey, You forgot the power glove
Pow!
Boing, boing
Be like me Be like me
What do you know?
I beat my high score
Great to be back in business
thanks to you
Daddy's waiting for you,
little girl
Shut the fuck up, man!
Spencer's gone
I couldn't stop it
John's still in there
I couldn't wake him up
Come on! Snap out of it!
What are we gonna do?
We're gonna pick him up
and get the hell out of here!
Not again
He's not gonna get me again
Nothing is gonna
make me get off this bed
Damn it!
I hate this house
Up here!
I know why you let me go
Do you think I'm your daddy?
Wrong!
But you let me live
Only long enough for you
to bring me back my daughter
Your daughter?
And now
she's gonna take me
to a whole new playground
Grounded!
Oh, my God, Maggie!
What's going on?
Come on, Maggie Let's go!
Come...
Let's get out of here!
Let's get the hell out of here!
It... it's not a boy
It's
Come on!
We gotta get out of here!
Now! Come on!
Let's go!
You forgot
where you came from, kid
but I know where you're going
It's traveling time!
What's wrong?
Maggie, get in the van!
Come on!
We gotta get the hell
out of here!
Oh, God
Let's go!
Whatever happened
it wasn't your fault
Carlos, Tracy, and Spencer
stowed away in the back
of the shelter van
They were trying to escape
Can you believe it?
So I took them to the phone
They were supposed to call you
John Doe and I were gonna
check out the school
But Tracy got separated
And then they ran away
What the hell
are you talking about?
I'm talking about Carlos
and Spencer and the John Doe!
Kelly, they just disappeared!
Been handling
too many cases, Maggie
Those kids were never here
I would've remembered
any new arrivals
Kelly, I'm talking about
forty-eight hours ago
I brought you a John Doe
Don't tell me
you don't remember that!
You the one who's handling
too many cases!
Get some rest, Maggie
And then
we got back and
no one remembers John or Carlos
It's like they never existed
I've been hearing strange shit
Like some of the kids
are dreaming about Carlos
And they don't even
remember him
I remember him
Why?
Because I can control my dreams
I'm not fooled
by this thing you saw
Whatever he is
he's fucking with the line
between dreams and reality
He didn't just kill Carlos
and the others
He erased them
It's not a boy
Mother!
Shit
You're getting ready
to kill somebody
Defend myself
It's your mind he'll go for
Your fear
I knew it, I knew it, I knew it
Maggie, what are you doing?
Who are they?
Let me have that
-I have to know
-I don't know
I don't know who they were
They wouldn't tell me
They have rules
about no contact
Oh, there's been contact
Find me
Find Daddy
You're it
Come to Daddy
I won't tell
Oh, God
Fred, please
I won't tell
We need to talk, Loretta
Go inside, honey
I won't tell
I told you never
never to go in there
I told you that! I told you
Catherine
You were such a little artist
No, it can't be
I know who I am
You're my blood
Only you could have
brought me out
in your mind
But you can't be my father
They took you away from me
but I made 'em pay!
I took all their children
away from them
and now
that's over
Come on
The shelter
Time to start all over again
But this isn't Springwood!
Every town
has an Elm Street
Tracy girl
Daddy's home
Daddy youre dead
I'm home, darling
Come say hello
I don't want to, Daddy
Come on, give Daddy some honey
No one has to know
You're not my daddy
Come on, Tracy
Here! Do you love me now?
He's dead!
My daddy's dead
No honey for Daddy?
What's with kids today, huh?
No respect
You can't scare me anymore
Oh, you better speak up
Must be my deaf ear
Kung fu this, bitch
This is my dream,
and I do what I want
Might be your dream
but it's my rules!
Doc... I need to talk to Doc!
Come on!
Doc? Doc, is that you?
Yeah, Tracy Where are you?
I'm over here
in one of the lockers
You gotta get me out!
Where the hell are you?
Right here
You taught her a lot
but there's so much more
to learn
How about this, Doc?
Sticks and stones
may break my bones
but nothing will ever kill me
Well, let's see now
First they tried burning me
Then they tried burying me
But this... this is my favorite
They even tried holy water
But I just keep on tickin'
because they promised me that
They?
The dream people
The ones that gave me this job
In dreams
I am forever!
Too bad you're not
Thank God
I think I've got a way
to get him
So what's the plan, Doc?
Thanks
You can't get him
in the dream
but if this can come out,
he can come out
And if he can come out,
he can bleed
-And die
-Right
How will you know
when I got him?
I'm gonna find you with this
and then I'm bringing you out
You've got to be holding him
to carry him out
I know
He's gonna try and trick you
just like Tracy
He'll try to use your eyes
to fool you
You'll use these
Get the hell outta here
You want to live?
These mean nothing here
but in a dream,
they can be anything you want
He got inside your head
You get inside of his
That's my job, isn't it?
Be careful He's good at
finding out what hurts the most
Exactly
That's why you gotta take me
with you
I can't
It's gotta be me and him
All right, Doc
Put me in
Strap her in
Take a deep breath
Good
Ten
nine
eight
seven
six
five
four
three
two
one
Get inside his brain
I'm in his memories
Son of a hundred maniacs
You ready for it, boy?
You been a waste
since the day I took you in
Now it's time
to take your medicine
Thank you, sir
May I have another?
You want to know
the secret of pain?
If you just stop feeling it
you can start using it
Child killer!
We know what you want
I want it all!
Of course you do
Then open up
And you shall be forever!
Mommy!
Don't worry, baby
Mommy just had
to take her medicine
for snooping
in Daddy's special work
But you won't tell, will you?
I won't tell
But you did tell, didn't you?
And now it's time
to take your medicine
You killed my mother!
She's got him!
Let's get her out of there
I've got you!
I had him!
Where the hell is he?
Maybe the trip killed him
No because
I'm still seeing things
the way I did in my dream
It's not over Let's go
The cops were supposed
to pick this stuff up
I'm glad they didn't
We'll have to hit him
with everything we've got
Check out this knife
-Hey, put that away
-That's too small
Guess so
You sure that's big enough?
Still believe
he's gonna show up, huh?
Come on, Tracy Over here
I can feel it
You're real here
It wasn't my fault
It wasn't
You saw what they did to me
when I was a kid
You saw
I loved you
And your mother
I tried so hard to be good
I know, Daddy
But when they took you
from me
it wasn't right
Oh, I knew you'd believe me
Come to Daddy
Over here!
I'm OK
Maggie, watch out!
-Where's the key?
-I don't know!
The lock's jammed!
I didn't need a glove
to kill your bitch
of a mother
and I don't need one now!
Come on
Let go
I'll show you how
Like you showed my mother?
And Carlos?
And Spencer?
Give Daddy the glove back,
princess
Never!
Give it to me!
Gimme the glove!
In your dreams!
Oh, Daddy, I remember when we
used to hold hands together
when I was a kid
I didn't like it then, either!
I forgot how much it hurts
to be human
Go ahead
put it on
It's in your blood
That's it Put it on
Feels good, doesn't it?
Yeah come on
Let your daddy show you
how to use it
Happy Father's Day
Come on, Doc!
Come on! Let's hurry!
Let's get outta here! Come on!
Oh kids
-You all right?
-Yeah, I'm OK
Freddy's dead