Stasis interrupted.
Fire in cryogenic compartment.
Repeat,
fire in cryogenic compartment.
All personnel...
report to emergency
escape vehicle launch pod.
Deep-space flight will commence
in T-minus twenty seconds.
Get going!
Jesus Christ!
Hell of a way to land!
Get the torch.
How many?
Don't know. Three, maybe four.
Frank, can we hurry?
It's going to be
forty below in five minutes.
Aah!
I'm going to kill that thing.
That stupid dog
of yours. Get it out!
I hate that thing.
Get rid of the dog.
He's gone.
Not a bad way to go, huh?
Ha ha ha.
Frank, let's go!
Wait!
One of them's still alive.
All right.
We'll need all of those.
That's it. OK. All right.
This is rumor control.
Here are the facts.
As some of you know,
a 337 model EEV...
crash-landed here
at 0600 on the morning watch.
There was one survivor...
two dead, and a droid
that was smashed beyond repair.
The survivor is a woman.
Is she pretty?
I've taken a vow of celibacy.
So have we all!
That also includes women.
We've all taken the vow!
I'd like to say I do not
appreciate Company policy...
allowing her to intermingle
with inmates and staff!
What brother means is we view
the presence of any outsider...
especially a woman,
as a violation of the harmony...
a potential break
in the spiritual unity.
We're aware of your feelings
in this matter.
You will be pleased to know
I have requested a rescue team.
Hopefully, they will be here
inside of a week...
and evacuate her ASAP.
Don't give us that!
What's her medical status?
She's not badly damaged.
She's unconscious.
I can't be more specific now.
Will she live?
I think so.
It's best for all that
she stay in the infirmary...
until the rescue team arrives.
And certainly not
without an escort, right?
Sir.
Gentlemen!
We should all stick
to our set routine...
and not get unduly agitated,
correct?
All right.
Thank you, gentlemen.
Better get here soon,
or there won't be much left.
What's that?
Just a little cocktail
of my own mix. An eye-opener.
You a doctor?
My name is Clemens.
I'm Chief Medical Officer here.
-Here?
-Fury 161.
It's one of Weyland-Yutani's
backwater work prisons...
it grieves me to say.
Do you mind?
It's basically a stabilizer.
I ought to shave your head.
We have a big problem
with lice.
I'll give you some clippers
for your private parts.
How did I get here?
You crash-landed in an EEV...
evidently separated
from your mother ship...
before you hit our atmosphere.
How long were you in hyper sleep?
Coming out that way
can jolt your system.
I'll be sick
for a couple of weeks.
Indeed.
Where are the others?
They didn't make it.
-What?
-They didn't survive.
I have to get to the ship.
Have to get to the ship.
You're in no condition.
Want to get me some clothes,
or should I go like this?
Given the nature of
our indigenous population...
I would suggest clothes.
They haven't seen a woman
in years.
Neither have I, for that matter.
This used to be
a 5,000-convictfacility...
but it's been reduced to a
custodial staff of twenty-five.
-Why?
-Keep the pilot light on.
Pilot light for what?
Blast furnace. Natural methane.
We have a foundry,
Lieutenant Ripley.
The inmates forge lead sheets
for toxic waste containment.
How do you know my name?
It's stenciled
on the back of your shorts.
Hey! Pick them up!
Release the cable!
Where are the bodies?
We have a morgue.
We put them there until
the investigators arrive...
in about a week.
There was a droid.
Disconnected. There
were pieces of him all over.
We put what was left
on the rubbish tip.
The corporal was impaled
by that safety support.
He never knew what hit him.
And the girl?
She drowned in her cryo-tube.
I don't think
she was conscious...
when it happened.
Um, I'm sorry.
What's the matter?
-Where is she?
-In the morgue.
I have to see her.
I have to see
what's left of her.
God, there you are!
I've been looking
everywhere for you!
Where you been, huh?
Come here.
You OK?
Let me see, Spike. Are you OK?
Let me see.
What have you been
sticking your face into?
Did somebody do this to you?
What kind of animal
would do this to a dog?
Um...
could I have a moment alone,
please?
Yes, of course.
Forgive me.
What's she doing?
OK?
No.
We have to do an autopsy.
-What?
-I told you.
We have to make sure
how she died.
And I told you she drowned.
I'm not so sure. I...
I have to see inside of her.
You're disorientated.
Half your system-
I have a very, very good reason.
Perhaps you'd like to share it.
Possible contagion.
What kind, exactly?
-Cholera.
-Cholera?
There hasn't been a case of
cholera for two hundred years.
Please.
Everything's in place.
There's no sign of infection.
No indication of disease.
Chest. Open the chest.
Careful.
Lungs.
Flooded with fluid.
Ergo, she drowned.
Now, since I'm not
a complete idiot...
want to tell me
what we're really looking for?
Mr. Clemens.
Superintendent.
I don't believe you've met
Lieutenant Ripley.
What's going on, Mr. Clemens?
That's right, sir.
What's going on?
Well, first...
the lieutenant is feeling
much better, I'm happy to say.
Second, in the interest
of public health...
I am performing an autopsy.
Without my authority?
There didn't seem to be time,
but it's turned out all right.
-There's no contagion.
-Good.
It might help if she didn't
parade before the prisoners...
as I'm told she did
in the last hour.
It might also be helpful
if you kept me informed...
as to any change
in her physical status.
Is that asking too much?
We have to cremate the bodies.
Nonsense. We'll keep them on ice
till the rescue team arrives.
On ice.
There is
the public health issue.
The lieutenant feels
there's still the possibility...
of a communicable infection.
You said there was
no sign of disease.
It appears the child drowned...
but without the benefit
of proper laboratory tests...
it's impossible to be
absolutely certain.
I would consider it unwise
to tolerate...
even the possibility
of an unwelcome virus.
An outbreak of cholera...
would look extremely bad
on a report, would it not, sir?
Ahem.
We've twenty-five
prisoners in this facility...
all double-Y chromos...
all thieves, rapists, murderers,
child molesters...all scum.
Just because
they've taken on religion...
doesn't make them
any less dangerous.
I try not to offend
their convictions.
I don't want to upset the order.
I don't want ripples
in the water...
and I don't want a woman walking
around giving them ideas.
I see.
For my own personal safety.
Exactly.
I'll leave the cremation details
to you, Mr. Clemens.
They may use the furnace...
but I want everyone in lockup
by 2200 hours.
"We commit this child
and this man...
"to Your keeping, O Lord."
"Their bodies have been taken...
"from the shadow of our night."
"They have been released
from all darkness and pain."
"The child and the man...
"have gone beyond our world."
"They are forever...
"eternal, and everlasting."
"Ashes to ashes, dust to dust."
Why?
Why are the innocent punished?
Why the sacrifice?
Why the pain?
There aren't any promises.
Nothing's certain.
Only that some get called...
some get saved.
She won't ever know
the hardship and grief...
for those of us left behind.
We commit these bodies
to the void...
with a glad heart.
For within each seed...
there is a promise of a flower.
And within each death,
no matter how small...
there's always a new life.
A new beginning.
Amen.
It's fucking weird.
Only a woman
survived that crash.
What trouble can she cause?
She's already
changed everything.
What are we
supposed to do with her?
I mean it.
Not around here,
that's for sure.
Hello.
I just wanted to...
say thanks for what you said
at the funeral.
My friends
would have appreciated-
You don't want to know me, lady.
I'm a murderer
and rapist of women.
Really.
Well, I guess
I must make you nervous.
Do you have any faith, sister?
Not much.
We've got a lot of faith here.
Enough even for you.
I thought women weren't allowed.
We've never had any before,
but we tolerate anybody...
even the intolerable.
Thank you.
That's just a statement
of principle, nothing personal.
We've got a good place
to wait here.
And until now...no temptation.
Dillon and the rest
of the alternative people...
embraced religion, as it were,
about five years ago.
Take two.
I'm on medication?
Hardly.
What kind of religion?
Some sort of
apocalyptic, millenarian...
Christian fundamentalist...
-Right.
-Exactly.
When the Company
wanted to close the facility...
Dillon and the rest
of the converts wanted to stay.
They were allowed
to remain as custodians...
with two minders
and a medical officer.
And here we are.
How did you get
this wonderful assignment?
How do you
like your new haircut?
It's OK.
Now that I've gone out on a limb
for you with Andrews...
damaged my less-than-perfect
relationship with him...
and briefed you on the humdrum
history of Fury 161...
can't you tell me
what you were looking for?
Are you attracted to me?
In what way?
In that way.
You're very direct.
I've been out here a long time.
In the year 7510
If God's a-comin',
he oughta make it by then
Maybe he'll look around and say
Guess it's time
for the judgment...
Yecchh!
In the year...
Hey, Spike.
Spike? Spikey.
Are you down there?
What are you doing?
Aah!
I really appreciate
your affections.
But I am aware
that they deflected my question.
In the nicest possible way,
of course.
You're spoiling the mood.
I have a job to do.
I want to know why we had
to cremate the bodies.
I had a terrible dream
in hyper sleep...
and I had to be sure
what killed her.
Anyway, I made a mistake.
Possibly.
Now I've made another.
What's that?
Fraternizing with a prisoner.
Physical contact.
It's against the rules,
isn't it?
I'm not a prisoner.
You have a bar code
on the back of your head.
That does deserve
an explanation.
Now is not the moment.
Mr. Clemens.
Mr. Aaron.
Superintendent Andrews
would like you to report...
to vent shaft twenty-two
on the second quadrant-now.
We've had an accident.
Something serious?
You could call it that.
One of our prisoners
has been...diced.
Sorry.
I have to go.
Official duties.
Who was it?
Murphy.
How do you know?
That's his boot.
I gave him the assignment, sir.
He was a wanker.
No apologies, Mr. Aaron.
It wasn't your fault.
Not much to say, is there?
Death was instantaneous.
No shit.
He was pulled into the fan?
Sudden rush of air, except-
Right.
Almost happened to me once.
I've told them so many times,
"Stay away from the fans."
Nobody bloody listens.
Except the fan was blowing.
-What's that?
-I don't know.
I want to see you
in my quarters in 30 minutes.
Got any ideas?
Here you are.
Wandering around unescorted...
is really going to piss
Superintendent Andrews off.
Want to tell me
about your accident?
A prisoner has been killed.
-Really?
-Hmm.
-How?
-In the air shaft.
Poor sod
backed into a nine-foot fan.
I found something
at the accident site...
just a bit away
from where it happened.
A mark.
A burn.
Rather like the one you found
on the girl's cryo-tube.
Look...I'm on your side.
I want to help, but I need
to know what's going on...
or what you think is going on.
If you really want to help...
find a computer
with audio capabilities...
so I can access
this flight recorder.
We don't have anything
like that.
What about Bishop,
the droid that crashed with me?
I can point you
in the right direction.
I can't join you.
I have a previous engagement.
Listen to me,
you piece of shit.
You screw with me again,
I'll cut you in half.
I'm sorry.
I don't think I understand.
At 0700 hours, I received
word from the network.
This is the first
high-level communication...
this installation has ever
received, to my knowledge.
They want this woman
looked after.
They consider her to be
high-priority.
-Why?
-I have no idea.
Why did you let her
out of the infirmary?
This accident with Murphy...
is what happens when one
of these dumb sons of bitches
walks around with a hard-on.
I'm a doctor.
You're the jailer.
We both know exactly
what you are.
Sit down.
It might be better if I left.
I find you
unpleasant to be around.
You do? Isn't that lovely?
Consider this, Mr. Clemens.
Would you like me to explain
your sordid history...
to your newfound friend?
For her personal edification,
of course.
Now sit the hell down.
Now...is there anything
I should know?
Aah!
Shut up! Fucking bitch.
Shut up, you bitch.
Goddamn it, let go of me!
Fuck you!
No!
Shh, shh, shh.
No, goddamn it!
Aah!
You OK?
You son of a bitch!
Take off. I got to re-educate
some of the brothers.
We got to discuss
some matters of the spirit.
This is like ten city blocks.
How many?
This makes
one hundred seventy-six.
Can't you chew a little quieter?
I'm trying to figure out
how big this compartment is.
I can't think
with this goddamn noise.
You're not supposed to swear.
I'm sorry.
We've encircled
this entire compartment once.
-Hey!
-What?
What the shit is doing that?
Swearing.
It's OK to say "shit."
It ain't against God.
What the hell is going on
with the candles?
Must be the wind
from one of the vent shafts...
backwash from the closest
circulating unit.
If they go out, we'll be lost.
Somebody
will have to re-light them.
Guess I'm nominated.
Watch your step, brother.
OK, who are the comedians?
Aah! Aah!
Aah!
Go!
Come on! Quick! Grab it! Here!
Help me!
Go! Fucking go!
Go on! Quick!
Run!
Aah!
Give me that.
Get this fucking thing off me!
Aah!
Let me go!
-Aah!
-No!
Hey.
Hello, Ripley.
Hi, Bishop.
How you feeling?
My legs hurt.
Hey, listen, I'm sorry.
It's OK.
I'm just a glorified toaster.
How are you?
Ah, I like your new haircut.
Can you access
the flight recorder?
No problem.
I'm home.
What happened on the Sulaco?
Why were our cryo-tubes ejected?
Stasis interrupted.
Fire in cryogenic compartment.
Repeat. Fire in cryogenic-
What happened?
What started the fire, Bishop?
Can you hear me?
The fire was electrical.
It was in the sub flooring.
Did sensors find anything moving
on the ship before separation?
It's very dark here.
I'm not what I used to be.
Just tell me. Does
the recorder indicate anything?
Was there an alien on board?
Yes.
Is it on the Sulaco?
Did it come in the EEV?
It was with us all the way.
Does the Company know?
The Company knows everything
that happened on the ship.
It all goes into the computer
and gets sent back to network.
Then they want it.
I hurt. Do me a favor.
Disconnect me.
I could be reworked, but I'll
never be top-of-the-line again.
I'd rather be nothing.
You're sure?
Do it for me, Ripley.
It wasn't me!
I didn't do it!
It was-It was the dragon.
Feeds on minds.
Nobody can stop it.
What about Boggs and Rains?
Got slaughtered like pigs.
It wasn't me. It wasn't me.
Stark raving mad.
It's no one's fault, but
he should've been chained up.
You called it, sir.
Mad as a fucking hatter.
Keep him separated
from the rest.
Don't want him causing a panic.
Clemens, sedate this poor idiot.
Not until we know
about the brothers.
Now, now,
pull yourself together.
Talk to me now.
Where are Boggs and Rains?
Hopeless. You won't
get anything out of him.
We'll send out a search team.
We'll have to assume
this bastard murdered them.
You don't know that.
He's never lied to me.
He's crazy, he's a fool,
but he's not a liar.
He's telling the truth.
I'd like to talk to him
about this-this dragon.
It's a dragon.
You're not talking
to anyone, Lieutenant.
I'm not interested
in your opinion.
You don't know the facts.
He's a convicted
multiple murderer...
known for particularly
brutal crimes.
Isn't that right, Mr. Dillon?
Yeah...that part's right.
Then I'll talk to you.
It's important.
When I'm finished
with my official duties...
I'll be pleased
to have a little chat. Yes?
Let me see if I have
this correct, Lieutenant.
It's an eight-foot creature
with acid for blood...
and it arrived
on your spaceship.
It kills on sight
and is generally unpleasant.
You expect me
to accept all this?
No, I don't expect anything.
Quite a story, Mr. Aaron.
Right, sir. It's a beauty.
Never heard anything like it.
Expect not.
Tell me, Lieutenant,
what would you suggest we do?
What kind of weapons
have you got?
This is a prison.
It's not good to allow prisoners
access to firearms.
Keeps them from killing you.
Yeah. There's no way to escape.
When the supply ship arrives,
the Company will eliminate it.
This is
a maximum security prison...
and you have no weapons
of any kind?
We have carving knives
in the abattoir...
a few more in the mess hall...
some fire axes scattered
about the place.
That's all?
We're on the honor system.
Then we're fucked.
No, you're fucked.
Confined to the infirmary.
Quarantined.
Mr. Aaron will escort you.
You'll be safe from any large,
nasty beasts while you're there.
That's a good girl.
Report to the mess hall.
Andrews wants a meeting.
Mess hall right away, people.
Isn't there any way
off of this place...
some way to escape?
No.
Supply ship
comes every six months.
-That's it?
-That's it.
Fuck.
They're sending
somebody to pick you up soon.
Really? What's soon?
I don't know.
Nobody's ever been in a hurry
to get here before.
Do you want to tell me what
you and Andrews talked about?
No.
You'd just say I'm crazy.
That's a bit uncharitable.
How are you feeling?
Not so hot. Ahem.
Sore throat, sick to my stomach,
pissed off.
That's understandable,
given the circumstances.
Perhaps I should give you
one of my special cocktails.
Why does everybody
blame everybody?
Nobody's perfect.
We're only human.
I don't know a perfect human.
Nobody I know.
You married?
Me?
Get married, have kids.
Pretty girl.
I used to know
lots of them back home.
They used to like me...
for a while.
You're going to die, too.
Are you?
What?
Married.
Why?
Just curious.
No.
How about leveling with me?
When I asked
how you got assigned here...
you avoided the question.
When I asked about the prison
I.D. tattooed on your head...
you ducked me again.
It's a long, sad story...
and more than
a little melodramatic.
Try me.
If you insist.
After my student years...
despite the fact that I'd become
secretly addicted to morphine...
I was considered
to be most promising-
a man with a future.
During my first residency, I did
a 36-hour stretch in E.R...
so I went out, and I got
more than a little drunk.
Then I got called back.
Boiler had blown
in a fuel plant...
and there were
thirty casualties.
Eleven of them died...
not from the accident...
but because I prescribed
the wrong dosage of painkiller.
I got seven years in prison
and my license reduced to a 3-C.
At least I got off the morphine.
I'm sorry.
I think I was let off lightly.
You served your time here?
I got to know
this motley crew quite well...
so when they stayed, I stayed.
Nobody else would employ me.
Do you still trust me
with a needle?
Aah!
Once again,
this is rumor control.
Here are the facts.
At 0800 hours,
prisoner Murphy...
through carelessness
on his part...
was found dead in vent shaft 17.
He seems to have been sucked
into a ventilator fan.
At about 2100 hours...
prisoner Golic reappeared
in a deranged state.
Prisoners Boggs and Rains
are missing.
There seems to be a good chance
they have met with foul play...
at the hands of prisoner Golic.
We need to organize
and send out a search party.
Volunteers will be appreciated.
It's fair to say
our smoothly running facility...
has suddenly developed
a few problems.
I can only hope we are able
to all pull together...
over the next few days
until the rescue team...
arrives for Lieutenant Ripley.
It's here. It got Clemens.
-Stop this raving.
-I'm telling you, it's here!
Get that foolish woman
back to the infirmary.
Aah!
Fuck!
What do we do now?
Who's in charge?
Organize!
We got to organize, right?
Right. I guess I'm next in line.
Eighty-five's in charge? Jesus!
Don't call me that.
There's no way
I can replace Andrews.
He was a good man.
You didn't appreciate him.
Aaron, we don't want
to hear that shit now.
Sister, what about you?
You're an officer.
Show us a little leadership.
Forget Shirley Temple.
You take charge.
You run things here anyway.
No fucking way.
I'm not the officer type.
I just take care of my own.
What does
this fucking beast want?
Is this mother
going to try for us all?
-Yeah.
-Jesus!
Ain't that sweet?
How do we stop it?
Ahem.
We have no weapons, correct?
Right.
I haven't seen one
exactly like this before.
Moves differently.
But the others were afraid
of fire, not much else.
Can we seal off this area?
No chance.
The installation's
ten miles square.
There's six hundred air ducts.
What about video?
I see closed-circuit
monitors everywhere.
The video system
hasn't worked in years.
Nothing much works here.
We've got a lot of technology,
no way to fix it.
Eighty-five is saying we've got
no entertainment center...
no climate control,
no video system...
no surveillance, no freezers...
no fucking ice cream,
no rubbers, no women, no guns.
All we got here is shit.
What are we talking to her for?
She brought the fucker.
Why don't we shove her head
through the fucking wall?
Morse?
Why don't you shut the fuck up?
Right.
What will we do?
What's this?
Leads from the mess hall
to the infirmary.
It's a ventilation shaft.
Then we go in there.
Flush it out.
There's miles and miles
of tunnel through there.
It won't go far.
It'll nest in this area.
Right around...
here.
How do you know that?
It's like a lion.
It sticks close to the zebras.
Zebras?
Oh, right.
But running around in the dark-
are you kidding?
Once you get out the main shaft,
there's no overheads.
Don't we have flashlights?
Thousands, but no batteries.
Nothing works.
Torches? Do we have
the capacity to make fire?
Most humans have enjoyed that
privilege since the Stone Age.
No need to be sarcastic.
Never been used.
They meant to dump
nuclear crap there.
Never did. It's clean inside.
This the only way in or out?
That's right.
Walls are six-feet-thick,
solid steel.
Really knew how to build
these babies.
You're saying we get
something in there...
there's no way it can get out?
That's right. No fucking way.
This is where we keep it.
I forget what it's called.
Quinitricetyline.
I knew that.
Right. I've got to get
these section arrangements...
organized with Dillon
for the paintbrush...
so, um...
-David.
-You organize these drums.
Right, Eighty-five.
And, uh, don't call me that.
What's this "Eighty-five" thing?
Couple of us sneaked a look
at his personnel file.
It's his I.Q.
I saw a drum of this stuff fall
into a beachhead bunker once.
The blast put a tug in dry dock
for seventeen weeks.
Great stuff!
Let me get this straight.
You want to burn it down
and out of the pipes...
force it in here, slam the door,
and trap its ass?
Right.
And you want help
from us Y-chromo boys?
Got something better to do?
Why should we put our ass
on the line for you?
Your ass is already on the line.
The only question is...
what will you do about it?
What is this stuff?
Man, this stuff stinks!
So you miss Doc, right?
What makes you say that?
I thought you two
got real close.
I guess you've been looking
through some keyholes.
That's what I thought.
Oh!
I hate this place.
There's definitely
something in here with us.
Don't light the fire
until I give the signal.
This is the signal.
Got it? Can you remember that?
Aah!
Aw, shit!
Aah! Aah!
Aah!
B...
Wait for the fucking signal!
Get down!
Aah!
We got to find the sprinklers!
We got to help these guys!
Aah!
Come on!
Get to the waste dump!
Don't open the door!
Dillon, over here.
Here's another one.
Aw, Jesus. This makes ten.
Fucking great!
Now what are we going to do?
You OK?
Piss on her!
The fucking thing's loose.
What do we do?
I said that,
you miserable shit!
Cut that shit out.
Tell your fucking bozo
to shape up!
What do you think?
I think I have to get
to the EEV.
Why? What's up?
I just have to use
the neuroscanner.
You don't look good.
Who cares? What do we do?
Want a smack in the mouth,
wanker?
Shut the fuck up.
Stop causing panic!
Panic? You're so stupid,
you couldn't spell it.
We ought to fucking panic!
Shut up, both of you!
Shut up!
Well, I'm out of ideas!
Surprise me.
What about outside?
Sun's not up for
two days. It's forty below zero.
The rescue team's
ten hours away.
You want to let this thing
have us for lunch?
I want you to get everybody
that's left together.
Go down to the furnace.
OK.
Need any help?
I didn't mean to scare you.
You shouldn't
wander around alone.
Do me a favor
and run this keyboard, will you?
OK.
What do I do?
Hit "B" or "C."
What's "C"?
"Display biofunctions"?
That's it.
OK, we're hot. Now what?
Let it run a cycle.
It's real fuzzy.
Hit enhancement.
Keep looking.
I don't know
how to read this stuff.
Hemorrhaging
will show as a dark patch.
Look for...
hairline fractures
through the base of the skull.
Little white lines.
What is it?
I think there's one inside you.
That's not possible.
What does it look like?
Horrible.
I have to see it.
Freeze it.
-You don't want to see.
-Freeze it!
I'm sorry.
It's up.
What do you want to say?
Tell them
the whole place is toxic.
Are you kidding?
Then the rescue team
will turn back.
Yeah. I know.
What are you talking about?
Our only hope
is that they kill this fucker.
Maybe they can do
something for you-
freeze you, an operation.
They've got the technology.
If this organism
gets off the planet...
it'll kill everything.
The Company doesn't care
about that.
They just want it
fort heir bio-weapons division.
So we can't let them come here.
Fuck you.
I'm sorry you've got
this thing inside you...
but I'm getting rescued.
I don't care
about the prisoners.
I've got a wife, a kid.
I go home next rotation!
I know this is hard.
I'm going to send this message.
I need that fucking code.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
It's classified.
Listen, you stupid little shit!
This has got to be done.
There are no alternatives!
You're not getting it!
No fucking way!
Look...
it's nothing personal,
understand?
I think you're OK.
Thanks.
Have you got any ideas?
I don't know.
Maybe I'll go find it.
We'll see how smart it is.
You're going to look for it?
Yeah.
I have a pretty good idea
of where it is.
It's just down there...
in the basement.
This whole place is a basement.
It's a metaphor.
Want to come?
Fuck me.
Where are you when I need you?
Don't be afraid.
I'm part of the family.
You've been in my life so long,
I can't remember anything else.
Now do something for me.
It's easy.
Just...
Just do what you do.
Oh!
It won't kill me.
You're supposed to be
laying low.
I have one inside of me.
What are you talking about?
I saw it on the CAT scan.
It's a queen-
an egg-layer.
It can make thousands more
like the one here.
Still sounds like bullshit
to me.
If that thing's inside you,
how did it get there?
When I was in hyper sleep,
I guess.
I don't have much time...
and I can't do what I should.
I need you to help me.
I need you to kill me.
What are you talking about?
I'm dead anyway.
I can't survive it...
but the one inside me
can generate thousands more.
It has to die...
so somebody's got to kill me.
Are you up to it?
You don't have
to worry about that.
No speeches.
No prayers.
-What's going on?
-I don't like losing a fight.
Not to nobody, not to nothing.
That damn thing out there has
already killed half my men...
got the other half
scared shitless.
As long as it's alive, you're
not going to save any universe.
You said you'd kill me.
You fucking coward!
I want to get this thing,
and I need you to do it.
If it won't kill you,
maybe that helps us fight it.
Otherwise, fuck you!
Dillon?
We waste this thing,
then you take care of me.
No problem.
Quick, easy, and painless.
You die sitting here on
your ass, or you die out there.
At least we take a shot.
We owe it one.
What are you talking about?
Killing that big motherfucker!
Doesn't mean we should
fight it. Give us a break!
You have to be nuts!
I've got a wife-
Nobody cares about you,
Eighty-five.
You're not a believer.
You're a fucking Company man!
OK, I'm a Company man
and not a fucking criminal.
You keep telling me I'm dumb.
I'm smart enough
not to have a life sentence!
Fuck you!
I'm smart enough to wait
for firepower to show up...
before we fight this thing!
Right.
Just sit on your asses. Fine.
How about if I sit here
on my ass?
No problem.
Oh, I forgot.
You're the guy that's made
a deal with God to live forever.
And all the rest of you pussies
can sit it out, too.
Me and her
will do all the fighting.
OK. I want to see it dead, too.
I hate the fucker!
It killed my mates, too!
Why the fuck can't we wait
to have guns on our side?
Why go on
some fucking suicide run?
Because they won't kill it.
They might kill you
just for having seen it.
That is crazy!
That is horseshit!
They will not kill us!
When they first
heard about this thing...
it was "crew expendable."
The next time,
they sent in Marines.
They were expendable, too.
What makes you think they'll
care about a bunch of lifers...
who found God
at the ass-end of space?
You think
they're going to let you...
interfere with their plans
for this thing?
They think we're-
we're crud.
They don't give a fuck
about one friend of yours...
that's-that's died.
Not one.
Have you got a plan?
This is a lead works, isn't it?
All we got to do is lure
the beast into the mold...
drown it in hot lead.
Right. How do we do that?
What are we
going to use for bait?
Aw, fuck!
You're all going to die.
The only question
is how you check out.
Do you want it on your feet...
or on your fucking knees...
begging?
I ain't much for begging.
Nobody ever gave me nothing...
so I say fuck that thing!
Let's fight it!
Fuck it!
Let's go for it!
OK.
Fuck me.
Let's kick its fucking ass.
What if it runs at us?
That's a fucking good idea.
When did you use
this place last?
We fired it up five,
six years ago.
You sure the piston
is gonna work?
There's nothing for sure
in this place.
We trap it here first,
then you pull the lever.
The piston will push
the motherfucker into the mold.
One of the guys
will pour the lead.
End of story.
What if somebody screws up?
We're fucked.
You got one chance.
We'll never have time
to reset it.
Remember, when you pull
the lever, for a few seconds...
you'll be trapped in here
with that fucking thing.
If you guys don't drop the ball,
I won't.
You better be right about
that thing not wanting you.
Because if it wants out,
that's how it's going to go.
Through that alcove,
through you.
Where are you going to be?
I'll be around.
Where are the others?
Praying.
-I have a problem with this.
-What part?
Running around in a dark maze
with that thing chasing us.
Lead it down channel "B"
to the piston chamber.
I'll close the doors behind you.
What if it won't cooperate?
What if we get lost?
This was her idea.
I don't know about this shit.
Hey, guys!
My door ain't working!
What the fuck's he saying?
I think we'd better
rethink this thing!
Did anybody hear anything?
Come on!
Come and get me, you fucker!
It's behind me!
It's started.
It's still behind me!
It's in channel "B"!
You guys! Shut the doors!
Must be heading
over to channel "A"!
This thing is really pissed off!
-Did you say "B"?
-No, "E"!
-You said to stay here!
-Move your fucking ass!
Morse?
Kevin?
Yoo-hoo!
Hey, fuckface!
Come and get me!
Take your best shot!
Kevin, where are you?
A-7 closed.
Aah!
Over in the east wing!
Door B-7 safe!
-You, too?
-Yeah!
Over to "E," everybody!
-Where the fuck is "E"?
-This way!
Here...
Here, kitty, kitty, kitty.
Here, kitty, kitty.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my...
You bastard!
It's coming!
It's coming down!
Jeez, it's coming!
It's after us!
Shut the fucking doors!
That was the plan!
Jesus,
it's on the fucking ceiling!
Dillon! Anybody!
This is not a drill!
Kevin! Gregor!
Where the fuck are you?
Now we're back in "A"!
Door three, "F" channel closed!
I hope.
Fuck.
-What the fuck are you doing?
-What?
Don't hold it like that.
Hold it like this.
You'll fucking kill someone,
you moron!
Aah!
Morse!
Kevin!
Gregor!
All they have to do
is run down the corridor.
Stay here.
Where the hell is it?
Aah!
No! Don't start the piston!
No! We have to trap it! No!
What are you doing? It's gone!
No! No.
It's gone.
OK?
OK.
Uhh.
Aah!
Kevin! Don't struggle!
Don't move! No!
Don't struggle.
Come on, Kevin! Come on!
Come on! Come on!
It's coming!
Take the piston!
Come on, it's all right.
It's OK.
It's OK. It's all right, Kevin.
Kevin. Kevin!
Kevin.
Leave him.
Leave him. He's dead.
Lure it in.
Shit. How much time?
I'm not sure.
Four or five minutes.
We've got to get it back in here
before the piston
seals this place up!
Let's move it!
Help me!
Jude!
Dillon!
Help me, Dillon!
It's coming at me!
Don't look back, Jude!
Run as fast as you fucking can!
Help me! God! Please!
Jesus Christ!
Thank God you're here.
Warder Aaron, sir. 137512.
Not many of us left.
Where is Lieutenant Ripley?
Is she still alive?
If she's alive,
she's in the furnace.
She's in the lead works
with the beast.
Wouldn't wait.
Jesus Christ.
You fucker. Scared me shitless!
I thought you were
the fucking beast, you fuck!
Aah!
Wanker!
Move.
Come on, you bastard.
Come on!
Come on, get out of there!
Come here!
Ripley,
we're running out of time!
Ripley, where are you?
No!
Come on.
Get out of there!
What the fuck
is wrong with you?
Let it go!
Ripley.
Yeah! It's working!
Scream. Let it follow us.
We got to get it
in front of the piston.
It's following us!
Motherfucker, come on!
Come and get us! Come on!
Come on, come on.
Come on, motherfucker! Come on.
Come on! Get the door!
Get the door!
Morse!
-Now!
-Shut it, Morse!
Morse! Shut that door!
-Now!
-Shut the fucking door!
I'm going for the lead!
-What about you?
-I'm staying.
Bullshit! There'll be
ten tons of hot lead in here.
I want to die!
We got a deal! Remember?
It dies first, then you!
I'm not moving without you!
Now get going!
Dillon!
I've got to hold it here.
What about me?
God will take care of you now.
No!
Pour the lead.
Fuck you.
-No!
-Pour it, Ripley!
Go on!
God damn it!
Pour the lead, Ripley!
Come on!
Come on, that's all you got?
Fight, motherfucker! Come on!
Morse!
Morse, over here!
-Ripley!
-Pour the lead!
Pour the lead!
Pour it!
Aah!
Ha ha ha!
I hate bugs!
Ripley! It's burning hot!
Hit the sprinklers!
Douse the fucker!
Ohh!
Gotcha!
Yes!
Don't come any closer.
Wait. They're here to help.
Stay where you are.
Ripley.
Bishop?
I'm here to help you.
No more bullshit.
I just felt it move.
You know who I am?
You're a droid,
same model as Bishop...
sent by the fucking Company.
No. I'm not the Bishop android.
I designed it.
I'm very human.
The Company sent me here
to show you a friendly face...
to demonstrate
how important you are to us...
to me.
You want to take it back.
We want to kill it
and take you home.
Bullshit.
You're wrong. We want to help.
What does that mean?
We're going
to take that out of you.
And keep it?
Can't let it live.
Everything we know
would be in jeopardy.
You don't want to take it back?
Ripley, time is important.
We've got a surgical bay
on the rescue ship.
Come with me.
You still can have a life.
Children.
Most important,
you'll know it's dead.
Let me help you.
What guarantee do I have...
once you've taken it out...
that you'll destroy it?
You'll have to trust me.
Please?
Trust me?
No.
What's this going to achieve?
-Aah!
-Stop!
Aw, Jesus!
Aah! Aah!
Morse.
Will you help me?
What do you want me to do?
It was a mistake!
There was no need for any of it!
Fucking android!
Ripley, think of all
we could learn from it.
It's the chance of a lifetime!
You must let me have it.
It's a magnificent specimen.
What are you doing?
No!
-Come on, you, get going.
-Aw, fuck you!
Ash, Captain Dallas.
Cargo and ship destroyed.
I should reach the frontier
in about six weeks.
With a little luck,
the network will pick me up.
This is Ripley...
last survivor of the Nostromo...
signing off.