Try as they will and
try as they might,
who steals me gold won't
live through the night.
A limousine?
What in the world has
gotten into you, Mr. O'Grady?
Just the start, my dear.
Just the start.
Take the last look at this dump.
Tomorrow we'll be
looking at mansions.
Mansions? Will you
listen to yourself?
And a limousine?
We've got no money for this.
Right inside.
Did the funeral parlor
deliver the package?
Aye. 'Tis on the porch
where they left it.
I don't want to touch it.
Will you tell me what's going
on here, Daniel O'Grady?
Will that be all, sir?
Joseph.
Bon voyage, captain.
Thank you very much, sir.
You have a nice evening.
Ma'am.
What's going on here is we're rich.
You were supposed
to bury your mother,
not send her ashes all
the way from Ireland.
- What are you going to do?
- It's not me mother's ashes.
Gold, Leah! Gold!
What in the Lord's name?
A pot of gold.
A wee person, a leprechaun.
I caught him and made him
show me where his gold is.
It's the rule, you know.
Aye, you're a drunken fool,
and a storyteller.
- It's the truth, I'm telling...
- There's a storm brewing.
I'm telling you the truth.
Come on to bed, now, and I'll
make you a pot of nice hot tea.
Leprechaun indeed.
Pot of gold. Whatever next?
Dan? Dan, is that you?
Mary had a little lamb
Little lamb, little lamb
Whose fleece was white as snow
He followed her to school one day
School one day school one day
Which was against the rules
I can't breathe.
Please open the suitcase.
I'm going to suffocate.
Do you like the gold
buckles on me shoes?
I want me gold now!
Oh, God, no!
Oh.
No problem.
I smell some tea brewing.
I hid the gold, Leah. We're rich now.
Where did you hide it, Dan?
Did you hide it somewhere
near the house?
Tell me where you hid the gold.
How did you find me?
The wee people have
their magical ways.
I knew it. What have
you done with my wife?
Oh. Oh, the poor lass.
I should've told her
to watch her step.
I got ya! It's my gold!
I'll fix him. I'll get him.
Your wife makes a fine pot
of tea, Danny me boy.
Where did you get that?
- I'll fix you, you bastard!
- No! No!
Here's what you'll get, you monster.
Get it away! Put it away!
I got the gold fair and square.
Them were the rules.
Catch me if you can!
You can't get away.
Looking for something?
What did you do?
You... You killed my wife.
Hello, Dan. I'm okay.
I just got a little kink in me neck.
I should have killed you when
I caught you in Ireland.
Give him the gold, Dan.
He's a nice little leprechaun.
I'll give you more than gold!
Your bullets won't stop me forever.
I'll keep coming back.
The power of this clover will
keep you in there forever.
Get that damn clover off this crate!
I told you you couldn't kill me.
Where's me gold, Danny me boy?
Oh, Danny, don't strain yourself now.
No, not gasoline.
You can't burn me. I won't let ya.
Don't strain yourself.
You're not as young
as you used to be.
You might have a stroke.
I curse ye for all eternity.
I traded me soul for me gold.
You'll trade your life.
If you give me me gold back...
I'll go away.
- Oh!
- Danny! What's wrong?
Burn in hell,
you little green bastard!
Did the match go out, Danny?
I say I need a four-leaf clover
One that's strong
and won't blow away
Won't you be my four-leaf clover
Be my lucky charm
that's here to stay
Dad, I'm still depressed.
I mean, come on.
Here I am in New Mexico
with my hick father
for the whole summer.
- Hey.
- No offense.
First of all, it's not New
Mexico, it's North Dakota.
Like it matters. All I care
about is it's not L.A.
Wait.
This is a joke, right?
This is our poor neighbor's house,
and then you're gonna
take us to our house.
Never judge a book
by its cover, honey.
Dad, this book doesn't
even have a cover.
I'm going to be miserable here.
There's no swimming pool.
There's no shopping malls.
There's no cable.
Bet you don't even have a TV.
Oh, this sure ain't Beverly Hills.
I can't wait to see this house.
Careful.
Oh, great.
Just when I thought this house
couldn't get any worse,
an old basement.
Well, great place to store all the
rocks and pinecones I'm gonna find.
Okay, okay. It's a little dusty.
I admit that.
Just clean it up a little bit,
splash some paint around.
Oh, God. You'll need to slap
some bulldozers around
to fix this place up.
Oh, God! Gross. Cobwebs.
You're making too big a
deal out of this, honey.
This is a great house.
I got a great buy on it.
Yeah, from who, Dracula?
How about I get a hotel
somewhere in town,
and you can come visit,
like, once a week?
- Hey, I'll pay for it.
- Tory, honey,
you really think money's all you
need to get by in this life?
Okay. I'll go with that theory.
Oh...
Dad! Do you see that spider?
It's huge. That thing could kill us.
Okay, I'm going to turn around and
I'm walking out of this basement,
and I'm going back up to the jeep.
I'm making a reservation at
the nearest hotel in town.
This is worse than summer camp!
I'd rather sleep in a tent!
Wait. Hold on. Hold on.
Hello? We're breaking up.
Wait. Okay. Okay. That's good.
Okay, hi. I'd like to
make a reservation.
Yes. I'd like it to be a really tall
room, and I want it to be very...
- Oh!
- Great!
Who are you?
I was a guy carrying
some paint thinner.
Oh, G... Okay.
Here. Does that cover?
Wait. Hold on a second.
You knock over my can
of paint thinner,
and then you offer me 20 bucks?
Okay. Okay.
How about that? Will that do it?
No.
But maybe if you said you were
sorry, you know, it might.
Okay. Here. Look, keep the change.
I'm in a really big hurry.
There's a big, ugly, disgusting house
I'd just like to distance myself from.
What, you mean this house here?
The O'Grady place?
Yeah, that place. It's really gross.
There's bugs. There's cobwebs.
God only knows what else is in there.
What's so funny?
Well, I just think it's
funny the way girls
are always afraid of spiders
and stuff, you know?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Okay, wait a minute.
Did I misplace my 1950s
calendar here? Girls?
Listen, Bud. Okay, this is the '90s.
Women are treated equal.
Well, first off, my name
isn't Bud, it's Nathan.
And I don't know many guys
that are afraid of houses.
- Oh, is that so?
- Yeah.
Well, you know what? Neither am I.
I'm not afraid of anything.
- Okay.
- Right.
- Tory? Honey?
- Yeah?
- What?
- Let's go.
What are you talking about?
What are you doing?
I'm not gonna fight you anymore.
The house. You hate the house.
- No...
- It's dirty, it's dusty.
You really think I'm afraid of
a little dust and some bugs?
Come on. Just put
the bags back, okay?
I want to stay.
Dad, would you put the bags back?
I'm gonna stay.
Anyway, listen, listen.
It came right down out of the sky.
There it was,
this flying saucer.
Had these really weird
lights, you know?
And making all these weird noises.
Kind of like... Kind of like,
"boop boop boop boop..."
Ozzie, I thought you weren't
gonna tell any more stories.
This really happened, Alex. It did.
It's like magic, you know? Like...
Like, um...
Well, when you see
a star in the night sky...
the first star...
you can make a wish.
- It'll come true.
- Stop with the magic stuff.
And no more lies, okay?
How ya doin', boys? I'm J.D.
I just met your brother Nathan.
Hi, I'm Alex. Nice to meet you.
This is my friend Ozzie.
- How you doin', Ozzie?
- Hi.
So, you boys need any help out here?
I'm afraid that our
liability insurance forbids
anyone but us handling
the tools and equipment.
But thanks for the offer.
Boy, I could go for a beer right now.
You're too little to drink.
Don't you ever,
ever drink that stuff!
- Hey, Ozzie, what's this?
- Hey!
Gotcha! Whoa! Let go!
Nathan?
Oh, geez, I'm sorry. You all right?
I was on that shelf, looking for tarps.
I didn't know you were down here.
I was just trying to
make a peace offering,
but I think it's all in that crate.
Hope I didn't ruin what's inside.
Oh, you couldn't
damage what's in here.
- The O'Gradys collected a lot of junk.
- The O'Gradys?
Yeah, Dan O'Grady.
He used to own this place.
He was really a weird,
strange guy, you know?
Oh. You mean, weird and strange
like guys who drive dented pick-up
trucks and paint houses for a living?
Hey, let's see what
he's got in this thing.
Yeah.
Well, that is, of course,
unless you're scared.
Scared? Me?
Give me a crowbar.
I'll bust it open myself.
Got a hammer.
Fine. Hammer is good. Hammer.
That sounds like Ozzie.
Oh, no!
As fashion statements go,
blue is not your best color.
Alex, I asked you to
hold that ladder steady.
Now look what happened!
I'm not even gonna ask
what happened, really.
There's a bathroom off
the kitchen in there.
At least, it looked a
little like a bathroom.
I don't even like blue.
Twinkle, twinkle
Little star
- How I wonder
- Hello?
What you are
Up above the world so high
- Who's in there?
- Like a diamond in the sky
Twinkle, twinkle, little star
How I wonder what you are
Hello?
Wow. What neat junk.
Please let me out. Please.
Why won't you let me
out of this crate?
How did you get in there?
Please, let me out.
Please, I don't like it in here.
Please.
Hello?
I'm back.
Hey, tubby, you got a light
for an old leprechaun's pipe?
I'm starved.
Haven't eaten in ten years.
What... What are you?
What do I look like, me lad?
See the hat? The buckles on me shoes?
Why, I'm a leprechaun.
A shoemaker by trade.
And speaking of shoes,
yours could use a shine.
But first...
have you seen a crock
of gold lying around?
Tell me, or I'll bite your ear off,
and I'll make a boot out of it.
You only got away 'cause
me powers are weak.
I need me gold!
There's a leprechaun in the basement!
Oh, there's a leprechaun
in the basement!
- Hold on. Slow down.
- He come right up out of a box.
He had these long really
scary fingers, and...
He wasn't nice like Lucky Charms or
anything, and then he ate a bug!
A leprechaun?
Can we inject a little bit
of reality in here, please?
I saw him! I really did see him!
He even tried to polish my shoes!
- So, then, where's your pot of gold?
- That's what he said he wanted.
- He said he wanted his pot of gold.
- All right.
Where you going?
Well, if it'll make you
feel any better, Ozzie,
we'll all go down in the
basement and check it out.
Don't go in there, don't go
in there, don't go in there!
Hey. Okay? Just in case.
I better go with you.
Just in case.
Nathan? Nathan?
I don't think that stick's
gonna be big enough.
Well, wait. Wait for me.
I'm coming, just in case.
Geez, Ozzie, you really
busted up this crate.
No, no, no. No, I...
I did... I didn't do that.
That... that was the leprechaun.
Leprechaun.
Well, I don't see anything, Ozzie.
But... this guy was real.
I mean, he had buckles on his shoes,
and he had them real horrible teeth,
and they were all rotten and
everything, and... and...
Oh, I... I know he
never does brush 'em.
Th-That's him.
He's gonna kill every one
of us, and I'm first.
- Ozzie, come here.
- I ain't goin' in that dark corner.
Neither am I.
What was that?
Hey, hang on. Hang on.
It's only a rat.
It's just a rat.
Well, Ozzie, I think we
found your leprechaun.
No, no, no.
Y-You don't understand. He...
He was bigger than that.
All right, all right. I think
we've solved this mystery now.
Can we just get out of here?
- Hey! Hey, look up in the sky!
- So what, Ozzie?
- It's just a rainbow.
- It's a magic rainbow.
Leprechauns and rainbows.
It's a sign.
Yeah. Yeah, it's a sign, all right.
It's time to get back to painting.
- Come on.
- No, no, no. No.
We gotta go... go see
what's at the end.
Ozzie, you're embarrassing me.
Come on. Go with me.
We... We gotta get to
the end of the rainbow.
- There's always a pot of gold!
- Ozzie.
He's so easily sidetracked.
Like always, I'll take care of it
and get him back on the job.
Ozzie, come on! Alex!
Oh, come on. Let 'em
go chase rainbows.
Let's you and I go paint.
Um, this is biodegradable, right?
Ozzie, this is stupid! You can't
find the end of the rainbow!
It's where the rainbow ends.
It does sort of look
like where it ends.
Hey, look. It's going away.
Don't cut yourself on any
of this rusty old metal.
If you do, it'll make
your jaw lock shut.
This is neat. Hey,
Ozzie, I got an idea.
- What?
- Let's hotwire this.
I don't think the battery
would be any good.
Ooh.
Look at that.
- Ooh!
- Give me it!
- No, no, no.
- Just let me look at it for a minute!
- Give me it!
I'll give it right back to you,
I promise. I promise.
- Give me that.
- Hey!
Wow! Look at that!
All right, here's your coin.
I found a bag full of 'em!
- Wow!
- Cool!
I told you. I told you!
It's what that leprechaun
was talking about.
Will you stop with that
stupid leprechaun stuff?
We found this gold. Finders keepers.
I just hope it's real.
I know how to tell if it's real.
You just bite on it.
I seen it in a movie.
Oh, my God.
I swallowed that gold coin.
Nice going, Jaws.
Hey, hey, hey, can you die
from swallowing gold?
Yeah, after I kill you!
Now, you just let me
take charge, okay?
I'm just gonna keep one,
and then I can get it checked out
in town and see if it's real or not.
We're gonna hide the rest.
We can't tell anyone about this.
Right, right. Why?
'Cause you know how adults are,
especially when it comes to money.
They'll just try to take it away.
I got the perfect place to hide it...
the old well beside the house.
Hey, Ozzie, do you
know what this means?
We're rich, and... and I
can buy comics every week.
- Yeah, but you know what else?
- What else?
We can get you an operation.
- For what?
- To make you smart.
See, we can go to the hospital
and have them operate
and fix your brain.
But... But I-I'm smart.
Yeah, well, sort of.
What I mean is,
we could make you real smart.
That way, people won't
make fun of you.
- They make fun of me?
- Not in front of you.
Only behind your back.
Come on. Let's go the well.
Come on!
Um, wait. Here, start in the corners.
Nice, even strokes.
Wow. That's it.
- You got it.
- Not bad?
Yeah, yeah. A regular Picasso.
Put me out of business.
- Oh, need another can of paint.
- Oh, okay.
Well, you just watch how
a pro gets a can of paint.
All right. Let me get a rag first,
all right? Go ahead.
Oh...
Nathan.
Nathan, come on. What are you doing?
Oh, my God.
Oh, what was that?
Oh, geez.
Honey, are you okay?
I heard you scream.
I thought that was
you rubbing my leg.
- And you let me?
- That's not the point.
Something was rubbing my leg,
like caressing it,
and it ran off over there.
It's probably just an
old possum, honey.
No, Dad, that was
not an animal, okay?
I know what it feels like
when a man caresses my leg.
You do?
Look, we gotta get
these cuts cleaned up.
Yeah, I should probably go
look for that animal?
- Absolutely.
- Wait. Why?
- Might have rabies.
- Great.
It was a cat.
I think we found your
secret admirer, honey.
It wasn't a cat.
Sounds hurt. Come on,
kitty, kitty, kitty.
Here kitty, kitty, kitty, kitty.
Come on, kitty. Come on.
Here kitty, kitty, kitty,
kitty, kitty, kitty.
Here kitty, kitty,
Come on. Come on,
kitty, kitty, kitty.
What? What?
- What?
- The cat bit me!
- Oh, my God.
- Okay. Put pressure on it.
- It bit me! It bit me!
- Oh, my God!
- Stay there. Put pressure on it.
It's gonna be okay, Dad.
We're gonna take you to the hospital.
- Truck. Ozzie, Alex!
- It bit me!
We're taking him to the
emergency room, all right?
Sit down, boy.
Aw, man.
- Oh, no!
- Come on.
- Alex!
- Shoot! The distributor cap.
Right.
Come on, come on!
Hey, guys, we may be a while, okay?
So why don't you go get
a bite to eat at the café?
- We'll see you in a bit.
- All right.
- This is our chance.
- What, to get something to eat?
- No, to check out the gold coin.
- Oh, yeah.
- Come on. It's getting dark.
- Okay.
I have never seen a coin like this.
The symbols,
incredibly strange markings.
Cut to the chase. What's it worth?
Well, if this is solid gold,
could be worth $500.
But if there's historical value,
it could be priceless.
Could I keep this
overnight and study it?
You won't lose it or
anything, will ya?
No, no. I'll put it in my safe.
I'll write up a receipt.
You... You reckon that...
that coin
might've come from a leprechaun?
Never mind.
Okay, we'll come back tomorrow.
And let's just keep this between us.
- Okay.
- We better get to the restaurant.
They're gonna be pissed
we were gone so long.
I must be hearing things.
Well, okay. I'll get
this put away right now.
Three left. Right.
There we go.
I want me gold coin!
Me coin!
It's not nice to steal gold
coins from a leprechaun.
Bad shop owner. Bad shop owner.
I'll be back.
Now we're going to play.
Do you want to play with me?
Oh, no!
No!
This old lep, he played one
He played pogo on his lung
Teach you to steal me gold.
Aw.
Can't have dirty shoes, now, can we?
There. Nice and shiny.
Oh. You'll bounce back in no time.
One gold coin, 99 to go.
By the luck of the Irish.
Oh, won't you please
Be my four-leaf clover
Can you be my lucky charm
Are you sure you told Ozzie
and Alex where this place is?
I mean, they were
supposed to meet us here.
Relax. They're kids.
Probably just stopped off
to buy Ozzie a comic or something.
Boy, what a night.
My first day here, and my
father ends up in the hospital.
Well, it's just for observation.
He'll be fine in the morning.
Look on the bright side, Tory.
I mean, the worst is over.
Oh, won't you please
Say, aren't we a little
young to be out this late?
No. I'm 600 years old.
Okay, smartass.
Why don't you take that ridiculous
mask off and step out of the car?
It's not nice to make
fun of a leprechaun.
Is that so?
So now you're a leprechaun?
You sure you don't want anything?
No. I mean, yes, I do want something.
What I wanted was a watercress salad
and an Evian water,
but they don't have that here.
All they have is cheap
whiskey and warm beer.
Well, here's water.
Geez. Thanks.
Okay. Okay.
Get away from me, you little creep!
Get away!
Oh, God! Okay.
So, you want to play
hide-and-seek?
Over here!
I'm over here.
Stop.
Stop!
Leave me alone. Leave me alone.
Leave me alone!
No more.
Where the fuck are you?
Oh, thank God.
Thank God...
No! Oh, God!
Now, that was fun.
You know, Tory,
you look a little skinny.
No offense, but,
you should have some meatloaf.
- I got plenty, really.
- Oh, no.
- Do you know what that is?
- Yeah, it's meatloaf.
No, that's cut-up dead cow.
Okay? And that's if you're
lucky, in this place.
See, I don't eat meat,
and I don't kill living things.
- I feel very strongly about that.
- Really?
Really.
All right.
What are you... Nathan,
what are you doing?
Cut-up dead cow. That's what
your shoe is, you know?
Nathan, give me my shoe.
Nathan, give me my shoe back!
Come on! Look,
Alex and Ozzie are coming.
Would you try to set
a mature example?
Sorry we're late.
- Hey.
- Where have you been?
We were down over at that place.
Now, where's me crock of gold?
There.
Dad!
Daah! Bah!
I want me gold!
There.
- Geez.
- Oh, God.
What the...
Oh, my God.
I think something got in here.
No shit, Sherlock.
You better watch your
mouth and go wash it out
with soap right now, boy.
Sure. Sure.
And right after that, Ozzie,
I'll be sure to ground
myself for two weeks.
This is crazy.
- What the hell's going on here?
- Well, it could've been a bear.
They sometimes come down
from the hills looking for food.
Great. My dad had to bring
food into this place.
You know what? That leprechaun...
he tried to shine my shoes,
and he said he was a shoemaker.
Look, you guys can sit
around here and theorize...
bear or no bear...
but I am getting out of here.
As a matter of fact,
I'm walking out that door,
and I'm not coming back.
A little too dark out there.
All right. Let's clean
this place up, all right?
Here. You know how to
work one of these, right?
Okay. Fellas.
Man!
Well, we finally got that
kitchen straightened up.
Yeah. I'm really beginning to
get the hang of this thing.
- What's that?
- Sounds like a bell.
Look what I found.
- Great, Ozzie.
- Great.
I'm gonna go check out the bedrooms,
find out where we're
gonna stay tonight.
Oh, great. While you do that,
I'm gonna find my purse
and check into a hotel.
Alex,
do you think you could
kill a leprechaun?
Ozzie, you can kill anything.
You just gotta know how to do it.
Now, me? Give me a .357 Magnum,
press it to the little
green critter's temple,
and blam!
Brains and guts and
oozing cruddy stuff
dripping all down its head.
The guy's gone with a capital "Dead."
Ozzie, will you cut it out
with that stupid bell?
Wait. It sounds like it's
coming from the kitchen.
We're, like, really scared, okay?
Stay here. I'm gonna check it out.
Nathan, be careful.
My leg!
Caught you in a bear trap.
I caught you in a bear trap.
- You look like a stupid sap.
- What the hell are you?
Oh, oh, it looks like you're hurt.
Let's play surgeon.
No!
- Nathan!
- Tory, no!
- Tory, get back!
- What the hell happened?
- My leg!
- Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! Ozzie, call the police!
Call the police!
Get off me!
- You can't hurt me.
- Oh, my God!
Alex, get the shotgun!
All right! I'll get the shotgun.
- Hurry up, Alex!
- Ozzie, it's me!
- I gotta get the shotgun!
- Hurry!
Help! Help! It's happening!
The attack is on.
O'Grady farm. Send help.
The... The leprechaun is attacking.
Army, navy, guns, marines.
- And we're gonna need some medicine.
- Okay, thanks.
Hey, Sheriff, I just got a call from Ozzie.
Says the leprechaun is attacking.
What was it last week? Was it UFOs?
No, no, it was Bigfoot.
Well, you'll learn about Ozzie.
He's a good boy.
A leprechaun.
That's a good one.
I'm coming! Here's the shotgun!
Take it!
Kill him! Kill him!
Yeah!
Ozzie, hurry up!
- Get this thing off me!
- Ozzie, get Alex on the porch!
- Come on, boy.
- I don't want to go to the porch!
Okay!
He went off through the bushes.
God! Nathan,
that was no fucking bear.
My God. It's gone.
God, Nathan, your leg. Look at it.
Oh, my God! Okay,
we gotta call a paramedic.
Oh, I took care of it. I called them,
told them we needed the army
and... and the medicine
and a paramedic.
Ozzie... Ozzie, y-you didn't tell them
that it was a leprechaun, did you?
Of course I did.
That's what it was, wasn't it?
- Okay. Okay. All right.
- Oh, geez.
All right. We just gotta get him
back to the house. Come on.
Shit! The line's dead.
- Alex, you a member of the Boy Scouts?
- Cub Scouts.
Good enough. Okay,
you gotta help me with this.
We gotta stop the bleeding.
Ozzie, go to the bathroom,
get everything you can:
tissue, alcohol, cotton.
Tory, did that thing look...
look like a leprechaun to you?
- Ozzie, go!
- Come on, man.
You're gonna be okay, Nathan.
Okay. So, as soon as
we stop the bleeding,
we're gonna take Nathan
out to the pickup.
But what if that thing
is still out there?
No way. I shot it. I put six
rounds into that thing.
- Yeah. It's gotta be dead.
- Yeah.
All right. Alex, go the fridge.
Get me some ice.
It'll stop the swelling
on Nathan's leg.
Alex, get the door.
Come on.
Hurry up and get him out of here!
I don't see him.
- Where is the old guy?
- Hurry.
- Come on. Be careful.
- Hold on, Nathan.
- Need help?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Oh, God. Do you see him?
- Oh, God, that hurts.
- Almost there.
Hurry up! Get him in the truck!
- What if he comes?
- Hurry up. Hurry up. Get in.
Thanks.
Nathan!
- Okay. We made it.
- Yeah.
- What's wrong with the truck?
- Oh, no!
- Shit!
- The distributor cap.
- Alex, be careful.
- Yeah.
Hurry!
- Let me in!
- Hurry! Get in!
- Close the door!
- Roll up the window! Hurry!
- Roll it up! Roll it up!
- I'm rolling! I'm rolling!
Come on out and play, me friends!
Get away! Get away!
No!
Come on!
Burn and die, you monster!
My... My ear! He... He got my ear!
Hey, chill!
What the heck is he doing in there?
Ring around the rosie,
a pocket full of posies
Faster! Faster!
No!
Ashes, ashes, we all fall down
Where'd you go, me friends?
I want to know where me gold is.
Give it back to a nice
little harmless leprechaun.
Okay. Let's go. Now.
Where is he?
Where are you going, me friends?
Hurry!
- What are we gonna do now?
- Phone.
- Phone. I gotta call for help.
- The phone is dead.
The phone is dead. Okay. My portable!
Hello? I need the police.
This is an emergency.
Yes. Hello. This is Tory Reding.
I'm calling from the O'Grady farm.
Um, something really
terrible has happened,
and we need you to send
someone out here right away.
Okay. Please hurry.
You've got... Hello?
Damn it! Okay. The battery died.
- Oh, no!
- It's okay.
I got through, and they're
gonna send somebody,
and we're gonna be okay.
It's gonna be fine.
Deputy Tripet, come in.
This is Sheriff Cronin.
Tripet, do you read me?
I read you, Sheriff. Yeah, go ahead.
Yeah, yeah, this is Sheriff Cronin.
We got a... a call from over
there at the O'Grady farm.
A female, name of Tory Reding,
called in an emergency.
Get out there on a code-one
priority right away.
Roger, Sheriff.
My ETA is less than three minutes.
- If I need backup, I'll call it in.
- Roger, Tripet.
You got the back door, right?
Right. And the basement
windows are locked up tight.
All right. Now double-check
the windows in the kitchen.
Oh, my ear sure hurts, Tory.
I bet that leprechaun
made a boot out of it.
You're gonna be okay, Ozzie.
He didn't get your ear.
- He just bit it.
- Where the hell are the police?
Well, they should be here by now.
Okay.
All right. Now, I'm gonna have to
make this a little tighter, okay?
Too tight?
No, it's all right. It's all right.
Boy, that leprechaun sure is mean.
It is not a leprechaun, damn it!
Ozzie, now, I admit I don't know
what the hell that thing was,
but it is not a leprechaun.
Do you understand?
Well, what about the
gold in the old rusty car?
Oh, ne-never mind what I just said.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Wait, wait.
What do you...
What do you mean, gold?
Alex.
Tell me, Alex. The gold?
We were gonna save it to get
Ozzie an operation to fix his brain.
Alex, you can't fix Ozzie's brain.
I know that, but he doesn't.
Okay. Okay. Tell me about the gold.
Okay. In the water bucket, right?
Right. Just pull it up,
and there's a bag of gold coins.
Okay. This has gotta work.
If all he wants is his gold,
he's gotta leave us alone.
- Let's go. Come on.
- No, no, no, no.
- No, you're hurt too bad.
- Come on.
- All right, all right.
- Sit down, Nathan.
- Okay, look, take this gun with you, okay?
- Okay.
Just cock it, aim it,
and pull the trigger.
Okay.
You ever work one of
those things before?
Nope.
Watch out for those teeth.
God! Come on. Come on.
- Is that me gold?
- What the hell are you?
I'm a leprechaun, me dear.
Here. This is what
you're looking for, right?
Me powers are returning.
It sounds like me gold.
It looks like me gold.
It smells like me gold.
It tastes like me gold.
Oh, God!
Oh, God! Oh!
Me golden delicious gold.
Be calm. Be calm.
Okay. He took it.
Okay, so he got what he wanted.
Now we can get everybody to
the hospital and, call for help.
It's over.
94...
95...
96...
Oh! 97...
And 98...
and 99...
A missing coin.
I've been tricked.
They've got me coin!
No one takes a leprechaun's gold.
Oh, God. Alex, you gotta
get some ice for Ozzie's ear,
and boil up some water.
I'll cover you.
Put me down!
We're cooking now, kids.
Ozzie!
Okay. Over there.
Oh, God, he's in the cabinets.
Okay. Tory, I want you to open
it up and get back quickly, okay?
- Okay.
- Go.
God!
I want me gold!
- Quick!
- Okay.
Oh, God!
You should have picked
door number two, me lad.
Okay. Okay.
You missed me.
- Oh, my God!
- Where is he?
- You can never catch a leprechaun.
- There he goes!
Come on.
There he goes. He's getting away.
- Where the hell did he go?
- He went in there!
Alex, go stay with Ozzie.
Come on.
Ho-ho-ho!
I'm right here, and I
ain't no Santa Claus.
We got the sucker!
Nathan, be careful.
You think it's dead?
Yeah. Yeah, he's dead.
Not a chance, me lads!
Fiddle-dee diddle-dee dee,
a leprechaun me
All right. Hang on. Hang on.
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
- What the hell is that?
- I don't know.
I don't know.
Oh, God!
Come on.
Okay, where the hell is he?
Wait, wait. Hold on. Hold on.
Toward the basement.
Toward the basement!
No. Listen. Over here.
- Yeah, he's over there. I hear him.
- He's over there.
Wait. No. Listen.
All right. Okay, he's going
this way. Going this way.
- Right here.
- Okay.
Okay, come on, you little green
fucker, poke your head out.
- Come on, you little...
- Where is he?
- He went outside.
- He's gone.
- Crap.
He's...
It's gonna be okay.
Do you hear anything?
He's going down in the basement!
Hello, hello! Help us, please!
Come help us!
We're trapped inside of here!
Where's the rest of me gold?
Having problems?
Do you need a hand?
God, I don't get what
the fuck's going on!
I gave him his gold!
I... I think I know what he wants.
What?
He... He wants his last gold coin.
Stop him! He's got the last
gold coin in his stomach!
Ozzie, come on!
You can't go out there!
There's gotta be another way.
That thing is a leprechaun,
and we've gotta find a way to stop it!
Wait. Old man O'Grady.
He might know how to kill it.
- What?
- When I was a little kid,
he used to tell me stories
about fairies and leprechauns.
If anybody would know how
to kill this thing, he would.
He owned this house. He...
He probably put that thing in its crate.
- Well, where is he?
- Old man O'Grady
is in a rest home at the end of town.
He had a stroke about...
what... 10 years ago.
Well, then we gotta go there.
We gotta go there right now!
- How we gonna get there?
- The jeep. Okay...
Wait a sec. Wait. I got an idea.
Okay.
Alex, keep the door unlocked.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Hello, love!
Farther! Come on!
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Shiny, shiny.
Oh.
Good.
- Okay, Tory, we're clear.
- Okay. I'll be back.
Oh.
No! No! No!
Oh, God.
O'Grady, O'Grady.
Dan O'Grady.
Mr. O'Grady?
It's out. It's out of the crate.
You believe it.
No one believed it was a leprechaun.
I believe it. How do we stop it?
There's only one way...
one way to kill a leprechaun...
but I'm not going to tell ya.
What?
I'll never tell ya!
Oh, my God! Oh!
No! Oh!
Oh, God! Oh!
Oh! Oh! Come on! Open, open, open!
Come on! Oh!
Oh, God. Oh...
No!
He came back for me.
I knew he would,
but no-nobody would believe me.
God, we've gotta get you down.
No. No. It's too...
too late for that now.
But you have to...
you have to kill it.
How? How can we kill it?
A four-leaf clover,
freshly plucked from the clover patch
beside the well.
You gotta put it on his body.
It has to touch him.
Then you can kill him.
Okay.
No...
Little girls shouldn't look
for four-leaf clovers.
Come to me, me dear.
Oh, G...
Oh, my God, a cop! Oh, my God, a cop!
Help! Please!
You gotta help us! Please help us!
Please! Please! Oh, my God!
You've gotta help us!
Oh, my God, no!
I want me gold!
Oh! No!
Oh, no! Get out! Please get out!
An eye for an eye, me dear.
Oh, please, please get out!
Tory!
- We heard your screams.
- Oh, my God.
- Where's Alex?
- He's okay. He's up in the house.
- He's safe.
- Okay. Oh, God. Okay.
O'Grady said that we need
to have a four-leaf clover.
A four-leaf clover will
kill the leprechaun.
We better get outta here
before that thing wakes up.
Okay. There's gotta be a four-leaf
clover in the patch up there.
- He said there was.
- Okay, come on. Let's go.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Whoa, look at this, you guys!
We're never gonna find
a four-leaf clover in here.
Yes, we can. I found one
once when I was a kid.
- Hey!
- What?
Oh, never mind.
Oh, God, Ozzie!
I gotta get him.
I'm not afraid.
I can get that leprechaun.
Please don't be here yet.
I know I can get him. I'm not afraid.
I'm gonna kill him.
I can get him. I can get him.
I'm not afraid.
Forget it. We're not gonna find it.
Y-You can, too, find it.
You just gotta believe.
Damn it, Ozzie!
I'm so sick of your magic
and your stupid fantasies!
Okay, it's too late for that now!
We don't have time
to sit here in a damn clover
patch and look for clovers!
- That thing is gonna wake up!
- You've lost your faith.
You gotta believe. You got to.
All right, Ozzie. Here. Look.
Here. Look.
I believe. I believe!
Look. You... You found one!
I told you. I told you!
Yes!
- We've gotta get this on the leprechaun!
- Yeah! Come on!
Top o' the morning, me lad!
- Please! Let go! Let go!
- Now I'll finish what I started.
- Get down!
- Help! Please!
Nathan! Ozzie! Please,
somebody help me!
He's gonna kill me!
Let go! Please, help!
No! It's me!
It's me you want, you little
green son of a bitch!
I've got the last gold coin.
I swallowed it. It's in my stomach.
Then it's your belly I want.
- Use the clover! Use the clover!
- How's your leg?
Are you okay?
- Wait! No!
- I gotta go see Ozzie!
Alex!
I want me last coin!
Me gold!
Hang on, Ozzie! I'll save you!
One second!
I'll save you! Hang on! Hey, lep!
Fuck you, Lucky Charms.
We did it.
I did a smart thing. I did
a smart thing, didn't I?
You're really smart, Ozzie.
You just hang in there, okay?
Hey, Alex, what's that?
Gotcha.
First time I ever got ya.
You sure did, Ozzie.
I want me gold!
Oh, Jesus.
I'll not rest till I have me gold.
Curse this well
that me soul shall dwell
till I find me magic
that breaks me spell.