Get off me!
Oh, please.
Please, don't hurt me.
It's wrong! She's too young!
The sins of the flesh will ruin her.
Please don't hurt me!
Please!
The wicked will be punished.
"The mystery heart condition that has
killed over 30 people in 4 years...
has claimed another victim.
Doctors are baffled as to why
fit and healthy people...
are suffering massive heart attacks.
Many residents claim that
the 'Shadow of Death'...
has again descended on the town. "
"Shadow of Death"?
I don't like it.
That's what they're saying.
People are scared out there.
"For decades, Fairwater
has been linked with death...
following the 1964
Bradley-Bartlett murder spree.
Thirty years later,
as the death toll steadily rises...
it appears the Grim Reaper
has once again returned...
to the quiet streets of Fairwater. "
Oh, no. Steve, no.
I asked for a new angle.
Give me something fresh.
I want to see the human face of
this tragedy. Talk to the families.
How has this affected
the local community?
Yes, Miss Rees- Jones.
And, Steve...
no more references
to death as a person.
Friend of the family?
Really such a shame.
Go on. Get out. Go on.
Get out!
Damn.
Oh, my God!
I don't believe this.
This is not happening. My lawn!
You ruptured my lawn!
Hey, how you doing?
Give me a call.
I'll pay for the damages.
You're damn right! I'm suing your ass!
Don't get litigious. Send me a bill.
"Frank Bannister, Psychic Investigator"?
So why didn't you see
the corner coming?
You stupid moron!
This is goddamn bullshit!
This will cost you big time!
You're paying for a new fence!
I want this lawn
completely resurfaced!
Budzo!
I got your license plate number!
You bastard!
This is private property.
Mrs. Bradley? I'm Dr. Lynskey.
I work at the medical center.
You do not.
I know who works there.
I started 3 months ago.
Dr. Kamins is my physician.
He's attending a funeral.
I'm seeing his patients today.
She was cutting vegetables.
The knife slipped.
She just needs a few stitches.
I'll drive you to the clinic.
That's impossible.
It's a deep cut.
Leave us antibiotics.
Mother, please.
Patricia never leaves the house.
But it hurts.
To your room this instant!
Wait. Just a minute.
Who did that to you?
I think you'd better go now,
Dr. Lynskey.
You don't know
who my daughter is, do you?
Patricia's not to be trusted.
I beg your pardon?
I can have her locked up
anytime I want.
They said she was
an accessory after the fact.
I know the truth.
It was cold-blooded murder.
In the space of 27
blood-soaked minutes...
12 innocent people were shot by
hospital orderly John Charles Bartlett.
Patients, medical staff, visitors...
no one was spared in this rampage
through Fairwater Sanatorium.
Not even the hospital chapel...
provided sanctuary, as those in prayer
were shot on their knees.
We're reporters.
We have to get the news!
A seemingly senseless crime...
Bartlett's motive
remains a mystery to this day.
Johnny Bartlett.
He's got a demonic look
on his face.
Any comments, Johnny?
Got me a score of 12, sir.
That's one more than Starkweather.
Six years earlier,
Charles Starkweather had murdered...
eleven people
in a Nebraska killing spree.
Guess that makes me
public enemy number one!
Fifteen-year-old
Patricia Anne Bradley...
daughter of
the hospital administrator...
was also implicated in the killings.
She was madly in love
with the psychopath Bartlett.
That's her!
I was in her house this afternoon.
Terrific. We're in town 3 months and
you've befriended the Manson family.
2200 volts of electricity...
ended the life of Johnny Bartlett,
the unrepentant killer.
As they threw the switch,
he screamed:
"I got me a score of twelve.
Beat that. "
In what some considered
a miscarriage of justice...
Patricia Bradley was sentenced
to life imprisonment...
although it was never proven
she participated in the killings.
Five years ago,
Patricia Bradley was granted...
a conditional release
by the governor.
Today she lives a reclusive life
back in the family home...
Should have fried her
along with Bartlett.
She was fifteen years old.
She fell in love with the wrong guy.
Could happen to anyone.
Sweetie, don't go back there.
Place gives me the creeps.
I don't think...
Come on, honey.
I think tiger's
getting a little lonely.
What the hell is this doing here?
I thought I tore this up.
- Did he come back here?
- Who?
The moron who tore up my fence!
He's alive.
Ray, get me off!
You sick thing!
Lucy, I don't want
that con man in my house!
There has to be some kind
of rational explanation for this.
Ray! We have got a poltergeist!
It's nothing the police can't handle.
Bannister.
Dr. Lynskey, I'm on my way.
Persistent residue of the departed.
Always a problem this time of year.
Thank you.
Thank you for coming.
The activity is located where?
I don't know. It went quiet
about 5 minutes ago.
Went quiet?
The dining room table spun
in a counterclockwise direction?
I don't think that happened.
The toilet seat lid
banged up and down?
- Did the bed levitate?
- Yeah. With me on it.
Spontaneous recurrent psychokinesis.
Oh, boy.
This could be the worst case
I've ever seen. It's bad.
Well, I can do a clearance,
but it's not going to be cheap.
I do offer a six-month guarantee.
How much?
249.95.
And there is a 30% surcharge for making
a house call after midnight.
And there's vehicle, gas.
I'd say the whole thing will set you
back about $450.
We could forget about the fence,
call it even.
Stand back, ma'am. I don't want you
to have to sign a waiver.
Plus, a hundred bucks
for materials.
Just do it, for Christ's sake.
Here we go.
Why us? Why are they in our house?
Emanations are normally confined
to the cemetery...
although they do escape.
Usually young ones.
Oh, for God's sake, come on.
Come on.
It's holy water.
This is bullshit.
This is total bullshit.
Come on...
Okay, these belong to you.
Six ectoplasmic emanations.
Don't worry. They can't escape.
Some people like a souvenir.
I really don't think we want
to keep those. Thank you. Do we, hon?
I could give a rat's ass.
Okay, we'll just...
They can't feel a thing.
At least that's what the book says.
You never know for sure.
All right. Thank you, Bannister.
You can go.
What are you staring at?
What's with the number?
What number?
If you're trying to freak me out,
it's not working.
He's just trying to get
more money out of us.
Get your shit and get
the hell out of my house.
Come on.
Move!
Thank you so much.
There you go.
Why must you always
alienate everybody?
I think I'm going to throw up.
Damn.
I hate that trunk!
I don't want ectoplasmic muck
all over my car seats.
The ectoplasm is the only thing
sticky enough...
to hold the damn car together.
I'm sorry about your shit Volvo,
but we won't ride in the trunk no more.
We could like to cruise
with some style, man.
You two left me high and dry.
I get to the house, nothing's
happening. I couldn't believe it.
Hey, Stuart... in or out.
Not even a banging toilet lid.
I looked like a asshole.
We strained our backs
lifting that heavy-ass bed.
Oh, yeah. What idiot put the number
on the guy's forehead?
It wasn't funny.
Start pulling your weight,
or it's back to the cemetery.
Pull this, Frank. I'm about
to go like Jesse on your ass.
I'm going to find some other
black ghosts and organize a march.
The African-American
Apparition Coalition. The AAAC.
I'll tell you something.
Nothing's worse than some pissed-off
brothers that's already dead!
Therefore, a happy ghost
is a productive ghost.
To that end, I've drawn up
a list of suggestions.
Bear in mind, we have given you
five years of loyal service.
Flies. That's what
you've given me, flies.
Why do flies stick to you guys
like shit to a blanket?
Very funny. You're a funny guy.
You only think about yourself.
I could complain, too.
I need some new clothes. I still look
like Linc from "The Mod Squad".
You died in the '70s. Bummer.
Now, Frank,
we got to talk about cigars.
You promised to buy me a box.
I hate to tell you,
but you're dead. You can't smoke.
Light one and blow the smoke
in my face.
If I light a cigar,
I'll blow my lunch in your face.
Everybody, get down!
Damn it, Judge!
Put the shooters away!
That was a head shot!
He could have killed me!
If I wanted to get shot at every day,
I'd move to Los Angeles!
When a man's jawbone drops off...
it's time to reassess the situation.
I got myself...
a nice little grave
up there at the cemetery.
It could soon be time
to lay my bones.
You're my go-to guy.
Without you, I'm out of business.
Frightening...
that's a young man's game, Frank.
I ain't got no more hauntings
left in me.
What? You're in...
great shape.
My joints are getting powdery.
The dog is running away with my face.
Hell, I'm falling apart.
You have been for years.
Don't say nothing to the boys, but...
my ectoplasm is all dried up.
I'm sorry to hear that, Judge.
Give it up, Frank.
Death ain't no way
to make a living.
I have to finish this house.
You'll never finish this house!
You'll never finish nothing!
You're fooling yourself, Frank!
Too many skeletons in the closet.
Okay, this is it.
We got to be hard.
We go in like Charles Bronson.
We don't stop till the screaming starts.
I'm with you.
Let's go.
Yeah. Let's kick some ass.
Here we go.
One, two, three.
Good morning,
my darlings. Hello.
The mail is on the table,
Mrs. Waterhouse.
Sylvia, Mother is coming for lunch.
Pick up. Quick.
Big kiss.
Quit jumping around like a baby.
This is serious.
We're going to scare the living
daylights out of your parents.
- Will you help us out?
- Are you with us?
See? He gets it.
The kids always get it.
Let's go.
Mrs. Waterhouse.
Mrs. Waterhouse!
Damn. Here, man.
This one did le poo-poo.
- Get it away from me.
- Oh, man, it smells.
My babies!
Frank Bannister.
I'm on my way.
Persistent residue of the departed.
Always a problem this time of year.
Frank Bannister. I believe you called.
Not a minute too soon.
- Frank, she...
- Shut up.
Frank, it's no use.
This is bad.
Recurrent spontaneous psychokinesis.
This could be the worst case
I have ever...
seen.
I apologize for calling you,
Mr. Bannister. Please leave.
What are you doing to me?
Preying on the bereaved
is as low as you can go.
You're a parasite.
People should be warned.
I've a right to offer
my services to the public.
In case you haven't noticed,
we are having a major health crisis.
The last thing the people here need
is a two-bit charlatan...
passing on bogus messages
from the other side.
Now, if you will excuse me.
I'm just trying to make a living.
Living? Not a word you'd know
a lot about, is it, Mr. Bannister?
Hey, easy.
You all right, buddy?
That was quite a fall.
Bannister!
You have to help.
They're going to bury me.
What is happening to me?
You appear to be dead, Ray.
That's impossible.
I'm in the prime of my life.
I work out.
My wife's a doctor!
- Why didn't you take the corridor?
- What corridor?
The passageway to the other side.
Because I don't belong there!
Jesus Christ, I'm only 29!
Just relax, all right?
Tell me what happened.
I was on the rowing machine.
Suddenly, I felt this vice-like grip
squeezing my heart...
and I couldn't breathe, Frank,
I just couldn't breathe.
I have the shakes.
I need some vitamin B.
You can't take vitamins anymore.
You don't eat, drink or go to
the bathroom. All that's over with.
In a year, you'll get another chance
for the other side, to be a pure spirit.
In the meantime,
you're an earthbound emanation...
a rotting cloud of bioplasmic
particles, dripping ectoplasm.
Relax, Ray.
All right, Bannister.
Can you give me a ride
so I don't miss my funeral?
Don't worry.
They won't hurt you.
What in the hell is going on out here?
Get back in your graves!
Son of a...
Holy Jesus.
Frank Bannister!
Go ahead. I'll handle this.
What are you doing in my graveyard?
You have been told to stay away!
Sound off like you have a pair!
It's a public place, Hiles.
I do not like you!
Do not bring your spooks in here
without permission. Disappear, scumbag!
I am not one of your shitty
little emanations!
You cannot push spirits around!
You are scum!
Using spooks to put the frighteners on
people! That makes me physically ill!
We have a lot of lowlifes around here!
I will provide an armed response
at any sign of trouble!
They must be contained!
Catch you later, Hiles.
My tour of duty
runs another 85 years!
There's a piece of dirt here
with your name on it.
I'm waiting for you,
you little maggot!
There were times
when people accused Ray...
of being less than generous,
but I am sure that deep down...
the man possessed a heart of gold
and a generous spirit.
It's true. He wouldn't lie,
not at a time like this.
Because God has chosen...
to call Ray from this life to Himself,
we commit his body to the ground.
Earth to earth,
ashes to ashes, dust to dust.
Jesus, what a waste.
It's a goddamn tragedy!
Good-bye, Ray.
Oh, sweetheart, don't cry.
Oh, shit!
Hey, Frank!
I know you can hear me!
Get me out of this hole!
Frank! Get me out!
Hiya, Frank.
Hi, Walt.
I'm surprised to see you.
Here on business?
Not exactly.
They're going to bury me alive!
I hear you and Lynskey had a little
run-in the night before he died.
Apart from his wife...
you were the last person
to see him alive.
You're the one here on business.
No. The FBI is very concerned
about these deaths.
They look like heart attacks...
but when they slice these people open,
their arteries are...
clean as a whistle.
But there's been tremendous pressure
on the heart...
like the life's been
crushed out of it.
You got any theories?
Bannister!
You mind if I pay my last respects
before they fill him in?
Yeah. I'm sorry.
Bannister!
Please.
Mr. Bannister.
Did you want to see me?
My God, Frank, she can see me!
I thought perhaps you
might have a message from Ray.
Tell her. Tell her I'm here, Frank.
Tell her.
Everyone says you're a fraud,
but I've seen what you can do.
Frank!
You must think I'm very stupid.
Excuse me.
Lucy.
Ray says he loves you very much.
Here is your table.
Is Ray with us?
Tell her she looks great.
He says you look great.
Tell her they're from me.
Those are from Ray.
It's our anniversary.
He says it's your anniversary.
Is... Is Ray beside me?
Greetings.
How are you this evening?
May I offer you some wine?
Lucy, do you want some?
What... red, white?
Red. We always have red.
White.
I've never liked red.
Lucy!
So you used to be an architect?
Long time ago.
Can it. She doesn't want
to hear your life story.
Wow. So, did you
build your own house?
Is it your dream home?
You could call it that.
I'll build you a dream home
once I get on my feet.
Why is it you can see Ray
and I can't?
I was in an accident.
It was a car accident.
About five years ago.
They say that...
sometimes when you have
a traumatic experience...
it can alter your perception.
So after that,
you could just see spirits?
I mean, what happened?
How about you talk to Ray?
That's why I'm here.
Finally, I'm in the conversation.
Terrific.
I do have an important question
I have to ask Ray.
He can hear you.
Ray...
I really need to know
where you invested my money.
The $16,000 that I had saved.
The attorneys can't find it.
Oh, shit! I blew it
on a bad investment.
Don't tell her that.
Let me think.
It's gone.
Lucy, it's gone.
Blown on a bad investment.
You asshole!
Tell her I'll look out for her.
I'll move back into the house.
That's not a good idea.
This doesn't concern you.
What's Ray saying?
He left. Ray left.
He said he's sorry, but you
should get on with your life.
Bannister, I'm going to kill you!
I can't believe it. That's just like
Ray to just take the money and run.
Ray and I haven't been honest with each
other in a long time, Mr. Bannister.
It wasn't what you would call
a good marriage.
You bitch!
It'll be okay.
Hands off my wife!
Goddamn it!
Sorry.
I can move shit, Bannister.
You better watch your back.
I better clean this up.
Be right back.
Good food, huh?
Yeah... it's great.
Mom!
Looks like another heart attack.
Can't confirm it till the autopsy.
Damn.
A waiter saw a guy exit the john
right before the body was found.
And who was that?
Frank Bannister, pale and shaking.
The waiter thought he was sick.
Damn.
Hi, Lucy.
Dr. Lynskey works for me.
We're colleagues.
She's a material witness.
Bannister was last seen
in the restaurant parking lot.
He took off at high speed.
Bring him in.
Look at that!
So your dead husband
was having dinner with you?
What did he order?
Oh, God. Excuse me.
Timmy, front desk, please.
Thank you.
Lucy, this is Special Agent
Milton Dammers of the FBI.
I came by train. I planned to fly,
but I didn't feel good about the plane.
At what time...
precisely, did Bannister
leave for the bathroom?
You.
I'm not sure...
precisely.
Did he use
excessive amounts of salt?
Answer the question.
For Christ's sake,
it's really late!
I don't remember!
What is this?
Excuse me, Lucy.
I'll be right back.
Milton...
Sorry, Sheriff.
I have a problem
with women yelling.
Can I get you anything?
Sheriff Perry!
You are violating
my territorial bubble.
Lucy, you're still grieving.
It would be easy for a man
like Frank to take advantage.
You have such closed minds.
I object!
Special Agent Dammers has over...
20 years' experience
in the area of...
paranormal psychology.
Much of that was spent undercover...
with various...
cults and sects.
I get all the fruity cases,
Mrs. Lynskey.
For God's sake, Milton,
come in and sit down.
I'm more comfortable standing.
What has this to do with Frank?
Mrs. Lynskey, you know
nothing about Frank Bannister.
You claim
he's a bona fide psychic...
yet all I have heard
is ill-informed, meandering waffle.
On the third day of July 1990...
Frank Bannister,
then a successful architect...
was overseeing construction
of his new home.
The contractor...
Jacob Platz...
would later confirm that Bannister
was consuming alcohol that morning.
12:23 P.M.
Platz sees Bannister
arguing with his wife, Debra.
It appears he had
promised Debra a garden...
and then, without consulting her,
laid a 4-inch thick concrete slab...
creating a basketball court
for himself.
12:31 P.M.
Platz watches the couple drive away.
Bannister kept a tool box
in the back of his car.
In it was a utility knife...
with a retractable blade.
Bannister purchased seven...
new blades that morning...
at Jesson's Hardware Store
and Building Supply...
on Third and Garrett...
Third and Garrett.
Third of July.
Seven blades. Three.
Milton...
you're mumbling; we can't
understand a word you're saying.
12:33 P.M.
Their '84 Volvo heads into the hills.
It is the last time anyone
will see the couple together.
By Bannister's admission...
the argument continues,
reaching a point...
when Debra demands...
to be let out.
At that moment, probably 12:36,
12:37 P.M., the car...
leaves the road on a curve...
presumably because Bannister
was driving too fast.
She was killed?
Her body was found
15 yards from the car.
Bannister...
was picked up 2 hours later,
wandering in the woods.
He claimed to have no recollection
of the events...
that occurred after the accident.
But here's the odd thing,
Mrs. Lynskey.
His utility knife...
was missing.
And to this day,
it has not been found.
But do you know
what was really bizarre?
Debra's corpse
had the number 13...
carved into its forehead.
Unlucky for some.
You're insane. You're talking
about a mythical figure.
A pseudo-religious icon
from the 12th century.
Save your pea-brained prattle
for the classroom, boy.
That was the Soul Collector.
He's been taking people out
since time began.
He's going about some dark business
here in Fairwater...
and we ain't nothing
but worm bait!
When your number's up...
that's it!
There's another one gone.
He's gone.
There's no money for you here,
Mr. Bannister.
You're next.
Are you threatening me?
That's not what I'm saying.
He's threatening to kill me.
- Will you relax?
- He is threatening to kill me!
Bannister!
Oh, great.
Hey, fellas.
Excuse me, excuse me.
Put the gun away.
- Freeze!
- Just take it easy.
Okay, Bannister,
you're under arrest.
Just stay there, Bannister.
Yes.
Great.
I did it.
Bannister. Stop.
Looks like I ain't shooting
with blanks no more!
Mighty fine woman.
Good teeth.
Judge.
Down!
They don't call me
the hanging judge for nothing.
Stay right there.
Heads up!
Good catch.
Freeze!
Good shooting, Tex.
And she was
so young and beautiful!
I like it when they
lie still like that.
This is heavy.
Hey, guys!
My juices are flowing again!
Judge!
Bannister!
Frank, get out of here, now!
Bastard!
Got to go.
Bannister!
Stop!
Damn! Come on!
Just get down!
Get down and stay down.
Magda!
Listen to me.
No!
Where'd he go?
You killed me, you bastard!
You're sick!
Is this how you get your kicks?
Did it feel good killing me?
Did it feel good
killing your wife?
You're a murderer!
He won't get far.
We have the state line covered.
Sheriff Perry...
I seriously doubt we will
see Bannister any time soon.
He is resourceful beyond anything
you can comprehend.
Hello, Frank.
Hey, Walt.
I've come to report that...
Magda Rees- Jones's...
body is lying near my car...
off Holloway Road.
Did you have anything
to do with her death?
Frank, are you okay?
What happened?
What are you doing?
You're arresting him?
Please leave.
Frank, you need a lawyer.
Go home, Lucy.
But you haven't done anything.
He hasn't done anything!
How do you know?
Do you know me?
Am I a nice guy?
Because...
that cozy scene in the restaurant
was bullshit.
Because...
I was doing my job.
I don't give a damn
about you or anyone.
What are you saying?
Go home.
Are you okay to drive?
There has been a destructive force
unleashed on this town...
such as I have never seen.
We have a body count...
of 28.
You're a very dangerous man.
You're not seriously suggesting
that Frank is responsible for...
You're way out of your depth here,
Sheriff. Please leave.
Frank Bannister is my prisoner.
By the power invested in me by
the President of the United States...
I am telling you...
to get the hell out of this room.
Have you ever heard
of Nina Kulagina?
March 10, 1970, Nina Kulagina,
with the power of her mind...
stopped the beat of a frog's heart.
The record of this experiment
is currently held...
in the files of Professor Gennady
Sergeyev of Saint Petersburg.
As Sergeyev
interpreted the cardiogram...
the heart experienced
a flare-up of electrical activity.
The heart imploded...
all because Nina Kulagina
wanted the animal dead.
I don't kill people.
Part of you believes that.
There's another part of you, Frank...
that's out of control.
Your destructive impulse.
I've seen a figure in a cape.
I've seen him reach into people's
chests and squeeze their hearts.
Who was it?
Death.
I can communicate
with the other side.
I can see spirits.
I don't know why.
I can't understand it.
You think you're quite unique,
don't you?
But in my business, I deal
with your type every other week.
This death figure...
is nothing more
than a homicidal alter ego...
that satisfies
your compulsion to kill.
Every time
you want to kill someone...
"death" does it for you.
It's your way
of absolving yourself of guilt.
No!
When did you first start
seeing spirits? After Debra's death?
You killed your wife.
No!
I have studied...
the coroner's reports
of every death here since 1985.
Twenty-eight cases
involved crushed hearts...
arteries choked until they burst.
That started in 1990, with your...
beautiful wife, Debra.
She was the first.
Ray Lynskey.
You argue with him,
3 hours later he's dead.
We know you didn't like
Magda Rees- Jones.
But what about the guy in the toilet?
What did he do to you, Frank?
Piss on your Hush Puppies?
Why are you shaking?
Oh, my.
My, my. You're doing it right now,
aren't you?
You're trying to kill me, right now.
Well, forget it, Bannister.
I'm wearing a lead breastplate!
We have 28...
unexplained deaths here.
You know what I think?
I think you...
are involved in each
and every one of them!
Well, so much for the dream home.
What are we doing here, Lucy?
Look at this place.
It's a dump!
God, this guy is a loser.
Perfectly good basketball court
gone to pot.
Yeah, Bannister.
Mr. Bannister, help me!
My daughter, Patricia,
is communing with the Evil One.
He's in this house
at her instigation.
Help me drive them out!
Lucy, why do you keep
shutting me out?
Lucy!
Patricia?
Dr. Lynskey.
Patricia, are you all right?
It's your mother.
She's been hurting you.
She needs help.
She's delusional.
You can't go on like this.
You don't understand.
No!
My father killed himself
after the murders.
Mother says it was my fault.
So I have to keep his ashes
in my room.
Oh, my God.
She says I'm evil.
Just like Johnny.
Come with me to Mother's room.
This isn't you.
This isn't who you are now.
It was Johnny.
He went crazy.
I couldn't get away from him.
I thought he'd kill me.
You have to get out
of this house.
You can start over.
It's Mother. Please hide.
Please.
I'll take her to the kitchen.
You sneak out later.
What are you doing in here?
I thought I heard a noise.
I'll make you some coffee, Mother.
Mother.
The coffee's ready.
Lucy, go.
Thank you, Deputy.
Just call me when you're done,
Dr. Lynskey.
Frank, listen to me.
I found your knife,
hidden in old lady Bradley's closet.
She's crazy, Frank.
You haven't hurt anybody.
You're a good person, Frank.
Don't do this.
Please, don't do this.
Do you think you're the only person
who ever lost somebody?
You walk around like you
have no feelings...
but the truth is
you're just scared!
Goddamn hypocrite.
Why are you doing this?
What are you afraid of?
I don't want to hurt you, Lucy.
Oh, that's crap.
Don't give me that.
Look at me.
I'll be outside. This shit is like
walking in on your parents.
Oh, right. I'll be outside.
I'll just...
What is it, Frank?
Look out!
You son of a bitch!
What's happening?
Grab him! Grab him!
Okay. Listen to me.
Call for the deputy.
And try to sound calm.
Deputy!
I'm ready to leave.
Where did he go?
Stuart, where did he go?
I think we got him.
You son of a bitch!
Get out, Frank! Go!
It's this way. Go.
Freeze, Bannister.
- Help.
- I got you now.
Help me. He's gone crazy.
Okay. Ah! Stay back!
Now...
Frank, come on!
Go, Frank!
Get out of here! Now!
Frank, let's go!
This way. Come on.
Shit!
What was in that cell?
Something was crushing my heart.
I can't fight him, Luce.
I can't protect you.
There's one way
to deal with this thing.
I have to have an out-of-body
experience, and I have to have it now.
Go away, Luce.
Walk the other way.
Wait. Wait.
This will slow your heart
and lower your temperature.
You'll have 20 minutes. Any longer
and there's a danger of tissue damage.
That's only if I successfully
revive you. There's no guarantee.
Frank, you don't have to do this.
Better close the door.
Hurry up.
It won't take long.
I didn't know you had
an interest in cryogenics.
I'm reviving him at 9:00.
Why would we want to do that?
Luce!
Lucy?
There we go.
Let me go, you bastard!
Let me out now!
You bastard,
let me out of this car now!
I find cemeteries very...
restful places, don't you?
Turn this car around
and take me back.
I intend to, Mrs. Lynskey.
In exactly... eleven hours' time.
Son of a bitch!
Let me out of here!
Come back here, you creep!
My body...
is a road map of pain.
But pain...
has its reward.
The power of the mind...
is absolute.
Frank, is that you?
I'm doing this?
I'm moving the car
with the power of my mind!
Yes!
No!
Wait!
Get back in the goddamn ground!
You unorganized grab-asstic gob
of teleplasmic shit!
Who the hell are you?
Sound off like you've got a pair!
Hey, asshole.
He's dead!
You're too late!
Lucy!
Who are you?
Who...
are...
you?
Johnny Bartlett.
I thought guys like you
fried in hell.
I got out, Frank.
I've been carrying on the good work.
Got me a score of 40.
Harry Sinclair.
I want to shake the hand
of the man who avenged my death.
You have a number.
Bartlett carved it
into my forehead as I lay dying.
I was the last.
He couldn't be more wrong,
could he, Frank?
Shit!
Oh, Frank.
Just breathe.
Breathe slowly. Breathe.
You're okay.
Oh, Frank.
All right, Lucy, come on.
Get me 100 milligrams of lidocaine
and 1 cc of adrenaline.
I didn't get him.
Who? Who didn't you get, Frank?
Johnny Bartlett. He's back.
He's hallucinating.
He's killing again.
Patricia.
You have to get her
out of the house.
Go.
Go!
Patricia!
Listen to me.
We have to get out of here.
Patricia never leaves the house!
She's coming with me.
You have no right.
Get upstairs.
This is stopping now.
What do you mean?
Why do you have
Frank Bannister's knife?
You've been in my room!
Mother!
Mother wants to go to the police.
She'll be down in a minute.
Patricia, we have to go now.
It's not safe here.
Johnny Bartlett is back.
I know.
He visits me at night.
I don't know why he comes.
He torments me.
Why has he come?
Am I being punished?
Patricia, let's just go. Please.
I want to kill her, Patty.
That'll give us 41.
That's 8 clear of Gacy.
Nine more,
we break Bundy's record.
I can't wait to see his face
when he hears the news.
- Yes!
- What?
I'm sorry.
We really should wait for Mother.
That asswipe psychic
nearly ruined it for us, Patty.
He made us look stupid.
You'll be okay.
Everything will be fine.
Shut up! That Russian cannibal creep
is telling everyone he did 50 plus.
That reflects badly
on both of us, Patty.
This record should be held
by an American.
I quite agree.
You can come...
stay with me, if you like.
I'll kill her now.
I'd like that.
I'll just get my coat.
Patronizing do-gooder bitch!
Oh, Patricia.
You kill her. I'll watch.
Mrs. Bradley?
Mrs. Bradley,
are you coming with us?
Oh, my God.
Lucy!
No, not that way!
Jesus.
These are Bartlett's ashes.
We must get them
to the other side.
A church. We have to get them
to a church.
There's a chapel in the old hospital!
No!
Let's go down here.
Where is it?
You look there.
Lucy?
Oh, this is great.
Frank?
Excuse me, Doctor.
We're looking for ward 12.
Go up the stairs to the 4th floor,
then turn right.
It's opposite the chapel.
I'll get someone to help.
Orderly!
Orderly, are you deaf?
I said, orderly are you deaf?
Moron!
I guess that makes you number one.
Get down!
Frank, are you okay?
The chapel's on the fourth floor.
Watch out!
We got to go. Go!
Lucy.
Lucy!
You're all the same.
Wait!
Put the gun down, son.
The law is on its way.
What's the score, Patty?
Eleven.
That's the same as Starkweather's.
Lucy?
It's jammed.
Take it. Just take it!
Be right back.
Don't go anywhere.
Give that to me.
Let me guess.
You must get these ashes
to consecrated ground...
to destroy the forces of evil.
Give me the goddamn urn!
Under no circumstances
must these ashes ever be released.
Oops.
You have no idea
what you've just done.
You just don't get it,
do you, Frank?
This is all about your pathetic need
for self-glorification.
You are such an asshole.
Yes, I am.
I am an asshole...
with an Uzi!
Get up!
You make me sick!
I won't shoot you in the back.
Turn around.
I said, turn around!
As a U.S. Government agent,
I order you to turn around!
Oh, my God, Frank.
Debra.
You killed her.
You're next, pal.
Take him out, baby.
Get him!
Stop!
Frank, no!
Get him, Patty.
Oh, baby, you are an artist.
You're 42!
Yes.
I'm in the mood
for a little vivisection.
No! No, please.
Me, too.
Oh, me, too.
You bitch!
I got your girlfriend, Johnny!
Come get her!
Goddamn you!
Let go of her!
Come and get her, you coward!
Let go of my little Patty!
See you later, Frank!
We got you!
We're going back down
to get us some more!
Yo, Frank!
How's it going?
Bye, Frank.
Johnny? Johnny!
Step back, Frank.
This won't be pleasant.
The old express bus to hell.
No lines, no waiting.
It's really something, isn't it?
Excellent libraries.
Premium cigars.
And, of course...
the honeys.
How about that? Stu's
a regular chick magnet up here.
Hello, Frank.
It's time to go home.
I am home.
Ahhh, no.
The authorities have informed us
that it's just not your time.
Start living, dude.
Be happy.
There's something
I have to tell you.
Sorry to interrupt.
It's all right, Walt.
Frank, what do you know
about Ouija boards?
Not a lot.
I found a stack of them
at the Bradley house.
Looks like Patricia got herself
a direct line to Bartlett...
once she was released 5 years ago.
I thought you and I could collaborate
on a book about this.
It could be my ticket
off the force.
That's not my area.
If you need a collaborator,
how about your guardian angel there?
You got me, Frank.
I got you.
I'll see you, Frank.
Bye-bye.
Boy, that Dammers,
he sure looks pissed.
Sometimes when you go through
a traumatic experience...
it alters your perception.