I'd come to this project with many of
the same assumptions that you have
concerning the Jersey Devil murders
and the guilt of Jim Suerd
His characterization as a troubled
young man responsible for a spree of
The question in my mind had been
why ?
Why would a man commit such
crimes?
After reviewing hours of archived
footage generated by Steven Avkast
and Locus Wheeler, the hosts of
Fact or Fiction,
I've been forced to
change my perspective.
The question for me now is What?
What really happened that night, and
is Jim Suerd truly responsible?
Ironically in the course of this
project, Jim Suerd has died in prison
under mysterious causes.
His death will forever shroud the
reconciliation of this case.
As they said on Fact or Fiction,
you decide.
911, what is your emergency?
My name is Jim Suerd, and I just
hitchhiked here from the middle of
the pine barrens, and I can't seem to
find the people I was in the pine
Barrens with- and I was cam ping
with them last night doing a project.
Are you lost?
I'm not I'm not lost, I'm just trying,
just trying to... I can't find the
people that drove me here. I looked
around for them and I went back to
nowhere to be found... I don't know
where they are...
The vehicle is still there?
The vehicle is still there and I had to
hitchhike to this pay phone.
How far are you from the vehicle
right now?
About... about five, ten miles,
I don't know.
Okay Jim, we'll send someone out.
Yeah, you should send someone
out... I don't know... I have a bad
feeling. You might wanna send
someone out quickly and uh...
WBRK time it is 5:00". it's time for
afternoon drive you love so much-.
Hey guess who made the missing
reports? It's those hosts from
Factor Fiction. Missing. Ha!
Bob, you know those guys are
going to show up saying
"surprise did you miss us?"
Let's go to the phones and we'll ask
you... do you miss them?
We have found bodies. At this time
we don't know who they are
or how many we have found.
We can not assume at this time that
it is the Factor Fiction crew.
At this time, we have arrested
Jim Suerd for the murders
of Rein Clackin and Locus Wheeler.
Behind me is the house where
Jim Suerd resided till his arrest
nearly seven months ago.
Inside, amongst his dirty laundry,
blood evidence was found
linking him to the grisly
Fact or Fiction murders.
Today Jim's own life hangs in the
balance as Jurors decide his fate.
I had heard of the
Fact or Fiction murders.
They were big news for a period of
one year and then like so many
things in today's fast paced
world, were forgotten.
I was intrigued by how this case, this
story, was so well documented.
How, in spite of the remote
location of the murders
and the rural nature of the people
prosecuting Jim, that these were
murders of a high tech age.
I was intrigued by the fact that the
four individuals were indeed
children of a digital age.
Mostly though, I wondered why the
man named Jim Suerd would
commit such horrendous
acts of violence.
This is Johnny
and we are live in the pine barrens
where tonight we are doing a first
ever internet broadcast, cable, ham
radio broadcast All live- all real -
and we are doing with the help of a
psychic and a sound man who
has the ability to record sounds from
other worlds, otherworldly sounds.
Yeah, that's right Steven. We're here
in the Pine Barrens; southern
New Jersey live and direct, coming
right at you in your living room.
First ever web simulcast, cablecast
and everybody is on the edge
of their seat. And I know you are,
because I am and I'm sure
Steven is too.
A little later we're going to be
showing you the campsite
but right now we're going to do a
little recapping and you're going to
see some tape of the history of the
legend of the Pine Barrens
and the Jersey Devil.
They lived their show; Factor
Fiction. Here's this real eerie
circumstance that comes into
play and they were
actually the victims of it.
He had the opportunity.
It appears as if he had the motive.
He did lure those people up there in
a veil of secrecy.
I would say yeah - I think he
fits the profile.
Who was Jim Suerd?
The answer proved more difficult
than I imagined.
His mother had died four months
before the murders;
his father, five years before.
The only two people I was able to
speak with, that actually knew him
personally were his landlady,
Joyce Dryer
and a child Psychologist named
Dr. Orstall.
I was sort of a father figure to
him
I feel sort of a surrogate father,
if you will.
He didn't talk a whole lot
about his family life,
but one of the things I know, his
father left them when he was
very young - ran off with
another woman.
He had few friends, if any.
He was very reclusive.
I remember him being a loner, he
seemed to stay in his room quite a bit
when he wasn't at work.
And the computer seemed to be a
highlight in his life.
With the advent of the internet, of
course he got into that years after I
was seeing him... it wasn't even
available, I don't think, at the time.
It opened up a whole new world for
a guy like Jim.
Often he would be on the internet,
and of course we know the horrible
situation that has come up because
of the internet fiasco with him being
blamed for these murders.
The internet was the first of two
interests that would lead him to the
Fact or Fiction show. The second
interest was a bit more obscure.
Jim had a fascination with magic, a
true fascination. As I said he was
very reclusive sol believe he must
have spent countless hours in his
room, alone, working on tricks. He
used to come in and start the session
with a trick. Often it was a simple
card trick. Very quickly he built
skills and became very
proficient at magic.
The internet and magic.
Both interests generally considered
harmless. Both interests that could
have a sinister edge to them. Either
way, it was a combination that
virtually sealed his fate with
meeting and Steven Avkast
Locus Wheeler - the hosts of
Fact or Fiction.
Welcome to Fact or Fiction.
Welcome to Fact or Fiction. We are
rolling, we are on, we are ready to
go. Locus, you joker, you knew
all along we were on didn't you?
Yes, welcome to our new show.
Well actually ifs not a new show,
it's got a new name. Thanks to
everybody out there who helped us
come up with new great name,
Fact or Fiction.
That's right.
Fact or fiction was one of those fluke
successes that no television producer
would ever predict. Short on
production value, talent, and
execution, it maintained a following
of youth probably more amused by
it's kitsch value than anything else.
Steven Avkast, the creator of Fact or
Fiction, is remembered.
Steven - I always got bad vibes
from Steven.
He always came in with this
attitude... all he was doing was
making a little cable show...
Nobody ever goes anywhere with
this stuff, but he had this idea that he
was destined for stardom;
that he was going to be rich, millions
of dollars.
He basically had that big “director”
stereotype.. like he was a big time
Hollywood director... He really had
to put it in perspective.
Steven's long time friend Locus
Wheeler was the cohost of the show.
Their pairing was like oil and water-
Locus- He and Steven would have
problems getting along sometimes,
but I think Locus... he knew what he
was doing with this. He knew it was
just a little cable show. I think he
was just in it for the fun.
Somehow Steven, a misguided
egomaniac and Locus, a sardonic
slacker managed to keep turning
out shows for the better part of 1995.
The ideas were slim, however
they did latch onto one idea
that intrigued many.
We are also doing something new
tonight. We are on irc... live... Irc is
Well I'll have to say that the one
thing that they did, at first it was
people can ask questions on the
show? Well they tied this into the
internet with IRC chat, so people
could ask questions on the show, but
they rigged up some text to speech
converter so whatever was typed in
was actually said on the show,
like it was a voice.
It was this idea that provided the
impetus for what would ironically
give Steven the fame he so craved.
By the fall of 1995 the one joke
television show was losing
popularity. By November
the show was about to self destruct.
Everyone had this sense.
Once again, Steven in his
delinquency and procrastination, has
At this desperate time, Steven turned
to viewer suggestions, one of which,
would take took hold in his mind.
It provided the seedling
with which Steven hoped to rebuild
the show's popularity.
We had an IRC come in the real
eerie voice. It almost drove me
nuts...l almost couldn't stand it
after a while. This voice. Hello...
why don't you do a show about...
Why don't you do a show
about the Jersey Devil?"
Steven's idea was to do a first ever
live broadcast of Fact or Fiction.
It would be broadcast simultaneously
to cable television and the internet.
The promotions began immediately,
and with ratings dropping at an ever
increasing speed, the concept was
implemented immediately.
This Jersey Devil cable cast; I for
one knew it would never work.
These guys couldn't even make a
halfway decent TV show. Now they
wanted to do a live broadcast from
the Pine Barrens; have radio and
internet, this and that... I knew it was
going to be a fiasco... I never thought
it would and up they way it did but I
knew it wasn't going to look pretty.
Since the show was going to air from
a remote location, Steven hastily
looked for people who might be able
to help. A former employer of his,
Sam Woods was approached.
This is the room of Sam Woods.
I used to out his grass.
He's a filmmaker. He used to direct
soap operas and we're going to ask if
he wants to direct the show, because
he'd be perfect, and he's a “name”.
So I've had to talk to Locus and try to
convince him about it... here they
come so I'm going to turn
the camera down.
...and this is Locus.
Well they say that up to fifty
thousand people could be watching
selling lots of t-shirts, sol
think that's a good sign.
Anyway, we have this idea where we
want to take it in this direction where
it could become much bigger. It
would be really cool if you could
help out... direct the show. I know
you used to direct soap operas...
This union of cable access show and
former network soap director never
made sense to anyone, though it was
later discovered that Steven was
paying Sam out of his own pocket,
in an act of desperation to save
Fact or Fiction.
Sam Woods, a once successful
television soap director
became one of the people I would
question about these events.
In stark contrast to his work, meeting
him was another road sign on my
travel into a surreal world.
Well this devil hunt thing
never appealed to me.
We were getting into a pretty flaky
area there, you know.
The kids, they were asking for it with
that one. Not the kind of work that
I do. Not what I do...
For the internet and, Jay Mcdowell
was enlisted.
Well they came to me with this
seedling idea, they said,
"We want to use some of this
technology we've been using for
teleconferencing, for video
conferencing, and we want turn this
into a live broadcast thing...
They'd heard some talk about it and
they'd seen some sites that were
trying to do that, so they wanted to
do something like that.
They wanted to do a live thing.
Rather than streaming canned video,
they actually wanted to stream and
compress it all live.
So they came to with this concept
and I had to figure out all the
technical aspects of it, how to make
it real... kind of the packaging for it;
what it was really going to be in
the final product.
Steven and Locus decided that
they needed additional help
at the actual location.
They searched vaguely for a sound
man and a guide and on
December 21995, worlds collided.
Okay. We're here at Ram's and we've
come today to meet him in hopes
that he'll be able to help us out on
our trip to the pine barrens.
Basically Rein is an audio wiz...
and suppose-bly he's been able to
document... supposed-l}; he's been
able to document paranormal
occurrences on tape. So that's what
we're going to see today.
We're also going to be meeting Jim,
who does some psychic things,
and we'll see. Hopefully these guys
will fit the bill and we'll be able to
go down to the Pine barrens with
them. We could use the extra help.
Is that good. Yeah, You got enough?
I hope this damn mic works.
You ready?
Okay, Remember play it cool...
play it cool...
ls this going to blow it for us, this
airplane sound?
Steven, this is Rein...right Rein?
I'm Locus.
Locus?
So you just taped us?
Yeah I guess so, Accidentally.
So do you have some kind of
surveillance setup or something?
For the time being I kind of do. I
have plugins where I can plug in on
the wall... At one point this was like
a working studio.
I think that Jim has arrived now.
How are you?
You're pretty determined that
we've met.
Hey Jim what's up?
How are you... Lotus.
Uh... Locus.
How are you. I'm Jim.
It was inevitable that the
combination of the internet, a
television show about paranormal
happenings and similar ages
would draw Jim Suerd to
Fact or Fiction.
Okay, just to give a little
background. We're going to be doing
a webcast - cablecast in search of the
jersey devil down in the Pine
Barrens, and basically the reason
we've gotten you guys together is
because you have skills - Rein
regarding paranormal audio, and
Jim, you can help us with the
psychic thing.
I have psychic abilities, my psychic
abilities. I feel that I can really help
out. I understand what you're
trying to do and I really think
that I can help out.
You can help us find a location?
You can really help tap into
whatever we needed?
I can pinpoint that location.
Jim came to me one day and told me
how excited he was about how he
had met these people over the
internet. It was some show, Fact or
Fiction; and he was to be their guide,
in the Pine Barrens. And what really
amazed me... I just didn't think he
knew or had any knowledge of the
Pine Barrens to even be a guide...
But he seemed so excited about it.
Is this good?
Do you want to hold them up
or do you want me to
Just like this... You can't touch them.
Six spade...
seven spade...
four spade...
five spade...
eight club...
eight diamond...
I saw him about two or three weeks
before the incident. I ran into him at
a shopping mall. He was very excited
about his life.
He was studying acting. His magic
was coming together people were
appreciating it. combined with the
acting he had done a few gigs.
It was going very well.
Give him more ashes. Give him
more ashes.
There's something on his arm.
What does it say? one three nine
five... What does this mean Jim?
What does this mean Jim ?
I don't know
Back off. Back off.. are you
recording this?
Was Jim a psychic? It was not likely.
The card demonstration and the
supposed psychic fit in which
numbers appeared on his arm were
nothing more than simple tricks,
known by any amateur magician.
To Steven and Locus, Rein Clackin
and Jim Suerd were perfect
for Fact or Fiction; youthful, eager...
and strange.
On December 15, 1995 Steven
Avkast, Locus Wheeler,
Rein Clackin and Jim Suerd headed
for the Pine Barrens of New Jersey
to do a live broadcast in search
of the Jersey Devil.
Jim Suerd would be the only
one to return.
911, what is your emergency?
My name is Jim Suerd and I just
hitchhiked here
from the middle of the pine barrens
and I can't seem to find the people
I was in the Pine Barrens with and I
was cam ping with them
last night doing a project.
Are you lost?
I'm not I'm not lost, I'm just trying,
just trying to I can't find the people
that drove me here. I looked around
for them and there not at the van and
there nowhere to be found. I don't
know where they are.
The vehicle is still there?
The vehicle is still there and I had to
hitchhike to this pay phone.
About... about ten miles, I don't
know.
Okay Jim, we'll send someone out.
After Mr. Suerd made the call, we
went to the area he specified and did
a preliminary look around under a
missing person's investigation.
I mean I just figured it was one of
their little stints to do to get that
extra sensationalism... Sol didn't
think anything of it at first.
I kinda of expected them to try
something like that.
We have a one eighty seven.
Repeat... we have a one eighty seven.
This isn't a missing persons report
anymore.
Nine one twelve.
We're clear. Do you need emergency
support?
Ten Twelve. No this guy is
definitely DOA.
One body we found approximately
2.5 miles from the campsite.
The other body we found
3 miles from the campsite.
The body of Steven Avkast was
never found. Large amounts of blood
in the snow and a hat were all that
remained of this third victim.
In any murder investigation, anybody
associated with the victims is a
suspect. Our job is to eliminate
suspects based on the evidence we
sift through and gather- and as we
sifted through and gathered the
evidence there was only one suspect
left at the end, and that suspect was
Mr. Jim Suerd.
Who led everybody to the site?
I did
You did.
Did anybody else know where you
were going to set up and cam p?
Well I was asked to find a place for
us to camp. I thought
I was doing a good job. Rein
continued to provoke me
and give me a hard time about my
abilities to find a location for the
camp. Ultimately it led to an
argument and that's when
I ran away from the group.
Did you hit him at first?
I -I- I don't know. I might have
pushed him. Sometimes I can't
remember... I did what I... I ran
away from the group and I found the
spot that would be good to locate the
Jersey Devil.
After we got the permission from the
state of Pennsylvania to search
Mr. Suerd's residence, we went to his
residence and we did conduct a
search for anything that we felt
would help us in this case and we did
find the garments Mr. Suerd was
wearing that night, with the blood of
the three victims on it. Interestingly
the garments Mr. Suerd was wearing
were merely lying on his bedroom
floor, along with
the other dirty laundry that was
there.
Even as Jim was arrested, evidence
continued to mount against him.
We could tell that the nature of the
blows with the weapons that were
used were consistent with the size
and build of the accused.
In this case it was very clear that the
attacker was using both hands with
two weapons and was ambidextrous,
and the subject in this case is
ambidextrous which is quite rare.
He was the only survivor in a place
where nobody else was.
It doesn't look that good for him.
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury.
We will show that on
December 15, 1995 Jim Suerd
maliciously and with premeditation
killed Rein Clackin and Locus
Wheeler. We will show without
doubt how he planned this well in
advance of that day.
We will show with video shot by the
deceased, that Jim Suerd was and is
a devious and cunning person, using
the guise of psychic to perpetrate
these horrible acts.
The proceedings that summer turned
out to be one of the greatest
spectacles in Baroake County's
history. The trial attracted a strange
assemblage of cult followers, ritual
homicide fanatics and others seeking
to satisfy their morbid curiosities.
Eventually it became a matter of
trying to keep the tabloid press
at bay;
an attempt which was not
entirely successful.
When the court case came up, the
media frenzy was hysterical. I felt
like somebody was watching me
every minute. Talking to
everybody... everybody who had the
slightest thing to do with the show.
Who knows they probably even
talked to everyone who said they
watched the show. Reporters day in
and day out. The police here. Taking
everything- every tape, props. I don't
know what they were looking for.
All they were getting was a bunch of
bad television.
In an election year, what the
prosecution was looking for was an
open and shut case. And in the state
of New Jersey Vs Jim Suerd, they
found it. Not content to leave any
stone unturned, they decided to
utilize the very video that Steven
Avkast and Locus Wheeler had shot.
The man who would later come to be
known as the killer cutter was hired
to go through this video and put
together an incriminating
image of Jim Suerd.
The prosecution contacted me in
early January 1996. They had a
pretty good case against him from
what I saw. They had blood
evidence. They'd found the blood
and this was the only guy there, and
he was the only one who knew
where it was. But they really wanted
to clinch this case. They really
wanted to get him. They didn't want
to leave any question that he had
done it. So they came to me with all
this video tape... 15 hours of video.
This was video that these guys had
shot- on location. Now I had never
seen anything like this. Video from
the crime scene. Normally I have
hours and hours of talking heads,
shot in a room somewhere, badly I
mean this was badly shot, but
at least it was out in the woods.
It was different.
The Prosecution's video was
intended to show facts.
Perhaps, not inadvertently, it also
created an intimacy with the
murdered three that the defense was
unhappy with.
They protested it, deeming it an
unfair swaying toward a guilty
verdict. This was not enough reason
for the video to be struck down, and
so... it was used.
The first point demonstrated that Jim
was indeed leading the group into
very remote regions of the New
Jersey Pine Barrens areas where
there was no hope for help or aid
from the civilized world.
The following represents excerpts
from the first section of the
wandering deeper into the Pines was
shot. It is estimated that the four
walked for more than two hours
before Jim finally decided upon the
locations of their operation.
Hey guys he's starting to go Let's get
this stuff together.
So what's up Jim?
When Jim finally found the perfect
location, it was more than three
miles from the van and the nearest
access road.
The second point was to make
evident a defendant who had an
agenda... an agenda warped enough
to commit these murders.
I've been contacting the supernatural
world for the last week, for the last
couple of days. I've been in contact
getting my spiritual self together for
this journey that we've put ourselves
out on... and we are headed in the
right direction, I can assure you . I
can feel it. It's a gut instinct in my
body that we are going to find the
Leeds Devil... and that we're going to
settle this case... once and for all.
I feel that what I'm doing here and
for you is perfectly authentic and I
have a feeling inside it's a definite
feeling.. it's a place where we will
Repeated phrases such as "We're
going to settle this thing once and for
all" and "I know we're headed in the
right direction" seemed to clearly
show Jim's agenda. It didn't take
much to read into these phrases and
see an individual with a plan that
was to be carried out in the desolate
Pine Barrens.
As the prosecution's video
progressed, Jim's personality
changed; from a quiet and shy person
to one that presented the Prosecution
with an opportunity to show the
violent nature just below the surface.
Look Man...
I don't know. I don't know what Jim's
doing. I think he's talking about
burning something.
An agenda proven and a potential
violent streak proven, the
prosecution solidified their first
degree murder case against Suerd
with video taken in the barn; video
in which the original date of the trip
appeared on Suerd's arm.
The defense attempted to have this
also struck from the records,
claiming the video of Suerd to be
that of a character he was playing.
The prosecution countered by
agreeing fully with this assessment
of Suerd and the events in the barn.
Events that had taken place a full
two weeks before the trip; the best
argument for premeditated murder.
The trip began at sunrise. Steven ran
a video camera much of the time,
documenting what should have been
amusing but banal preparation.
Locus, you wanna do a blurb?
Yeah I'll do it.
What do you mean the back light's
killing my face?
Why don't you adjust it?
What you mean you can't adjust it?
Hey... I'm trying get this on
camera...
The trip, guided by Jim took, them
into the loneliest of areas, on a
lonely cold day. A stop at a gas
station, was the last obvious
land mark, before they moved into
the unidentifiable roads of
the Pine Barrens.
At a certain point, at Jim's request,
they stopped, parked, and started
walking into the woods... following
the psychic visions of Suerd.
No... What I'm saying is... if he's
gonna do it, this is part of the show.
We've gotta do it in a place he thinks
is right. Because if we're going to
find something I mean... yeah we
could fake it, but I don't go for that. I
think we should go for real and he's
off doing his thing.
That's why we got him here.
I'm just getting cold
Well we knew it.. We knew that we
were going to be out here.
Here he comes.
Where did you get this guy from
anyway? Psychics R us?
I think this is a pretty good idea.
Us waiting around and his
finding the spot, and then taking
the stuff over to it.
We still gotta go back to the oar and
get stuff. I don't think he knows that.
He's not volunteering much.
Yeah, well he's not carrying too
much but you know what he said
about that. It's a vibe thing.
Tension increase, as they work
further into the forsaken pines-.
And then, a key point in the
prosecutions video arrives...
Jim... are you a psychic...
or a psycho?
I'll see you back at camp man...
Approximately one hour later,
judging from the sun, a camp is
being built. Discussions are already
being had about Suerd. Suerd is not
helping. He is keeping to himself.
For the next two hours, the video of
the group is a mixture of promotions
for future cable shows, the camera
frequently left on between takes.
This is Locus reporting from the Pine
Barrens and I'm with Rein,
our sound man. Gee Rein I sure
am parched.
I sure am too.
Wow. ls that Mulberry natural spring
water?
Yes from Mueller's.
Wow. I wish I could have a sparkling
glass of that.
Boy. I'm telling you. and in a
gallon jar.
Jug
The mood is good.
Let's do that again.
Jim doesn't join in, instead staying in
the tent on IRC.
I don't really feel like I'm being taken
seriously, by really, any of you.
I'm taking you seriously.
We set up here.
I'm doing what I do and I don't
appreciate being laughed at.
Well, it's just a stress thing, you
know? We're going to be going on
in a bit. Do you think you're going to
come out for the show?
I think that I'll probably stay in
here... stay on IRC.
Okay.
At 10PM in what will be, The Last
Broadcast, Fact or Fiction goes live.
This is Johnny
and Locus
and we are live in the pine barrens
where tonight we are doing a first
ever internet broadcast, cable, ham
radio broadcast
Jim has been on IRC for 2 hours and
30 minutes. A surveillance camera
records the camp to vhs tape. It runs
for 2 hours before shutting off.
At 1:00 am, the last tape in the series
of 22 tapes shot by Locus Wheeler
and Rein Clackin reaches it's end.
Hey what the hell...man this thing's
still on... what's going on here?
Oh I must have left it on. We should
change tapes. Did you change tapes?
Here I'm going to change tapes.
There is no indication that this is
done. No other footage exists.
The tapes show a group of men,
going through a wide range of
emotions, seemingly enjoying their
jaunt into the pine barrens. The tapes
show the brooding nature of one man
who does not share in the frivolity.
The tapes do make clear the
maladjusted nature of Jim Suerd.
Though Suerd maintained his
innocence,
the facts were indisputable.
Four people went into the Pine
Barrens. Only Jim returned.
Blood of all three was found on Jim's
shirt. His pushing Rein showed a
potential violent streak. The angle
and depth of the cuts and lacerations
matched somebody of his height and
weight, and more importantly,
ambidextrous nature. The number,
which closely matched the date of
the murders appearing through ashes
on his arm was deemed to be a good
case for premeditated murder.
The tape showing the four walking
further and further into the woods,
virtually guaranteed a seclusion from
civilization that would make the
killing easier.
The defenses one victory was
getting the third charge of murder
against Avkast dropped. Though a
body is not needed to prove murder,
the prosecution had more than
enough evidence with the
two bodies that were found.
On July 161996 Jim Suerd was
to two life sentences
to be served consecutively.
I think the whole trial was a
kangaroo court of sorts, a pig circus.
The police obviously didn't do their
homework. They're not investigating
this to the best of their ability,
because their has to be some
evidence indicating something else
or someone else.
The case they built up against him; it
was all circumstantial. I mean they
didn't have any actual evidence that
he did this, but they didn't have
anything else or anyone else
to go on.
I don't consider having the blood of
murdered victims all over your
clothes as circumstantial. That's
pretty hard evidence as far as I'm
concerned. You don't get blood on
your clothes from a murder victim
from out of the air. You have to be
there, conducting those murders, to
get that blood on your clothes. I don't
consider that circumstantial.
I can't explain that, why there would
be blood on my shirt.
Would you agree it looks bad?
Excuse ma?
Would you agree that it doesn't look
very good for you right now?
The way that you're telling me it
doesn't look very good, but I can't
understand where this evidence
came from.
The evidence of blood on Jim's shirt
was a strong point for the
prosecution. DNA tests showed
indisputably that it was the blood of
the three that had gone into the
woods with Suerd. As I look at the
images of DNA patterns and pools of
blood, I wonder though if perhaps
the jury, anxious not ignore DNA
evidence as had happened in other
trials, perhaps looked too closely.
Through the magnifying glass of the
prosecution's microscope, the
evidence was solid, however a
macroscopic view begged another
question. Could the master of this
orgy of violence have walked away
from his work, with merely the
equivalent of 17 eyedrops of blood
on his shirt... and nothing else?
Every piece of evidence they would
get, they would use in a way like
instead of "Gee does this have
anything to do with the case"?
They would go like "How could
Jim have used this"? It was like
building a house of cards.
Eventually they had enough to
get a case against him.
I wasn't really monitoring their
conduct outside of cam p.
What were you doing?
I was on IRC.
In the tent?
Yeah
All night?
All night.
About what time did you start on
IRC?
Probably around 8:30
When we interviewed the individuals
that Suerd claimed to have been
talking with on IRC that evening,
and we've looked at their logs, their
chat logs from their computer and
we have determined there was a
45 minute gap in time from when
Suerd made one comment to the
time he made another comment. And
45 minutes is an awfully long time to
not be responding to other people on
the internet.
They say that the connection
dropped out and that was when Jim
killed them... I guess that's possible.
It is possible yes. You don't have to
be a world class sprint runner to
cover that amount of ground in
45 minutes.
I have to raise doubts about just one
guy doing all that to these bodies.
They were darlings of the media.
That was one of the reasons they
jumped on this thing so quickly and
had to come up with a conclusion of
what happened. It was their very
own.
As professionals in law enforcement,
we do not feel the pressure from
outside sources, be it the media or
otherwise, to conduct our
investigations. We conduct them to
the best of our ability at all times.
There were no other suspects to
apprehend, to interview or to
consider. All the evidence pointed to
the fact Mr. Suerd was the only
suspect and therefore all we had to
do was gather the evidence to prove
Mr. Suerd's guilt. We didn't have to
gather evidence to gather other
suspects.
On January 2nd, 1997 an event
occurred that forced me to rethink
the making of this documentary, the
very thesis with which I had begun
this journey. Jim Suerd was found
dead in his jail cell of undetermined
causes.
On January 3rd, a package arrived at
my door, which I think in
no way was coincidental with the
death of Jim Suerd.
The acquiring of mysterious
videotape has changed the mood
behind the making of this
documentary. Gone is the attempt at
pure objectivity with which we
started. Now we question who gave
us this tape, and more importantly,
what, if any, information does it hold
that was never brought up in the
trial? Going to the authorities with
this new tape is pondered, but
rejected. To them, the case is closed
and with Jim's death, appeals are a
moot point. Nothing is ruled out. The
tape could be a hoax. I am conscious
of one thing though; Our search for
the truth behind the Fact Or Fiction
murders has in some way become
part of the story.
There was this discussion on the last
\ tape that they were going to change
tapes, but whether that ever
happened or not, I don't know... I
never saw any other tapes and from
what I saw of the camera it was
pretty damaged, so if there was any
tape I doubt it could ever be played.
My name is Michelle Monarch. I'm a
magnetic media data recovery
specialist. The particular tape I was
given was mangled almost beyond
recognition. I digitized sections of
this particular video and am now
reconstructing the actual picture
frame by frame. I have to guide the
computer to complete these pictures.
There were some that were easy, and
some that were unrecognizable and
I'm rebuilding them now at this time.
As the tape is reassembled by Shelly,
it becomes apparent that some
sections are rather viewable.
And I'll say, "I'm hunting for the
Jersey Devil.
And I'll be like "Ahh shut up"
Yeah, you can be like "I don't see
him"
No we better not do that because
we've got to deliver on this
show...this is the big one.
I don't care if you here this or not on
camera. This is never going to make
it to anything but the cutting room
floor as they would say in Film days
from what Sam was saying.
I don't want to be a bitch all night.
Let's see how this works
I'm going to walk out into the woods,
scout out the location, I also kind of
have to go to the bathroom but get
on the trumpet, do some sound
Yeah, but Newark is doing it's thing.
Yeah, I know the airplanes are loud,
but we got only one machine going...
I want to see that reel to reel going, I
want to see you on that trumpet... I
want to see you working for the
reason that you're out here...
and Locus IR144xx is waiting
do some work man.
Whatever you say big guy.
I'm going to get going here. I'll be
back in a couple of minutes.
There goes the little tyrant.
Here come on. I got the camera
rolling. Do a little Steven imitation.
No I'm talking about Steven being a
pussy, not Jim
Jim's one psycho mother fucker...
Here let me get that on camera.
That thing isn't running is it?
Of course it's running We're
supposed to record everything.
Here do that imitation of when Jim
pushed you what were you thinking?
I was. a little bit... I don't know it
was weird. I didn't expect him to be
violent... I thought he was one of
these peace fucking meditation
dudes... I didn't think they did that.
Dudes... I didn't think they did that.
Following these recorded moments,
a large portion of the tape is
smashed. It is a section that Shelly
will attempt to restore.
The next section that is immediately
viewable happens somewhere in the
middle of the tape.
The first thing that is apparent is that
this is tape shot by Locus and Rein.
Steven is nowhere to be seen. They
are searching for him.
On her third day of restoration,
Shelly makes another discovery.
The anonymous tape is not from one
but two cameras.
Both Rein and Locus took cameras
into the forest.
Here we are. We can't find Steven.
Here we are in the pine barrens on a
trip he drug us out here for. We did a
webcast, cable-cast cast simulcast,
which frankly was pretty poor if you
ask me, but that doesn't matter
because our host, Steven - Johnny, is
gone.
He's missing and we can't find him.
All I want to do is drink some beer
this is for you Steven. Even though
we don't know where you are,
because you told us to record
everything... shoot shoot everything
In the 6th day of her work, Shelly
puts together a stunning piece of
tape. It is a moment in time that
proves so much.
Footprint. I think it goes off this way.
Do you see anything over there?
Do you know what time it is?
It's late. It's... 2... 45
2:45?
Rein and Locus were alive and
speaking the time, when they were
supposed to be being killed. And
they're alive. and they're saying the
time on video. To me that proves
absolutely that Jim couldn't have
been killing them at that time.
Jim's an innocent man. And this was
not investigated in any way shape or
form. It was overlooked.
So many details were overlooked.
Also, if he's an innocent man
there's a killer on the loose.
Shelly's work slowly gives voices to
the dead, ghosts caught on video.
The processing of the tape is quickly
becoming more difficult for Shelly.
Now only bits and pieces tell the
story of what happened in the woods.
On February 5, Shelly presents a
section of video tape that is nothing
short of horrifying. It intensifies the
question of who the killer is.
On February 7, Shelly finds what she
thinks is the moment in time from
Locus's camera. It cannot however
be viewed. She remains hopeful as
she begins the process of trying to
reconstruct a lost video.
The computer needs me to direct it.
It doesn't know how to
reconstruct a circle. Maybe it'll have
an opening at the side, and I have to
teach it to continue the circle. I'm a
guiding factor.
While Shelly begins the process of
attempting to restore video, I will
attempt to find a truth within the
videos I have already shot.
You know, sitting there, waiting for
these video images to render, I did
wonder about it myself. I mean...
sometimes I wonder if I'm doing the
right thing. Did this guy do it... it
seemed from what I saw that it was
pretty likely that he did it. You had
the blood evidence, stuff like that.
But then there was that one guy...
they never found his body...
Could he have done it? I don't know.
It is an obvious question; a question I
had presented to all the people
interviewed. The tape restoration is
showing Locus and Rein searching
for Steve, which only makes the
question more relevant.
What happened to Steven Avkast?
By process of elimination, I proceed.
We did some blood. and of course
the infamous Johnny hat that was
found. We were never able to find
any more remains of that person so
we don't know if he's dead or alive.
They never found Steven - Johnny's
body, but they found his hat- It just
seems weird that the only thing left
is... a hat?
We don't think Mr. Avkast would be
able to setup Mr. Suerd because the
amount of blood that was found of
Mr. Avkast's is so great that he
would have bled to death trying to
set Mr. Suerd up.
We... what's that...
It's Steven's his light... Steven?
In finding that Jim's alibi holds up,
we have to attempt to answer the
question raised... who killed these
people? The likely suspect would
appear to be Steven. As I watch these
frames though, I see no recognition
from Locus's face. I see Locus, a
man, larger than Steven, turn tail and
run as does Rein. Steven Avkast
being the culprit of the horrendous
massacre that took place in the
minutes that follow this tape, is
impossible to believe. Along with
the amount of blood that belongs to
Steven Avkast this makes me believe
that he also was murdered in the
Pine Barrens. I am now also of the
belief that the killer was somehow
something more horrendous than
possible to imagine.
What could have killed three
healthy men?
What would have left no foot prints?
What would have torn the men
into forty seven pieces,
leaving no evidence of a struggle?
We could tell by what was left of the
infliction of the wound that
it was a serrated type weapon.
There were no knife fragments or
any evidence of the actual weapon
used other than the cuts themselves.
We're a rural county, people here are
not greatly educated. Rumor and
folklore is common. I put no
credence in anything of that nature.
I go by the facts that the police were
able to ascertain.
A monster? Yeah. I think this person
is a monster. I don't believe
Fact or Fiction. I don't believe the
Fiction. I think this is a person and
I'm going to find out who it is. I'm
going to reconstruct... do my job to
recover what has been lost. The
facts.
It is as though the Jersey devil is a
monster reborn in a digital age,
reborn on the Internet. A demon
captured on IRC logs, mangled
video, whispers in the dark. It is to
these that I look.
It's totally anonymous. You can't
trace a call. You don't know if it's
man woman old young.
You don't know anything, so in one
way... I don't know why the oops
didn't try to figure out the suggestion.
Who made that idea?
Who came up with that suggestion.
Why don't you do a show about the
Jersey Devil?
We have this show, Factor Fiction...
it's a paranormal variety show.
Station so what we thought we'd
make a little excursion. There was
this suggestion via IRC. There was a
suggestion via IRC to
Well and also from the Mailbag.
That guy D...
Well one of the things about IRC is
that it really is hard to trace it... It's
not like you know the phone number
that they're calling from. This could
have shanghai where they writing
this message from. You just don't
know. That's the beauty and the evil
of it.
It is amazing to be so near, yet so far
to the possibility of knowing who the
killer is. D something?
Have guests come on. Well things
have been a little slow at the station
so what we thought we'd make a
little excursion. There was this
suggestion via IRC
Well and also from the Mailbag.
That guy D...
It's just not practical to keep that
stuff. I get so much email. It would
just clog up my system. Once a point
was done... I erased it as I went. I
mean there were some emails at the
and, but nothing illuminating.
Mean there were some emails at the
It gets harder and harder to stick
with your original gut feeling.
Because of the media and the
attention that the whole case got, and
how lopsided the whole thing
was. After a while you wonder...
maybe he did do it...Maybe there's a
side of Jim that I don't know...
That was capable of such an atrocity.
As this journey nears it's end, I
begin to fully understand the essence
of what this is about. The media
upon which these events were
recorded, the media that should have
been able to provide a truth more
pure than ever before, has somehow
become the story. This has become
more than a search for the truth
behind the fact or fiction murders.
It has become an indictment of truth
and how it is viewed through the lens
of the media.
Pretty exciting moment here because
the Fact or Fiction Logo is on screen,
which means that we are actually
getting our signal feed, to the station.
Reality television, the news, the 60
second clip of truth have made even
the strongest of doubters wonder
Are you a psychic or a psycho?
What did you say to him...?
What does he mean he's going to be
at the camp?... this is the whole
fuckin thing. where the hell is the
camp?
Well we're losing him.
Well go find him. I'm not going to go
anywhere near him.
What a fuckin asshole.
Just out the damn camera.
I mean what is the truth? The editing
process is like sifting that stuff out.
Not always with these legal videos
but with a documentary film,
ultimately it's what the filmmaker
perceives as the truth.
Ultimately it's what the filmmaker
I mean, don't you think? That's what
you're trying to do. Right?
The mistakes that were discovered
on this journey were stunning.
Shoddy police work and a
judgmental video presented the
world with a person, guilty before
ever being tried.
I know Jim is not guilty. I know that
the truth is still at large, potentially
closer than anyone can realize. It is
as though the real killer planned a
media event so amazingly cunning
that it could be thought of as
scripted. A Kill ready for prime time
so to speak.
Perhaps the demon we call the Jersey
devil did kill them in the
Pine Barrens, but if so, the Jersey
devil is the electronic image.
The sound, the communication to the
masses, somehow twisted into
a surrealist electronic world.
I always asked the question last... do
you think Jim did it? And with the
exception of authorities directly
accountable to the answer, I have felt
that the answer given has been "it
doesn't matter... the truth is what
time has made of this event. It has
been good for business;
often murder is.
So many involved have benefited
from this event. The inevitable book
deal is being replaced with a career
in the business of image control.
And most of the people interviewed
are ready to em brace it.
I guess it's a grim irony, as these
post-its can attest, that when we have
some real dead bodies that the sharks
start circling. It's strange that an
incident like that would be a prelude
to a new phase in my career.
Well it's interesting. After the
case...with all the publicity,
I started getting phone calls for a
couple job leads, so in one way this
might have helped me outta here.
How long will it to process the
entire tape?
It's not my intention to process the
whole tape. I don't need to do that. It
could take hours, it could take days. I
need to process a particular piece of
this tape that could potentially reveal
a killer.
Shelly continues to extrapolate
information from a frame while I
will reenact the events of
December 15, 1995
This is one of the stops that the guys
had made on their way to the
Pine Barrens. I know this from the
extensive documentary footage they
had taken. I don't know what good
this will do. I think it's to keep
myself clear of what happened, the
order of events.
Strangely the weather is almost
identical to the way it was that day.
I'm now traveling an access route
that I know Steven and Locus had
taken for the Jersey Devil project.
We're in the heart of the
Pine Barrens. I'm using this video
camera as a matter of convenience.
Using film out here would prove to
be logistically too difficult.
Hopefully we'll show you the area of
the campsite. And really
demonstrate the intrepid nature of
Steven and Locus.
I feel with some more work, that I
will find the killer.
I will see the face of the killer.
This site is a very close
approximation of the one used by
Steven and Locus on the night of the
Jersey devil episode. They'd chosen
a clearing like this for the base camp
of the telecast before venturing into
the pine barrens with their cameras.
They would never return alive again.
The documentary footage generated
that evening proves irrevocably that
Jim Suerd was not responsible for
their murders; that Locus Wheeler
and Rein Clackin were actually alive
at the time when they were
ostensibly being murdered and that
the police case was shoddy at best.
What is the Jersey Devil? It's a man
wandering into the Pine Barrens,
never to be seen again. It's an animal
found mangled on one of these
access roads, or perhaps its
something that rests within our own
psyche and that we'll never fully
understand. I've been on this project
for months now and haven't come to
a clear definition of what actually
happened or who was responsible.
All I know is it's a mystery and may
permanently remain so.
What is the Jersey Devil?
I'm now outside of Shelly's studio.
All the media
All the interviews
The truth finally comes down to one
frame.
I have determined that this is no time
to be distracted or set aside in the
course of the events that I have set
into motion. My next step will be
going into the Pine Barrens for a
reenactment of the trip of Steven
Avkast, Locus Wheeler, Rein
Clackin, and Jim Suerd. I am as
strong in my resolve as before in
proving that Jim had nothing to do
with the murders... that he had
neither the intellect nor the logical
capacity to carry them through. I
think the replayment of our events
be quite compelling in
roving Jim's innocence
This site is a close approximation to
the one used by Locus and Steven on
the night of the live broad...
they'd
This site is a close approximation of
the one chosen by Steven and Locus
This is the site of there Fact or
Fiction Jersey Devil broadcast.
They'd chosen a clearing similar to...
This site is a close...“
This site is a close approximation of
the...