23.976
(Screaming) Josh!
I'm Kurt Loderwith MTV news.
The film is The Blair Witch Project.
One of the scariest films
of all time...
I was terrified.
Oh, it scared me to death...
It all started with light heart
and the there documentary filmmakers...
...armed with a 16mm camera
and a video camcorder...
...head into the Black Hills forests
of Maryland...
...to make a movie
about a legendary witch...
...and they're never heard from again.
There's no doubt about of the box-office
success on The Blair Witch Project.
What's not clear
is whether the legend is true.
So far the fans are not only flocking
to the multiplex...
...they are flowing the little town
Burkittsville, Maryland.
People have started coming
to Burkittsville...
...as if itwere Charles Manson's
The Spahn Ranch...
...or Ed Gein the serial Killer's house,
to visit a haunted place.
"Burkittsville isn't a haunted place. "
"It's a place that a fictional movie
was set in. "
I wasn't able to see the movie...
...when it came out, because I was...
...in the hospital.
But as soon as they let me out...
I was at the movie theatre
seventeen times in a row.
The web-site sold me.
The web-site, you know...
...has all these police photos...
...and official police things...
...all this information...
...you really believe it.
Our stick men sold so well
on the internet...
...that we started selling them
in the yard.
Ant then somebody came by to buy them...
...and they wanted rocks.
So we got rocks
out of my rock garden...
...but I didn't want to get rid of them
so he offered me $10...
...after he started booting it up more.
His wife really wanted them,
so we sold them to him.
We sold some on the internet
but not many.
It costs too much to ship a rock.
Everybody that comes is like this.
I'm so used to being on video.
I make sure, if I go to my car,
or to get the paper...
...that I at least have full makeup on,
and a great night-gown.
I wish that they'd used
a fictitious town...
...and possibly thought ahead...
...toward what type
of repercussions could come...
...from using the word documentary...
...in their advertising,
and on their web-site.
Get out of these woods, and go home!
There was no goddamn Blair Witch!
You know, there are a lot of
naysayers who come and say nay...
...but then there is supporters who
come up to my town, come up to me.
They run up to me, they stop...
Hey, Selena!
They come over to me, they hug me,
and say, "Dude, I know it's real. "...
...and they squeeze me, and I say,
"I know it's real, too"...
...and we have a bond.
I say, "I know, and they go, I know, man,"
and I go, "I know"...
(Screaming)
You think you're a wise ass?
I didn't do anything wrong!
(Yelling)
Enough!
(Music fades)
They found blood in the van.
(Woman) Could you turn that down?
(Man) I'm just trying to set the mood
for the mission.
That's sweet,
but I feel like I'm gonna toss.
She's been feeling queasy.
No need to explain.
Your comfort is my concern.
Ladies and gentlemen, let's hear it
for Stephen Ryan Parker,
who has three names,
so he must be from Boston.
Apparently he's here researching
a book with his girlfriend.
The book's title is...
Blair Witch History Or Hysteria.
Hysteria Or History.
Why is it you guys can't get on
the same page about the witch?
We've always been misunderstood.
We embrace nature, not evil.
Thank you, Erica.
(Erica laughing)
Not only a hottie, but a real witch!
Blessed be.
Wiccan... Wicc it good. (Laughing)
(Stephen) Wait,
why are we slowing down?
This is where your other tour mate
wants to meet. She's a little weird.
She thinks she's psychic
or some shit.
When did you last talk to her?
E- mail, two days ago.
Are you sure she'll be here?
Yeah.
Kim!
Kim?
Yo.
Is that her?
Kim?
Yeah.
I'm Jeff.
I figured.
What are you doing there?
Trying to find the energy.
Inside the grave?
To stand up. I'm exhausted.
I've been on the road two days.
Want a hand?
I want amphetamines.
Weed is what I've got,
beer I'm gonna get.
Both - now.
(Jeff) That's right, friends.
For two luxurious days and nights,
my friends, you will walk the same
path the witch herself once walked,
sleep on the same soil where
her victims' blood was spilled.
Possibly losing your own souls
in the process.
I want to thank you all
for coming on the inaugural tour
of the Blair Witch-Hunt.
Inaugural?
You've never done this?
Never.
That's not what your web-site said.
"Over 10,000 satisfied customers. "
No, that's my web-store.
Stick men, t-shirts,
official Blair dirt.
Tours?
We're all virgins on this bus!
Here? You drove by a huge Safeway
two miles back.
That was in Burkittsville. I don't
shop there. I don't even piss there.
(Kim) Hell of a town you got here.
What century are they living in?
The gene pool's
a little shallow here.
Dive in,
you'll crack your skull open.
(Jeff) Ok.
Where are we going first?
The ruins of Rustin Parr's house.
(Erica) That guy who heard
the voices to kill, right?
(Jeff) Yeah, seven little kids.
(Kim) I hear voices all the time.
(Cracking)
Do we need all this shit
for a walk in the woods?
The Blair Witch-Hunt
provides all amenities
while you risk certain death
and dismemberment.
Give it up.
What's with all this camera stuff?
To record all occult phenomena
that may manifest itself
in the course of the tour.
Damn, you're really running
Bullshit Central, aren't you?
If you don't believe in the witch,
why the hell did you bother to come?
I thought the movie was cool.
How much further?
Couple more miles.
Jesus!
So how far along are you?
What do you mean?
The baby. How many weeks?
Six.
You don't want to keep it, do you?
No.
But Stephen wants the baby.
Yes. How do you know?
I don't know.
What are you gonna do?
(Jeff) Welcome to the Parr ruins,
ladies and gentlemen.
It's supposed to be
where they found Heather's footage.
(Tristen) These markings
are incredible.
(Erica) Ancient witches' alphabet.
(Stephen) Looks like recent graffiti.
(Tristen) They're so realistic.
It's a little scary.
Actually, some of these symbols
are positive.
Only those who don't understand
witchcraft would be afraid of them.
And remember, fear...
is the forerunner of failure.
Ok.
What's the story with this tree?
What tree?
Look behind you.
(Jeff) Where the fuck
did this come from?
This was never here before.
Nice try, dude.
What does that mean?
Maybe you should drop the tree bit
from your next tour.
No, no, I'm not making this up.
I need a beer.
Me, too.
Hey, geniuses, explain to me
why a house built in 1826
was built around a tree.
This would have been sticking
straight through the living room.
Jeff, nobody's scared.
(Screaming)
(Erica) Evil intent in the ground,
may a release soon be found.
In peace, release the energy
that be from my magic.
Are you casting
some kind of evil spell?
Widdershins - Reversing the evil.
The first law of wicca
is "Harm none".
Cos whatever you do
is going to come back threefold.
The karma's a bitch.
What are you really doing?
Communing with Elly Kedward.
The Blair Witch? I thought you
embraced nature, not evil.
You don't understand.
Elly... was a good witch.
She was an earth child, like me.
She's gonna be my mentor.
You've spoken with her?
Not yet...
but I will.
That's why I'm here.
To shed my mortal coil...
and commune with Elly.
(Tristen) Have you ever seen
her picture?
I don't think there are any.
Stephen and I found one.
Check it out.
We think it was drawn
before they banished her from Blair.
Banished, my ass.
They dragged her into the woods
in the middle of winter,
and tied her
to a fucking tree to die.
You make her sound helpless. Can't
witches summon powerful energy?
We can...
but we still have to eat, shit,
and die like the rest of you.
We just look good doing it.
Why do you need all these cameras?
I'm personally hoping for
an Elly Kedward sighting.
I've got a big beta
for a quality master.
I got a night vision, an infrared,
a cute little mini dv,
handhelds for everyone...
and this baby can even do
frame-a-second time lapse.
If anything comes in for a visit,
we're gonna catch it.
May I have permission
to take this leaf?
Thank you.
(Erica) Evil intent in the ground,
may your release soon be found.
And peace release the energy
that be from my magic.
So mote it be.
Evil intent in the ground,
may your release soon be found.
And peace release the energy
that be from my magic.
So mote it be.
Ok, wait... How many Heather Donahues
does it take
to screw in a light bulb?
How many?
Just one!
(Laughter)
Just one of them!
Do you know
what I could never figure out?
What's that?
Blair Witch Project, Ok?
Two guys and a girl, sleeping
in the same tent night after night,
and no sex?
It makes no sense.
You're so right.
I mean, they were scared
out of their minds,
and the greatest stress reliever
right at their fingertips...
and nothing.
I'm a little stressed.
Try some more weed.
Ok.
The Bermuda Triangle.
It's a place in the world
that's been created by hysteria...
...by people's own psychology,
by their own ideas of the place.
We were already
a persecuted minority.
This whole Blair Witch thing
set us back 300 years.
We're back in the burning times.
It fucked up our image.
Erica, people fear what they don't
understand. You must realise that.
No shit. People think that I drink
blood, that I sacrifice children...
...that I worship the devil
just because I'm a wiccan.
Where I come from, people think
because I dress in black,
I'm some kind of sick killer
or something.
I don't even believe in the devil.
Ok?
That's a Christian concept.
I believe in nature.
I hate nature.
Myth, for me... right?
...is just myth.
It's not history, it's not metaphor
and it's definitely not the truth...
Stephen, stories like this happen...
...because they exist
in a place of truth...
...because there's historical evidence,
there's fact.
That's what you don't understand.
(Jeff) I want to make a film.
Wicca... A Way Of Life.
Nice.
Yeah.
Wait, wait... Check this out.
Look at everyone.
Everyone is obsessed
with the Blair Witch
for their own reasons, including us.
Goth... A Way Of Life.
A documentary on you.
All real, all video.
Video never lies, Kim.
Film does, though.
Everyone wants to see something.
I'm telling you,
hysteria and delusions,
they breed in situations like this.
Why are you applying rational thought
to mythology?
Because if people believe something
enough, isn't it real?
Perception is reality.
You're not listening to me.
Babe, I know what you're saying,
I just think it's bullshit.
I think you're being
a monomaniacal reductionist.
(Eerie shrieking)
What the hell was that?
I heard that, too.
Burkittsville's funniest home videos!
You scared the shit out of me, man!
It answered every single one
of your wet dreams.
What are you guys doing here?
We've got a tour group,
the Blair Witch Walk.
What's your excuse?
Tour group, the Blair Witch-Hunt.
You're supposed to look out for stuff
like this. This is so not happening!
We have jurisdiction.
We have permits.
Yeah? From Cravens? Let me see 'em.
They're in the car.
Bullshit!
Let's put it this way, one of us
is staying - it's us or you,
and it looks like us, bitch!
It's gonna come back at you
threefold.
What?
In the wiccan...
Shut up!
Your balls will fall off
in three days.
Yo, guys, guys,
I think I can settle this.
Just give us till dawn,
then we're out of here.
We're cold, we're tired...
and we're a little shook up.
We saw something
up at Coffin Rock today.
Yeah... Yeah, up at Coffin Rock.
It scared the shit out of us.
Guys, stop talking about it,
because I'm gonna freak.
I just want to go home.
Can we see this thing...
Coffin Rock?
Blair Witch? Go to Coffin Rock.
It's your money, Greta.
Next time,
take the Blair Witch Walk.
Next time, take the Blair Witch-Hunt.
Here's my card. Call. I'm on the web.
(Giggling)
They were never seen again.
Their footage
was found a year later...
underexposed, and useless.
I don't trust that these assholes
aren't coming back.
They're going to be pissed
that we took the foundation.
I don't think it's anything
to worry about.
Besides...
We're gonna be up all night, baby!
(Howling)
Giddy-up!
We'll just keep our eyes open.
They're not coming back.
Why do you think that?
I just do.
(Kim) I'll be back in a minute.
Up all night!
How do your parents feel...
about having a witch for a daughter?
My father is an Episcopal minister,
in a one-church-town
back in Munnsville, Illinois.
Yeah.
That's a bummer.
How many beers is that for you?
I'm serious!
You're drinking like a fish.
I just think you should
take care of yourself.
Jesus! We've already gone
through this once today already.
(Man screaming)
(Girl panting)
(Baby crying)
What's going on?
What the fuck...?
This is my work.
This is all my research.
Our work.
Every word.
Where the fuck are my cameras?
(Stephen) This is all
of our goddamn work!
How the hell are we gonna make
the deadline?
We backed it up on computer.
No, Tristen, that was just notes.
Half this shit is original documents.
Where the hell was everybody?
We were all supposed to be awake.
Guys, where's Erica?
I'm right here.
We must have fallen asleep.
Asleep? It's like
we must have blacked out!
The last thing I remember
was that other group.
Yeah... those fucking dickweeds!
Who else could it have been, huh?
They came back from Coffin Rock,
and ripped us off!
Ripped? These things look like
they were bit off.
I- I-I... What am I gonna do?
At least the tapes are still here.
What?
The tapes. They're here.
Where? Do you see them?
In my mind, I see them.
Oh, Jesus.
You fuck.
They're there!
Where they found
the Blair Witch tapes?
You've got to be kidding me.
Come on! Why would they be in there?
Newsflash, everybody...
That was just a movie.
I don't know why, Stephen.
They're under the rocks.
There's nothing in there.
Reach inside.
Well...?
I don't feel so hot.
Jeff, is there anything in there?
(Erica) Jesus Christ.
How did those get in there?
Are they yours?
I think we should leave.
How did you know?
I don't know.
Are they yours?
Did you put them there? Did you?!
Jeff, are they your tapes?
Yeah, they're my tapes!
Then, why are they still here?
Why is the equipment trashed, the
cameras are gone, but not the tapes?
She's right. Wouldn't those guys
want to fuck up your tour footage?
Stephen, I want to leave.
How did this happen?
Oh, fuck!
Jesus Christ, the baby.
We found blood in the van.
Tristen had a miscarriage.
You know that, Cravens.
"She bled in the van
on the way to the hospital. "
This girl's hypothermic.
Get me heating blankets and a lamp.
It's like she's
been sitting in ice water.
We were just camping.
(Cravens) "The doctor thinks
it's hypothermia. "
Course, the way I see it
you brought her out here,
you took her into those woods.
She's your responsibility.
Are you charging me with something?
You have been... a pain in this town's ass
since you were 10.
You need to learn
to stay out of trouble, boy.
It makes you defensive...
Anxious.
Last thing you need
is to end up back in the loony bin.
How is she?
She lost the baby.
The doctor will keep you here
till your temperature stabilises.
You lost a lot of blood.
More than usual.
It's for the best.
Your body is telling you
something was wrong.
Something was wrong.
(Screaming)
How are you feeling?
I'm not staying here.
Five hours of our lives
are unaccounted for.
I want to see those tapes.
I want to know what happened.
I've got some editing equipment at my
house.
We should be able to come up
with some answers.
We're still in
the Black Hills, aren't we?
Yeah, right up there.
Let's get Tristen inside.
We can take care of the bags later.
I thought we were going
to your house.
RFD 431... Jericho Mills, home.
(Stephen) What did it used to be?
It was a factory after the war.
They were going to destroy it, so I
got them to sell it to me for a buck.
(Erica) Cool.
Sorry about the bridge.
It's the only way in or out.
It's pretty safe...
don't lean on the railings.
I am not a gambling man.
But...
I would bet my entire...
retirement pension...
that the blood in the van...
is gonna match those tourists.
You've been looking to pin something
on me since I was a kid.
(Dogs barking)
Come on, get in, quick. Before they
eat you. Quick, quick. Let's go.
(Barking)
(Barking stops)
Burkitt County's cheapest alarm.
And what's that do? Squirt water?
No, that actually works. Wave.
It's recording you right now.
I got 'em hooked up
through the building.
I'm a little paranoid.
Hah! a little?
I heard that.
But with good reason.
I got a lot of valuable stuff here.
Oh, my God!
(Kim) Yeah! You wouldn't want
somebody to come in here...
...and steal stuff
that you've already stolen.
Where it comes from is not
my business, nor should it be yours.
I just like to pass the savings
on to others.
Really? And how do you do that?
E- bay.
Buying, selling, trading, swapping.
I'm a major player.
I thought all your cameras
got trashed.
Well, you can never have too many.
Jeff, I think we've had enough
videotaping for one weekend.
Yeah, dude. Tour's over.
(Jeff) Maybe the tour has just begun...
...cos you're walking into
the official Blair store.
Come in, everybody.
This is where it begins.
This is the epicentre of
the Blair Witch-Hunt web-site.
I got my sticks... You can touch
these, they're for the stick men.
Don't touch those, those are drying.
Did you collect these
in the Black hills?
Yeah, every twig.
Here is a rock...
Oh, my God, who made that?!
Oh, I did, earlier.
We've got Parr ruins foundation dirt,
that's a big item. I sell that.
T- shirts and sweat shirts, and hats.
Here you go, Tristen.
That's for you, gratis.
I feel better.
You're as big an asshole
as the rest of them.
What are you talking about, Erica?
This stuff is hot.
This is what
the wiccan religion needs,
more capitalism based on
fear and lies.
Do you really think it's fair
to exploit our culture,
just to sell stick-figure key chains?
I think this place is cool, Jeff.
Thanks.
Jeff, we're tired.
I should get her to bed.
Oh, yeah. Sorry.
Let's see...
The stairs by the kitchen
lead to my editing loft.
The bedroom on the right is mine.
It's got the biggest bed
and it's own john. You guys take it.
Thanks, brother.
Sure.
Sleep well.
The rest of the bedrooms
are down the hallway.
Hey...
I really appreciate the hospitality,
but take me off your mailing list.
Ok.
They should have never let you out.
You're a long way from sane.
(Tristen) I saw something
at the hospital.
What?
It was just like the picture
in the Blair Witch black bible.
The same clothes,
that same face, like...
...she'd been drowned.
Who?
The little girl.
Eileen Treacle.
Sweetie...
Why don't we talk about this
after you get some sleep?
I want to talk about it now.
You need to sleep. You're in shock.
This is so... intense.
Chill out, Erica.
We've watched half of one tape.
We've got four angles,
we've got our handhelds,
we've got hours of tapes
we haven't seen.
Last night, when we were camping,
I dreamt I hurt the baby.
That's just because we've been
fighting about it so much.
You've been through a lot.
I know how much you wanted a baby.
I'm sorry I didn't want it.
I'm sorry that I lost it.
Guys, something just occurred to me.
Where's that tree?
(Kim) What?
That big tree that was right there.
Now there's just this tiny twig.
See, guys, I told you there was
something up with that tree.
Hand me another of those dv cassettes
maybe there's another angle.
Whoa, whoa... what is up with that?
I don't know. I think it's chafing
from the backpack.
Does it hurt?
Not really. It just kind of itches.
It's nothing. Here.
What was that?
What?
Rewind it.
What did you see?
I'm not sure. A flash, or something.
Coffin Rock.
What?
How the hell do you see Coffin Rock?
Can you see in other dimensions?
I don't know.
That's what it reminds me of.
Those guys
that were murdered there in 1886...
...after they were gutted,
their heads were arranged...
...in the shape of a pentagram...
Like that.
A great American pastime -
blame it on a witch.
(Jeff) Let me see
if I can get that image back.
(Tristen) Stephen!
(Erica) Is she gonna be Ok?
I don't know.
Stephen!
Tristen?
(Sobbing outside)
(Barking alarm)
Shut up.
(Girl's voice) "You brought it back
with you. "
(Shriek)
(Tristen) What was all that?
That was Jeff's stupid dog alarm.
The crying.
You heard that, too?
In my dreams.
I thought I was having
this horrible nightmare.
About what?
Children...
looking up my skirt
as I twirled round and round.
So I hurt them.
Stephen, what the hell
is wrong with me?
Nothing. Nothing. You're just...
(Wind howls outside)
Look, there are...
rational explanations behind this.
Behind everything that's going on.
I think we need to go home.
I'll get someone to drive us...
Not yet!
Why?
Just not yet.
I need to understand what happened.
You can understand it
on the plane ride home.
Here.
Take these.
Take them.
They'll help you sleep.
Come on, take them!
You're not making a believer
out of me, son.
It was an accident.
I swear to Christ,
it was an accident.
Jesus.
What the hell was that?
I'm not sure.
See that? Whoa, wait. Look.
Time code goes from 1:32am...
to 3:57am... back to 1:32am.
In the middle of the footage?
How does that happen?
I don't know. But those were
the hours that we fell asleep.
Can you make it bigger,
or slow it down?
Let me try slowing it down.
Ladies and gentlemen,
that is a naked woman.
What is a naked woman doing
swinging around a tree?
Are we sure these are our tapes?
I'm not sure of anything
in the last 24 hours.
I'll re-digitise this at a higher
resolution so I can blow it up.
This will take a few minutes.
I need alcohol.
Caffeine.
Caffeine!
Sure. I live to serve.
Ugh... great.
Stale coffee, no beer,
some old take-out chicken...
but plenty of batteries.
Hey...
What's going on?
We're leaving in the morning.
Really?
It's... It's Tristen.
She's in bad shape.
This whole thing has really
fucked her up.
How come you're the one who looks
like he's having a breakdown?
Look! I'm a little tense, all right?
Sorry.
No, I am...
sorry.
I just feel like my whole life's
been turned upside down
the past two days.
I know.
It's been really crazy for you,
but it's gonna be Ok.
I promise.
That feels good.
You ARE tense.
Like that?
Yeah.
Lower?
Yeah, lower.
How does that feel?
Good.
Lower?
How does that feel?
(Ripping and scraping)
Do they hurt?
No. They're just a little warm.
Don't worry.
I have them, too.
(Kim) Guys...
want to come up here?
You're out of beer,
if that's what you want to know.
Jeff found a better angle
on this naked chick.
What naked chick?
Cool. How?
I blew up the image.
(Kim) It's a bit weird to watch...
Like watching a hold-up
on a bank security camera.
(Kim) You get the gist.
(Stephen) Where is this?
(Jeff) The foundation.
(Erica) This was last night?
Yeah. During the big blackout.
(Stephen) Can you let us
see her face?
Sure can.
If this is a joke... it ain't funny.
No joke. It's serious, Erica.
While I was gone,
you messed with things.
(Jeff) No.
It doesn't make any sense.
I know.
We were hoping you could explain.
I don't have a clue.
You have no memory of doing this?
No.
(Jeff) If it's some wicca thing,
you can tell us.
(Kim) Try and help us understand.
We're just trying to put together
what happened last night.
Find out who trashed my equipment.
That wasn't me. I didn't do that.
Erica, that's you there
on the screen.
Leave me the hell alone, all of you!
Believe her?
I don't know.
Jeff, give me your keys to the van.
Where you going?
I have to get out. I need a beer.
Hey, see if we need more coffee.
(Erica chanting)
...earth and fire, water and smoke...
I am going to the store.
You want to come...?
(Continues chanting, sobbing)
Erica?
Erica!
We brought something back with us.
What are you talking about?
I can sense it...
...like someone's choking me...
...and squeezing the air out of me.
Look, we're just tired, Ok?
We're all really tired. That is it.
I want to show you something.
I have got the same thing.
It's nothing, it's like poison oak.
But, Kim...
They're growing.
(Erica) Ancient pagan alphabet.
They say it means
you've been touched by a witch.
(Sobbing) That you're next
chosen to die.
There's something here!
Sweet.
Yo, Morticia.
Hey, Elvira, I got something
you can suck the blood out of.
Oh, yeah? Whip it out.
Excuse me, sorry.
I'm finished now.
What the...?!
What is your problem?
You're with the witch people.
Lady...
I'm just here to buy groceries.
Witch!
Freak.
Am I gonna have a problem
with you, too?
No problem.
Good. Let's go.
Ok, look...
Either you ring this stuff up...
or I call your manager.
I am the manager.
Really?
Yeah.
Well, then, Peggy...
could you tell the bitch at the front
register to do her goddamn job?!
Get the hell out of here!
Not until I've completed my purchase.
We don't want people like you
around here.
You know what? I am gonna make this
so easy on you, Peggy.
I told you to get
the hell out of here.
You touch me again...
and I will rip out
your goddamn throat!
Keep your motherfucking change!
Persephone, do I invoke... by earth
and fire, and water and smoke...
Persephone, I invoke... by earth
Persephone, I invoke... (Sobbing) by
earth and fire, and water and smoke...
Persephone, I invoke...
(Continues)
(Sobbing)
(Indistinct disembodied chanting)
(Heavy metal)
(Increases volume)
Stone the witch!
Stone the bitch!
Fucking rednecks!
(Distant crying)
(Crying continues)
Ow!
(Jeff) Kim?
Make me a pot of coffee
on your way up.
You're welcome.
(Creaking and clock ticking)
Look, I fucked up your front fender.
I had to swerve
to avoid hitting these little kids.
They were dressed funny, like
from another time. Seven of them.
Jeff!
I know this is crazy,
but I know those are the kids
Rustin Parr killed!
Coffee.
Next to your arm.
Morning.
Hey. Did you sleep Ok?
Yeah, I slept Ok. You?
Yeah.
You ready to go?
Yeah. Are you guys ready?
Yeah.
I... appreciate your driving us.
Yeah. I'll get the keys from Jeff.
Come on, Tristen, wake up.
Come on, let's go.
Not yet...
Tristen, we're going home.
Erica?
Erica!
(Jeff) Not up here.
Not up there? You sure?
She was just here.
Didn't you hear me?
I just said she's not up here.
Why don't you go check out the van...
What the hell happened to the van?
(Stephen) Jesus Christ.
We are never gonna get out of here...
Kim, what the hell did you do?
You said you just busted up
the front end!
How the hell did you drive it back?
I swear it was just the front fender.
What the fuck is going on?!
They dip their hands in your blood
then press them on your body.
What are you talking about?
The children.
Something I dreamt.
Jeff dreamt it, too. Look.
Look!
Oh, Jesus! What the hell is this?
Something from the woods.
We've all got them. Me, her, Erica...
Where is Erica?
Erica?
Erica!
What the...?
(Dog barking)
Erica!
ERICA!
We would've heard the dog alarm
when she went outside.
It's like she fucking vanished.
Evaporated is more like it.
Yeah, right, Kim.
You were the one who found
her clothes and those candles.
(Kim) What the hell
is that supposed to mean?
A prank. Two little bitches
trying to freak us out.
You paranoid fuck!
Come on!
We'd never do something like that!
Where is she, Kim? Where is she?
Why are her clothes and shit
still here?
How would I know?
Can't you see her, Kimmy,
in your mind's eye?
Very funny, asshole!
I think something really bad
has happened to her.
Maybe she called somebody.
(Jeff) I'd like to speak
to Minister Geerson, please.
(Woman) "He's in a meeting.
Could he return your call?"
No. It's urgent.
"Could I tell him what it's about?"
Yeah. His daughter, Erica.
We wanna know if he's heard from her.
The minister and Mrs Geerson
have no daughter.
No, I know, like, they disowned her
or something because she's a witch...
"They've never had any children. "
(Dial tone)
So she made up a story.
She gave us a fake name.
It doesn't have to mean anything.
She lied to us.
Why are we seeing all this shit?
Why is all this happening?
I don't know. Collective delusion.
Group hysteria.
It's what my book is about. You get
a bunch of people scared enough...
Dude, spare us the bullshit. Please.
It's real. Dude(!)
It happens.
They teach it at junior colleges
I bet that even you could get into.
How did you get into yours?
You have to brush your teeth?
(Kim) Jeff, the screen.
Roll it back, rewind it.
No, more.
(Jeff) Oh, shit.
I knew they'd come back
and mess with my stuff.
(Phone)
Fuck off. No one's home.
It's Cravens.
"Sheriff?"
Funny. I just found out who trashed
my cameras. I was about to call you.
Turn on your TV.
"I don't give a shit.
I want you to see something. "
Me, too. News at 11:00.
Shit. Will you just turn that on?
Humour him.
You watching?
Like a hawk.
Listen, I'm trying to tell you
what I found out on Friday night.
"This is a special report. "
"A brutal murder in the Black Hills
discovered today"
"the bodies of five hikers found dead"
"atop the landmark
known as Coffin Rock. "
Disembowelled, Jeffrey.
"A re-creation
of the infamous Coffin Rock massacre"
"popularised by the movie
The Blair... "
Bodies were laid out
in the shape of a pentagram.
Sound familiar?
"We've received word that the victims
include two Chinese tourists"
"and one German, as well as
two unidentified white males. "
"Recently, the Black Hills
has been overrun with fans"
"wanting to get a glimpse
of where the movie was filmed. "
(Cravens) "You looking at me?"
What?
"Over here. "
(Kim) There.
(Jeff) Yeah?
"I didn't find your cameras. "
"Don't guess that's a surprise,
is it?"
What do you want from me?
I got five corpses here!
I had nothing to do with that.
You might not have been in charge
but you were involved,
so you and your little friends
had best just sit tight.
"And that means... you don't leave
this county till I say it's Ok. "
I don't know you, Stephen.
I don't know a thing about you.
I don't know how much to believe
about any of you people...
But from now on...
know this:
you are not leaving me here alone
to take the fall for this shit.
Nobody is going out of my sight.
We brought something back with us.
For Christ's sake, Kim...
I'll tell you what's going on here.
It's Erica...
or whoever the fuck she is.
Erica has got nothing to do
with this.
She's a witch, man!
She's one big pissed-off witch!
She's casting fucking spells,
making herself appear,
making herself fucking disappear.
It's been her since day one!
Smoke it up, cos you're not totally
psycho yet!
Where are you going?
The fuck away from you!
You're a dick.
Kim!
Jeff, you've got to have friends,
somebody with a car...
What did I tell you?!
You're not going anywhere!
Wipe that shit off your face.
You think that your makeup
and black clothes give you power...
...but you're just a scared, cowardly
little girl underneath all that.
(Erica) You don't understand.
Something happened to us
in the woods.
Something evil.
Why are you so mad at me?
(Siren)
Calm down. I'm not that pissed.
Just stop badmouthing Erica.
She's outside.
Where?
Right there.
There's nothing out there.
Tristen, let's get you back to bed.
You just got to look, Stephen.
Let's go to the bedroom.
Look again.
She's out there!
(Dogs barking)
Erica.
What happened to you?
Don't be afraid.
You know who it is.
What?
And you know what you have to do.
Erica!
You know who it is.
Erica?
(Distant laughter)
Tristen, help me. Help me!
Tristen!
Aw, Tristen...
Stephen! I got you, grab my hand.
Come on, hold on.
They did it, the little Buster Boys.
They did it! They hanged her!
The little Buster Boys!
Tristen! Shh! Shh!
It's only a dream. It's only a dream!
They're Elly Kedward's dreams!
I don't know why I'm having them.
Why do you think
they're Elly Kedward's?
Cos I was seeing them
through her eyes...
...tied to the tree
where they banished her to.
And the bad little boys
from Blair village...
...sneaking out to the woods
to see if she was still alive...
...and... and they let their big dogs
bite her...
...and they poked her with sticks and
then when the blood came out of her...
...they put their palms in it
and pressed it on her flesh!
And then, when they found
she was still alive...
...they untied her... and they put
the ropes around her neck...
...and they hanged her
from the big tree!
Stephen, I think I'm going
fucking crazy!
No! No, you are not going crazy.
Do you hear me?
You are not going crazy.
It's Ok.
It's all right.
(Footsteps approaching)
Jeff? Listen, I'm really worried
about Tristen.
Do you know the name
of the doctor she was with?
No, no, I don't.
Then I think you need to call
the hospital.
Ok. I think there's a phone book
in the desk drawer.
What is this?
What the fuck is this?
What?
These!
I don't know. Where did you get 'em?
In your desk!
What, are you spying on us?
What the hell are you talking about?
No, I'm not!
I've no idea where this came from!
Where'd you get this? Answer me!
She found 'em.
Maybe she put 'em in there!
I wanna know where you got these!
I've no idea!
We've been looking into
your background, Stephen.
You've been such a good little boy
all your life.
How did you get mixed up in all this?
(Phone)
What?
"It's Cravens, you little shit!"
Sheriff, I'm a little preoccupied
right now.
"I need to talk to you.
Get your butt down here. "
My van is trashed. And you know mommy
doesn't let me out after dark.
"I'm right at your front door,
you little twerp! Get down here!"
How can he be out there?
The bridge is gone.
(Kim) This is too weird.
(Bang)
(Cravens) Here!
Jeffrey!
(Bang)
It's Cravens!
(Banging continues)
We got a few things
to talk about, boy!
(Banging)
You were a punk as a kid,
and you're still a punk!
Open up, Jeff!
(Banging)
Open the goddamn door!
If you know what's good for you,
you'll open the damn door!
You open up
this goddamn door right now!
I told you to stay out
of those woods.
They're not gonna just send you back
to the loony bin this time.
Open the goddamn door!
(Barking)
(Barking continues)
Jeff!
What the fuck, dude?
Put the gun down.
Put the gun down!
Erica.
What are you doing?
(Kim) That's gross!
(Stephen) She... she's...! Oh, God!
(Flies buzzing)
(Clock ticking)
You were the last one to see her
still alive.
The last time I saw her,
she was heading up here to see you.
I didn't kill her, Stephen.
Don't even think it.
Kim was up here with me!
Well, let me clue you in
to something, all right?
She didn't commit fucking suicide!
One of you...
Oh, wait!
What about you?
What gets you off the goddamn hook?
My word!
Which is worth exactly shit to me!
Where was your little girlfriend
this whole time?
Oh, for Christ's sake!
She can barely get out of bed...
It's backwards.
Go back to bed, Tristen.
The little girl backwards.
Erica dancing...
backwards.
Everything backwards.
What are you talking about?
Widdershins.
Undo the evil.
What the fuck is a widdershin?
(Speaking gibberish)
All right,
she's lost her fucking mind.
That's it.
Backwards.
Backwards!
What?
We need to run the tapes backwards.
Why?
I don't know.
I think it'll help us find out
what happened to Erica.
This makes no sense!
I know it doesn't. Just please do it!
(Tristen murmuring)
See? Nothing.
Try the-the-the
keystrokes backwards.
You know, the fucking commands.
You see? You guys happy?
There's nothing!
There's your missing hours.
(Jeff) This must be
when we blacked out.
Tristen...
What is this?
What did you make us do?
You're leading us, aren't you?
Weren't you watching
the fucking screen?
No.
Get back here!
Grab her!
Get your hands off me.
What did you do, Tristen?
Stephen, please tell them to stop.
Why aren't you marked like this?
Like the rest of us, like Erica?
What did you do to Erica?
Stephen, why are you letting them
do this?
(Kim) You killed Erica!
(Tristen) You two are crazy!
Shh, shh, shh! Listen.
Just admit it to the camera.
We're not gonna take the fall
for Erica.
Ok? Just admit it. Don't worry,
sweetie. We're not gonna hurt you.
Not like you hurt the baby.
What? I didn't have anything
to do with the baby.
The witch kills children!
I... haven't killed anybody!
(Kim) Bullshit!
Oh, God, Stephen.
Tristen, just say the words!
Just say the words...
(Kim screams)
You're all gonna fucking die.
You wanna kill me?
No.
No, I just want to understand.
But you can't understand
because you're so afraid!
Just like the pathetic children
of Blair village, so frightened!
Aren't you, little girl?
Who are you?
She's the witch, man!
(Gasps)
(Deep voice) Is that
what you think... crazy boy?
Tristen! Tristen, talk to me!
Stephen...
What is it, baby, what is it?
Tristen's gone.
(Kim) Get away from him!
That's not... how you do it.
This is what you want.
Tristen, whatever you're doing...
don't!
I'm not doing anything, honey.
It's all up to you!
Witch bitch.
Why did you kill Erica?
(Sniffs)
(Sniffing)
I can smell the fear on you.
Stay away from me.
You wanna kill me?
You can't, can you, Kimmy?
I will rip your fucking head off!
Then fucking do it!
Stop it!
Stop it.
Aw, isn't that
what your book's about, Stephen?
People just want to see something?
You have no balls.
You can't do it, you weak,
little pathetic...
Oh, you were the last fucking one
with the balls, you little bitch.
No!
(Screams)
(Screaming)
(Rope creaking)
"I'm standing in front
of an abandoned broom factory... "
"... in Jericho Mills, a few miles from
the town of Burkittsville... "
"... where, just hours ago, police
arrested three obsessed movie fans... "
"... who allegedly committed a series
of ritualistic murders... "
"... after watching last summer's
blockbuster... "
"... the Blair Witch Project. "
'This vehicle,
which you see behind me... "
"... is owned by one of the suspects... "
"... and there is blood evidence linking
the suspects to these murders. "
"Sadly, as has happened so many times
before in this country... "
"... violent art has inspired
real-life violence. "
"In this case,
it's the Blair Witch Project. "
(Cravens) I ain't no documentary
film-maker,
but I had your videotapes
slapped together
over at Montgomery College.
Sorta tells the whole story.
Great.
You could see how fucking insane
Tristen was.
She practically begged Stephen
to push her.
Gutting those tourists...
How'd you have the stomach for that?
Yeah...
I don't remember doing that.
Let's talk about... Peggy.
What?
(Reporter) "Apparently one woman
was hanged, and the other victim... "
"... the cause of death has yet
to be determined.
"Ironically, both women were murdered
by their friends... "
"... after allegedly participating
in a vicious killing spree... "
"... in the Black Hills. "
(2nd reporter) "The police
have not offered a motive... "
"... but apparently the two slain female
killers were involved in witchcraft. "
And, um... what about the redhead?
She was a real pretty girl.
She wouldn't put out or something?
No, we just found her in the closet.
It was Tristen.
The witch got into her...
fucked with her mind or something.
And your girlfriend? Killing her
because she had a miscarriage.
Whoo-whee! Now, that's harsh.
She wrapped the rope around her neck.
She was taunting me...
begging me to push her.
You're not making a believer
out of me.
It was an accident!
(Sobbing) I swear to Christ
it was an accident!
(Reporter) "Local officials are urging calm... "
"... and trying to keep curiosity
seekers at bay. "
"And as has happened in the past... "
"... rumours about a... "
"... supernatural presence
causing these murders... "
"... are spreading like wildfire
over the internet. "
(Stephen) W-wait... wait.
Wait a... wait a second.
Jeff...
He...
He videotaped the whole thing.
Watch the tapes. You'll see.
Look at the goddamn tapes!
Yes, sir.
Too much trouble
to pay for your beer?
I didn't do that.
Oh, yeah?
Then, um...
who's this?
I didn't do that.
That's not how it happened.
Stop it.
(Jeff) "Just... just do it!
Just admit it to the camera. "
"We're not gonna take the fall
for Erica. "
"Don't worry,
we're not gonna hurt you. "
"Not like you hurt the baby. "
"What? I didn't have anything
to do with the baby. "
"The witch kills children!"
"I... haven't killed anybody!"
"Bullshit!"
"No!"
"Tell us the truth.
Tell us the truth. "
"Confess. "
"God!"
"Stephen, this is me.
What are you talking about?"
(Tristen screams) "Stop it!"
"Tristen!"
"No! No!"
"Stop! Oh... "
(Jeff) "She's the witch, man!"
"Jeff, what are you saying?
I'm not the witch. "
"Yeah, you are. "
"What are you saying?"
You know what I'm saying,
goddamn it!
(Tristen) "Stephen, please. "
(Stephen) "Did you kill Erica?
Confess, confess. "
"Stop it. "
"Say the words. "
"Oh, God, Stephen, don't! Please!"
"No!"
"Fucking witch!"
This is wrong.
Somebody fucked with this tape!
Somebody fucked with that tape!
That tape is wrong!
That's fucking bullshit!
(Sobbing) That's fucking shit!