Katsunori Takahashi
Ayane Miura
Yoshio Harada
Based on the novel by
Koji Suzuki
Music: Koji lke
Directed by Chisui Takigawa
He is now a gluttonous insect.
See ...
That's strange...
Huh?
Go away. GO AWAY!
RING
Let Me Guess,
You're a reporter from the cultural section, aren't
you?
You're close, I work at the Toto newspaper
But that's a good guess.
Well, if you're around here this late,
aren't drunk and are still at work;
then there aren't many jobs, other than a
reporter
You act like one too,
like all full of curiosity.
Sorry, but that's a wrong guess.
I was a reporter, but right now -
I'm just proofreading columns.
Proofreading?
Yeah, stuff like correcting missing periods,
misspelled words...
Ah, well that's an important job, too...
Yeah...
Hey... what are you doing?
What happened? Are you alright?
What happened?
Are you all right?
Go away!
GO AWAY!
Please make a statement about the damage for
my taxi company!
An ambulance!
I'm home.
Welcome home.
How are you feeling?
The third month is an important time, right?
You should be sleeping, you don't have time to
wait up for me.
Take care of yourself.
Did you go to see the doctor?
He said there aren't any problems...
But...my sister called me and said that..
Tomoko died.
Tomoko?
They said she had a heart failure ...
Heart failure? But she's only in high school!
When my sister came home, they found her
collapsed on the floor.
They took her to the hospital, but they couldn't
do anything.
Sister...
Shizuka... Tomoko is ...
Tomoko...
Then we'll be leaving. Thank you.
Thank you.
Excuse me officer?
When will we get Tomoko's body back?
As long as there aren't any problems, then it will
be later today.
Why would there be problems!?
Let me see her face! Let her come home!
Excuse me, but was it necessary to perform an
autopsy?
Yes, there are doubts about the case.
What kind of doubts?
She didn't seem to have a weak heart,
plus she was lying on the bathroom floor in the
middle of the night...
The door was locked from the inside.
From the inside?
TOTO NEWSPAPER CO.
Editing/Proofreading Sector
Mr. Asakawa, did my article meet the deadline?
I brought it in at the last minute so I wanted to
know how they handled it.
Here.
Mr. Asakawa, weren't you in the Society Sector
before?
Yeah.
What's this company thinking? Why would they
move someone like you to desk work?
I don't know.
Honestly, don't you want to go back to the
Society Sector too?
Suicide in a car7 Heart failure7 The mystery of
a young couple's death...
Hey, Yoshino!
Yeah?
Do you know who investigated this article?
That's one of mine, I wrote it.
Can you tell me more about the story?
This case is mysterious
Takehiko Nomi. Yoko Tsuji
These two ... at first, we thought it was just a
suicide.
But something's strange about it.
First of all, what couple would commit suicide
with their underwear off?
And secondly, as they were dying, they used all
their will to get out of the car.
That could mean there was something inside the
car.
And the police report? They did an autopsy,
didn't they?
They said it was just heart failure.
Both of them? There's no fucking way!
A young couple can't have their hearts fail at the
same time!
I thought so too, that's why I wanted them to
investigate this deeper.
Could it have been drugs?
No, apparently there were no substances.
Could it be anything like a new virus?
Mr. Asakawa, you seem to be very curious about
this.
Actually, there have been two other incidents
similar to this one.
Two other incidents?
Both were sudden heart failures, and I
witnessed one of them myself.
They found these two around dawn right? Was
there a time of death announced?
It's ..um.. last night between 11 p.m. and 2 a.m.
What?
The time was 1 2:49 a.m. Something could've
happened at that time.
Mr. Asakawa!
Tomoko Oishi, 12:49 a.m. Bathroom in her
home, locked from the inside.
Iwata Shuichi, 1 2:49 a.m. Falling off his
motorbike at an intersection.
'"Go Away!'"
Takehiko Nomi,
1 2:49 a.m. Inside a parking garage, trying to
escape out of his car.
Yoko Tsuji,
1 2:49 a.m. Inside a parking garage, trying to
escape out of Nomi's car.
Are you sure this isn't all just some big
coincidence?
All the locations and situations are different...
Listen: four, healthy, young teens died on the
same night at the same time,
And you think it's all just a coincidence?
I know, but...
We should tell the Assistant Editor...is he here?
He should be at his desk.
Sorry to disappoint you, Asakawa, but this won't
make an article.
In this vast city that Tokyo is, four people had
heart failures at the same time.
It'll make the readers laugh.
But...think of it this way:
Couldn't they have all gotten together and taken
the same drug?
Maybe all at the exact same time?
If there was a drug like that, it would've come up
by now.
Maybe it's a brand new drug? Even AIDS
started as a small occurence!
Let me check it out!
You're not a Society Sector reporter anymore.
And there could be the possibility of other
victims.
There could be other people who have died at
that time.
That's enough! You remember, why the kicked
you out of the Society Sector?
Ryuji Takayama! I don't want to be involved with
that guy!
I understand that you want to use a good story
to get back into the Society Sector.
But any way you look at it this is just a
coincidence. Okay?
I understand.
Go back to your work area.
I will do this by myself.
I will not cause any problems.
Hey, Asakawa!
Assitant Editor, who is Ryuji Takayama?
You don't know?
Well, I know it has something to do with
Asakawa -
But he never wants to talk about it.
Wife killing.
What?
Not guilty on lack of evidence.
What do you mean?
Even with the credibility of being an assistant
college proffesor -
he had a very strong opinion favoring
clairvoyance and abnormal powers.
Magazines and television picked it up and it got
popular for a short period.
Then, he started saying he'll take on unsolved
cases using clairvoyance.
Huh...
Asakawa was the one who organized it.
Mr. Asakawa...
If it stopped there it could've just faded out
slowly...
But after that, Ryuji Takayama's wife suddenly
died.
The one who found her body was Takayama
himself.
No motive of suicide, nothing weird at all.
The police suspected Takayama himself right
away.
Why was he judged as not guilty then?
Takayama left his appearance at a show in the
countryside to come back to Tokyo
and found his dead wife.
He said that the reason he came back was that
he '"Felt like his wife was going to die.'"
What?
Asakawa trusted Takayama's premonition
and represented his innocence in a newspaper
article to the public.
The paper was chaos after that.
It was a big mess, with the police coming and
going,
Even instances of people denying our coverage.
Poor Asakawa, but we needed him to go
somewhere else.
No wonder. So what's this Takayama like?
A fraud.
An impressive one, even to convince Asakawa
Asakawa!
Hey, Asakawa!
Good Evening
What is it?
You're Yutaka Nonoyama, right?
Yeah... What is this about?
The car, that Takehiko Nomi was in the night he
died -
- is your car, correct?
You're a news reporter?
The police already asked me plenty about that
day, so please ask them.
Wait a second. Does this name sound familiar
to you?
Tomoko Oishi and lwata Shuichi.
I'm trying to find a connection with the other two
victims.
Why would I know these people?
One is an eighteen year old high school student/
The other is a nineteen year old pre-college
student at Number One Pre-college.
We said we don't know. You're relentless!
Wait, Number One Pre-college?
Do you remember something?
Yeah, like a week ago, I lent him my car so he
could go out drinking ...
He said something about going out with
someone named lwata from there -
- and two high school girls he picked up.
- To a resort club in Hakone.
High school girls? Is it Tomoko?
Tomoko Oishi?
Yeah, Tomoko. That was it.
I thought so...
do you know the name of this resort club?
It's called '"South Hakone Pacific Land.'"
I have a membership for this rental cabin resort.
Thank you very much.
A link has been discovered between the four
victims.
One week ago, those kids were together at a
rental cabin at a Hakone resort club.
But... what happened there? ...
Excuse me.
Yes?
Hello.
My name is Asakawa, I made a reservation.
Mr. Asakawa from Tokyo?
May I request a particular cabin?
Sure, I don't mind.
B-4
B-4?
Is that the one four teens used about a week
ago?
They did?
Takehiko Nomi, Yoko Tsuji, lwata Shuichi,
Tomoko Oishi.
Do you remember?
Oh yeah.
This room...
One week before their death, they all stayed
here.
What happened here?
Hello? It's me.
Kazuyuki? What's the matter?
I'm not feeling very well, I don't think I'll make it
home tonight.
I have this rush job.
What? I even made beef stew.
Sorry...
Is it really work?
What? What are you trying to accuse me of?
Anyway, how are you?
Yeah, I can't say that!
Don't worry, bye.
Warning: Cowards, don't watch this.
You'll be sorry.
S.I.?
Shuichi lwata
Was there something on top of this?
'"Don't watch this...'"
Excuse me?
Yeah?
Um, excuse me...
What is it?
I thought I'd watch a video or something...
Sure, which one would you like?
That's a good one
that one is really good.
Me, I like this zombie movie.
Hey ... what's this video?!
Oh ... I found this one in B-4,
- so I just brought it in. Someone probably
forgot it.
Really? Can I rent it?
Are you sure you want this one?
Yeah, yeah.
YAMA
[Old Japanese]
If you just keep shomon, the bokon will come for
you ...
SADA
You, who saw these images,
- have seven days left.
Seven days later at this time, you will die.
If you don't want to die, then...
Hello?
It's a lie!
This is a joke...
This is one for the books!
What's so funny?
This is just like you. Thinking this would be a big
story, you jumped on it -
-but nobody else thinks so. So you research it
all by yourself.
Now you think your life is in danger and you're
completely freaked out.
Four people have already died!
Why don't you show that tape to everyone? It
would be hilarious.
Everyone would start working to figure out the
missing part of the tape.
Wouldn't you rather do that than be alone?
Takayama!
I'm just kidding. Well... Since I'm like a bad
omen to you,
-this must be something for you to come here.
PARAPS YCHOLOGY/CLAIRVOYANCE
Head Doctor: Ryuji Takayama
So, let me watch the video. I'll even put it into
my collection.
Are you sure?
You'll die if you see it ...
Yeah, whatever. The fear that you felt when you
watched this video...
If we decipher the psyche, then maybe we'll be
able to understand the structure of this strange
world.
Wow... is it already that time?
I have to go show these idiots my supreme
lecture.
Takayama?
Copy it onto this one. You can figure out how to
do it.
After I'"m done I'll just leave the copy here.
Yeah, I'll watch it as soon as I can. While you're
alive...
Hey, Asakawa!
Since you've been gone, everyone has had their
hands full.
Its been two days. You're being lazy! Show
some remorse.
Sorry,
I shouldn't have gone to see someone like Ryuji
Takayama.
Maybe I'm into my own assumption
Then this tape is just a prank?
I'm home.
Welcome home!
Sorry about last night.
Hey, Kazuyuki, are you still seeing that
Takayama?
Why?
He called a few times
Kazuyuki!
It's okay, I'm just going to tell him to stop getting
involved.
Hello, this is Asakawa.
It's me. Can you come here right now?
The video I got from you ...
it's a forewarning message to commit murder.
If we leave this as it is, we might actually be
dead in a week...
No fucking way!
I don't have any real assurance...
How do you know?
A hunch. And I've never been wrong about this
kind of thing.
You should know the most about this. Hurry up
and come over.
You've got six days to live, and I've got seven.
There is a way to be saved.
What do we have to do?
Firstly, who is the one who erased the end of
this tape?
Maybe it was one of the four? The program that
was recorded at the end was aired the night they
stayed in Hakone ...
Those kids tried to freak out the people who saw
the tape next -
-and half jokingly erased the important part of
the message ...
Then there are probably more than those four
that have seen this tape.
And those people would know how to be saved.
Yeah...
Find out about everyone else that stayed in that
room.
Good evening.
Hello.
She's a student from the university.
Sensei, should I make some coffee?
I guess I'll tell you the reason I think this video is
for real.
This footage, for something that's manufactured,
it's really good.
It could be a pro, and in reality there are four
people dead.
But the contents are very sporadic. I feel
sometimes though...
What?
Some abnormal power.
..it's gone into the world you dislike.
However, we should approach this in a realistic,
logical way
This video has two main overall points.
'"If you keep shomon, the bokon will come for
you,'"
- this is some old Japanese dialect. I'll ask a
linguist about it.
Next, there's the clip of the volcano.
Find out where this volcano is and when it
erupted.
Can we solve it this way?
We won't know until we try.
Wait a second...we might die!
Are you scared of dying?
Of course!
We lose everything if we die.
Really? Have you died before?
Of course I haven't!
I'm the only one who can help you.
If you want to live, then listen to what I say.
We've started down a road, which we can never
come back from.
I took days off of work, told my wife I was going
to work and started our investigation.
According to the innkeeper, it was one month
ago that the video deck was installed in that
cabin.
Since then, there were eight groups that stayed
there.
I called them individually and asked if they had
seen a weird video.
But none of them knew about it.
One by one, I erased their names.
The old lady's regional Japanese, it's from the
lzu-Oshima Island.
Yes, from Oshima. There's also a southern
accent included in it -
- from Sashikiji prefecture.
Izu-Oshima island?
Well, the volcano is Mt. Mihara, from the lzu-
Oshima.
And the meaning of the old lady's words...
'"How has your health been since then?
'"If you just keep playing in water - '"
'" - monsters are going to come for you.'"
And finally, we found out that the last people that
stayed in that room didn't know about the video.
We don't have a chance unless we solve this
mystery ourselves.
Five more days.
Four more days.
Three more days.
If I die, will my wife be able to survive on her
own?
And what will become of my child,
who will never see their father's face?
Time is the only thing passing, which is as fast
as it's cruel.
The black frames...
Yeah, I watched in slow motion and realized it
for the first time.
They're really instant, but it also happens
multiple times.
Yeah, it was on my mind also ...
All right, lets organize this.
The naked baby lying down: one.
The man with the bleeding shoulder: five.
These are all the black frames, that I counted.
What do you think of all this?
There are some parts with the black frames, and
some without them.
The ones with the black frames, are the volcano
eruption -
- the baby, -
- the man, -
- and this other man...
That's it ...
That's exactly it!
Only the concrete parts, which are memories of
actual events, have the black frames.
And the black frames occur on average about
once every three or four seconds.
Do you get it? It's the blinking of a human eye.
Blinking?
Yeah.
Wait a minute, this is a video! Why would it
have anything to do with blinking?
So this footage is not something recorded with a
camera.
What?
lts a materialization of human will?
A materialization of human will?
This is someone burning their memory onto the
tape.
And their grudge, too.
A very strong curse.
What!? Something like that couldn't happen!
It does happen!!
Materialization is a life force, which contains
energy and is an element.
Modern science has philosophized this.
So it means we have to find whoever made this
as quickly as possible, and release the grudge.
How do we find this? I don't have a clue!
For someone that could create,
- materialization like this had to have been
recorded in some form.
Wait...
Izu-Oshima
NEVER SEEN BEFORE!
DEMONSTRATION OF THE EXISTENCE OF
CLAIRVO YANCE
For this organized event, we have people from
all different subjects of study.
A man, who strongly believes he has found the
existence of clairvoyance -
Professor Heihachiro lkuma, is in front of these
examining scientists.
The outcome of dice, thrown into a special lead
container,
will be predicted by Shizuko Yamamura,
using her power of clairvoyance in this
demonstration.
But no matter how many times she tried,
-she couldn't guess the number on the dice.
The crowd, who attended the experiment,
became disgusted at her failure
- and started yelling. They left their seats,
-and some of them even started throwing things.
Assistant Professor lkuma's reputation was
seriously hurt.
But she failed the experiment! How could she
be a clairvoyant?
Well ... there's a newspaper article left.
The reason Shizuko Yamamura got discovered
was through her power of clairvoyance.
She saw through all these statues.
The the one who made the video is Shizuko
Yamamura.
No, no, no...
- the daughter. Who we need to find is Sadako
Yamamura.
Heihachiro lkuma and Shizuko Yamamura had a
daughter.
How do you know that?
Look at this video.
This is the eye level of a child.
At that time Sadako was 8 years old.
If the mother had the power of clairvoyance,
there's a very good chance -
the daughter had psychic abilities too.
You're saying that Shizuko Yamamura had real
powers?
Yes, but the powers her daughter Sadako had
were even stronger.
That's why she's able to make images on tape,
and even kill somebody.
All right, let's fly to Oshima tomorrow. Sadako's
relatives might still be alive.
This is getting to be quite entertaining.
What's wrong?
Sorry, but I'm not going.
What?
This isn't a game!
The only time I have left is tommorow and the
next day.
Only two days left!
If that's the case, I want to spend that time with
my wife.
Excuse me.
Wait a second.
Asakawa!? Are you sure you want to do that!?
I'm home.
Welcome home.
What happened, you're early today?
I thought you were going to be late for the next
few days.
Oh, the rotation changed a bit. Anyways, here...
What...what's the occasion?
It doesn't have to be an occasion to get you a
present.
I thought it'd look good on you. It's a summer
sweater.
I'm so happy! Can I open it?
Yeah, of course.
Hey Shizuka! Did you ...
Oh sorry, it was in the VCR so ...
That gross video.
You saw it?
Yeah what is it?
When did you see it?!
When did you see it!?
This afternoon, after I got home from the
hospital so a little past 2 pm ...
Idiot!
What happened?
lzu-Oshima Island
Mt. Mihara
It's all my fault.
Since I rushed into this big story, now even my
wife is involved!
You and I will be saved! So your wife will be
saved too.
Why do you have so much confidence?
It might be all over for us, haven't you thought of
that?
Maybe you don't understand,
but there's a mystery and a depth of this video
that I'm attracted to.
I think we'll definitely meet the creator of this
video.
The Yamamura house was a well known
household in this area.
There is still a cousin of Shizuko Yamamura
living here.
YAMAMURA
Are you Mr. Yamamura?
Shizuko is dead. She threw herself into Mt.
Mihara and died.
It all happened long ago.
Shizuko saw a lot of terrible things.
she often complained about having a headache
and was bedridden.
That Heihachiro lkuma used her as a tool to
make money!
And he wanted a wife and child
so he got Shizuko pregnant!
Is that child Sadako?
Yes it is. Shizuko went crazy from being shown
off in front of crowds.
and even her second child died soon after
birth ...
She came back from Tokyo as if she escaped
from there.
She left Sadako and jumped into the volcano!
After that, Sadako was left all alone.
She possesed even stranger powers than her
mother.
Because of that, she was tormented a lot when
she was young.
Do you know what happened to Sadako after
that?
She said she was leaving and she escaped off
the island -
- saying she was going to be an actress.
She was in an acting troupe called '"Hisho.'" Or
something like that -
- but I don't know what happened after that...
She was a beautiful girl, she was probably
tricked by some pervert.
Asakawa! Where the hell are you?
You're absent without permission. The entire
office is pissed off.
I'm sorry, but I need something looked up...
About 30 years ago, there should have been
someone named Sadako Yamamura -
in an acting group called Hisho. Can you look
up what she's doing now?
And the assistant Professor at Taido University,
named Heihachiro lkuma ...
Iook up the disappearance of this man too. I'm
counting on you.
It's a nice bath. You should take one too.
Well then, let's eat something.
What's the matter?
Tommorow at this time, right?
Tomorrow at this time I might die.
Why are you so discouraged?
You wouldn't understand, Takayama.
Even after I die, you still have fourteen hours
left.
Don't give me that bullshit!
Right now fourteen hours is a long time!!
Knock it off
Knock it off, idiot
Twenty-four hours left.
The goal of this game is in our sight!
Anyway, go back to Tokyo tommorow morning,
and gather information about Sadako.
Believe me! Once you lose hope, you've lost the
game.
Understand?
With Yoshino's report, I found a former member
of the Hisho acting troupe from back then.
Excuse me, are you Arima?
Were you ever in an acting troupe? An acting
group called Hisho...
Yeah..
Do you remember a Sadako Yamamura
Sadako Yamamura...
Can you remember anything?
She was supposedly in the acting group around
the same time...
It was a long time ago ...
Can you wait here for a second?
Why are you running away?
Let me go!
I have nothing to do with it! I am of no use for
the police!
I'm not the police!!
I'm a newspaper reporter. I just came to ask a
little bit about the past.
Sorry about that.
We were getting a lot of heat from the police.
More than 30 years ago ...
Sadako Yamamura
She was a beautiful woman.
Like something so pure,
nothing you'd ever find in Tokyo...
But she just wasn't normal ...
'"Hey'"
Shigemori, who was in the group at the same
level I was -
- started saying he was going to make Sadako
his girlfriend
So we went to Sadako's house one late night,
then ...
'"Is that Sadako's voice?'"
Then we saw there was someone there before
us ...
Sadako called out to the other person ...
What do you think she said?
'"Father'"
Father?
Yeah ... If that was it, the police wouldn't have
been so involved.
But the story doesn't end here.
Sighemori went crazy after seeing them ...
He said something like,
'"There's no way she could do it with her father
and not with me!'"
After that he rushed to Sadako's apartment.
What the hell ...that guy did ...
then I will too ... Sadako!
And then?
Shigemori died ...
Died?
Sudden heart failure.
Heart failure?
Hello?
I saw the son of Heihachiro lkuma.
Yeah ... Heihachiro fell physically ill, but his
doctor, Nagao, lives in Atami.
ATAMI
Excuse me, is Dr. Jotaro Nagao here?
Are you here for an examination?
No ...
Are you Dr. Jotaro Nagao?
Yes.
Sadako Yamamura ... You know her don't you?
Hey you -
what did you do to her?
Sadako ...
It was over 30 years ago.
She was the daughter of Heihachiro lkuma, who
was a patient of mine
My father ... he's not going to make it, is he?
He's going to die soon, isn't he?
I was wellll aware that Sadako shared an intimate
rellationship with her father.
But even though I felt sorry for her, I didn't think
she was tainted.
Later, I was suddenly attracted to the purity of
Sadako's heart.
And eventually, Sadako thought about me too ...
We never brought it to words, but we were in
love.
Until that incident ...
'"No, we can't drink this water.
'"Sadako ...'"
'"No, no, no!'"
Sadako, I love you... Sadako ...
Is it true? You really love me?
I love you. I even want to marry you!
No matter what? You will marry me?
No matter what. I'll marry you.
Sadako was not a woman, nor a man.
She was a hermaphrodite.
Hermaphrodite?
She had Testicular Feminization Sydrome, to be
exact.
I thought so. You're all the same ...
No
I'll kill you
Sadako's voice echoed in my head.
I'll kill you...
Then suddenly in my chest!
I'll kill you!
Stop it Sadako!
I thought about it over and over.
I'm innocent, truly innocent. Believe me.
She possesed me to commit murder!
She made me do it!
Then you're the murderer!
Nagao? Tell us one last thing.
The hospital you worked in, where was it located
back then?
Fujimi town in Hakone.
The town's name might be changed by now,
though ...
Fujimi town in Hakone?
Here! It's here! Right were the cabin I saw the
video tape in is!
Then it's true
The cabin was built right where the hospital was.
Under the floor there's a ...
... there's a place where Sadako sleeps now.
We'll pull Sadako out of the well and then give
her remains a proper burial.
That is the only way left for us who have seen
the video ...
There's still more that I don't understand.
What?
Why did Sadako have an intimate relationship
with her father?
Nah, the initimacy with her father is not the
problem.
The problem is that she was born with the
disgust of all the beautiful things -
- which make us human.
It doesn't seem strange to me that the two
longed for eachother -
after they were both abandoned by society.
Why do you think Sadako went on to murder
everyone without motive like this?
Normally, wouldn't she take revenge on the one
who did this to her?
I think in the span of her life of less than 20
years,
she felt more pain and misery than any person
could imagine.
That's why she takes all that in, covers herself,
sits with mostrous rage and sleeps in that well.
That's what I think.
where's the room where you watched the video?
Right there
Hurry Up!
Takayama!
It's right there!
What are you doing?
Bring the crowbar.
Hey ... try to break this right here.
Hey! Light!
We have to hurry up and stop Sadako from
doing this.
That's the answer to the problem.
All right then, I'm lowering myself below, so stay
up here and pull the bucket out.
You got it?
I understand.
Are you sure this is all right, Takayama?
And you, are you all right?
Make sure you're okay!
Yes, yes.
So let's go.
Are you all okay, Takayama?
Yeah ... it's pretty deep ...
Be careful.
That almost hit me!
I'm sorry.
What's the matter?
Switch.
Let's switch.
Wait a second. I can't bear to do this.
What the hell are you saying?
Don't get all touchy. You don't even have any
strength left to lift the bucket.
Look at the watch! How much time do you think
we have left?
Get ahold of yourself! Asakawa!
Yes.
Damn it!
We don't have time!
Be careful!
Are you okay!?
Don't worry, I'll be right here.
I'm all right!
Sadako!
Asakawa!!
Takayama ...
Takayama.
I'm awake ...
what the ...
It's over
Doctor?
Dr. Nagao?
NOOOO!!
Yeah, really?
The old man took it in silence?
That's good.
Yeah, as soon as I showed him the ashes he
knew what it was.
But he didn't take the video. He told me to
'"erase it, please.'"
Yeah, so that's that.
Good, then shall we have a drink to celebrate
us coming out alive?
Yeah, that sounds good.
Then I'll catch the next flight to Haneda, how
about 2:30 at the bar in Haneda?
Then 2:30 it is. Got it.
Ms. Sadako.
That's your child?
It's the thing you wanted most of all.
If you don't want to die, there's only one way to
live.
Your child.
Professor? Professor?
No, professor, no!
He's dead...
Why!?
No one knew him really ...
but he was a really good person.
I know. I knew him very well...
He never slept with me, but we were doing very
well...
Hey ...
how did Takayama die?
Anything ... did you notice anything at all?
Anything!
I don't know ... He said '"Your child,'" to himself.
Your child?
Why didn't we break Sadako's grudge?
Why?
I'm alive but ...
- You watched it!? -
- Yeah ... -
'"Your child?'"
Wait, wait. I did something Takayama didn't
do ...
What ... what is it?
What!
Child. Child.
Child.
- Make a copy of this, you can figure out how,
can't you? -
That's it!
I copied the tape for Takayama and showed it to
him.
- So after I copy it , I can leave it here right? -
- Yeah. I'll watch it is as soon as I can. While
you're alive ... -
That's it!
Sadako was using the videotape to reproduce
her own grudge!
- If you don't want to die,
there's only one way to live:
Those who have seen this video must become a
servant that leads a new person to death. -
Lead one to death?
Shizuka needs to show someone else the
video?
That's how she can be saved?
Find another victim?
Takayama, in order to sever the connection of
Sadako's horrifying grudge, chose death ...
But I can't do that.
I am going to have my wife make a copy of the
tape and show it someone else.
And after that and after that ...
Then the human race will have to continue on
like this forever.
If and when this ring becomes severed ...
Then that's the real beginning of Sadako's
revenge.