Is it me
or is the smell getting worse down there?
I told you before,
it changes from one area to the next.
This is actually the fresh part.
- Fresh?
- Mm.
It's like,
how many different ways can shit stink?
It depends which area you're in.
If you're in the sewers under Chinatown,
there's a strange kind of seafood smell to it all.
- Whereas in Soho, you've got...
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. Stop right there.
This ain't the fucking Discovery Channel.
I only need to know the basics, man.
I'm just trying to educate you.
Trust me,
there's nothing I want to know about shit.
Now... this is the kind of thing
we're on the look for.
You see... if this ain't cleared,
the people upstairs are gonna be trading turds
through their kitchen sinks.
- What is it?
- It's shit.
Er... tampons, condoms -
pretty much anything that'll fit down a toilet.
And since you're the new boy...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, all right, all right.
I got it.
I swear to God, man...
if it wasn't for my little girl...
...I'd tell 'em to shove
the parole up their arse.
Mother... fucker!
What are you laughing at, man?
- I could catch the plague or something.
- You just might.
What was that?
- What was that?
- It's just echoes.
Echoes? From what?
The zoo?
Very funny.
So what did you get sent to prison for
in the first place?
What?
I said, what did you get sent down for.
A fucking travesty, that's what.
I mean, I get sent down for dealing weed
and that shit's legal now.
If I got busted now
for what I had on me then,
they would have thrown it down the drain
and not me.
Oh, you're a drug dealer.
The chap I had last week was a pimp.
- Now what?
- I don't know.
- What do you mean you don't know?
I haven't been down this tunnel for about a year,
but this wasn't here. I'd have reported it.
This is amazing.
Am I missing something here?
- I've got a new tunnel.
- So?
Well, so - I've been walking these tunnels
for 20 years and now I've got a new one.
Well, if that's what does it for you,
I'm scared.
Let's take a look.
I ain't going down there!
That shit's too deep.
- What's the matter with you?
- I can't swim.
And I don't share your interest
in pipes and tunnels.
All right. You... stay there.
Yeah. You go for it, Sherlock.
Arthur?
Are you OK, Arthur?
You better not be fucking with me.
Shit.
Arthur?
Oh, yeah.
OK, I get it, I get it.
Forgive me...
Arthur.
Arthur!
Arthur, mate.
Arthur.
What did you see?
# Madder
# This one day bam bam bam
# Bammer, bammer, bammer
# Don't make you feel like...
Have you seen Jemma?
# This one day bam bam bam...
Hey, Kate. How are you doing?
# Madder, madder, madder
# This one day bam, bam, bam
# Bammer, slammer, bammer
# This want to make you feel
# If I ever needed inspiration
# Right about here's where I lose my patience...
- Hi, Kate.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- Hey, boys.
- Have you seen Jemma?
- Yeah, yeah, I have.
She's in the back office.
Now, why did I have a feeling you would know?
Because you have a lot of feelings for me, Kate.
No, I have two. Pity and disgust.
I hope you remember that
when you're trying to score later.
What, I have to flirt with you to get a line?
Just a few compliments maybe.
- Guy, I'd rather sniff glue.
- Where are you going after this, Kate?
- Why, what are you doing?
- I haven't made up my mind yet.
Well, why don't you make a list of possibilities
so I know where to avoid?
- She'll be back.
- Yeah. Looks like you nailed that one, mate.
- Hey.
- That dress is amazing.
Where's the party and why aren't I invited?
- Jemma and I are on a secret mission tonight.
- Go on.
Two words. George Clooney.
What, he's in town?
Yep. And I know where he's hanging out tonight.
Are you gonna try to pull him?
Oh, my God, no. I'm just gonna ask
for his autograph! What do you think?
So, what are you gonna say?
I don't know. I haven't got that far with the plan.
But, you know what? In the end, he's a man.
Men are simple creatures.
Watch this. Guy.
See? So simple.
Karen, Kate's gonna shag George Clooney.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I know where he's hanging out tonight
and Jemma has tickets to the VIP lounge
- and hopefully nature's gonna run its course.
- But Jemma's already left.
- What are you talking about?
- I put her in a cab.
- Don't joke.
- I swear to God.
Kate, please - tell me you're still going.
Taxi!
Spare us some change, please.
This machine dispenses notes.
If you're looking for change,
why don't you hang round a phone box?
.. on the Northern Line,
between Charing Cross and Golders Green
and between Euston and East Finchley
in both directions.
It's exact money only. It's not giving change.
You'll have to go to the booth.
Er... do you have any change? I don't care
if it's the correct amount. I'm in a real rush.
No, I'm sorry. You'll have to go to the booth.
Are you enjoying this?
I just want to get to the machine.
- Excuse me, do you need a Travelcard?
- Yes, I do. How much?
- £1.50.
- I'll give you 20.
- Are you serious?
- Absolutely. 100%.
It's illegal to buy off tramps anyway.
Thanks very much.
# Ambient
Hello?
Hello? Hello?
Scheisse.
Hello?
Anybody in there?
Excuse me. I fell asleep on the platform.
Don't you check them before you lock up?
Huh?
I mean, it's a little weird to me.
There's nobody in charge here?
Excuse me, do you mind answering me?
You're starting to freak me out.
Well, fine. My boyfriend's up the front.
I'll just go get him.
Kate, it's me. It's Guy.
Guy? You scared me to death.
I'm sorry. I was just playing with you, that's all.
Hang on - what are you doing here?
What do you mean, what am I doing here?
This is what you wanted.
What?
Come on. You wanted me to come tonight.
What are you talking about?
You know exactly what I'm talking about.
Guy, you're mentally ill, do you know that?
Freak.
- Kate, where are you going?
- Out of here.
Good luck.
Now, what's that supposed to mean?
I think we might be here till morning, that's all.
No.
- You might, we won't.
- You could always look on the bright side.
How much of that have you had?
Not much. There's plenty left.
Want some?
No, I don't.
Hello?
Did you kill the driver?
I don't think any knight in shining armour's
going to come and rescue you, Kate.
Now, what say you take that dress off?
- What did you just say?
- Come on, you heard me
Yeah, I did hear you but I'm going to forget what
you said because you're not thinking straight.
I am thinking straight.
It's you that's confused, Kate.
Whoa, whoa! What are you doing?
I'm just breaking the ice.
Come on. Admit that you want my dick.
You're joking, right?
But you like it, don't you?
I don't know what to say.
Er...
it's like a penis, just smaller.
- What are you...
- Don't fuck with me.
- What are you doing?
- Ssh.
- Get off me!
- You fucking bitch!
Stop it! Get off!
Guy!
No! No! Arghh!
No!
Guy?
Run.
What?
Come on. No.
Hello! I'm trapped in here!
Hello!
Hello.
Oh.
I know you. Hi.
Oh, wait. Wait a second. Wait.
Wait.
Hello?
- Who's there?
- Jimmy, what's going on? Who is it?
- Turn the fucking light on.
- I'm sorry. I'm stuck down here.
- Who is it, Jim?
- I gave you £20 for the Travelcard, remember?
Do you want your money back or something?
Oh, no, no, no. I'm stuck down here.
I got locked in. Someone's chasing me.
She's fucked. You'll not get any sense out of
her. You'll be lucky to get any sense out of me.
Look, someone's been attacked, OK?
- What are you going on about?
- I got stuck on a train with this guy from work.
And he was attacking me.
- What, the guy from work?
- Yeah. He went crazy and he...
He was... he was trying to rape me and then
the train doors opened and someone got him.
What do you mean they got him?
Pulled him off me! And... I don't know...
Hey, hey, all right, all right. What's your name?
- Kate.
- Kate. All right, Kate.
Well, look, I'm Jimmy, right?
My wee beautiful wee lady here - this is Mandy.
- Have you got a cigarette?
- Yeah, but...
No, no, nay buts, all right.
Let's just have a cigarette, all right.
- Have a seat.
- OK. I'll have a seat.
OK.
First off, you can't get out of here at night.
- What?
- It's true.
Once you're in, you're in. It's totally locked up.
But... isn't there a guard?
There's one in the control room,
but we're not messing with him.
- What do you mean? Why not?
- Cos he don't mess with us.
There's a maniac out there.
Nah, you don't know that.
It sounds to me like some vigilante train driver's
got a wee bit carried away.
The way I see it, you should be thanking him
not running away.
No, no, no, no, no. You have no idea.
You didn't see what he did to Guy.
The rapist?
You got a fag, Jim?
I'm telling you...
something is not right down here.
There's a lot of things not right down here,
sweetheart.
Can I have a fag, Jim?
You've got one in your fingers, babe.
Now, if you don't mind... I want
to get good and messy with my wee lady here.
You're welcome to stay
if you'll not mind my habit.
So er... you're just gonna do nothing?
Well, I wouldn't say that.
Here, move.
That's sleeping bag's not as damp as it looks.
You can sit there.
All right. OK. I'm gonna pay you, all right?
I'm gonna pay you
if you get me to the control room. OK?
I've told you, we're not messing with him.
How much?
Er...
Fifty pounds?
Well... er...
You know...
I guess rules are made to be broken, eh?
Thank you.
Babe.
Mandy.
Gonna go and help the wee lady here.
- Who?
- I'm gonna help our friend Kate, here.
I'm gonna take her to see the guard.
Do you fancy her?
No, I fancy you.
So, what are you, French?
- No, I'm German.
German. I support Germany
when they're playing against England at football.
Come to think of it, I support anyone
playing against England at football.
- How much further to the guard?
- It's quite a way yet.
This place is a rabbit warren.
Do you know, there's 400 miles of track
down here? Plus loads more that ain't in use.
Really?
Aye, really.
Jim?
I think I might know
what happened to your friend.
What?
A while back,
some homeless people went missing.
- What do you mean "missing"?
- Disappearing.
There were rumours that something was
creeping up on them and taking them.
Are you joking?
Course I'm fucking joking. Homeless people
don't go missing. Homeless people are missing.
Jim?
Shit.
Ray!
Come here!
Ray, come here.
I've been trying to get me and Mandy in a hostel
cos the weather's getting cold.
But the housing man,
he's not been round for months.
But he cannae get in touch with me
on the phone cos I've not got a phone.
We were gonna stay at my mate Tommy's,
but he got busted, he got done for dealing.
OK, listen, sweetie.
I'm sorry, I really don't mean to be rude,
but... I don't care about your lifetime story
right now, OK?
We have to get to the security guard
as soon as possible.
You're a cheeky fucking bitch.
- Do you know that?
Kate.
Guy?
Oh, my God, it's Guy.
We're just gonna get help.
We'll be right back, OK?
What are you looking at me for?
I don't know.
- Can't we just get him off the rails?
- He tried to rape you.
- Let him rot.
Please... help me.
Fuck off.
OK, listen... listen.
Will another 50 do it, huh?
You're lucky she's a soft touch, you know.
If you tried to do that to my girl,
I'd cut your fucking balls off.
- Fucking hell.
- What is it?
All right, put your arms round my neck.
Fuck!
Jimmy, is that your dog?
Mandy.
Jimmy?
We should stay together!
Oh...
Guy.
Who did this to you?
I'm sorry, Kate. I'm sorry.
Mandy!
Where is she?
Fuck!
Guy, listen.
I'm gonna go and get Jimmy, OK?
And I'm gonna go and get the security guard
and then we'll get out of here, OK?
Just stay here. You'll be fine. You'll be fine.
Just stay awake and you'll be fine.
Kate...
You'll be fine.
You will.
Come on.
# Chamber piece
Hello?
- Hello?
- Who is that?
Hello. Are you the security guard?
I'm the security supervisor.
- Now, who are you?
- Um... well, I got locked in here and...
Look, you have to help me. Somebody's
really badly hurt down here and... he's dying.
Are you part of the homeless crowd?
What? No, no.
Well, yes, but no.
- Well, which is it?
- What difference does it make?
Call an ambulance!
Where is this person? I don't see him.
Where are you?
Is that you? Well, he's down here.
Well, you'll have to put him into view.
Are you kidding me?
Just call an ambulance for God's sake.
I'm not calling anyone until I've established
exactly what it is I'm dealing with here.
For all I know there could be
a gang of crackheads down there with you.
Do I look like a crackhead to you? Huh?
It's hard to tell. I'm watching you
on a black-and-white monitor in a long shot.
Listen, just call a fucking ambulance.
The guy's bleeding to death.
And as soon as you confirm that, I will.
- Asshole.
- I heard that.
Well, good.
I'm going to get him, OK?
OK, Guy. I'm sorry.
I'm gonna have to move you one more time.
You'll be fine, OK?
Guy? What are...
Guy?
OK, OK, OK.
Into shot... where the fucker can see you.
Look, asshole! Is this enough?
He's dead!
Now get me out of here!
OK, er... wait there.
Get off!
Go on, get out.
Shoo! Get away.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck.
Jimmy.
Jimmy. Where's Mandy?
Did he get Mandy?
The security guard's killed and Guy's dead.
We have to leave right now.
Jimmy.
No. No!
Listen. Can you hear me? Can you hear me?
I'll make it very simple for you, OK.
If... if I go through the next tunnel to the
next station, is there going to be another guard?
Huh?
Answer me, please.
Fuck you, I'll do it by myself.
Are you finished?
There's a torch over there.
You'll need a pair of boots.
Jimmy.
How far is it to the next station?
Huh?
Jimmy, how far is it?
Er... don't know.
What about the live track?
Er... you'll be all right
if you don't touch that one... that one...
W-wait. Which one?
Um...
- Don't touch any of them.
- Ah. OK.
Wait.
I was gonna take her home.
I was gonna take her back to Scotland
and get her off the gear.
I was gonna let my mam look after her.
But I didn't.
What was that? Jimmy, what was that?
A train.
- Don't joke.
- Don't joke on railway lines.
Come on then. Shit!
It's stopping. It's stopping!
- What if it's him?
- it'll just be a driver.
- We don't know that, do we?
- What are you on about?
They drive all night.
They stop if someone's on the line.
Kate, are you not listening?
The driver's gonna get us out of here.
I'm not listening cos you're not thinking straight.
You're fucked out of your head.
We have to assume it's him.
Maybe you're right, but we have to assume.
Look, there's a passageway back there. Let's go.
Do you think whoever's driving the train
killed Mandy?
I don't know,
but I really don't want to stay and find out.
- I think I do.
- No, come on.
Seriously. Come on!
You don't understand. I wanna meet him.
Don't be stupid. Come with me.
Look, if it's the driver, I'll call for you, all right?
If it's not... I won't.
No, I'm not leaving you here.
It's exactly what you're gonna do.
Take Ray and go.
Go!
OK, OK.
Fine. OK.
Here I am!
Where are you, you fucker?
Come on, you fuck!
Come on!
Fucking come on!
Mate. Mate.
Jimmy.
Jimmy!
Argh.
Hello?
Argh!
Get that thing away from me.
I ain't dead.
I thought you was dead when he brought you in.
Look... are you injured?
No... I don't think so.
Well, check yourself.
I think I'm all right.
What is this place?
The sewage system.
What's your name?
George.
George. Really?
What's so funny?
I... I was supposed to meet a George tonight.
This is not quite what I had in mind.
What was that?
- Huh?
- Ignore it.
What do you mean "ignore it"?
Has the girl been here? Huh?
I don't know.
- Oh, God!
- What? What?
There's something in here.
Something just touched my leg.
- What is it?
- Dunno.
It's just some blockage from the pipe.
How did it get in your cage?
How should I know?
Maybe it... floated underneath.
So?
Maybe the bars in between the cages
don't touch the floor.
So?
So maybe we can swim underneath...
...pull ourselves out... and get out.
You see, over there... there's an open cage.
Swim through, haul yourself out,
then open mine.
I can't.
Why?
- I can't swim.
- You don't need to swim.
- Just pull yourself under, OK?
- I can't do that either.
- Are you kidding?
- I can't hold my breath underwater.
Listen... you better learn now
cos if you don't, the only way
you're going to get out is if he pulls you out.
Sorry. This ain't no time for swimming lessons,
all right, lady?
Just one more cage. Go on.
Arghhh!
Argh!
Come on, come on.
Come on.
Here, take this.
What is this place?
Oh, no.
That's Mandy.
- You know her?
- Yeah.
- Do you think she's alive?
- What?
- Could you...
- No.
Can you please check if she's breathing?
- Look at her.
- Please. Please check.
Are you OK?
She's dead.
Come on, come on, come on.
Ssh, ssh.
- It's my fault!
- Listen, listen...
- I paid Jimmy to come with me.
- We've got to think about getting out of here.
He would have protected her.
She would not be dead.
Listen, I've got a daughter.
And I really wanna see her again.
All right? Ssh.
Listen... we're gonna get out.
OK?
Yeah? Come on.
Please.
Hang on. Give me the torch.
There's a tunnel behind this wall.
The bricks are loose. Give me a hand.
Fuck the bricks. Move, move, move.
Yeah.
OK, OK.
Hang on, it's all right. Hang on, hang on.
Quick!
Quick! Move, move!
Jimmy!
Jimmy.
No.
Please... no.
Please.
Please don't hurt me.
I'll do anything you want.
Please.
I'll do anything.
Please, no.
If you let me go, I won't tell anyone, I promise.
Please don't hurt me.
No
No.
Jimmy!
Jimmy.
No.
What was that?
Was Mandy still alive? Huh?
No. No, she wasn't.
Wait!
- Was she alive?
- No!
And I ain't going back there to find out!
What do you see?
- A dog... in a birdcage.
Ray.
Are you OK? Come on.
Look at this.
What was that?
Where are you? Hey!
Where?
Where are you, man? Come on!
- Show yourself!
- Stop it, George!
- Stop it!
- I can't take this shit no more.
Calm down, calm down.
- What are you doing?
- Where are you hiding?
- Come on! Get the fuck out of there!
- No! George!
Fuck.
I can't take this shit no more, man.
You know what?
I'd say let's get the fuck out of here.
All right. OK.
Can't take this shit any more.
Ain't so clever now, are you, motherfucker?
Wait, wait, wait.
You stand aside, I'll get him with this. I'll kill him.
Please.
Please don't... hurt... me.
I'll do... anything... you... want.
Kill it, Kate!
If you let me go, I won't tell anyone, I promise.
Jimmy.
Argh!
Argh.
Craig.
Is that your fucking name?
Craig. Craig.
Craig.
No!