Created and Encoded by --  Bokutox -- of  www.YIFY-TORRENTS.com. The Best 720p/1080p/3d movies with the lowest file size on the internet. World of Warcraft - Outland PVP (EU) - Torporr (name)
He came back again last night
and tore me like paper.
He opened me like a flower of pain...
...and it felt good.
He sank into me and set me on fire...
...like he always does.
Made me burn from the inside out.
How did you know it was the devil?
I know what you're thinking.
I know you think
I'm talking about my stepfather...
...because you don't believe
in the devil.
Okay, let's talk about your stepfather.
You know about my stepfather.
You know I cut his throat.
I cut his Adam's apple in half...
...like a piece of fruit
on a summer day...
...so he wouldn't say a word.
I sat next to him
and watched him die...
...slowly.
It was the only way to help him stop.
Stop what?
Stop fucking me!
You're not listening.
I am listening, Chloe.
You're not listening with your heart.
Just your brain.
Your brain is the problem.
You have no idea
how it feels not to be trusted.
You've got to trust me too, Chloe.
You can't trust someone
who thinks you're crazy.
Okay. I think that's enough for today.
But I do think we made
some really good headway...
...found out some new things--
Do you know what it is
to burn from the inside?
-Do you know? Because you are dead!
-Let her go, Chloe.
I am. I'm not touching her!
I'm not touching her! Let me go!
Let me go! Let me go.
Thank you.
You're driving me crazy! Stop!
-Stop it!
-Let go!
Stop it!
I can walk by myself!
Stand up!
Look at that.
"I'm a doctor."
"Open this door."
Hey, you are dead!
Get in.
She's nuts.
Hey.
Sorry.
I need to cross-reference some files
with you on Monday.
How's your morning?
-Check with Anna. She'll fit you in.
-Thanks. Sorry.
I'm not discharging her, period.
If you want to pursue this, sir,
have a judge order her transfer.
Until then she's mine.
Thank you.
Lawyers.
Hey, come on in.
What's up?
Chloe. She's embellishing
her rape story again.
She says that the devil
is visiting her in her cell.
-Okay.
-It's the third time in three months.
It has something to do with
her stepfather, possibly remorse...
...but instead of assessing
the memory and accepting it...
...she just falls into these
satanic meanderings.
Time. Give it time.
I've given it time. Time and Elavil.
And Mellaril and Haldol.
Maybe they're just...
...too medicated.
I know we all create our realities
to some extent. Yes, true.
But what she creates
is so far from any objective reality....
Chloe's mind only runs on one track.
Well, right now,
my mind is running on empty.
Come here.
You have a brilliant mind.
You'll figure it out.
Throw it on the mirror.
This is what she sees now.
-A distorted image of herself.
-Who are you in all this?
-I'm the mirror.
-You are the mirror.
If I'm the mirror and she's the image...
...then who are you?
I can see both of you...
...so I'm God.
Or just an overworked
hospital bureaucrat.
"God" is good.
Always remember,
the ability to repress...
...is actually a vital survival tool.
Without it...
...Chloe might not have survived.
Sorry, am I interrupting
the happy couple?
Dr. Graham. We were just discussing
repression as a survival mechanism.
Oh, yeah, I had a date last week.
I barely survived it.
I'm trying to forget it.
I'm sure your amorous adventures
are fascinating, doctor...
...but sadly, I'm on my way out.
-Well, don't let me-- I'll just--
-No, no, no, I'm leaving.
I'm gonna run out to Willow Creek.
Meet the new contractor.
I'll be here. See you at dinner.
Keep an eye on my wife for me, Pete.
I know you will. Here.
-No, thanks.
-No, let me circumcise it for you.
Smoke it tonight while it's fresh.
-Good night, boss.
-Good night, kids.
Why don't we share one of those
golden-crust, cheese-filled specials.
-It sounds like a great offer...
-Here's the file.
-...but I got work to do.
-I'm buying.
-It's cold when it gets here.
-We could warm it up.
-I hate pizza.
-Who doesn't like pizza?
Come on, you gotta eat.
Not with you.
Come on, we're supposed to celebrate.
I just got circumcised....
-Who's inside?
-We have Shelley for observation.
-Why? What happened?
-She had another attack.
-What'd you do, up her meds?
-Yeah, 25 milligrams.
That's extreme.
That dose is way too high.
I want a copy of that on my desk
by Monday, okay?
-Okay.
-Thank you.
Damn generator.
Not again.
Irene, is that you?
This electric system's
gonna give us trouble.
Fourth time this week.
I'm going for my swim.
Well, I'm gonna do my job,
as long as these damn lights stay on.
-Good night, Joe.
-Hey, how many laps, doc?
Fifty-five, but who's counting?
Oh, you've outdone yourself.
Hey, safe drive home.
-Thank you. Say hi to your wife for me.
-Will do.
All that education
but you can't remember an umbrella.
-Did you get my note?
-I got your note. Your business note.
Right. So how was your date with...?
With what's-her-name? It was like all of
my dates. It was brief. It was pointless.
She didn't respond to my sense
of humour, my boyish good looks...
...so I started talking about work.
She said that was not
a suitable topic for a first date...
...and that was it.
I mean, it was just drinks, you know.
I mean, we didn't even have dinner.
She's not right.
When you know, you know.
I know.
-I'll follow you down the hill.
-You don't have to.
-I'm supposed to keep an eye on you.
-Since when did you listen to the boss?
Severe showers all over northern
Connecticut and New Hampshire.
-I know, I see that.
--rain in Lennox County....
--flooding throughout
Lennox County and closure....
-I can't let you through. Road's closed.
-What's going on?
-I got this.
-There's a sinkhole.
-Hi, Bob.
-You picked a hell of a night for a drive.
There's a sinkhole up here,
you can't get through. Sorry.
-What should I do?
-Go a quarter of a mile, take a left--
You know that bridge
that Doug and I fish at?
-Yeah, the little white one?
-That's the one.
-Yeah.
-You can go across there.
-Okay, thanks.
-Hey, tell Doug to give me a call.
Will do.
-Doug, you're home?
-Yeah, where are you?
I got detoured, so I'll be home in a few
minutes, okay? How was Willow Creek?
This rain is slowing the work down.
It's a big mess.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
Doug.
Doug!
Are you okay?
Hey!
Oh, my God. Okay. Okay. Okay.
I'm a doctor. I'm gonna take you
to the hospital. I'm a doctor, honey.
I'm gonna help you, okay?
You're gonna be okay.
Help me!
Somebody!
Dr. Graham!
You better tell me
why I'm in here, Irene.
She got up wild.
-Bring your ass back in here.
-Give me 40 milligrams of Ativan.
-Get your hands off me.
-Stay in the cell.
-Keep her off.
-Restrain her.
Keep her off of me. Get off of me.
Do you hear me? Get off of me.
Hold on. Calm--
What are you doing?
What are you doing to me?
Thank you, nurse.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah, she calmed down.
This is so sad.
Miranda, this is very awkward.
I suppose that technically
I shouldn't even be treating you...
...but I managed to get the court
to grant us a waiver...
...until you're transferred.
Anything we discuss
is in strict confidence...
...and won't go anywhere but this room.
How long have I been in here?
Three days.
Why? Why?
You were admitted to our neurosurgical
unit, you were seizing violently.
We did scans and they revealed
left-sided weakness, numbness...
...severe frontal-lobe deficits.
You received Haloperidol,
Ativan injections.
When you came out of it, we tested.
You were negative for PCP.
You were put in restraints for a day and
a half so you wouldn't injure yourself.
And then you basically
went into a state of catatonia.
This is the first time
I've seen you lucid.
I wanna talk to my husband.
Where is he? Where is he?
You know, you're the most
logical person I know, bar none.
You rely only on the facts.
So why am I telling you this?
You're establishing my personality.
You think I'm a rational person. You
don't think I'm impulsive or emotional.
And following this pattern of analysis,
we are about to discuss...
...a traumatic event which has rendered
this psychological profile useless.
-You think I'm in denial.
-Don't analyse yourself...
...just focus on remembering.
Miranda...
...what's the last thing you remember?
I remember Chloe.
I was having my Friday night
session with Chloe.
How did that go?
She was embellishing her rape story.
-I saw Doug.
-Dr. Graham.
You were there.
When I went back to my office,
I worked on Chloe's file.
I decided to call it quits, I went down
to the pool, had a swim, 55 laps...
...saw Joe, got my keys.
Went to my car. You walked me to it.
-Yes.
-But--
-There was a detour.
-Oh, hey, tell Doug....
I had to go over the bridge,
so I went over the bridge.
I wonder what else happened.
Try to remember.
I got home.
I saw Doug. He was on the couch.
Try to remember.
There was a girl.
-Yeah, there was a girl.
-No, there was no--
Yeah, there was a girl.
-A girl at the bridge.
-There was no report--
-There was some kind of accident.
-No.
-The girl was bloody. On the bridge....
-I want to ask you about Doug.
What's the last thing you remember?
Why are you asking about Doug?
I'm telling you about a girl I saw.
Was there any trouble
in your marriage?
No, there was no trouble
in my marriage.
And why are you using
the past tense of the word?
Miranda...
...you don't remember anything
about Doug? Anything at all?
Don't tell me something's
wrong with Doug.
I have to tell you something.
Something very difficult.
No, no, no....
-Don't tell me something's with Doug.
-Miranda...
...Doug is dead.
You killed him.
-No! No! No!
-Orderly!
I didn't.
-No, I didn't.
-Orderly!
I didn't! I didn't do it! No!
No! No! No, don't do it!
-It's okay.
-I didn't do it. I didn't do it.
I'm on your side.
One little bit more.
Rita. Let go.
It's Dr. Grey.
Look it up. Don't look at me like that.
I'm the official champion again.
Hello, Miranda. Welcome.
You're one of us now.
You know I don't belong here, Chloe.
If you're here,
it must mean that you belong.
You are not a doctor in here.
And even if you tell the truth...
...no one will listen.
You know why? Because you're crazy.
And the more you try
to prove them wrong...
...the crazier you appear.
You are invisible now.
Can you feel it?
Don't touch me.
Are you scared?
No.
You should be.
I'm dreaming.
Dream logic, primary process,
that's what this is.
I'm dreaming.
I'm dreaming. I'm dreaming.
I'm not crazy. I'm dreaming.
Rise and shine, honey. It's a new day.
I wanna talk to Pete.
You'll see Dr. Graham all in good time,
but I want you to have some breakfast.
-Why are you doing this to me, Irene?
-I'm just doing my job.
You don't want me to get Jim
to help me, now do you?
Good girl. You're doing good.
Come on, sweetheart,
now it's time for a shower.
Come on, honey,
time to wash away your sins.
You're a nut.
Yeah, it's you. You.
Get away. Get away.
What's your problem?
I looked away for a second.
It's unacceptable.
It's not your fault.
Patients always find a way to hurt
themselves, if that's what they want.
I never pegged her for a cutter,
that's all.
Neither did I.
Shelley says Chloe's
been threatening Miranda...
...so I put her in isolation for the day.
How is she?
She's a mess.
I can't believe she's lost it so quickly.
I've never seen that before.
She cut herself 35 times,
a lot of blood, but it's superficial.
-What was the implement?
-Probably a scalpel...
...though how anybody
got it in there, I have no idea.
Hey, Tony. We're fine.
Come on.
You think I did this
to myself, don't you?
Did you?
No.
Well, I don't know.
Who would it be, then? Would it be...
...Chloe, or...?
I don't know.
By your own admission
you have difficulty...
...distinguishing what's reality
from fantasy, so is it possible?
Yeah, as a doctor,
I understand why you think that.
But something
is really happening to me.
What about this moment, right now?
What about it?
Is this a hallucination?
Is it?
I suggest that we simply
increase the medication...
...until things make sense.
Or maybe until I can get myself
a new doctor.
Pardon?
Since I'm hallucinating
and I can't seem to remember things...
...you can help me with something.
Yeah. Inhale.
Did we have an affair?
No.
Did you want to?
Yes.
Did you think I wanted to?
Then why didn't we?
Because you were married to the boss.
But I'm not now.
I'm here-- I'm....
I'm trying to help you.
Why don't you trust me?
Because you can't trust somebody
when they think you're crazy.
Phil.
Hello, Miranda.
I need to talk to you for a minute.
This is about Pete.
What about him, Miranda?
I don't think he's the best doctor
to be treating me.
Is your complaint about him
on a personal level?
Pete's the best doctor
I have on my staff now.
And he has my full support.
Now, if you'll excuse me, Miranda.
-Miranda.
-Hi, Teddy.
-How are they treating you?
-Like I'm crazy, Teddy.
-They think I did it, but I didn't do it.
-All right. Thank you.
-I didn't do it, Teddy.
-Have a seat.
Let's not....
Let's not talk about what you did
or didn't do, all right?
What's important is what
I can do for you now.
Now, the DA is pushing for a hearing
as early as next week.
Next week? We haven't even
had time to investigate.
We can't have a hearing next week.
As your attorney, I gotta tell you
the evidence is overwhelming.
You've been placed at the scene.
The sheriff saw you driving home.
The neighbours heard the screams.
They've got the murder weapon
with your prints on it.
Your prints are on the floor,
walls, everything.
Yeah, but what's my motive?
I don't have a motive, Teddy.
Why would I do that?
Maybe one of his ex-patients came.
Has anybody checked the files?
Has anybody escaped?
That person would have a motive.
I was there, and I would scream.
-Maybe I went into shock.
-Miranda.
The only shot we have
is to plead temporary insanity.
I don't even know if that's gonna work.
You're a brilliant psychiatrist.
That will make jurors think
"If she wanted to kill somebody...
...she could probably fake insanity
and get away with it."
I'm not crazy.
-That's the point.
-No, the point is...
...I'm the only one around here
that believes I didn't kill my husband!
Do you think I'm crazy?
That's all right. Forget it.
Forget it.
Sheriff Ryan is here.
He'd like to talk to you.
You know he was Doug's best friend,
so I'd advise against it.
It's fine, Teddy.
I don't have anything to hide.
Five minutes.
Hi, Bob.
Miranda.
I just have a few questions
that we need to clear up.
When you first came in
and he was sitting on the couch...
...the way we reconstruct the crime...
...is the first blow came
from in front of him.
Which means he must have
seen it coming.
And what we don't understand is
how he....
-Why did you do it?
-Sheriff.
How could you kill Doug like that?
He loved you.
-That's the question I need answered.
-You don't have to answer.
I don't have any answers
to the questions, Bob.
You don't?
You better start thinking...
...of some answers,
because you're in some trouble.
-Sheriff, that's enough. That's enough!
-No, no, no.
I need her to tell me why she did it.
Okay, we're done. Enough!
Let's kill your friend, see how you feel!
-You said no shock treatment.
-Here's some shock treatment!
-Stop it. Why would you take these out?
-Don't look.
Don't look at them.
I had to pick him up
off the floor, Miranda. In pieces!
Miranda, what's that?
It's okay. It's okay, Miranda.
-Why are you doing this to me?
-Miranda, let's just go. We're done.
-It's okay.
Why are you doing this to me?
Why are you doing this to me?!
Come in, Miranda.
Please, take a seat.
So....
You wanted to see me.
I was there.
I was there when Doug was killed.
But I wasn't alone.
I wasn't there alone,
and that's what "not alone" means.
-Who was there with you?
-I don't know who it was.
I don't know. I don't know who it was.
But somebody else was there.
Miranda.
We know you have no family left.
We are your family now.
I know. I know you....
I know.
I want you to know that we're gonna
do everything we possibly can...
...to help you
and to make you feel secure.
And to make you feel
that you can trust us here.
But there's a hearing scheduled.
-Miranda. Sit down.
-Just-- Come on, sit down.
Miranda.
Who is this girl?
-Put the picture back.
-Who is this girl?
That's my daughter, Rachel.
No, this is the girl I saw at the bridge.
This is the girl.
-No.
-How is she? Where is she?
-It's impossible.
-This is the girl I've been seeing.
This girl, right here.
She's dead.
Rachel died four years ago.
I'm a rational person.
I believe in science.
I don't believe in the paranormal.
And I don't believe in ghosts.
But if you are the ghost
of Rachel Parsons...
...then you would let me out of this cell.
Bob, you leave this?
Shit. Pete's office.
Chloe.
Chloe!
Help me!
Let me go! Let me go!
Check Chloe! Check Chloe!
She needs help!
-Did you talk to Chloe?
-Yes.
-Was she raped?
-Was she raped? No.
-Why?
-Did you check her?
Did I--? She was checked.
Of course she was checked.
-He didn't have time.
-He?
-What about her face? She had a cut.
-Ran into a wall. She did that to herself.
I saw a tattoo.
Did she talk about a tattoo?
-Why don't you sit down. A tattoo?
-Yeah, a tattoo.
A woman in flames, hands up like this:
Like a Biblical image.
The Anima Sola?
-The Anima Sola. That's what I saw.
-It's a common archetypal image.
I mean, it's the woman in chains,
awaiting her fate.
I'm talking about something I saw
on the chest of a man.
-That's what I saw.
-You're in crisis.
This image is tailor-made
for your state of mind.
A woman in purgatory.
I need you to explain this
to me, though.
-Rachel did not commit suicide.
-She jumped off a bridge.
-When I saw her--
-She was washed downstream 5 miles.
-She was cut up.
-You saw her?
-I saw her. Someone did that to her!
-Police, newspapers, coroner wrong?
-Let's reopen the case.
-Maybe they should!
-I saw her. And she's connected to me.
-Delusions, hallucinations...
-How, I don't know.
-...disorganized speech, incoherence--
Don't rattle off your psychiatric shit!
I know it like the back of my hand!
Good.
Saves me the trouble.
Glass cells
are having electrical problems.
I'm gonna transfer you
to a Psych Ward cell.
One strike, you're going to solitary.
Don't screw up.
Rachel Parsons was there.
Dead or alive, I don't know.
That girl came to me.
She came to me.
Hi, Chloe.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I didn't believe you.
I need you to tell me
who did this to you.
Tell me his name, Chloe.
Chloe, tell me.
Tell me anything. Tell me.
I'll tell you one thing:
He can have my body...
...but he will never have my soul.
Never.
The devil.
It's okay.
He said you're next.
-Try to stay awake.
-Yes, ma'am.
If you need me,
I'll be in the coffee room.
Lights out.
Leave me alone!
-Doesn't even look like a real ant.
-It's got disco balls for eyes.
-'50s B movies, man.
-Giant bug movies are great.
Hey, what is that?
It's Dr. Grey.
She's trying to kill herself.
Level C, we've got suicidal behaviour
in cell 33. Sending backup.
Open it!
Dr. Grey's in trouble!
Number 33, open it now!
Oh, damn.
Damn, what a mess.
-Hold her, I'll medicate her.
-What the hell for? She's already out.
Don't argue with me.
Jesus! Easy, easy.
No, don't hurt me.
Stop her! She's got my keys, stop her!
Shit!
Hey! Hey!
Wait! Hey!
We got a runner! Inmate escaping!
Block Three!
-Stay with me.
-All right.
She's gone this way. Let's go!
Clear!
Split up! Keep moving!
She's going up the North Tower!
Shit!
Hey! It's already open!
She's on the upper level!
Hold it right there!
-Dr. Grey!
-We're on Three, she's heading for One!
Go! Go!
Go the other way!
Circle back.
Come on, Hank.
Don't think she made it
to this building anyway.
Yeah, but even so,
there's no way she can get out.
Hide-and-seek. The longer it lasts,
the more overtime we make.
-You should be a professor.
-Professors nail the pretty students.
Let's go. I don't think she's in here.
I got it.
Is it clear there?
We checked corridors Four and Five.
-We're headed to Six and Seven.
-Yeah. It's Joe, up at the desk.
-What's going on down there?
-Looks dark down there.
What do you mean, what do I mean?
Look, this is the fourth time this month
this has happened. Never mind.
-Ye-- Thank you.
-Finally.
-Took long enough.
-Shit.
Hey, Joe.
You see something?
Yeah, just now
when the monitors came on.
Corridor Six, something flashed
in front of the camera.
Frank, East Wing. Don, take the West.
I'll take the stairs.
Here, take my car.
Go. Go.
Go on.
What do you want from me?!
Okay. Now what?
Miranda, no!
Doug?
No. No, Miranda, no.
Miranda, don't! No, don't, please!
Please! No! Miranda, no!
No, please!
Please! Don't do this to me! No!
Don't! No! Miranda, no, wait!
Don't do this to me, please, Miranda!
Miranda, no! Don't! No!
Don't do this to me, Miranda!
Miranda, please!
I love you.
What did I do?
Why?
Why me?
Why? Why?
Willow Creek.
How was Willow Creek?
This rain is slowing the work down.
It's a big damn mess.
I'll see you in a couple of days.
It's good to be God.
I love you.
-Drop the knife!
-Drop the gun!
Put it on the ground now!
-Drop the knife!
-You drop it!
-Holy Christ.
What?
Help me, please!
Help!
Carter, get down here now!
Help me, please!
Please!
All I can tell you is that the girl
has been identified as Tracy Seavers.
She was reported missing
two weeks ago.
She was found this morning
by two patrolmen in Willow Creek...
...at a farm belonging to Dr. Douglas
Grey. She is now hospitalised.
Can she speak?
Has she told you anything?
-We can't comment on that.
-Are there others?
We can't confirm that. Excuse me.
Sheriff, is the FBI taking over
this investigation?
Why don't you ask the goddamn FBI?
We need her at the hospital
for medication.
Consider house arrest pending trial,
given the circumstances.
Last night,
your client dropped a guard...
...assaulted a nurse, escaped from
an institution, stole a car--
And saved a girl's life.
-How did she know she was there?
-I don't know.
-But the point is--
-The woman is still a murder suspect!
Come here.
The FBI says there could be
more victims.
There were needles down there,
a video camera.
Once the press gets ahold of it,
it'll get big and ugly.
Now, I need some answers,
and I'm running out of time.
So your client isn't going anywhere
until my team....
I need to talk to her.
It's hard to believe
Doug did something like this.
We worked together a long time.
I thought I knew him pretty well.
How could I be so blind?
Well, you weren't the only one, Phil.
Do you think my daughter could
also have been a victim of Doug's?
Yes.
That's what "not alone" means.
Rachel was trying to tell me that
she was not Doug's only victim.
And all this time...
...we thought our baby
had committed suicide.
You see...
...even after she was gone....
Well....
What?
I had this recurring dream about her.
Eventually I took medication
to block it out.
What kind of dream?
She was burning in flames,
in terrible pain.
I couldn't save her.
I saw her exactly the same way,
burning in flames.
What does that mean?
Miranda, I-- I....
I wouldn't look for
a real-world explanation.
It's a dream, a delusion.
A delusion that we both seem to share.
-Yeah.
-Pete.
I was just talking to Parsons.
I've been wrong about
everything until now.
It's finally clear to me.
The image is finally clear.
The man raping women in prison
is connected to the murders.
It goes back to the Anima Sola tattoo.
Miranda, you have to stop doing this.
Do you understand me?
Every time people start taking you
seriously, you talk about delusions.
I'm not deluded, Pete, I'm possessed.
I don't believe in ghosts.
Neither do I, but they believe in me.
Great, just great.
Let's go. Come on.
I need to talk to Sheriff Ryan.
He's working with the FBI team.
He won't be back tonight.
It's really important.
I'll leave him a message.
Thank you.
Screw it.
I got a message
you wanted to talk to me?
Yeah, Bob.
I wanna talk to you. Maybe this time
you can actually hear me.
The last time, all you wanted to do was
scream and yell and accuse me--
-Is this what you wanna talk about?
-No. I wanna talk about the facts.
They're a little different now, right?
Do you know what happens
to a small-town sheriff...
...when the FBI takes over?
-If you know anything, anything--
-Not alone.
What?
Not alone.
I know what it means.
There are two killers.
Parsons and I both saw a girl
burning in flames.
Then I saw Chloe being raped by a man
with an Anima Sola tattoo on his body.
A woman burning in flames. Get it?
Okay, it's crazy. I know it sounds
crazy. Pete has told me it's crazy.
-You told Pete? When?
-Yes.
Yes.
This afternoon. Why?
I don't think you're crazy at all.
I don't know why he would dismiss it.
-You actually saw this tattoo?
-Yes, I saw it. On a man.
I've heard of serial killers
who hunt together.
Classic mentor and disciple syndrome.
So we're looking for the disciple?
Who could it be?
-I don't know.
-You're a psychiatrist.
What kind of guy
would this have to be?
Okay.
He would have to be someone
who grew up in a household...
...that had an absent father.
He developed...
...an obsessive, over-dependent
relationship with his mother...
...which then turned into some
inappropriate sexual attraction.
He probably even got off
torturing little animals as a kid.
And as a man he is totally confused
about his sexuality.
That's who he is.
Man, that's screwed up.
But a guy like that could seem
smart and normal, right?
Yeah, they usually do. Yeah.
Look, Miranda,
I don't wanna scare you...
...but if there is a second killer
out there...
...he is frantically trying
to cover his trail.
You're a big threat to this guy.
Who knows how much more you know?
I don't know anything else.
You saw the tattoo,
found the girl at the barn.
Yeah, but I found all that by instinct.
This guy is facing the electric chair.
He doesn't have the luxury
of believing in instinct or ghosts.
He's gotta believe that Doug
confessed to you what he was doing.
But he didn't confess.
Maybe he didn't spill it out loud, but....
Well, you know, you're a psychiatrist.
There's a lot of ways to confess.
I'm just trying to put myself
in this guy's place.
Then why didn't he go back
to Willow Creek?
-Take care of the girl, clean up?
-Yeah.
Well, that's how you get caught.
You panic.
Better to let the dust settle.
But about you...
-...he's desperate.
-Yeah?
Desperate enough to...
...talk to me?
Well, you're right.
I do fit the profile.
Long-time friend of Doug's,
access to the prison.
I never did get a kick out of
torturing animals, though.
Stop it!
-No!
-Yes!
-You can't kill me!
-I'm not gonna kill you.
After this kicks in, I'm gonna have a lot
more fun with you than Doug ever did.
Help!
Miranda!
Damn it!
Help me! Help!
Help me!
Okay.
You tried to escape, Miranda.
That means I can do
whatever I want to you.
Rachel wasn't the first, you know.
Doug killed a girl when he was
15 years old!
I helped him bury the body.
What are best friends for?
We got older. But I gotta tell you...
...you never lose your taste
for the young girls.
Then we stopped for a long time.
But then Dougie
saw sweet Rachel and....
That was an itch way too deep
not to scratch.
And then we had the time of our lives
out at Willow Creek.
Everything was perfect.
Those girls would do anything.
We were their god.
Until you--
Miranda!
You and I both know
you're not getting out of here.
So let's be logical...
...and end this thing.
Thank you, Miranda.
Rachel?
This isn't logical.
You're already dead!
Logic is overrated.
I'm sorry, Miranda.
So it's been almost a year
and I still have bad dreams.
Sometimes I wake up screaming.
That's normal.
No, not these dreams.
Everyone thought
you and I were crazy...
...but we were seeing the truth.
More than they could see.
Once you open the door,
you can never close it.
Not true. I closed it.
Then I locked it...
...and then I threw away the key.
I really hope that's true.
You know, my train leaves
in half an hour.
Okay. I'll get you on your way.
So good luck with your job, okay?
I wanted to thank you for what you did.
You really helped me.
You helped me.
You taught me how to listen.
Thank you.
We made it.
No!