Cigarette.
Light.
We're almost
at my parents' house, sleepyhead.
l don't believe the dream l just had.
l was in a forest, running barefoot.
l was hurt, and l was being followed
by somebody, and....
Well, the more l ran,
the more l could sense him coming closer.
Who was the guy stalking you?
lt wasn't a guy. lt was me.
That's the weirdest part.
-lt was me running after me.
-Don't you ever have normal dreams?
No.
Being like everyone else is a bore.
We shouldn't have partied so much.
l feel shitty.
Take a rest. l'll wake you when we get there.
-Real funny.
-l'll drive if you like.
-Like last Friday?
-Oh, come on, it was late, and l was tired.
-Tired? More like wasted.
-Well, it was your fault for dumping me...
for three hours
and disappearing with God knows who.
l hope, at least, that he was worth it.
He was unbelievable.
What a slut!
-Asshole!
-Bimbo!
-Bitch!
-Skank!
You're a pig.
Are there any cool places to go out
here in the country?
l'm afraid the town hall
is about the only place.
Wow, if l had to live here all year round,
l think l'd shoot myself.
Well, it's just a different lifestyle.
Besides, remember...
we're here to study, not to party.
-We are not deaf, huh?
-Chill out, Marie.
Come on, Hendrix. Come on. Come on.
l'm gonna get you.
l'll get you, Hendrix.
Tom, stop shouting. Go inside.
You're giving me a headache.
l'm just waiting for Alex to get here.
She'll be here by the time
you take your bath.
No, l can't. Alex hasn't seen the cowboy.
All right, go inside, take your bath,
then put the cowboy suit on again.
Come on, Hendrix.
Come on. Let's go.
Eyes on the road.
You've still got some sarcasm, you know.
Are you sure it's this way?
Of course. Just up ahead.
You turn right at the cornfield.
Oh, look, look. There it is. Turn right.
Now you go straight for about 4 kilometers.
-Wow, easy to get lost.
-Nobody uses this road except for tractors.
Four kilometers of this,
and it's goodbye, car.
You can't act that way
every time a guy tries to talk to you.
-l don't act that way with everyone.
-Come on, Marie, it's always the same story.
And you know it.
-Stop!
-What's wrong?
l think l saw someone.
That's not funny, Alex.
l'm not kidding.
l saw someone in the cornfield.
Stop screwing around like that, will you?
Alex, come back, please.
Alex!
Shit.
Alex.
lf this is a joke, l'll make you regret it.
Alex, where are you?
Alex?
Where are you?
l'll get you for this, damn it!
Alex, cut it out.
Alex?
Alex!
Stop, bitch. Come back.
Come back!
Come on, l am sick of your little game.
Damn you. Enough is enough.
-l could have left you out here, you know.
-Yeah, very funny.
-You scared the hell out of me.
-No.
Go on, laugh your head off. Very funny.
Marie, remember,
my family just moved here six months ago.
Their French is worse than mine.
Here we are.
All right.
l see why you passed your exams so easily.
You spend all your time here. There is
not too much else to do except study.
That's right. The only real excitement
around here is when a train runs through.
Take it easy, Hendrix.
Easy, boy.
-Hi.
-Hello, Dad.
How are you?
-Don't worry, he doesn't bite.
-Are you talking about me or the dog?
Marie, this is my pop. Pop, Marie.
Nice to meet you.
So nice to see a person
and not just a photo of you.
-Photo?
-You know, the one l took in Spain.
-lt's on the fireplace.
-You're part of the furniture.
And this is Tom. Hello, cowboy.
-Aren't you happy to see me?
-Of course he's happy.
He insisted on waiting up all night for you.
And your mother has been worrying
the whole day, of course.
Mom always worries for nothing.
-l think she left you something in the oven.
-l told her she didn't have to do that.
Well, she wasn't sure
if you were gonna have time to eat.
Oh, Mother.
l'll put Tom Thumb to bed,
and l'll show Marie her room.
Right. All right, then.
l still have some work to do.
Good night, girls.
-Good night, Pop.
-Good night, sir.
Sweet dreams.
-So, what was this place before?
-lt was an old farm that my father renovated.
There're lots of them in the area.
Most of them are in ruins.
lt's too bad.
They've lived here half a year now.
Did they have any problems with neighbors?
You mean the rednecks? Yeah.
They first thought my parents were hippies
here to make goat cheese...
but things are fine now.
Well, here's my room. Yeah?
Okay, follow me.
My parents' room is on the right.
This is Tom's room.
You're upstairs in the guest room, okay?
l'm just going to put him to bed.
Okay, all tucked in.
Nighty-night.
ls that you, Alex?
My mother. l'll meet you upstairs.
-Hi, Mom.
-ls your friend all settled in?
-Show her where the blankets are.
-Okay.
-Clean towels are in the closet.
-Don't worry.
Your very own bathroom, huh?
The heater's electric. Do you want it on?
-No, l can do it if l get cold.
-Well, then...
-what do you think?
-lt's like a doll's house, very pretty.
The problem is, he's got a girlfriend
he doesn't want to split up with.
-Why are you so interested, then?
-Someone who's taken must be worth it.
l'm skeptical of single guys.
-Here. Finished?
-Thanks.
l think it's too easy to be a womanizer
when you're already taken.
Could be right, l guess.
Maybe he doesn't even like me.
-What's his girlfriend like?
-She's Brazilian.
They've been together three months.
A Brazilian?
What, is he into exoticism or something?
Whatever. l need to get a tan, quick.
And l gotta work on my ass.
l tell you, that girl is built.
lf you do salsa, l'll go with you.
Go easy on them, all right?
Or they'll be up all night, chirping.
And you, Marie?
-Are you going to finally take the plunge?
-Don't start with that.
-You're gonna end up alone.
-l'm not a slut like you.
-You're so scared.
-Well...
l'm gonna have a smoke outside.
How about you?
l'm beat. l'm going to bed.
Don't be too long.
-l'll wake you at 9:00.
-What's the game plan?
-l was thinking international law to start.
-Okay.
-Good night, Alex.
-Good night.
Hey, Alex?
l'm glad that l finally met your family.
Come on, Hendrix. Let's go.
Good night, Hendrix.
l'm coming.
Quiet, Hendrix.
Who is it?
-What's going on, Mommy?
-Nothing much. Now go to sleep.
But what's that noise?
Tom, did you hear what l said?
l told you to go to sleep.
Daniel?
Dan?
Shit, the TV plug!
l can't believe it.
Why me?
Oh, shit!
Alex?
Alex!
Hold on.
lt won't come off.
Wait.
Mommy! Mommy!
Mommy!
Try to calm down, Alex.
lf he wanted to kill you,
he'd have already have done it.
Now listen to me, Alex. Listen. Listen to me.
Listen to me, for Christ's sake.
Tell me where l can find a telephone.
ln the kitchen?
Answer me, Alex. Look, l need your help.
l can't do anything alone. l need you.
l'll be back.
l'll be back, Alex. l swear.
He couldn't know
anyone else is in the house. Okay?
l don't believe it.
The phone's been cut.
l'm gonna get you out of here. l promise.
You have to stay quiet, Alex.
You might have a chance to get away.
Come on.
Alex.
Alex, we're gonna get out of this,
l promise you.
Even if we have to fight our way out,
we're gonna make it.
Listen, Alex, those other girls were alone,
but there are two of us.
lt's gonna work. lt's got to.
Just a little more.
Alex, l got it open.
We're in a gas station.
This could be our only shot.
The knife.
ln case l don't come back.
-Miss?
-Please call the police.
What?
Miss!
Hey, Jimmy!
-How are you?
-Good.
On your own tonight?
Yeah, weekends are slow.
So they left you to mind the store.
l guess.
This is the ideal place to bring girls.
Don't tell me it's never happened.
lf l did, my boss would fire me.
Come on....
The old rich ladies that drive through....
Don't tell me
they never ask for your services.
Ain't that right, Jimmy?
Yeah, l guess.
How do l look?
Do they suit me?
Yeah.
They look good on you.
-They are good protection?
-From what?
From the sun.
Yeah, they're sunglasses.
They're good protection.
How much do l owe you?
28.... Are you taking the glasses?
l don't think so. But l need some booze.
Can you give me a bottle of J & B?
Do you have Campbell?
l'm not supposed to sell alcohol this late.
-Don't tell the boss, okay?
-l promise.
CLOSED
What were you looking at, Jimmy?
What were you looking at?
Fucking come on! Pick up!
-Come on!
-State police.
Please help me!
Calm down. What's happened?
The Sorals, they have a farm.
l'm a friend of their daughter's.
Some guy broke in and he killed them all!
He's taken Alex in his truck.
God knows what he'll do.
-He axed the gas station guy.
-The gas station guy?
Are you in a gas station? Which one?
Hold on. l'm looking.
l don't know. l was in his truck.
l couldn't see.
lt's an old rusty truck.
-Did you get the license plate number?
-No, l was inside! l couldn't see.
You know how many trucks
there are on the road?
lt can't be fucking hard to spot
an old truck at this time of day!
Stay calm and simply tell me where you are.
The bastard's getting away.
Send a car or Alex doesn't stand a chance.
l need your location to be able to help you.
lf l blow up this fucking place,
will you finally see it, asshole?
Keys....
Where are you going, you bastard?
Fuck....
Where did he go?
What do you want from Alex?
She turns you on?
She turns me on, too.
She turns me on.
All lights are out. The station looks closed.
We'll take a look anyway.
Fernand, go round the back.
-Be careful.
-Yes, sir.
Sir, the back door is locked. We need....
Call the DA.
This is Fernand.
We got ourselves a homicide.
Oh, my God!
lt's me, Alex. lt's me.
lt's all over.
There.
Don't you touch me!
Don't you touch me, l said!
lt's all over. He's dead, Alex.
He's dead. lt's over.
l don't know what you're saying.
-He is dead.
-Just leave me alone!
-lt's over, Alex.
-Get out!
-Alex.
lt's over, Alex. l killed him.
Alex.
-Please, come down.
-Don't come near me!
Come on, Alex. Come.
lt's all over.
Now he can never do anything to you again.
You bitch, you're crazy.
l'm gonna tear you to shreds!
lt's me. lt's me, Marie, your friend.
l'm on your side.
l killed him, Alex. lt's finished. He's dead.
You murderer, you murdered my family.
God damn it, my family!
There was nothing l could do to save them.
There was just you.
Alex.
Everything's gonna be okay from now on.
Please, Alex, trust me.
Calm down.
You can't escape from me, bitch!
l'll take care of you, Alex!
l'm gonna take care of you, Alex.
Help! Help me, please.
Please!
She's not far. Come on! Come on!
What's going on?
Hurry!
l'll rip your head off!
You'd drive a woman crazy. You little slut.
Do you love me?
You don't love me, do you?
-You don't.
-Yes, l do.
Yes, l love you!
Yes, l do love you!
Nobody will come between us, ever...
ever again.
l won't let anyone
come between us anymore.
I won't Iet anyone come between us....
l won't let anyone
come between us anymore.
She can't see me, right?