(somber music playing)
Man's voice:
A WEEK AGO, THE ONLY THING
I THOUGHT WAS
OUT OF THE ORDINARY WAS
THAT IT WAS MY BIRTHDAY.
( sighs )
- ( meowing )
- ( barking )
SORRY.
I'M JUST BORED.
OH.
Woman on radio:
Unit 5, come in.
DO YOU READ ME, UNIT 5?
( sighs )
Man's voice:
OF COURSE, THINGS
DIDN'T REALLY START HERE.
( audio rewinding )
( Christmas music playing )
* I'LL HAVE A BLUE... *
HOW DO I LOOK?
- THE TRUTH?
- I LOOK LIKE
A ROCK STAR, DON'T I?
- YOU LOOK GREAT.
- HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON
WITH YOU?
- WHAT?
- WHY ARE YOU ACTING
SO WEIRD?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- YOU GOT DRUGS ON YOU?
SMOKING CIGARETTES?
- HUH? OH, JUST HOLDING
THEM FOR A FRIEND, HUH?
- HAVE A GOOD TIME.
- HA HA.
AGGIE, YOU OKAY?
- ( laughs )
- SEXY.
DO YOU HATE ME?
AS MUCH NOW
AS THE DAY I MET YOU.
- YOU KNOW,
I MIGHT BE CONTAGIOUS.
- I COULD BE IMMUNE.
- WHAT ABOUT THE PARTY?
- LIKE THEY'RE GONNA MISS ME.
WHAT ABOUT THE CAKE?
Man's voice:
I'D LIKE TWO WORDS
ON MY TOMBSTONE--
"WHAT IF?"
WHAT IF I HAD SAID
SCREW THE CAKE?
SINGLE TONIGHT, WALTER?
NOT ACTUALLY, NO.
- OH, HEY!
- OH, COME ON.
WHY DON'T YOU
WAG YOUR TAIL AT ME
IN THE BITCHES' ROOM?
- SYBIL.
- ( laughing )
Walter's voice:
WHAT IF I HAD BEEN
A BIT MORE...
SYBIL, I WOULDN'T WAG
MY TAIL IN THE BATHROOM
WITH YOU IF YOU WERE
THE LAST BITCH ON EARTH.
...TACTFUL?
Sybil:
Sparrow, I repeat.
WE HAVE AN UNIDENTIFIED
SCAVENGER SIGHTING.
IT'S ONE MINUTE
TO 5:00, SYBIL.
THEN WE'RE AGREED
YOU'RE STILL ON DUTY.
( speaking
foreign language )
MM-HMM, YEAH, SURE.
SOUNDS DELICIOUS.
CAN I GET IT TO GO?
RIGHT.
OKAY OKAY.
( sighs )
( dog growling )
( keys rattling )
( Walter chuckles )
COME TO PAPA.
MAYBE YOU'D LIKE
TO HEAR A STORY.
- ( barks )
- HMM?
YEAH, ONCE UPON A TIME
THERE WAS A DOG
WHO LIVED A LIFE
OF TERROR,
FEARED NO ONE.
BUT ALTHOUGH HIS TEETH
WERE SHARP
AND HIS BELLY FULL,
HIS HEART WAS EMPTY.
HE DECIDED TO GO
ON A JOURNEY
TO A LAND FAR FAR AWAY,
WHERE HE CAME UPON
A WOODEN SHACK ONE DAY
WITH A THIN OLD MAN
INSIDE.
AND HE INVITED HIM IN.
THE DOG...
WAS OVERJOYED.
AND THAT NIGHT
WARM SMOKE BILLOWED
FROM THE CHIMNEY ABOVE,
BUT, OH...
WHAT AN ODD-SMELLING
SMOKE THIS WAS.
YOU SEE,
THE LAND WAS CHINA.
AND IN CHINA,
- THEY EAT DOG.
- ( growling )
- WHOA! OOH!
- ( barking )
LET ME SEE WHO YOUR
IRRESPONSIBLE OWNER IS.
( grunting )
OH, GOD!
DAMN IT!
DIDN'T LIKE MY STORY,
HUH?
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
I CAN TAKE CRITICISM.
( call bell rings )
OH, GOD.
OH, I DON'T BELIEVE
THIS SHIT.
ALL RIGHT, BUDDY,
PICK A SPOT.
NOW WHERE'D YOU GO?
Walter's voice:
DESTINY--
MAYBE THAT'S TOO BIG
A WORD FOR IT.
IF I'D BEEN NICER TO SYBIL,
SHE NEVER WOULD HAVE SENT ME
AFTER THAT DOG.
I WOULDN'T HAVE BEEN LATE
TO MEET AGATHA,
AND NONE OF THIS
WOULD HAVE HAPPENED.
BUT I WAS LATE.
AND THAT'S ALL IT TOOK.
OH!
- TAKE A LOOK AT THAT.
TRY NOT TO THROW UP.
- OH OH, GOD!
"NASTY EVIL DOG"--
THAT'S WHAT "NED"
STANDS FOR.
IF I EVER SEE HIM AGAIN,
HE'S GONNA BE NED
WITH TWO D'S--
"NASTY EVIL DEAD DOG."
- ALL RIGHT, NOW TAKE
A DEEP BREATH.
- DEAD NED.
- THAT'S WHAT HE'S GONNA BE.
- AND REMEMBER,
IT'S YOUR BIRTHDAY,
OKAY?
- YEAH, I'VE BEEN
THINKING ABOUT THAT.
- MMM-HMM.
WHY IS IT WE GO
AND SEE YOUR FRIENDS
ON MY BIRTHDAY?
UM...
PROBABLY BECAUSE
YOU DON'T HAVE ANY.
- ( laughing )
- OH.
MAKES SENSE.
SO I'M OLDER,
I'M DISFIGURED,
AND I'M SPENDING
AN EVENING IN HELL.
- NO.
- I SUPPOSE I'M BUYING
THAT FOR YOU TOO.
WELL, ACTUALLY,
I'VE HAD A GOOD LONG TIME
TO FLIP THROUGH IT.
WHY DON'T YOU
GIVE IT A TRY?
HAVE SOME WRITER FILL
MY HEAD WITH NONSENSE?
I'LL WAIT FOR THE MOVIE.
YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE MISSING.
HMM, AND YET
LIFE GOES ON.
"'THE NUMBER 23.'
A NOVEL OF OBSESSION
BY TOPSY KRETTS."
HMM.
"A HEART-WRENCHING ODYSSEY
INTO PARANOIA.
ONE OF THE MOST HORRIFYING
METAMORPHOSES EVER TOLD.
BEWARE OF THE DOG
NEXT DOOR."
GET OUT OF HERE.
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
I'M BUYING THIS
FOR YOU, OKAY?
- WOULD YOU GET THE CAKE?
- YEAH.
Walter's voice:
FEBRUARY 3rd, THAT MAKES
ME AQUARIUS.
EXPERTS SAY FRIENDS
ARE VITALLY IMPORTANT.
- HI.
- HELLO.
- HEY.
I'M SORRY WE'RE LATE.
- NOTHING A KISS WON'T CURE.
- OH!
Walter's voice:
I AM LIVING PROOF OF
THE FALLACY OF ASTROLOGY.
HI. HOW'S YOUR ARM,
BIRTHDAY BOY?
- YOU OKAY?
- JUST WAITING FOR IT
TO FALL OFF.
- GOOD THING IT DIDN'T
BITE YOU SOMEWHERE ELSE.
- OH.
- Woman: FIVE SECONDS.
FIVE SECONDS.
- FOURTH WORD.
- BIRDS, BUTTERFLIES, BIRDS.
- IT FLIES.
- BIRDS, BIRDS.
- FLIES, FLIES.
- "LORD OF THE FLIES"!
- ( shouts, laughing )
- OKAY, YOU'RE NEXT.
- THANK YOU.
Walter's voice:
"ALL THE CHARACTERS IN THIS
BOOK ARE FICTITIOUS,
AND ANYONE
FINDING A RESEMBLANCE
TO ACTUAL PERSONS,
LIVING OR DEAD,
SHOULD PROCEED NO FURTHER."
- Walter: NOW IT'S TIME
FOR BIRTHDAY SEX.
- ( both laugh )
I NEED A LOT
OF BIRTHDAY SEX.
- YOU KNOW WHAT?
- WHAT?
LET'S SIT OUT HERE
FOR A WHILE.
OH-- OH, HONEY.
- COME ON, IT'LL BE ROMANTIC.
- YEAH, BUT IT'S ALSO COLD.
HERE, TAKE MY COAT.
YOUR JACKET, TAKE IT.
I'LL CALL YOU.
MOM, DAD. I THOUGHT
I HEARD VOICES.
WELL, YOU KNOW,
IF SOMEONE WAS IN BED
ASLEEP THE WAY THEY WERE
SUPPOSED TO BE,
- THEY WOULDN'T
HEAR ANY VOICES.
- IN BED? OKAY.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO BE IN BED.
OH, DAD. DAD, I, UH,
FORGOT TO GIVE YOU THIS.
- HERE.
- OH, COOL.
- YEAH,
I WRAPPED IT MYSELF.
- YEAH.
I ACCEPT BRIBES ANY TIME
OF THE DAY OR NIGHT.
BACK DOOR?
SHE WENT DOWN THE ALLEY.
WOW, THAT'S COOL.
ROBIN,
SHE'S A NICE GIRL.
MAKE SURE SHE STAYS
THAT WAY.
ALL RIGHT.
GOOD NIGHT, DAD.
- HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
- THANKS.
Walter's voice:
"CHAPTER 1: YOU CAN
CALL ME FINGERLING.
IT'S NOT MY REAL NAME.
IT CAME FROM A BOOK
I READ AS A CHILD,
'FINGERLING
AT THE ZOO.'
PAPER FLAP LONG GONE,
IT HAD A GREEN HARDBACK COVER
AND MOTTLED TEXTURE.
IT WAS POSSIBLY
MY VERY FIRST BOOK.
FUNNY,
I CAN'T RECALL
WHAT IT WAS ABOUT.
THE ONLY THING
I REMEMBER IS THE NAME--
FINGERLING.
I WISHED IT WAS MINE
AND NOW IT IS."
THIS IS YOUR FIRST BITE?
FIRST ANIMAL ONE, YES.
MY WIFE, SHE HAS
THESE GNAWING URGES
IN HER SLEEP AND...
TELL ME ABOUT THIS
CANINE NED.
WHAT WOULD YOU DO
IF YOU CAME ACROSS
HIM AGAIN?
IF I WAS IN MY TRUCK,
I'D ACCELERATE
UNTIL I HEARD A THUD.
( chuckles )
I'M SORRY.
I'M JUST-- I'M JOKING.
I JUST--
THIS IS JUST SILLY.
MR. SPARROW,
ANIMAL-CONTROL
REGULATIONS STATE
THAT ANY OFFICER SUFFERING
AT THE HANDS OF AN ANIMAL
MUST UNDERGO PSYCHOLOGICAL
COUNSELING WITHIN SEVEN DAYS
TO EVALUATE THEIR
STATE OF MIND.
I GAVE HIM MY ARM
ON A PLATTER.
CAN'T BLAME A CREATURE
OF LOWER INTELLIGENCE FOR THAT.
I MADE A MISTAKE, OKAY?
WRITE THAT DOWN.
I MADE A MISTAKE.
IT'S MY FAULT--
LIKE WHEN I TOLD MY WIFE
SHE COULD CHOOSE THE COLOR
FOR THE LIVING ROOM WALLS,
YOU KNOW?
NOT THAT WOMEN ARE OF
LOWER INTELLIGENCE, JUST...
HAVE A GOOD DAY,
MR. SPARROW.
( laughing )
NO, I'M JUS--
NO, AGATHA IS THE MOST
INTELLIGENT PERSON I KNOW.
WHAT SHE SEES IN ME,
I'M NOT SURE.
LOOK...
I LOVE MY JOB,
AND I'M GOOD AT IT.
NED GOT AWAY.
WELL, YEAH, BUT...
DON'T WORRY.
APART FROM A FLAWED
SENSE OF HUMOR,
I'M GIVING YOU
A CLEAN BILL OF HEALTH.
YOU'RE NOT A DANGER
TO ANYONE.
THAT'S WHY YOU CAN GO
AND HAVE THE WHOLE DAY OFF.
REALLY?
I'LL TAKE IT.
- MR. SPARROW.
- YEAH.
WHAT COLOR DID YOUR WIFE
CHOOSE FOR THE WALLS?
RED, BLOOD RED.
Walter's voice:
"CHAPTER 2:
IMAGINE ME, IF YOU MUST,
AS SOMEONE YOU ONCE KNEW.
SOMEONE PERHAPS
YOU LIKED.
OR BETTER YET,
IMAGINE ME AS YOU.
AS A KID,
I WAS TOP OF MY CLASS,
NOT BECAUSE I LIKED STUDYING,
BUT BECAUSE I REALIZED
THAT AN EDUCATION WAS
MY BEST SHOT AT GETTING OUT.
SEE, THE STORK DROPPED ME
IN A SMALL DUSTBOWL OF A TOWN.
THERE WASN'T ANYTHING
WRONG WITH IT.
AS FAR AS
BORING TOWNS GO,
I'M SURE IT RANKED
ABOVE AVERAGE.
I HAD FRIENDS, BUT...
I ALWAYS FELT ALONE.
NO ONE EVER LEFT,
BUT I WASN'T GONNA
DIE HERE.
AS MUCH AS I LOVED HIM,
I DIDN'T WANT
TO BE ANYTHING LIKE MY DAD.
HE SEEMED SO DISTANT
AND SAD.
NUMBERS WERE HIS LIFE.
HE WAS AN ACCOUNTANT.
AND I GUESS HE HAD
EXPECTED ME TO TAKE OVER
THE BUSINESS HE HAD BUILT,
BUT I HAD OTHER PLANS.
MY MOM WAS TICKLED PINK
ON MY EIGHTH BIRTHDAY
WHEN I ANNOUNCED
I WANTED TO BE A DETECTIVE.
CAN'T SAY THE SAME
FOR MY FATHER.
IT REALLY PUT THE KIBOSH
ON HIS MASTER PLAN
AND IT FUELED HIS HATRED
FOR THE WIDOW DOBKINS.
SHE LIVED NEXT DOOR.
- IT SOUNDS ODD,
BUT HER DOG ALFIE...
- ( dog barking )
IS THE REASON
I BECAME A DETECTIVE.
THE GRASS IS ALWAYS GREENER
ON THE OTHER SIDE,
AT LEAST ACCORDING
TO ALFIE.
THAT'S WHY HE WAS ALWAYS
IN OUR YARD,
AND IT WAS MY JOB
TO CATCH HIM.
BUT I NEVER CROSSED THE FENCE
INTO THE WIDOW DOBKINS' YARD.
THAT WAS
MY FATHER'S RULE.
ON MY EIGHTH BIRTHDAY,
I BROKE THE RULE.
NOW I MUST ADMIT
THAT MY LONELINESS
AND OBSESSION
WITH DETECTIVE STORIES
HAD FUELED FANTASIES.
SO I'M NOT SURE
OF ALL THE DETAILS,
EXCEPT ONE.
THE WIDOW DOBKINS
WAS DEAD.
IT WAS A WHOLE HOUR
BEFORE THE DOCTOR ARRIVED,
AND IN THAT
UNCERTAIN HOUR
MY EIGHT-YEAR-OLD MIND
RACED.
I DECIDED THAT
THE WIDOW DOBKINS
WAS KILLED
BY A MAN
WITH A DERANGED MIND,
A MIND SUCH AS OUR TOWN
HAD NEVER SEEN BEFORE.
NO ONE WOULD BE SAFE
FROM HIM, NOT EVEN
HIS LOVED ONES.
ESPECIALLY HIS LOVED ONES.
OF COURSE, A DOCTOR
LATER CONCLUDED THAT
IT WAS SUICIDE,
BUT I NEVER BELIEVED IT.
BY THEN,
MY MIND HAD BEEN OPENED
TO A WHOLE NEW EXISTENCE.
FROM THIS,
A DETECTIVE WAS BORN--
DETECTIVE FINGERLING."
THIS HAS PROMISE TOO.
HEY, THERE YOU ARE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'LL CLEAN
THIS UP LATER.
FILLING YOUR HEAD
WITH NONSENSE, ARE YOU?
- DID YOU READ THIS?
- MOST OF IT.
- IT'S VERY CREATIVE.
- THIS FINGERLING GUY.
YEAH, IT'S A COOL NAME.
YEAH, WHAT DID
YOU MAKE OF HIM?
I LOVED HIM AT THE--
WELL, AT THE BEGINNING
I DID.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
AT THE BEGINNING?
WELL, HE--
HOW FAR HAVE YOU GOTTEN?
- OH, TWO CHAPTERS.
- OH.
HONEY, WILL YOU MOVE
THIS LADDER FOR ME,
JUST RIGHT OVER HERE?
YOU KNOW, HONEY,
THIS FINGERLING GUY
REMINDS ME OF MY LIFE.
IT'S SO WEIRD.
LIKE, IT'S LIKE
MY CHILDHOOD, MY MEMORIES,
YOU KNOW?
WILL YOU HAND ME
THAT BLUE PAINT?
- HERE.
- FINGERLING'S NOTHING
LIKE YOU.
OH, YEAH,
LOOK AT THAT?
"FINGERLING AT THE ZOO."
MY MOTHER READ IT TO ME
WHEN I WAS A KID.
I'M SURE A LOT OF PEOPLE
READ THAT AS A KID.
- DID YOU?
- NO.
- HA-AA!
- BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
EVERY TIME I READ A BOOK,
IT'S LIKE, THE AUTHOR
STOLE A PART OF ME THAT
I THOUGHT ONLY I KNEW.
SOMEDAY I'M GONNA WRITE
A BOOK AND I'LL DO IT
TO SOMEBODY ELSE.
I DON'T KNOW, HON.
IT'S-- IT'S JUST REALLY
- KIND OF STRANGE.
- YOU KNOW WHAT?
THERE'S A LOT
OF NEIGHBORHOODS WITH
HOUSES JUST LIKE YOURS,
WITH STREETS
JUST LIKE YOURS.
YEAH?
WITH DOGS NEXT DOOR?
OH, YOUR NEIGHBOR HAD A DOG.
WELL, THAT'S SHOCKING.
( scoffs )
IT WASN'T CALLED ALFIE.
IT WAS CALLED CHIEF.
"MIS-CHIEF"
MY FATHER CALLED IT.
HE USED TO ESCAPE ALL THE TIME.
THAT'S WHY I BECAME AN A.C.O.
FINGERLING'S A DETECTIVE.
I USED TO COLLECT
DETECTIVE MAGAZINES.
AND THE WIDOW NEXT DOOR,
MRS. DOBKINS,
WELL, THAT'S LIKE
MY MOM.
SHE DIED
ON MY EIGHTH BIRTHDAY.
LOOK, I GOT
FREAKIN' GOOSE BUMPS.
HONEY, KEEP READING,
OKAY?
SOON YOU WILL DISCOVER
THAT FINGERLING IS
NOTHING LIKE YOU.
SOMEBODY WROTE A BOOK
ABOUT DAD?
- NO.
- YES. YES.
- HOW'S SCHOOL?
- HORRIBLE.
AM I IN IT?
I MEAN, IF THE BOOK'S
ABOUT DAD,
THEN I SHOULD HAVE, LIKE,
A STARRING ROLE OR SOMETHING.
YES, YOU SHOULD,
AND YET YOU DON'T.
NOW WHAT DO YOU THINK
THAT MEANS?
- HMM, JEEZ.
- WHO'S THAT?
- Walter: FABRIZIA.
- Robin: FABRIZIA?
UH-HUH.
( rock music playing )
* GOT A BIG PLAN,
THIS MINDSET *
* MAYBE IT'S RIGHT
AT THE RIGHT PLACE
AND RIGHT TIME *
* MAYBE TONIGHT
AND THE WHISPER *
* OR HANDSHAKE
SENDING A SIGN *
* WANNA MAKE OUT
AND KISS HARD? *
* WAIT, NEVER MIND *
* LATE NIGHT AND PASSING *
* MENTION IT FLIPPED
HER BEST FRIEND *
* WHO KNOWS SAYING
MAYBE IT SLIPPED *
* BUT THE SLIP TURNS TO TERROR
AND A CRUSH TO LIGHT *
* THEN SHE WALKED IN,
HE THROWS UP *
- * BELIEVE IT'S THE FRIGHT,
IT'S CUTE IN A WAY... *
- ( camera clicking )
* TILL YOU CANNOT SPEAK
AND YOU LEAVE TO HAVE
A CIGARETTE *
* YOUR KNEES GET WEAK,
ESCAPE WAS JUST A NOD *
* AND A CASUAL WAVE,
OBSESSED ABOUT IT *
* HEAVY FOR THE NEXT
TWO DAYS *
* IT'S ONLY JUST A CRUSH
IT'LL GO AWAY *
* IT'S JUST LIKE ALL
THE OTHERS, IT'LL GO AWAY *
* OR MAYBE THIS IS DANGER
AND YOU JUST DON'T KNOW *
* YOU PRAY IT ALL AWAY
BUT IT CONTINUES TO GROW *
* I WANT TO HOLD YOU CLOSE *
* SKIN PRESSED
AGAINST ME TIGHT *
* LIE STILL,
CLOSE YOUR EYES, GIRL *
* SO LOVELY
IT FEELS SO RIGHT. *
( thunder rumbles )
( sighs )
( Walter sighs )
Walter's voice:
"CHAPTER 5:
I MEET
THE SUICIDE BLONDE."
I GOT A TIP FROM YOUR
NEIGHBORHOOD WATCH.
I KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE UP TO.
THIS BEFRIEND-ME CRAP,
IT WON'T WORK.
COME ANY CLOSER
AND I'LL DO IT.
WELL, I HOPE YOU DON'T.
IT'S MY BIRTHDAY TODAY.
YOU END UP HANGING
YOURSELF, IT'LL BE
THE WORST ONE EVER.
YOU'RE PATHETIC.
- I'M SERIOUS.
I'LL DO IT.
- HANGING--
IT'S A PAINFUL THING.
MOST PEOPLE GET
THE NOOSE WRONG,
END UP WALKING AROUND
WITH A PERMANENT NECKLACE...
AGONIZING REMINDER
OF HOW FUCKING PITIFUL
THEY ARE.
COME ON, LET'S TALK.
IF YOU'RE STILL BUMMED,
I'LL PUT ONE RIGHT
BETWEEN YOUR EYES.
I'M A GOOD SHOT.
IS IT REALLY
YOUR BIRTHDAY?
Walter's voice:
"THE SUICIDE BLONDE TELLS
ME SHE WAS A GOOD PERSON ONCE,
BUT NOW..."
I'M A BAD PERSON.
I DON'T WANNA
MAKE YOU BAD.
YOU DON'T HAVE
THAT POWER.
GO SEE MY EX-BOYFRIEND.
HE'LL SHOW YOU.
Walter's voice:
"I SHOULD HAVE GOTTEN
OUT OF THERE
RIGHT AT THAT MOMENT,
BUT THEN SHE SAID..."
IT'S THIS NUMBER!
THIS FUCKING
NUMBER-- 23.
IT RULES MY WORLD.
IT'S MY FATHER'S FAULT.
HE SAID HE'D FOUND
A WAY TO BEAT THE NUMBER,
THAT HE'D BEAT IT,
THAT I WAS SAFE.
HE SAID, "DADDY LOVES YOU.
AND HE'S GONNA DO SOMETHING...
Both:
...TO GUARANTEE THAT YOU
WON'T INHERIT THE CURSE."
( gunshot )
HE WAS WRONG.
HIS GUARANTEE WASN'T
WORTH THE BLOOD IT
WAS WRITTEN IN.
I GUESS DADDY
DIDN'T LOVE ME ENOUGH.
IT'S EVERYWHERE--
DATES, TIMES,
LICENSE PLATE NUMBERS,
PAGES OF BOOKS,
EVEN ELEVATOR
FLOOR LIGHTS.
SOON I FOUND IT WAS
IN MY NAME. IT WAS IN
THE WORDS I SPOKE.
NOTHING, NOTHING
IS SAFE.
PINK IS MY FAVORITE COLOR.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT PINK IS?
RED 27, WHITE 65.
65 PLUS 27-- 92.
PINK HAS FOUR LETTERS.
92 DIVIDED BY FOUR.
TWENTY-FUCKING-THREE!
Walter's voice:
"I'LL BE HONEST--
I DIDN'T GET IT.
I ASKED HER
THE ONLY QUESTION
I COULD MUSTER."
ANY MORE COFFEE?
Walter's voice:
"IT WAS IMPORTANT TO KEEP
HER TALKING,
SO I TELL HER A STORY."
Fingerling:
I HAD THIS UNCLE,
HIS NAME WAS CHARLIE.
AND, UH, ONE DAY,
HE READ IN HIS STARS
THAT HE WAS
GONNA FALL IN LOVE
WITH A WOMAN IN RED.
SO HE WENT OUT
LOOKING ALL DAY LONG
AND HE FOUND ONE.
SIX MONTHS LATER,
THEY WERE MARRIED.
YOU'RE LYING.
TWO YEARS LATER,
THE WOMAN IN RED
DIVORCES MY UNCLE,
TAKES HIM FOR
EVERYTHING HE'S GOT.
HE'S OUT THERE
RIGHT NOW
AT THIS VERY MOMENT...
STILL LOOKING
FOR THE WOMAN IN RED.
FIGURES HE JUST GOT
THE WRONG ONE.
AND THIS IS SUPPOSED TO MAKE
ME FEEL BETTER HOW?
YOU LOOK SMARTER
THAN MY UNCLE CHARLIE.
( chuckles )
Walter's voice:
"SHE HAS A FACE MEANT
TO SMILE.
AND AS I EXIT THE BUILDING,
I FIGURE IT'S ANOTHER JOB
WELL DONE.
THE NEXT DAY I TRACED
THE EX-BOYFRIEND
SUICIDE BLONDE
MENTIONED.
BURNING COFFEE GROUNDS
IS AN OLD TRICK
COPS USE TO TAKE AWAY
THE SMELL OF DEATH
AT A CRIME SCENE.
BUT SOMEBODY HAD USED
ALL THE COFFEE.
WHEN I TELL FABRIZIA
ABOUT THE SUICIDE BLONDE,
SHE BEGS ME TO TAKE HER
TO THE APARTMENT.
HER REACTION
IS PURE FABRIZIA.
DEATH AND SEX--
WHAT A TURN-ON.
AS THE PAGES FELL
FROM THE WALLS,
THE SCOPE
OF THE SUICIDE BLONDE'S
OBSESSION BECAME CLEAR.
SHE HAD REDUCED
EVERYTHING TO 23."
Suicide Blonde's voice:
IT'S EVERYWHERE--
DATES, TIMES,
LICENSE PLATE NUMBERS,
PAGES OF BOOKS,
EVEN ELEVATOR FLOOR LIGHTS.
SOON I FOUND IT WAS
IN MY NAME.
IT WAS
IN THE WORDS I SPOKE.
IT WAS IN MY NAME.
IT WAS IN THE WORDS
I SPOKE.
Walter's voice:
"WHEN I FOUND OUT WHAT
HER NAME WAS,
THAT ADDED UP TOO.
MAYBE IT WAS
JUST A COINCIDENCE.
I MEAN, A NAME IS
JUST A NAME.
AND A NUMBER IS
JUST A NUMBER.
ISN'T IT?"
IT'S SELF-PRINTED,
SELF-PUBLISHED,
AND IT'S BY AN AUTHOR
I NEVER HEARD OF.
( typing )
LOOKS LIKE OLD TOPSY HERE
HASN'T WRITTEN ANYTHING
BEFORE OR AFTER SINCE.
( inhales )
Agatha:
WALTER, WHAT ARE
YOU DOING?
CHECK THIS OUT.
WALTER SPARROW
DOESN'T WORK.
BUT IF I USE
MY MIDDLE NAME...
- WALTER.
- 5-1-1-9-7.
- ISN'T THAT AMAZING?
- WHAT?
IT'S ALL 23.
MY BIRTHDAY-- 2/3,
DRIVER'S LICENSE,
SOCIAL SECURITY NUMBER--
EVERYTHING.
I WAS BORN AT 11:12 P.M.
11 PLUS 12.
IT'S LIKE
IT'S IMITATING
MY LIFE.
YOU CAN'T BE
SERIOUS.
THE AUTHOR KNOWS
SO MUCH ABOUT ME.
IT'S AS IF
HE CHOSE ME.
IS THIS WHAT YOU'VE
BEEN DOING ALL DAY?
- HAVE YOU
FINISHED THE BOOK?
- NOT YET.
YOU'VE CONCERNED
YOURSELF WITH MINUTIA
AND YOU'VE DRAWN WILD
CONCLUSIONS FROM THEM.
WHAT ABOUT
THE FACT THAT FINGERLING
BECOMES A KILLER?
- A KILLER?
- AND JUST HOW MANY PEOPLE
HAVE YOU KILLED?
WAIT, WHO GETS
KILLED?
ASK MR. FINGERLING.
I'M SORRY, HONEY.
WHY THIS COLOR?
WHY DID YOU CHOOSE
THIS COLOR?
I DON'T KNOW,
YOU TELL ME.
RED NUMBER FIVE--
R-E-D IS 27,
PLUS FIVE IS 32
WHICH IS--
YOU'RE REACHING NOW.
SURE, THERE ARE
DIFFERENCES.
FINGERLING'S A DETECTIVE,
I'M A DOG CATCHER;
HE MET FABRIZIA
WHEN HE WAS 32,
WHEREAS I MET YOU
WHEN I WAS--
- 23.
- AND THE DAY
WE MET WAS?
- SEPTEMBER 14th.
- 9/14.
- 14 PLUS 9 IS?
- 23!
( sighs )
WE MARRIED
OCTOBER 13th--
10/13, 23.
SUICIDE BLONDE SAID
IT RULED HER WORLD.
SHE KILLED BECAUSE OF IT.
THEN SHE HANDED IT
ON TO FINGERLING
ON HIS 32nd BIRTHDAY--
23 REVERSED.
FINGERLING CALLED IT FATE.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT FATE IS?
( whispers )
32.
I REST MY CASE,
YOUR HONOR.
- HONEY, I THINK YOU'RE
TAKING THIS TOO SERIOUSLY.
- WAIT WAIT WAIT
WAIT WAIT WAIT.
WE LIVE AT 1814.
I MEAN, 18 IS
ONE PLUS EIGHT
WHICH EQUALS NINE.
AND NINE PLUS 14
IS ALSO 23.
14 IS ONE PLUS FOUR
WHICH EQUALS FIVE.
AND FIVE PLUS
18 IS 23 TOO.
- OH MY GOD.
- ALL RIGHT, ROBIN,
PLEASE DON'T YOU
START THIS NONSENSE.
THIS IS NOT NONSENSE!
I-I MEAN, FIVE PLUS
18 IS 23.
WELL, IF THE BOOK
WERE 27 OR 150,
YOU COULD DO
THE SAME THING.
18 PLUS 14 IS 32.
23 REVERSED.
( sighs )
SPOOKY, HUH?
Walter's voice:
"CHAPTER 7:
THE SUICIDE BLONDE HAD
GIVEN FABRIZIA A TASTE
FOR NEW THRILLS.
I PLAYED ALONG,
BUT ALL I COULD THINK
ABOUT WAS THE NUMBER."
THANKS.
Walter's voice:
"I DIDN'T TELL HER
THAT THE CLOCK BEHIND
THE DESK READ 9:14.
( both moaning )
JUST RIP IT OPEN.
JUST RIP IT OFF.
( moaning )
PRETEND YOU HAVE A KNIFE.
( whispers )
COME ON.
( gasps, moans )
( moaning )
I KNOW YOU'RE
GONNA HURT ME.
( whispers )
YOU SHUT UP, BITCH,
OR YOU DIE.
Walter's voice:
"OF COURSE I WOULD NEVER
REALLY HARM FABRIZIA.
I LOVED HER.
AND I THOUGHT SHE LOVED ME."
( both moaning )
( heavy metal music playing )
Walter's voice:
"BUT I STARTED HAVING
TERRIBLE NIGHTMARES."
( exhales )
( whispers )
EIGHT, NINE, 10,
11, 12, 13--
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
READING.
YOU'RE INSANE.
( dialing )
- ISAAC?
- Isaac: SIMPLY PUT,
IT'S A BOX
THAT COLLECTS
ORGONE ENERGY.
( laughs )
WE'LL TALK ABOUT
WILHELM REICH NEXT WEEK.
THANK YOU FOR COMING.
WELL, IT SOUNDS LIKE
A FASCINATING READ.
OF COURSE THERE EXIST
FAR TOO FEW BOOKS
WHERE THE MAIN
CHARACTER PLAYS
THE SAXOPHONE.
I WASN'T AWARE
YOU ALSO PLAYED.
I DON'T.
THAT'S JUST IT,
IT DOESN'T ALL MATCH.
IT'S THE NUMBER.
I'M SEEING IT EVERYWHERE.
WELL, CONSPIRACY BUFFS
WOULD SAY, "OF COURSE.
AFTER ALL, THE WORLD
SPINS IN AN AXIS OF 23째."
WHEN YOU TELL THEM IT'S
ACTUALLY 23.5, THEY SAY
FIVE IS SIMPLY TWO PLUS THREE.
( chuckles )
23 IS VERY GOOD
AT THIS PARTICULAR GAME.
- GAME?
- YEAH, PARANOIA.
- THERE'S A FAIR BIT OF
LITERATURE ON THE 23 ENIGMA.
- THERE IS?
THERE ARE 23 AXIOMS
TO EUCLID'S GEOMETRY.
THE HUMAN BODY CONSISTS
OF 46 CHROMOSOMES--
23 FROM EACH PARENT.
BLOOD TAKES 23 SECONDS
TO CIRCULATE.
THE MAYANS BELIEVED
THE END OF THE WORLD
WOULD OCCUR DECEMBER
12th, 2012.
20 PLUS 12 IS?
23 REVERSED.
OR 20 PLUS ONE
PLUS TWO.
SO WHAT IS THIS?
WHAT IS 23?
IS IT...
GOD?
Isaac:
TWO DIVIDED BY THREE--
.666.
666, THE NUMBER
OF THE DEVIL.
THERE ARE ONLY 22 CHAPTERS
IN THE BOOK OF REVELATIONS.
WE ALL KNOW
HOW THAT ENDS.
SO IS 23
A BLESSING OR A CURSE?
WHAT'S TRUE IS THAT
THERE'S A SELECT GROUP
OF PEOPLE
THAT TAKE DELIGHT
IN PERPETUATING
THE NUMBER'S INFAMY.
LUCKY SEVEN,
UNLUCKY 13,
BALLPLAYERS,
LUCKY SHOES.
PEOPLE ONLY PRAY
BECAUSE THEY BELIEVE THAT GOD
WILL HELP THEM IF THEY DO.
THIS IS MAGICAL
THINKING,
NON-SCIENTIFIC
CAUSAL REASONING.
NOW YOU'RE--
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR 23
SO YOU'RE FINDING IT.
( chuckles )
AGATHA THINKS
I'M NUTS.
( laughs )
FINISH THE BOOK.
AND IF AFTER READING IT
IN ITS ENTIRETY,
YOU STILL BELIEVE
THE SUBJECT TO BE YOU,
THEN WHOEVER WROTE IT
KNOWS YOU VERY WELL.
AND ONLY THEY CAN
GIVE YOU YOUR ANSWER.
- THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
- AND IN THE MEANTIME
I CAN SPEAK TO AGATHA,
IF YOU LIKE.
HMM.
( moaning )
Walter's voice:
THE NUMBER WAS EVERYWHERE.
YOU HAVE 23 PAIRS
OF SHOES.
YOU'RE COUNTING
MY SHOES?
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- READING.
YOU'RE INSANE.
Walter's voice:
"NIGHT AFTER NIGHT I KILLED
FABRIZIA IN MY DREAMS.
I EXPLAINED TO THE DEPARTMENT
SHRINK WHAT HER FULL NAME
ADDED UP TO."
- 23.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
THAT MEANS?
I DON'T KNOW,
MILES.
MAYBE I SHOULD BE
A FUCKING ACCOUNTANT.
Walter's voice:
"THE WISE DR. PHOENIX
RECOMMENDS I TAKE A BREAK."
MAYBE YOU SHOULD
TAKE A BREAK.
Walter's voice:
"LIKE TIME IS GONNA
HEAL ME."
TIME IS A--
A GENTLE MAN.
Walter's voice:
"TIME IS JUST A COUNTING
SYSTEM,
NUMBERS WITH MEANING
ATTACHED TO THEM.
STILL, A BREAK
IS WHAT HE PRESCRIBES.
HE CALLED IT--"
EMOTIONAL LEAVE.
SO YOU'RE NOT
A DETECTIVE ANYMORE.
Walter's voice:
"FABRIZIA WAS NOT IMPRESSED."
I'M A DETECTIVE
ON VACATION.
- ( sniffs )
- AND YOU DON'T
HAVE A GUN?
I STILL HAVE THESE.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD
JUST GET SOME SLEEP
TONIGHT.
Walter's voice:
"THE NUMBER WAS EVERYWHERE.
AT THIS POINT,
I DON'T NEED TO TELL YOU
HOW MANY PAIRS
OF SHOES SHE HAD.
WHAT ARE THESE SHOES
DOING IN THE TRASH?
DID YOU KNOW
YOU HAD 23 PAIR?
OH!
YOU'RE INSANE!
THE HIROSHIMA BOMB
WAS DROPPED AT 8:15.
EIGHT PLUS 15 IS 23.
WACO, TEXAS,
AND THE OKLAHOMA CITY BOMBING
BOTH HAPPENED
ON APRIL 19th.
FOUR PLUS 19 IS 23.
TROPIC OF CANCER,
23.5째 NORTH;
CAPRICORN 23.5째 SOUTH.
10886 IS THE NUMBER
AL CAPONE WORE
ON HIS UNIFORM
IN PRISON.
TED BUNDY WAS EXECUTED
ON THE 23rd OF JANUARY.
IT'S ALL 23.
Walter's voice:
"SHE DIDN'T UNDERSTAND,
WHICH WAS FINE
BECAUSE NEITHER DID I.
ALL I KNEW WAS
THE NUMBER HAD GONE
AFTER SUICIDE BLONDE,
ISABEL LYDIA HUNT.
NOW IT WAS COMING
AFTER ME."
I CAN SPEAK TO FABRIZIA
IF YOU LIKE.
Walter's voice:
"I BELIEVE HE SAID IT
IN TOTAL INNOCENCE AT THE TIME.
BUT LOOKING BACK..."
I CAN SPEAK TO FABRIZIA
IF YOU LIKE.
"...I WISH I HAD
REACTED DIFFERENTLY."
( screams )
"I SHOULD HAVE REALIZED
THE TRUTH.
I KNOW IT'S ABSURD,
- BUT EVEN THE COLOR
OF HIS TIE BETRAYED HIM."
- ( spits )
DO YOU KNOW
WHAT PINK IS?
RED 27, WHITE 65.
65 PLUS 27-- 92.
PINK HAS FOUR LETTERS.
92 DIVIDED BY FOUR...
TWENTY-FUCKING-THREE!
IN THE MEANTIME,
I CAN SPEAK TO AGATHA
IF YOU LIKE.
( Isaac's voice overlapping )
PARANOIA.  23 IS VERY GOOD
AT THIS...
PARANOIA, PARANOIA.
IN THE MEANTIME,
I CAN SPEAK TO AGATHA
IF YOU LIKE.
...OF AN AXIS OF 23째.
WHEN YOU TELL THEM IT'S
ACTUALLY 23.5,
THEY SAY FIVE IS SIMPLY
TWO PLUS THREE.
Isaac:
IN THE MEANTIME,
I CAN SPEAK TO AGATHA
- IF YOU LIKE.
- ( glass shatters )
Walter's voice:
"CHAPTER 21..."
( panting )
( clicks )
( water running )
( shatters )
OH, GOD!
AG!
IT'S A NIGHTMARE.
IT'S GONNA BE ALL RIGHT.
NO!
( gasps )
( panting )
- ( sighs )
- ( clicks )
( car starts )
Walter's voice:
AG, I DON'T WANT YOU
TO BE WORRIED.
I JUST NEED ONE NIGHT
TO CLEAR MY HEAD.
PLEASE DON'T GIVE UP
ON ME.
YOUR LOVING
DOG-CATCHING HUSBAND,
WALTER.
Walter's voice:
WHY THAT STREET?
WHY THAT HOTEL?
LIKE IT WAS MY CHOICE.
- MORNING.
- WHAT CAN I DO
FOR YOU?
YEAH, UM, I'D, UM...
( clears throat )
LIKE A ROOM.
SIGN THE REGISTER.
27'S THE QUIETEST.
WHAT ABOUT 23?
WE'VE BEEN EXPERIENCING
SOME PLUMBING PROBLEMS
WITH 23.
Walter's voice:
CHAPTER 22 WAS AS I FEARED.
( gasps )
( police radio chatter )
( muttering )
TROPIC OF CAPRICORN.
Walter's voice:
IT WASN'T THE HAPPIEST
OF ENDINGS.
IT WASN'T AN ENDING
AT ALL.
AFTER CHAPTER 22,
THERE WAS NOTHING
BUT THE QUESTION.
DID THE NUMBER LIVE
TO KILL ANOTHER DAY?
THE NUMBER HAD
GONE AFTER FINGERLING.
- AND NOW IT WAS
COMING AFTER ME.
- ( dog barks )
YOU.
IT'S ALL YOUR FAULT.
IF YOU HADN'T MADE ME LATE...
ALL RIGHT,
THIS SUITS ME FINE.
A PLACE TO REST IN PEACE.
( growls )
YES!
I GOT YOU,
YOU SON OF A BITCH.
IT'S OKAY, BOY.
YOU'LL GET UP
IN A COUPLE OF HOURS
WITH A BAD HEADACHE.
THAT'S ALL.
NOT SO TOUGH NOW,
ARE YOU, NASTY EVIL DOG?
NED.
L, M, N-- 14.
A, B, C, D, E...
SHIT.
Man:
NED, NED!
I'M FATHER SEBASTIAN.
I TRUST THERE'S
AN EXPLANATION FOR THIS.
HE'S JUST SLEEPING,
FATHER. I'M AN ANIMAL
CONTROL OFFICER.
- IS THIS YOUR DOG?
- IT BELONGS TO BARNABY,
MY GARDENER.
DON'T WORRY,
BARNABY, HE'S ALL RIGHT.
HE'S JUST SLEEPING.
- WHY DID YOU NAME HIM NED?
- Sebastian: HE DIDN'T.
HE-- HE TOOK NED IN
AS A STRAY.
HE LIKES GRAVEYARDS.
HE SITS AND WATCHES
THE STONES
LIKE HE WAS WATCHING
OVER THEM.
THAT'S HOW HE
GOT HIS NICKNAME--
GUARDIAN OF THE DEAD.
LATELY IT'S BEEN
THIS ONE.
OH, NO WAY.
WHAT'S WRONG, SON?
SHE DIED
ON HER 23rd BIRTHDAY.
WELL, WE CAN
ONLY ASSUME.
- WHAT?
- THAT SHE DIED.
THEY NEVER FOUND HER BODY.
THIS IS ONLY A MARKER.
- WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
- LIBRARY. IT'S NOT
JUST A BOOK.
IT'S TRUE, THE NUMBER
SCREWS WITH YOUR MIND,
MAKES YOU DO...
TERRIBLE THINGS.
PERHAPS I SHOULD
BE GOING.
NO, I WANT YOU
TO SEE THIS, ALL OF YOU.
THERE WAS A COLLEGE GIRL
NAMED LAURA TOLLINS
WHO WAS MURDERED.
THEY NEVER FOUND HER BODY,
BUT HER BED WAS SOAKED
IN SO MUCH BLOOD.
THIS IS THE MAN
WHO KILLED HER, KYLE FLINCH.
POLICE FOUND
A MURDER WEAPON,
A BUTCHER'S KNIFE,
WITH HIS PRINTS
ALL OVER IT.
WELL, WALTER,
THIS WAS NEARLY
15 YEARS AGO.
AG, HE WASN'T JUST
HER PSYCHOLOGY PROFESSOR.
THEY WERE LOVERS.
EVERYTHING THEY DID
TOGETHER SEXUALLY
WAS EXACTLY LIKE
THE CHARACTERS IN THE BOOK.
HE SAID IT WAS HER IDEA
TO BUY THE KNIFE.
SHE WANTED
TO FAKE AN ATTACK.
KYLE FLINCH
IS TOPSY KRETTS.
THE BOOK IS HIS...
WARPED LITERARY
CONFESSION.
AGATHA SAID A-A DOG
TOLD YOU THIS.
NED ISN'T JUST A DOG.
HE'S THE GUARDIAN
OF THE DEAD.
Robin:
BUT WHAT ABOUT
ALL THESE 23s
IN-IN-IN YOUR NAME
AND EVERYTHING?
- IS IT ALL
JUST A COINCIDENCE?
- I DON'T KNOW.
BUT I KNOW
WHO CAN TELL ME.
( cell door opening )
WELL, YOU'RE
TWO DAYS EARLY.
YOU KNEW
I WOULD COME?
REPORTERS ALWAYS
COME ON THE 10th.
THE DAY YOU KILLED
LAURA TOLLINS.
THE DAY SHE WAS
TAKEN FROM ME.
I'M NOT A REPORTER.
MY NAME IS WALTER SPARROW.
I WAS BORN FEBRUARY 3rd.
HAPPY BELATED BIRTHDAY.
FEBRUARY 3rd.
2/3.
- YEAH.
- DON'T PRETEND
YOU DON'T KNOW,
TOPSY KRETTS.
I READ YOUR BOOK.
TELL ME
ABOUT THE NUMBER.
IS THAT WHY
YOU KILLED HER?
I NEED TO KNOW.
YOU HAVE TO TELL ME.
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
I'M AFRAID IT'S HAPPENING TO ME.
WHAT HAPPENED TO ME?
YOU WANT TO KNOW
THE WORST THING ABOUT
BEING IN PRISON?
YOUR FAMILY, YOUR SISTER,
YOUR PARENTS,
THEY COME TO VISIT YOU.
OVER TIME, THOUGH,
THE VISITS GET LESS
AND YOUR SISTER STOPS
COMING AT ALL.
THEN YOU START TO NOTICE
YOUR MOTHER WON'T LOOK YOU
IN THE EYE.
PRETTY SOON,
SHE STOPS COMING TOO.
EVENTUALLY, YOUR--
YOUR FATHER TELLS
YOU YOUR SISTER
HAD A BREAKDOWN...
UNABLE TO DEAL
WITH HAVING A MURDERER
FOR A BROTHER.
NOW THERE'S TEARS
IN HIS EYES WHEN
HE SAYS THIS,
BUT HE'S NOT SAD.
HE'S ANGRY.
THAT'S THE LAST TIME
YOU EVER SEE HIM.
I DIDN'T KILL LAURA.
I LOVED HER.
AND I DIDN'T WRITE A BOOK
ABOUT A NUMBER.
YOU'RE LYING.
I'M IN PRISON FOR A CRIME
I DID NOT COMMIT,
MR. SPARROW.
BUT SOMEHOW I THINK
YOUR PROBLEMS ARE
BIGGER THAN MINE.
FUCKING LIAR!
NO.
YEAH, NO.
IF I WAS
TO WRITE A BOOK,
I WOULDN'T USE A RIDICULOUS
NAME LIKE "TOP SECRETS."
( buzzer sounds )
( door closes )
HE WAS REAL CONVINCING
ABOUT HIS INNOCENCE.
WELL, KILLERS
USUALLY ARE.
HIS FINGERPRINTS WERE
ON THE KNIFE.
HER BLOOD WAS
ON HIS HANDS WHEN
HE DIALED 911.
- NO, HE'S INNOCENT.
- ( buzzer sounds )
ALL BECAUSE HIS NAME
DOESN'T ADD UP TO 23?
THE REAL KILLER,
THE AUTHOR, HE'S STILL
OUT THERE.
I HAVE TO FIND HIM.
WAIT, I--I--I--I KNOW
HOW YOU CAN FIND HIM.
Robin:
LAST NIGHT W-WHEN I WAS
READING THE BOOK,
I FOUND A P.O. BOX
ADDRESS IN THE BACK.
- ARE YOU SURE YOU DON'T
WANT ANYTHING IN THIS?
- JUST THE SNOW.
- WHEN DO YOU WANT IT
TO GET THERE?
- TOMORROW MORNING.
- IT'LL HAVE TO GO EXPRESS.
- FINE.
IS THAT ALL?
NO NO, WE WANT A--
WE WANT 23 OF THEM.
I DREAMT THAT
I KILLED YOU, AG.
- FINGERLING HAD
THE SAME DREAM ABOUT--
- SHH.
I'M GOING
WITH YOU TODAY.
AND ALL THIS
IS GONNA COME TO AN END.
YOU WOULDN'T HURT ME,
WALTER.
YOU WOULDN'T HURT
ANYONE EVER.
HOW DO YOU KNOW?
THERE'S YOUR BOXES,
KIDDO.
NOW WE'LL SEE
IF SOMEBODY SHOWS UP.
THIS MAY NOT BE THE AUTHOR.
HE MAY NOT EVEN BE A MAN.
WELL, WE'LL KNOW
SOON ENOUGH.
- WALTER, LOOK.
- HUH?
SOMEBODY'S GONE IN.
Robin: THAT'S HIM.
I-IT'S GOTTA BE HIM.
- Walter: YOU THINK?
- YEAH, I MEAN, LOOK AT HIM.
IT'S GOTTA BE HIM.
GAME'S OVER,
TOPSY KRETTS.
YOU SH--
SHOULD BE DEAD.
YOU SHOULD BE DEAD!
- WALTER, NO!
- I'M CALLING THE COPS!
STOP!
WHO ARE YOU?
THE NUMBER,
WHAT DOES IT MEAN?
I THINK YOU KNOW.
( groans )
- OH MY GOD.
GET AN AMBULANCE!
- WATCH OUT!
- DEAR GOD.
- GET AN AMBULANCE!
Walter:
DON'T YOU DIE ON ME.
YOU HEAR ME?
DON'T YOU DIE.
WALTER, PLEASE.
HE'S THE ONLY PERSON
THAT CAN HELP US GET
BACK TO NORMAL.
HONEY, YOU'RE NOT
HELPING, OKAY?
NOW I WANT YOU
TO TAKE ROBIN
AND GO HOME.
THIS MAN NEEDS
A HOSPITAL.
- I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT.
- BUT HE KNOWS, HON.
TAKE ROBIN
AND GO HOME.
I SAID I'LL TAKE CARE
OF IT.
HE KNOWS.
SHIT!
HARD TO GET RID OF...
- WHAT?
- I WAS INSANE.
WHAT WAS DRIVING
YOU INSANE?
HARD...
TO GET RID OF...
( gasps )
THE INSTITUTE.
GO THERE.
YOU'LL SEE.
OH MY GOD.
( siren wailing )
( telephone rings )
- AGATHA.
- WALTER, HE DIDN'T MAKE IT.
I'M SO SORRY.
Well, did he say
anything?
NO, I'M SORRY.
DID YOU FIND OUT
WHO HE WAS?
No.
I'LL BE HOME
IN A LITTLE WHILE.
( hangs up )
( water dripping )
- ( wings flapping )
- ( gasps )
OH, SHIT!
YOU GOTTA BE
KIDDING ME.
ROBIN!
EVERY 23rd WORD
ON EVERY 23rd PAGE:
"VISIT CASANOVA SPARK,
DIG BENEATH THE STEPS
TO HEAVEN."
- WHO'S CASANOVA SPARK?
- IT'S NOT A PERSON.
"I WARN YOU, HELL IS
WAITING, SPARROW MAN."
WE NEED TO GO.
( mumbling )
Man: 23!
Agatha:
WHAT WAS DRIVING YOU INSANE?
( gasps )
WANNA TAKE BETS THAT
THERE'S 23 OF THEM?
20, 21, 22...
ARE YOU SURE
YOU WANNA DO THIS?
WHAT IF MOM WAS RIGHT?
WH-WH-WHAT IF-- WHAT IF
THE MAN WASN'T THE AUTHOR?
WHAT-- WHAT IF HE WAS
JUST THE GUY'S FATHER
OR SOMETHING?
SOUNDS LIKE A LOT
OF WHAT IFS.
WOULDN'T THAT MEAN
THAT THE REAL KILLER'S
STILL OUT THERE?
Robin:
DID YOU HEAR SOMETHING?
YOU'RE STARTING
TO SOUND LIKE ME, KIDDO.
( clangs )
GIMME THE LIGHT.
( gasps )
OH, MY--
OKAY, WE GOTTA GO.
GO!
GIVE ME THE LIGHT.
LET'S GET OUT
OF HERE.
- Robin: THERE'S ONE
RIGHT THERE.
- WHERE?
( tires screech )
YOU STAY HERE!
Woman: 911.
What's your emergency?
YOU NEED TO SEND SOMEONE
TO CASANOVA'S PARK.
IS THIS YOUR IDEA
OF A JOKE?
IT'S EMPTY.
WHAT?
IT WAS RIGHT THERE.
WE'RE NOT CRAZY.
WE CIRCLED EVERY 23rd WORD
ON EVERY 23rd PAGE
- AND IT TOLD US
TO COME DOWN HERE.
- YEAH.
AND I SOUND
COMPLETELY CRAZY,
DON'T I?
Policeman:
JUST GET SOME SLEEP, OKAY?
WE'RE DONE HERE.
10-23, U.T.L.
MOM.
OH, HONEY.
- LET'S GO HOME, OKAY?
- YEAH.
SKELETONS CAN'T JUST
GET UP AND WALK AWAY.
YOU WERE RIGHT.
THAT MAN WASN'T THE KILLER.
THE REAL KILLER
IS STILL OUT THERE
AND HE KNOWS DAD'S
ONTO HIM.
THE BOOK, IT'S GOT
ALL THESE-- THESE--
THESE SECRET MESSAGES
EVERY 23rd PAGE.
- HE'S RIGHT, EVERY 23rd
PAGE IN THE BOOK.
- Agatha: STOP IT!
- YES.
- BOTH OF YOU, STOP IT!
NOW LISTEN TO ME.
23 IS A NUMBER, OKAY?
THERE'S NO MAGICAL MEANING.
ONLY PEOPLE CAN
GIVE IT THAT.
AND I DON'T CARE
HOW MANY LUNATICS
ARE FANTASIZING ABOUT 23.
THEY'RE WRONG!
THERE'S NO CURSE.
THERE'S NO KILLER
RUNNING AROUND OUT THERE.
- ( brakes squeal )
- Walter: JESUS.
IT'S HIM.
THAT'S NED.
NASTY EVIL DEAD DOG.
- DAD!
- WALTER!
( screeching )
( panting )
YOU.
IT WAS YOU.
YOU MOVED THE SKELETON.
PLEASE DON'T DO
THIS, WALTER.
THEN HOW DID YOU KNOW,
UNLESS...
YOUR MAIDEN NAME
IS PINK.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT
PINK IS?
RED AND WHITE,
92 DIVIDED BY 4.
SOMEDAY I'M GONNA WRITE
A BOOK AND I'LL DO IT
TO SOMEBODY ELSE.
- WALTER.
- OH, GOD.
WHOEVER WROTE IT
KNOWS YOU VERY WELL,
AND ONLY THEY CAN GIVE
YOU YOUR ANSWERS.
YOU WROTE IT.
ISAAC KNEW ALL ALONG,
DIDN'T HE?
WALTER, JUST LET IT
BE, PLEASE.
YOU'RE TOPSY KRETTS.
HE MAY NOT
EVEN BE A MAN.
- DON'T MAKE ME DO THIS.
- WHY, AG?
WHY'D YOU DO THIS?
- WHO HAVE I BEEN
LIVING WITH?
- WALTER.
( chuckles )
WHAT'S THIS FOR, AG?
WHAT WERE YOU
GONNA DO WITH THIS?
I--
I TOOK IT
TO PROTECT US
FROM WHOEVER WE WERE
GONNA MEET AT THE MAILBOX
FACILITY.
INTENDING TO KILL THAT
POOR OLD MAN WHO YOU GOT
TO PUBLISH YOUR BOOK
AND PROTECT
YOUR LITTLE SECRET?
- I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT.
- HE WAS ALIVE BEFORE
YOU SENT US AWAY.
- ROBIN WILL HEAR YOU.
- OH, WE WOULDN'T WANT THAT,
WOULD WE?
WOULDN'T WANT OUR SON
TO KNOW THE HORRIBLE TRUTH
ABOUT HIS MOTHER.
MOM, DAD, WHAT'S GOING ON?
SHE'S TOPSY KRETTS.
SHE WROTE THE BOOK.
NO, IT'S NOT TRUE.
NOW YOUR FATHER'S GONNA
PUT DOWN THE KNIFE.
- AREN'T YOU, WALTER?
- TELL HIM THE TRUTH.
- WALTER.
- TELL HIM HOW YOU TOOK
THE SKELETON.
YES, ISAAC AND I
TOOK THE SKELETON.
- YOU DID?
- AND I'D DO IT AGAIN.
BUT I DID NOT
WRITE THE BOOK.
DON'T LIE.
13 YEARS, AG.
13 YEARS OF LIES!
- NO MORE.
- DON'T DO THIS TO US, WALTER.
- MOM, WHO WROTE THE BOOK?
- TELL HIM WHO WROTE IT.
TELL HIM.
YOU WROTE THE BOOK,
WALTER.
I FOUND THIS
WITH THE OLD MAN'S THINGS.
YOU PUT MY NAME
ON THIS.
NO.
NO NO NO NO NO.
YOU'RE LYING.
SHE'S LYING.
I DIDN'T-- I DIDN'T
WRITE THAT.
THEN WHO DID?
YOU.
IT WAS BOTH OF YOU
ALL THE WAY ALONG,
WASN'T IT?
- NO.
- WHAT IS THIS?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
Robin: DAD.
DAD, WHAT'S HAPPENING?
WALTER, WE CAN
GET YOU HELP.
Fingerling:
THE WOMAN IN RED.
Suicide Blonde:
AND THIS IS SUPPOSED TO MAKE
ME FEEL BETTER HOW?
OH MY GOD.
SHIT!
WALTER.
NO!
GET OUT OF HERE!
GET YOUR CAR.
COME ON.
- Robin: LET'S GO.
- COME ON, HONEY.
( typewriter bell dings )
( gasps )
Walter's voice:
"CHAPTER 23:
YOU CAN CALL
ME FINGERLING,
BUT MY REAL NAME
IS WALTER.
WALTER PAUL SPARROW.
WHAT YOU HAVE READ SO FAR
IS NOT THE WHOLE TRUTH.
MUCH HAS BEEN CHANGED
TO PROTECT THE INNOCENT
AND THE GUILTY.
I ONCE READ THAT
THE ONLY PHILOSOPHICAL
QUESTION THAT MATTERS
IS WHETHER OR NOT
TO COMMIT SUICIDE.
I GUESS THAT MAKES ME
A PHILOSOPHER.
YOU COULD SAY
IT WAS MY INHERITANCE.
AFTER MY MOTHER'S DEATH
MY FATHER COULDN'T COPE.
( gunshot )
HE DIDN'T LEAVE A NOTE.
JUST A NUMBER.
THAT NUMBER FOLLOWED ME
FROM FOSTER HOME
TO FOSTER HOME,
TILL COLLEGE
WHEN I MET HER.
LAURA TOLLINS.
( panting )
( chuckles )
DO IT TIGHT.
PRETEND THAT
YOU HAVE A KNIFE.
I GOT A KNIFE.
CUT MY SHIRT.
- I'LL CUT YOU SOME MORE.
- ARE YOU?
YEAH, I'LL CUT YOU.
( panting )
CUT ME.
Walter's voice:
"I LOVED HER."
ONE LITTLE-KNOWN...
Walter's voice:
"AND I THOUGHT SHE LOVED ME."
...ESOTERIC PROCESSION
OF THE NUMBER 23.
DOES A THING ITSELF
HAVE A MYSTICAL POWER?
- DOES THAT EQUATE?
- YES, THAT-- THAT'S--
THAT'S THE...
Walter's voice:
"UNTIL MY FATHER'S NUMBER
RETURNED TO HAUNT ME."
ARE YOU INSANE?
Walter's voice:
"THAT FUCKING NUMBER."
( moaning )
"WHEN I CIRCLED EVERY
23rd LETTER OF HER NOTE...
IT BECAME CLEAR."
( crying )
"THE NUMBER HAD
GONE AFTER ME.
- AND NOW IT WANTED HER."
- ( knocking on door )
LAURA, THIS ROOM--
YOU GOTTA GET OUT.
- IT'S COMING FOR YOU.
I CAN'T STOP IT.
- WHAT?
- THE NUMBER.
- NO NO NO NO NO.
- LEAVE ME ALONE.
YOU THINK YOU HAVE
THE GUTS TO USE IT?
GO AHEAD.
KILL ME.
I LOVE YOU.
I NEVER LOVED YOU,
EVER.
HOW COULD I?
HOW COULD ANYONE?
YOU'RE PATHETIC.
JUST LIKE YOUR FATHER.
- GET OUT!
- ( screams )
LAURA.
LAURA!
LAURA!  LAURA!
LAURA! LAURA!
LAURA!
Walter's voice:
I WAS RIGHT.
SHE WAS IN DANGER.
I JUST DIDN'T REALIZE
THE DANGER WAS ME."
IT'S GONNA BE ALL RIGHT.
I JUST DIDN'T REALIZE
THE DANGER WAS ME."
( sobbing )
( panting )
HEY, LAURA.
LAURA?
Walter's voice:
"WHAT BEGAN AS A SUICIDE NOTE
TURNED INTO
SOMETHING MORE..."
( screaming )
SHH--
GET THE--
"...MUCH, MUCH MORE."
( mumbling )
23.
THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
23. 23.
23.
23, 23.
FUCK IT, FUCK IT.
I CAN SEE IT.
IT'S EVERYWHERE.
NO MORE FUN AND GAMES.
LAURA.
( mumbling )
SHIT!
THIS FUCKING...
IT'S NOT TRUE.
IT'S NOT
TRUE.
HE DOES NOT--
DOES NOT--
I LOVE YOU...
MORE THAN ANY OF...
PERIOD, EXCLAMATION.
REMEMBER THIS?
( glass shatters )
Walter's voice:
"THEY THOUGHT IT WAS
THE FALL..."
HE DOESN'T REMEMBER ANYTHING.
IT'S NOT UNCOMMON IN CASES
OF SUCH SEVERE HEAD INJURY.
HE COULD RECOVER
HIS MEMORY TOMORROW
OR NEVER.
WELL, OF COURSE YOU
HAVE TO FACTOR IN THE HISTORY
OF MENTAL INSTABILITY
OF THE PATIENT'S FAMILY.
HIS OWN FATHER
ATTEMPTED SUICIDE.
HE JUST MANAGED
TO BE A LITTLE MORE
SUCCESSFUL AT IT.
Walter's voice:
"...BECAUSE THE TRAUMA OF LAURA
APPEARED TO BE FICTION."
- AND ALL THAT SCRIBBLING?
- SEVERE GRAPHOMANIA.
THE RANTINGS
OF A DELIRIOUS MIND.
SOME SORT OF A SURVIVOR'S
GUILT MIXED UP
WITH A NUMEROLOGY
OBSESSION.
YOU HAVE YOUR
HANDS FULL, DOCTOR.
MMM.
I'LL DO WHAT I CAN.
SAY, UH, MAY I
HAVE THIS BOOK?
THANK YOU.
Walter's voice:
"MY NOVEL,
MY CONFESSION,
- I NEVER SAW IT AGAIN."
- MY NAME IS DR. NATHANIEL.
"SOME INJURIES
CAN BE HEALED OVER TIME.
SOME ARE JUST
TOO HARD TO DEAL WITH.
SO MY BRAIN
JUST BLOCKED OUT
THE TERRIBLE THING
I HAD DONE
AND THE REASONS WHY."
- TAKE CARE.
- I HOPE I NEVER
SEE YOU AGAIN.
- I HOPE NOT. I HOPE NOT.
DON'T COME BACK, FELLA.
- OKAY.
- OOH! OH MY GOD.
I'M SO SORRY.
- OH!
OH, NO.
Walter's voice:
"AGATHA KNEW NOTHING
ABOUT MY PAST."
OH, YOU OWE ME
A CAKE.
Walter's voice:
"THAT MADE TWO OF US.
I WAS FREE FOR NOW,
BUT THE NUMBER
FOUND A NEW VICTIM.
THE NUMBER LEFT ME ALONE
FOR 13 YEARS...
UNTIL THE NIGHT
SHE FOUND MY BOOK,
OR THE BOOK
FOUND HER."
THIS IS WHERE
I WROTE IT ALL.
IT WAS ME.
I'M A MURDERER.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
HAPPENED TO YOU,
BUT I DO KNOW THIS:
YOU WEREN'T A BAD PERSON
WHO GOT BETTER;
YOU WERE A SICK PERSON
WHO BECAME WELL.
I KILLED
LAURA TOLLINS.
THERE'S AN INNOCENT MAN
IN PRISON BECAUSE OF ME.
YOU'RE A WONDERFUL
HUSBAND,
AND YOU'RE THE BEST FATHER
A SON COULD EVER HAVE.
AND WHAT WOULD ROBIN DO
WITHOUT YOU?
YOU KNOW I CAN'T LET
AN INNOCENT MAN GO
ON SUFFERING
FOR MY HORRIBLE SIN.
WE'RE ALL BROKEN,
WALTER.
REMEMBER, YOU TOLD ME
YOUR LIFE STARTED
WHEN YOU MET ME?
WELL, MY LIFE
- BEGAN THAT DAY, TOO.
- YOU DIDN'T KNOW
WHO I WAS.
I DIDN'T KNOW
- I WANT YOU
TO LEAVE, AG.
- NO.
- YOU NEED
TO LEAVE BEFORE...
- NO.
BEFORE WHAT?
BEFORE YOU KILL ME?
DAMN IT, WALTER.
LOOK, THIS...
THIS IS WHO YOU WERE.
THIS IS NOT
WHO YOU ARE.
- THIS IS NOT
WHO YOU ARE!
- I'M A KILLER!
I HAVE KILLED SOMEONE.
I KILLED SOMEONE.
I COULD DO IT AGAIN.
YOU THINK YOU COULD
DO IT AGAIN? YOU THINK
YOU'RE A KILLER?
HERE, THEN TAKE THIS.
YOU GO AHEAD AND DO IT.
IF YOU'RE A KILLER,
THEN KILL ME!
LOOK AROUND AT ALL
THE BEAUTIFUL 23s.
YOU DON'T WANT
TO DISAPPOINT THEM,
DO YOU?
DO IT!
( crying )
I LOVE YOU.
NO, DON'T YOU SAY THAT.
- I LOVE YOU.
- NO, YOU CAN'T!
NOBODY CAN.
( horn honking )
DAD!
Walter's voice:
THERE'S NO SUCH THING
AS DESTINY.
THERE ARE ONLY
DIFFERENT CHOICES.
IT'S JUST A NUMBER.
Walter's voice:
SOME CHOICES ARE EASY;
SOME AREN'T.
THOSE ARE THE REALLY
IMPORTANT ONES,
THE ONES THAT DEFINE US
AS PEOPLE.
THE LORD IS MY SHEPHERD.
THERE IS NOTHING I LACK.
IN GREEN PASTURES,
YOU LET ME GRAZE.
TO SAFE WATERS, YOU LEAD ME.
YOU RESTORE MY...
Walter's voice:
13 YEARS AGO I MADE
THE WRONG CHOICE...
GUIDE ME ALONG
THE RIGHT PATH FOR THE SAKE...
Walter's voice:
I NEEDED TO PUT IT RIGHT,
AND NOT JUST
FOR MY SAKE.
TO DIE THERE IN THE STREET
WOULD HAVE BEEN EASY,
BUT IT WOULDN'T
HAVE BEEN JUSTICE,
AT LEAST NOT THE JUSTICE
FATHERS TEACH THEIR SONS ABOUT.
I'LL BE SENTENCED
IN A WEEK OR SO.
MY LAWYER SAYS
THE JUDGE WILL LOOK
KINDLY UPON ME
FOR TURNING MYSELF IN.
MAYBE IT'S NOT
THE HAPPIEST OF ENDINGS,
BUT IT'S THE RIGHT ONE.
SOMEDAY I'LL BE UP
FOR PAROLE
AND WE CAN GO ON
LIVING OUR LIVES.
IT'S ONLY A MATTER
OF TIME.
OF COURSE, TIME'S JUST
A COUNTING SYSTEM--
NUMBERS...
WITH MEANING ATTACHED
TO THEM.
( ticking )
ISN'T IT?
( rock music playing )
* I'VE GOT ME
A BADGE *
* A BRIGHT, SHINY
BADGE *
* I'M PAINTING
THE CREST *
* IN YELLOW
AND BLUE *
* I'VE GOT ME A CLUB *
* AN EXCLUSIVE CLUB *
* DOESN'T INCLUDE A PLACE
FOR YOU *
* HEY *
* HELLO, NEIGHBOR *
* RIGHT YOU ARE *
* IT'S IN THE WAY
THAT YOU WALK *
* ALL OF THE CHANGES,
ALL THE MISTAKES *
* IT'S IN THE DEMANDS *
* YOU CONSTANTLY MAKE *
* IT'S IN THE WAY
THAT YOU GRIEVE *
* ALL OF THE LOSS *
* YOU DON'T KNOW
WHEN YOU'RE BETTER OFF *
* OR AT WHAT COST *
* YOU'VE GOT IT GOOD *
* THE BANALITY *
* OF EVIL *
* BENEVOLENT MOTHER *
* SMOTHER THE CHILD *
* THE PERPETRATORS ARE
IN DENIAL *
* THE BANALITY *
* OF EVIL *
* KING OF THE CASTLE *
* ROOM AT THE TOP *
* OFF WITH THEIR HEADS *
* CHOP 'EM OFF *
* THE BANALITY *
* OF EVIL *
* BENEVOLENT MOTHER *
* SMOTHER THE CHILD *
* THE PERPETRATORS ARE
IN DENIAL *
* THE BANALITY *
* OF EVIL *
* KING OF THE CASTLE *
* ROOM AT THE TOP,
OFF WITH THEIR HEADS *
* CHOP 'EM OFF *
* THE BANALITY *
* OF EVIL *
* OF EVIL. *
( orchestral music playing )