How are you doing?
- Ready for this?
- Hell, yeah, we're ready for it!
You seem ready!
Well, okay!
SATAN
Tonight, at Styxx Club,
we're going to start some shit!
Tomorrow's Christmas Eve,
but we don't give a fuck about holidays!
LORD, DO NOT FORGIVE THEM,
FOR THEY KNOW WHAT THEY DO
Damn, Bart!
There's some bitches in tonight. Look!
The party's real fly! Lots of people tonight!
- No, it's not fly.
- Dope party!
- Where are the bottles?
- What bottles? We just ordered two of them!
- Nice shirt!
- Don't touch!
- Five minutes ago.
- Two bottles?
Didn't we ask for two bottles?
Five minutes ago?
It's our last night.
We want to bust out tonight!
- They should be here by now.
- I'll be back in five. Lf...
- What are you doing?
- Chill, homie!
- Sit down and shut the fuck up!
- Whatever!
- Yasmine, give me a vodka!
- Got money?
- No.
- Then no.
- Just one, for Christmas!
- I've been hooking you up all night!
Yasmine, not going to introduce me?
Sorry. Eve, a childhood friend.
Eve, this is Thaiii.
Yo, Ladj!
Last one!
- Ladj, Eve.
- What's up?
Eve, Ladj.
Want to dance?
- What's up, Yasmine?
- Hi.
Want a drink?
- What?
- A drink?
I'm going to go change. Meet me outside.
I need fresh air.
Hope you dug it because
I got a fucking Christmas gift for you all!
Barbarian bastards!
- Want to dance?
- I'm okay.
I didn't ask if you're okay.
I asked if you want to dance, bitch.
Your breath reeks!
- Got a phone number?
- No.
You think I'm going to buy that,
you ugly skank?
- Back off, moron!
- "Back off, moron."
- Back off!
- Are you crazy? That's enough!
- Stop it!
- Bring it on, asshole!
What's your problem? Get off me!
- Get your hands off me, motherfucker!
- Be cool! Be cool!
Out of the way! Get away! Move!
- I work with Byron.
- Since when?
What's going on?
Why are you pushing him?
Got a problem?
What's your problem?
Easy. Easy. Go on, beat it.
- Bart, are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Is it bleeding a lot?
- A lot.
- Give me a handkerchief.
- Just a minute.
There's a lot?
- What happened?
- Cocksucking bartender!
- Bart, you got your ass kicked?
- No, it was that guy...
- You started that mess.
- He busted a bottle in my face.
- Damn! He got you good!
- No big deal.
Come on, let's get out of here.
We're not going to stick around all night.
What do you mean? Are you crazy?
We're not going home, are we?
Girls, any ideas?
We can go to my place if you want,
in the country.
Got a ride?
They're assholes in that club!
Real pussies! He's a pussy!
Get out. Now.
- I'll beat your ass, you damn dog!
- Move it, Bart!
Move it. Move it.
- That dog reeks!
- Like his owner!
You think your shit don't stink?
- Damn, I'm low on gas.
- Go to lvry Garage.
- Who's got dough?
- I'm broke.
- Anyone got any aspirin?
- Sorry. Payday's next week.
- My head hurts.
- Fucking cheapskates.
Sorry. I'm broke, too.
Who cares? Let's gas and dash.
- I'm going to grab some food.
- Go on.
What's gas and dash?
- Give me that.
- What are you doing with my scarf?
Boss.
Can you fill up number 4, please?
- There.
- Thanks.
When is Christmas?
- When is Christmas?
- It's tomorrow, asshole.
You don't even know what day it is?
About that chick, are you going to hit that?
Don't worry. She's going to get it tonight.
Wait. Wait!
Let's go.
Now.
You little shits!
What is it?
Faggots!
- Take that side street!
- Slower! Slower! Slower!
Put some music on.
- Want some candy?
- I want to go home!
- What about me?
- Have one, too!
Go! Go!
Step on the gas! Fuck!
- Ladj! Ladj!
- Don't throw your candy on me!
Tyson, you want a cookie?
Don't feed him that shit!
Are you crazy or what?
Wake up, Bart!
Fuck, Bart!
Wake up!
- What?
- We're there.
- What's going on?
- The goats are blocking the road.
Hit the gas! Who gives a fuck?
Don't move. Stay there.
Stay.
What the fuck?
- Where's your crib?
- Over there.
- Yasmine, I think I love you.
- Quit it.
- I dreamt about your tits.
- Dream on.
- I was about to kiss you, and I woke up.
- Drop it.
You're so cute.
- Can't we fool around a little?
- You're retarded.
Bart, check out that one.
Come here. Look at that face.
Come here. Looks nasty.
Must have been in an accident.
I hold you
You hold me
By the goatee
The first one to grin
Gets a slap in the face
Motherfucking...
Are you crazy?
What are you looking at? Dirty bitch!
- You, too! Get away!
- Have you lost your mind?
- Get away!
- Bart, got yourself in a fight again?
Come on. What?
I told you last time to call me
when you're in trouble, and you got beat up.
I'm here now. You won't get beat up again.
Go for it!
Which one smacked you?
Tell me which one.
- He wants a fight or something?
- I'm kidding.
I don't care.
This is Joseph, the housekeeper.
Hi.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Hi.
Thaiii.
What's up?
- Marc.
- No, Bart.
- And Yasmine.
Hello.
Little Turk. She's pretty.
Big tits or what?
- That's Catherine.
- She's got milk?
Best in the county. Famous everywhere.
- Who wants some?
- Me.
- Chink?
- No, thanks.
- Your turn.
- I don't like milk.
- There, Marc.
- Yo! What's up?
- What's your problem?
- What?
- It's a joke.
I'm not joking with you.
Come on, let's go!
That guy's weird.
He looks like a dim-witted perv.
What's a perv?
You know, a pervert.
You stay there.
- Hit the gas!
- Go, Bart! Bart, push!
Forget about it.
We're fucked. Boss, got a vehicle?
- Get in, Bart!
- Come on, open the door!
- Bart! Bart!
- Come on! Come on!
- Stop teasing me! Quit it!
- Bart!
Stop playing around!
Ladj, you're crazy. He chased a goat,
and he sucked the milk out of its udder.
Then he sheared its hair
to make some boots.
Tyson, come here. Come.
Welcome.
This crib is fly!
You're a rich girl. What do your folks do?
My mum died giving birth to me,
and my dad hung himself.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm joking. Cheer up!
- What's this workshop?
- Hold on.
- Are your folks here?
- No, why?
No reason.
What's this workshop?
Dad owned a doll store. This is his stock.
- Dope couch!
- Want a tour?
- I ain't moving.
- Me, neither.
Got to rest.
- Coming, Yasmine?
- Sure.
Ladj, you're coming.
The toilet, my room, Joseph's rooms.
- He lives here?
- Sure. Let's go upstairs.
It's massive!
My parents' bedroom.
Coming?
- Nice bed.
- Come on.
- I saved the best for last.
- What is it?
You'll see.
Dad's collection.
It's beautiful.
Come on.
Bart, check it out.
So your folks are gone for the evening?
What's with the hand?
Acting all coy, huh?
Look for trouble, and you're going to find it.
Eve. Eve, stop it.
Your parents aren't here,
so you want to be naughty, huh?
That's what happens
when you get me started.
Take it like a big girl, like that.
Not acting like a grown-up now?
Hello, ma'am.
- You saw someone?
- Yeah.
You stay here.
Bart, check it out.
- Crazy blade, huh?
- Let me see it.
Don't touch! Leave it alone.
We saw a lady.
That's Marie, the housekeeper's wife.
She's pregnant. Be quiet.
- We were quiet.
- Want to see the greenhouse?
Don't worry, baby.
It'll all be ready for your birth.
Daddy's picking you some nice clothes
and beautiful eyes.
- That one's crazy.
- That's the slipper orchid. Come see.
Has to have pure water.
Brought you some milk.
Sir, I already told you. I don't like milk.
That's for reproduction.
The male insect works his way in there
and fertilises it.
Wild!
- It's hot.
- It's from the hot spring.
The hot spring's warm water
makes these plants grow so luscious.
Yo, Eve, Thaiii, want to go to the hot spring?
The two of us can go, if you want.
- Thaiii! Not just the two of us, sir.
- Why not?
We can swim there. I swear, it's very warm.
Trust me. That way, I can show you around.
Come on. Let's go, buddy.
Eve, he's nuts. No sir, please.
- Later.
- But it's really warm!
No one's around. You can skinny dip.
We all do it, even me!
Stop kissing ass!
- Lf not, I can lend you trunks.
- Bart!
Let go!
Fuck!
Look what you did!
Cut it out!
Shut up!
Guys, come here.
Yasmine, hold him tight, or they'll fight.
Don't worry.
My girl's sweating me. Let's roll.
Who's the boss? She got you tamed?
- Nobody tames me.
- So shut up.
So we're going to the hot spring?
Get away from my car!
- This is Gilou.
- Hey, Gilou.
Hey, Gilou.
Shall we go?
Bart, come here.
- Why are you cock blocking?
- What?
Don't act stupid.
I see what you're up to with Yasmine.
- You're nuts. I don't care about Yasmine.
- Hit on Eve, but leave Yasmine alone.
What?
- Who's that?
- You like her?
Want to fuck her?
Jeanne! Come on over! Come here!
- This is Bork.
- It's Bart.
- Marc.
- Hey, Marc.
- No, Bart. Nice to meet you.
- Hey, Bart.
This is Jeanne.
What's that?
- You want to know everything, don't you?
- What were you saying?
You two getting acquainted?
- Going to the hot spring?
- Right.
- Like her?
- Sure.
She's my niece.
- See you there?
- Right.
- That's all you got for me?
- Come on, Bart.
Bart!
What?
Watch it, motherfucker.
Are you fucking blind?
Go, Gilou!
Quit it! Fuck!
- It's warm.
- It is.
- Hurry. It's nice and hot.
- Like you.
- Come on.
- Damn!
- Coming in, Bart?
- I don't want to.
Where is he?
Joseph!
Dive under!
Something bit me!
Little Turk.
Did you get scared?
The little Turk got scared.
Gilou, come here a sec.
You want to take a hike?
Come here, you.
I saved your life.
- Is it because of me?
- What?
Titty hard-on.
- Stop.
- Stop what?
You don't like it?
Okay, enough, already!
What are you doing?
Knock it off. Get off me.
What are you doing? Go over there!
Why are you touching him like that?
Stop! Stop!
- What are you doing?
- You want to turn me on?
- Stop repeating.
You're insane.
Easy.
Fuck!
- What are you doing?
- That's enough! Stop it! Stop it!
Come on! Stop it! Fuck!
What's the matter? Want something?
- Are you talking to me?
- Who else?
What's up?
- Want to duel?
- I'm down.
Go for it.
Bring it on.
- It's on!
- Yeah! It's on!
- Bart.
- What?
Come get it.
- Want to hop on my shoulders?
- What?
On my shoulders?
- Think I'm a fag?
- Come on, Bart!
- I'm not doing it.
- Come on!
Come on, Marc. Come on, Marc.
- Go on, Marc.
- No way. That's enough.
- Go, Bart! Go, Bart! Go, Bart!
- No, no.
Let's go. Hop on my shoulders.
Only if we switch teams after.
Go! Go!
You cunt! Stop laughing!
Are you crazy?
Stop laughing, you stupid cunt!
Shut up, or I'll smack you, bitch!
- Chill out!
- What?
What, you want to be Rambo?
Don't tell me to chill out!
Get away!
- Look here, Barto.
- Leave me alone!
What the fuck am I supposed to do now?
- Careful, Ladj, you'll burn yourself.
- Don't worry.
Feel better?
Bart. Bart!
Get your dog out of here. Bart, get him out.
- Here.
- Thanks.
- Quit it!
- Isn't Bart cute?
Joseph's getting you dry clothes.
See, my darling?
You can come into this world,
just like I promised.
Your gift's almost ready.
Daddy's taking care of everything.
Marie, the scissors.
Hey, Yasmine!
- Who wants an apple?
- No, thanks.
- Yasmine?
- What?
Give me a massage.
- Watch it!
- What? I just wanted a rub.
- Want to help me get some wood?
- Sure.
- Leave the lovebirds to it.
- Whatever.
- Two's enough.
- We need more.
Get the clean ones, at least. Those are dirty.
Not too many!
- One more.
- Forget it.
- Now we're good.
- Take that one off!
- Fuck!
- What?
- Bart!
There's a snake. Don't send him my way!
- There it is!
- What are you doing? Get it away from me!
- What do you want me to do?
- Get it away! Stop playing!
What the hell are you doing?
What's wrong with you?
It's a Tarasque. They're almost extinct.
- I didn't mean to...
- You want me to tread on you, too?
- I just panicked.
- Go.
- Is he nuts?
- Help me pick them up.
Bart. Bart.
He disrespected you.
You're just going to sit there?
- He likes it.
- Really? You like being disrespected?
Leave him alone.
Next time, I'll mess him up.
Who does he think I am?
- A wimp.
- You're not a wimp. Have a bite.
- No thanks.
- Want a bite?
- A bite of you.
I'm crazy. No one fucks with me and my dog.
Tyson, come here! Shut up, Tyson!
What's that? Take that! Tyson, help me!
You want me to tread on you, too?
Sorry, sir. I panicked. I'm a wimp.
Leave me alone!
- Surprise downstairs!
- Coming.
Why make me look stupid?
You wimped out because you're a wimp.
I didn't say shit
because I saw he was an animal lover.
You were shitting yourself.
You broke my snake.
- Are you coming?
- Be right there.
Hello.
Baby, how are you?
I was going to call you.
"Baby, I was going to call you."
- I'm on the phone.
- "I can't stop thinking of you."
- Don't act like a kid.
- Stop it.
- Who's the boss?
Yeah.
We got held up.
Soon as my clothes are dry, I'm out.
What are you talking about?
- You heard me.
- It's on.
- What's on?
They act all easy, but they're dick teasers.
Teasers!
You say that because Ladj has got Yasmine,
and Eve's with me.
You're alone with your dog.
Looks like your only hope is Joseph.
Drop this Joseph shit!
Guys, Joseph brought us a present.
A young goat!
This food's making me feel sick.
- Your loss. It's tasty.
- Barto?
Delicious.
Joseph, you're the goat master!
Merry Christmas!
- Merry Christmas!
- Two and a three.
Wake up, sweet baby
Caresses and kisses
It's Christmas Eve
In Heaven and on Earth
Wake up, sweet baby
Caresses and kisses
Tonight's Christmas Eve
Encore! Encore! Encore!
Check out Jo-Jo!
- Why isn't your wife eating with us?
- That slut's a ball-breaker!
Your folks don't celebrate Christmas?
- I'm Muslim.
- So am I.
Same here.
Tyson and I converted, but I still eat pork.
- You're Muslim, too?
- No.
- You don't believe in God?
- That's not it.
My grandma was tortured in 'Nam.
She was fucked by sodding priests.
Religion's bullshit. Bullshit.
- Do you believe in God?
- Of course not.
- Why do you think you're here?
- Why?
My dad banged my mum, and now I'm here.
So what?
That's not what I'm asking.
Why are you here next to me?
Stop brainwashing him. Religion's bullshit.
- That's blasphemy. Have some respect.
- You're one to talk.
With a spliff in your mouth,
ready to gangbang?
Who are you to judge?
And you, serving booze
and shaking your ass for a living.
Working isn't in your religion?
- Who the fuck do you think you are?
- I've been busting my balls for 20 years,
and I have nothing to show for it.
God doesn't give a fuck about me.
I don't give a shit
if He fucks His own mother, either!
Don't talk like that, or I'll fuck you up!
Shit-face, the Sheitan's eating your brain.
He pushes us to sin.
He's everywhere, so don't talk like that.
- Who's the Sheitan?
- Satan.
The nigger's right!
If there's one thing
you ought to be scared of, it's Satan.
There was once a guy just like you, fearless.
Satan paid him a visit in his dreams
and asked him what he wanted to be.
The guy wanted to be invincible,
so Satan made him invincible.
Later that night,
well,
he climbed onto his sister
and fucked her like a pig!
Real deep!
But the next morning,
he realised she had a bun in the oven.
Pregnant.
Satan came back and told him,
"The rugrat,
who will be born on Christmas Eve
"when the church bells ring 12 times,
"it's my child," Satan said.
He told the guy, "You'll give him a gift."
Satan tells him,
"The gift for the nipper
"has to be..."
Look at the coon!
This shit makes me want to piss.
Where's the can?
The door at the end.
Fuck!
What's going on?
What is this?
What are you doing here?
What?
You got scared?
No.
Fearless, huh?
What's the matter, Bart?
What are you doing?
Joseph's driving me nuts,
acting like a psycho.
I've been telling you since the beginning.
He likes you. Seal the deal with him.
I'm not kidding.
Hold on. Come.
Come see. It's Eve's bedroom.
Come on, it's Eve's bedroom.
No!
Check it out.
Bart, wake up!
What is it?
Oh, shit!
Here's some pictures.
Isn't that adorable?
Her leotard with that camel toe.
Look at her mouth.
I bet her pussy's real fresh.
With a nice mouth like that,
she's got to have a fresh pussy.
- I don't agree.
- What are you talking about?
That girl, last summer?
- The Indian one?
- Not that one.
The one from the tent next to ours.
- She was ugly!
- You mean she was banging!
She had perky tits and the best ass.
- But she wasn't giving any away.
- No way!
Four days on her case and nothing!
She would only jerk me off, like that.
Finally, I'm like, "Heloise, we like
each other. Enough of this kid's stuff."
Know what she told me?
"Well, my folks are going out tonight."
That night,
we had the whole tent to ourselves.
Air mattress, ostrich down comforters.
I brought some vodka mixes
and got her drunk.
She gets wild.
I start unbuttoning her and going down.
She grabs my hand and says,
"I don't put out on the first night."
I start to suck on her titties,
and then I spot it.
- What?
- Her panties.
Fountain woman! Everything was drenched.
So I got suspicious.
I pulled down her panties,
slowly spread her legs, and there it was,
a fucking cold-cut platter!
I've never seen anything like it.
Disgusting! A cockscomb!
Flesh hanging everywhere, dripping.
- And then...
- No!
I did my thing.
- That's why your breath stinks!
- It stinks?
Get out of here. What are you doing?
Thaiii! Bart!
Thaiii?
What's this?
Are you upstairs? You here?
Bunch of jerks!
You guys are jerks.
- What did you do, Bart?
- I didn't do shit.
Who messed with my dad's dolls?
- It wasn't me. Word to Allah.
- It's not funny!
- Chill. Sit down.
- Bastards.
You think we want to play with dolls?
- We were just watching TV. Relax.
- Bastards.
- You cold?
- A little.
- Want some heat?
- Yeah.
- It's not working.
- It's all right.
- Where are you from?
- Algeria.
Algerian?
I never dated one before.
- You speak Arabic?
- A little.
Go ahead.
- Sounds like Chinese!
- Really?
Yeah.
- I really like you.
- Really? That's sweet.
Yo, Sheitan's video!
Think I'm cute?
Be honest.
- A little bit.
- A bit?
- Yeah, but...
- Just a bit?
- What?
- Nothing.
Kiss me.
- What?
- It's that...
You don't want to kiss me?
That shit's the bomb, bro!
This shit is wild!
Sorry. Back in two seconds.
Baby!
I'll call you back later.
- Where do I sleep?
- My parents' bedroom.
- Be up in a sec.
- Me, too.
- Yasmine.
- What?
- Seen Joseph?
- Why, you miss him?
Wait up.
Let me have a piece of that, bro.
Stop jocking her.
What are you talking about?
She's the one jocking me.
If I'm sexier than you,
blame it on Mother Nature.
You're going to leave me hanging?
Drop it. She's feeling me.
Let me warm her up, then you get a bite,
just like we agreed.
I don't want to do that.
- Makes me look like a loser.
- You are a loser.
- Here, towel and bubble bath.
- Thanks.
- So?
- What?
What's up?
I'm glad you're here.
Me, too.
See you later.
I miss you, too.
I don't know. They're barbarians.
Forget about it. Yeah. Yeah.
I love you very much.
You want to play with your dolls?
I'd rather play doctor.
You smell good.
Can I unbutton that?
Let me unbutton that!
- You're a pain.
- Stop it, Bart.
- Give me your hand.
- It's a princess.
Here, my doll.
My favourite song.
Knock it off!
You're ruining the vibe because you think
I messed up the dolls, is that it?
- Whatever.
- I see what you two are up to. I'm out.
You're making me nervous.
What?
Quit it.
What are you doing?
Let's go to your room.
Ladj?
Ladj, is that you?
Shit!
- Baby?
- Fuck!
Ladj, you're starting to piss me off
with that phone!
Whose voice is that?
Nothing. It's the TV.
At least put the light on!
Fuck. It's nothing. It's the TV.
Baby? Hello?
Fuck.
Yasmine, come here. Hurry up.
What?
Word to Allah,
Joseph was spying on Eve's room.
Go take a bath instead of talking nonsense.
What? Do I stink?
Like it in the dark?
- Real nice.
- Yeah, right.
Get her out of there! Get her out!
Come here! Fuck!
Yasmine! Come!
Is it ready?
Almost.
Come on.
Only the eyes are missing.
Where's the boy?
In her bedroom.
Joseph, he's moving.
It's almost time.
Let's roll.
- Jerks!
- What?
- It's that bastard.
- Who?
Your housekeeper. I saw him.
- Go in front.
- You go.
You've got the stick. Go.
Come out of there!
Come on!
- Stop running!
- What was that?
The guy from the spring.
There.
I'm going to fuck you up!
Hey, baby. You're here, baby?
Baby.
Little baby.
Damn it! Your cell phone!
Hello?
No reception!
I'm going to fuck you up!
- Either hide or come with me!
- Hurry up! Hurry up!
I'm going to fuck you up, motherfucker!
I'm going to stuff your mother!
Get on!
- There they are!
- Just give up!
What's going on?
Hail Mary, full of Grace, the Lord is
with thee. Blessed art thou among women,
and blessed is the fruit
of thy womb, Jesus...
Please, take care of the boy.
- What's going on?
- They played a prank on us.
Where's Bart?
They left.
What the hell?
What have you done?
Where are you going?
Why did you do that?
Why?
You want to blow it?
Stop, Joseph! Stop! Stop!
Stop! Stop! You'll kill him! Let go of him!
I'll be out front.
Fuck!
What the hell is going on?
Come here, big dog.
Leave him!
Tyson! Get off of him! Tyson! Tyson!
Get off of him!
Come here!
Where's Bart?
Come back! Over here!
Come back!
Where is he?
Tyson. Tyson.
Hurry, Bart! What are you doing?
Get in the fucking car! Come on!
Your eyes!
Your eyes, damn it!
Ladj!
What are you doing? Pull over.
Are you deaf? Stop the car!
- Get out of my car!
- What?
If you want to get her, get out!
Are you deaf or what?
Get out of my fucking car!
- But...
- No buts! Get out!
Yasmine!
Yasmine?
Tyson?
Tyson, what are you doing?
It's all right. It's all right.
Don't move.
What happened?
- Yasmine, where were you?
- Where was I? Here with Ladj.
- You okay?
- You okay, Bart?
Ladj!
You okay?
I'll be back. I'll be right back.
- Thaiii!
- You got your ass kicked?
- Where is she?
- Who?
The chick I was with?
Everything's under control.
- What happened?
- Got a bottle in my face.
No biggie. I've got to run.
The chick's waiting for me.
- All right. Ladj.
- Got to go, too. My lady's breaking my balls.
Rascal!
You're leaving him like this?
He deserved it.
The tough guy learnt his lesson.
See you later.
- Ladj, we have to take him to the hospital.
- I'll be all right.
Ladj, let's take him.
Let's go, pain in the ass.
I'm sure there's something in my eye.
- You got in a fight?
- Yeah.
Dangerous, especially with bottles.
It doesn't look too serious.
Okay. Don't open your eyes.
I'm pulling off the gauze.
There.
It's clean now.
Bring me anticholinergic
and a dose of phenylethylamine.
Two, maybe three stitches.
No big deal.
Thanks, Marie.
Ladj, let's go. They're all crazy in here.
Go away. I'm sick of you.
- Let's go!
- Shut the fuck up!
Shut the fuck up, son of a bitch!
Get out of here!
Henry, double dose of Prostatonin,
nine milligrams.
Benoît, gauze. No, that's wine.
- Relax.
- What's happening?
Calm down.
You're dreaming, Bart.
It's just as good.
It's a dream.
Calm down.
Joseph's driving me nuts,
acting like a psycho.
What's wrong?
The Sheitan is eating your brain.
- Who's the Sheitan?
- Satan.
I climbed on my sister
and fucked her like a pig!
Why are you here next to me?
Sweet baby
Open wide your pretty eyes
Your eyes, Barto.
Shut up. Shut up.
Let's sing and dance
It's Christmas Eve
In Heaven and on Earth
Wake up, Sweet baby
Open wide your pretty eyes