Mom?
Oh, my God!
Push it the other way.
Come on, guys, push it!
Move when you got the ball!
Nobody's moving.
Know where your teammates are!
All right, hold up. Hold it up.
New ball. We are going
to play with this ball.
- Invisiball.
Catch.
It's pretty funny. You
think it's pretty silly.
This is the place it's okay to feel silly,
the practice floor.
Not with people
in the stands watching you play.
All right, you guys. Run a couple plays.
Let's set it up. Three game.
- Where's the ball?
- It's in my mind, Coach.
- It is in your mind.
- It's in my mind.
One brain! One brain!
There you go! That's the way to move it!
You guys play better with the invisiball
than you do the real ball. I like it.
- Hey, kiddo.
- Hey, how are you?
Good, how are you?
You spaz. Yeah, I was there all alone.
- Hi.
- Hey.
You're late.
Practice ran long.
Oh, uh, Clyde, shoes, please?
What is this?
I needed the extra space for the business.
We're officially up and running.
Hmm.
Yeah.
The jewelry design.
I told you I was getting back into it.
Stephanie, I had a bunch of stuff in here.
Oh, yeah, I boxed up all your stuff.
I put your name on it.
Everything's in the closet
right here in the hallway.
Don't you think maybe
I should have packed up
my stuff from my office?
Clyde, it's not your office any more.
Hey, kiddo. You ready to go?
Which one do you think is a better slogan?
"Stop The Killing, Eat Vegetables,"
or "When You Eat Animals,
You Become One"?
First of all, that is awesome,
but I'm going to say, as far as slogans go,
"Stop The Killing," it's super catchy.
- Gets the message across?
- Loud and clear.
Miss Shandy said that if we get
200 signatures on this petition,
she'll take it to the principal
and they'll consider doing
meat-free Mondays
in the cafeteria.
Wow, that's going to make you so popular.
Dad, you need to understand that
we're all one big family on this planet,
no matter what species,
and we don't eat our own family, do we?
No, we certainly do not.
- Hi, Clyde.
- Hey.
Careful, Brett.
You are entering a shoe-free zone.
I know.
I got that sign for Stephanie.
You wouldn't believe the bacteria
that gets dragged into a house.
Oh, I'm sure I wouldn't.
- Hey!
- Hi.
So what are you guys up to tonight?
- We're going to a concert.
- Nice.
Season tickets. Wagner.
Wagner? Stephanie loves
Wagner, don't you, dear?
I'll have 'em back Sunday after lunch.
Okay.
Um, Em's still doing the vegetarian thing,
so keep an eye on her,
and her allergies, please.
Last time she came back with hives.
And just healthy food, okay?
Stuff that grows on trees?
No pizza, please. I mean it.
You done?
Yes.
- Stephanie...
- Yes?
I think I got this.
- Okay.
- Bye you guys! I love you!
- Bye!
Brett says I have an overbite.
Oh, give me a break. Your teeth are fine.
Brett's job is to tell
people that they have bad teeth.
That's how he makes his money.
No, he said he'd fix my teeth for free.
Uh, Dad?
Yeah?
You passed your apartment.
Oh, I did, didn't I?
Ta-dah!
What is it?
What is it? This is our new house.
It's in the middle of nowhere.
Isn't it awesome?
And critters come over
from those woods over there.
Yesterday, two raccoons on our porch.
Really?
Come on, Mopey McGee.
Wow, this is pretty cool.
Right? Bedrooms are upstairs.
I call the room facing the woods!
You got it. That's your room.
Dad, there's a doggie door!
Let's get a dog from the shelter, Dad.
Please, let's get a dog.
Please, pretty please, please.
You've got to be kidding me.
This does not work on me any more.
Daddy, yes, it does.
Please, please, please, please.
Cheers.
- Cheers.
- Cheers, kiddo.
You know, I think
Mom would really like this house.
We should invite her for breakfast.
Em, Mom and Dad
are officially divorced
as of three months ago.
Mom's not coming over for pancakes.
- Hannah, that's enough.
- But it's getting old.
Em's always talking about how you guys
are going to get back together.
Em, your mom and I, we just sort of, uh...
I don't know. We kind of
forgot how to get along.
And you're both moving
on with your lives.
I know. That's what Mom
always says.
Your mom says that?
Okay, well, then, there you have it.
You know, it's for the best.
Okay? So let's have our dinner.
I'm not hungry any more.
All right, clear your plate.
Hannah...
You can't say stuff like that.
It's going to upset your sister.
For real? You're going to
blame this on me?
Nice, Dad.
"Will you walk a little faster,"
said the whiting to the snail.
"There's a porpoise close behind us,"
"and he's treading on my tail."
How was your day today?
It was all right. How was yours?
Dinner was a failure.
Well, just make sure that
Mom doesn't find out about dinner,
because she'll be mad
that pizza doesn't grow on trees.
I'll give you $5 if you
don't tell your mother.
Make it 35 and we have a deal.
Go to sleep.
Leave the door open.
What's the matter? Are you scared?
No. Just... I want it open, okay?
Dad, you need dishes.
You have one unheard message.
Oh, okay.
Hey, Clyde, it's Trevor down at NC.
Hey, give me a ring.
I wanted to run something past you.
Hope you're good, pal.
Dad, look! Look, I'm a lady.
Cool.
Daddy, can I get this?
That is a lovely hat.
Whatever you want, kiddo.
So we found a couple of things.
What's the damage?
- How about 55?
- 55.
My daughters have cleaned me out.
I have $48.
We're happy to put something back.
Oh, no. No, no. That's all right.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
So you're gettin'
rid of a lot of stuff.
You guys, uh, moving or something?
No. Just a
couple of bills came up.
Oh.
No! No!
Look at these carvings. They're so pretty.
These directions are ridiculous.
Hey, Em, would you do me a favor
and hand me the small screwdriver, please?
But, Daddy, you said
you'd get this open for me.
Well, that's weird. There aren't any seams.
What does that mean?
Well, I think that means
that whoever made this
didn't want anybody to open it,
or at least they didn't want
anybody to open it easily.
You hear that? There's something in there.
So somebody had to open it,
once upon a time.
- That is absolutely correct.
- Daddy, no. Daddy, please.
- Sweetie, I've gotta take this.
Trevor, hey.
Sorry, I keep missing your calls.
Daddy.
- How's my old friend doing?
- Good, good, uh...
- Daddy...
You're running a good program up there.
You've had two back-to-back
conference titles.
You calling just to chat?
The folks on our
athletic board are taking note.
Thought it was time
you come down to North Carolina,
have a discussion about your future.
What are we talking about here?
We're talking about you moving
up to Division One, Clyde.
Does Coach Hill know you're doing this?
He's retiring end of the year.
He was the one who told me
to get in touch with you.
Said the school needed
one of their own boys
to come back home and take the reins.
What can I say? Hell, yes, I'm interested.
- What's going on?
- I don't know. It wasn't me.
- - Dad!
- Hannah! What is it?
It was on my face! Get it off!
What are you talking about?
It's under the covers! Get it off!
Dad!
You did not just do that on my bed.
Hannah, you told me to kill it.
I told you to get it out.
God, Dad.
She told me to kill it.
It's a moth!
Make some noise
for the most dazzling divas of dance
who always bring it fierce,
the Silverstars!
Hey, are you okay?
- I feel funny.
- What?
I feel funny.
What do you mean?
I don't feel like me.
I know this stuff with Mom and Dad sucks,
but we're just the kids,
and they're the adults,
and sometimes we just have to go along
with their stupid mistakes.
But I think you'll feel better
if you just stopped giving a shit.
Hi! Hey! on...
Oh, hi, Mommy.
- I missed you guys a lot.
- I missed you, too, Mom.
How was the weekend?
It was good. We had pizza.
Wow, yes, the new house has a pizza tree.
- Is Jen's mom coming?
- Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Uh, your outfit is on your bed,
and will you just take
one of your allergy pills just in case?
If one of your players had food allergies,
you'd be writing
threatening notes to the cafeteria ladies
with detailed menu demands.
Cut me some slack.
I was going to go inside, get the boxes.
- Okay.
Hey, hey, what's going on with this guy?
Is he moving in, or what?
No. No, we're just dating.
You're just dating?
He's getting awfully
comfortable around here,
just bustling around the kitchen.
Back off, Clyde.
In his little antiseptic socks.
Yeah, well, at least he's present.
Excuse me?
You know, presence, attendance,
being in the moment,
as opposed to being absent.
Absent like you were the whole...
Stephanie, I know what it means.
- I was being a smart-ass.
- Just don't forget your stuff.
Yeah, fine.
Hello?
- Clyde, it's Trevor.
- Hey.
Got your plane ticket lined up,
and I'm going to have
the university send a car,
pick you up when you land.
Oh, you're rolling out the welcome.
You're going to love it.
Okay. Yeah, all right.
Well, thank you for calling.
Keep me informed, all right? Bye.
So she's in the middle row.
Hey, Dad, you know Hannah's
big dance performance
next week?
- Oh!
It's her first time in
front of a real audience.
- That's cool.
- Are you going to make it?
Heck, yes, I'm coming.
Mom will be there, so don't
feel obligated or anything.
Are you kidding me?
I'm going to be sitting in the front row.
What's this in your mouth?
Hannah, I told you your teeth were perfect.
No, you said it was my decision,
and I decided that
I don't want to go through life disfigured.
Disfigured?
Who said your teeth were disfigured?
I did. I'm totally disfigured.
It's horrible.
You are perfect.
Hannah.
- Dad!
- What is it? What's wrong?
Go back outside.
Is there someone in the house?
- Shh. Go.
Who's there?
Dad?
It's okay, you guys.
I think we have a raccoon.
Emily.
Em, breakfast is ready!
Ace!
Can't you hear me yelling for you?
Breakfast is ready.
Em.
What's wrong, Daddy?
First the announcer
comes out and he announces us,
and he's got, like,
the most obnoxious voice ever.
I don't know why they don't let me do it.
And he goes, like, "Make some noise"
"for the most dazzling divas of dance,
who always keep it fierce,"
"the Silverstars!"
And we all have
to wear our hair in a ponytail
so that we look the same,
because we're, like, the chorus and whatnot
with the can-can, so...
And I told Jen not to get her haircut,
because now it's too short
and her mom's making her get extensions...
Em, slow down.
And they use real human hair,
like, Indian and Asian hair.
I personally think that
that's really gross.
Em...
They sweep the hair
into these bins and then they weigh them,
and then they take them
to the special place
where they maneuver them
into, like, these wigs, and...
Em, slow down!
I'm sorry, Daddy! I'm sorry, Daddy!
- I'm really sorry!
- Go to your room.
What? Hannah, what happened?
In there!
Oh, my God.
My God.
Em? Stay there, Hannah.
Close the door. Close it!
Are you storing
any large amounts of fabrics,
cotton, silk, somewhere in the house?
Come on, man, you got to be kidding me.
I don't want
to be in that house any more.
Yeah, I know. Look, it's just moths.
Moths are like butterflies without colors.
Hey. are you okay?
What happened?
Creepy.
I had no idea that
moths were attracted to pizza and soda.
The pest control guy said
they can take care of it.
I'm still getting your
email on my computer.
- Want me to take care of it?
- Yes, please.
- How was Wagner?
- It was good. Interesting.
"Interesting."
You know, "interesting" is Stephanie code
for you fell asleep.
- No, I didn't.
- You totally fell asleep.
I didn't fall asleep.
Okay, I don't know what this file is.
What am I doing?
Don't you remember that?
That was the weekend
that the kids were in camp, remember?
- Good morning.
Did you sleep okay?
I did. It's a little hot in this house.
Oh, I do remember.
No.
What are you doing?
That was a weekend.
Oh, Lord.
Nice legs, I'll give you that.
Oh, God.
Remember when...
- What?
- Nothing. Never mind.
Okay.
All right, there you go.
I am successfully deleted
from your computer.
Thank you.
I've been meaning to ask you.
Have you...
Have you noticed
anything odd going on with Emily?
Like what?
I don't know. She...
She has these moments where
she just kind of checks out.
We've...
We've disrupted their whole lives.
It's going to be a while before anything's
normal again, right?
Yeah.
- Okay. I'll see you soon.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Where's the communication?
I don't hear anything out here.
You going to pass it?
No, you're going to shoot it.
Put 20 minutes on the clock.
We're going to run a
full half of basketball.
If I don't see some hustle,
we're all going to stay late and run lines.
Let's go. Let's move.
Hey, Coach, didn't you say
you had to be somewhere at 5:00?
- What time is it?
- Past that.
Make some noise
for the most dazzling divas of dance
who always bring it fierce,
the Silverstars!
Hannah, I'm so sorry
I missed your performance.
I screwed up.
I promise you I'm going
to make it up to you.
She's mad at you.
Yeah, I know.
Is my box all right?
It's fine.
I don't want you going near it.
Okay.
Because I'm the only one
allowed to touch it.
Hey, Em, what's the deal with the box?
Just don't touch it, okay?
Okay. I won't.
- Good night, Daddy.
- Good night, baby girl.
What the hell is this?
What's in this?
Give it back!
Give it back to me! Give it back to me!
Give it back to me!
No!
Emily has displayed some
unusual behavior in the past few weeks.
She is becoming distant from her friends,
not doing her assignments.
She seems to have lost interest in things
that were once so important to her.
Well, Em's been going through a lot lately.
- You moved recently.
- Yeah, I moved.
Stephanie has the girls at the same house
they grew up in most of the time.
How are things
in your new home?
Things are fine.
Fine, given the circumstances.
Circumstances?
We're divorced.
That's always tough on the kids, isn't it?
I think it would benefit Emily
to talk to someone about her feelings.
Feelings? I...
I talk to her about her
feelings all the time.
About everything.
Still,
she seems extremely frustrated.
She scared everybody
with that box, Mrs. Brenek.
A little time away from
it will do her good.
That just doesn't sound like Emily at all.
I mean, she's never gotten
into a fight, ever.
This wasn't just a fight.
This was violent.
We've been separated for over a year
and the kids have never had an issue.
This weird behavior, there's
something else going on here.
Yeah, maybe she's insecure, you know?
Maybe she's afraid
you're not going to be there for her.
Still getting your email.
It's your flight confirmation
for North Carolina.
- I was going to tell you about this.
- When? After you took the job?
It's just to sit down and talk.
If they offer it to you,
you going to take it?
- Of course you are.
- Stephanie, wait.
Of course you are.
Anything to be a big shot again.
Meanwhile, your 10-year-old
girl's falling apart.
Em's behavior's got
nothing to do with this.
Great. Stay oblivious, Clyde.
It seems to be working well for you.
- Oh, come on.
You gotta be kidding me.
Hey! Stay away from my kid's teeth.
Oh, no.
So, Em, do you understand why
school was canceled today?
Because Miss Shandy's dead.
That's right. She was
in a horrible accident last night.
Can you get my box for me?
It's still in the classroom.
Let's... Let's talk
about this for a second, okay.
Why is the box so important to you?
Don't know. Just is.
Okay.
Um, you know, Emily,
I noticed that sometimes you talk to it.
I do not talk to the box.
I talk to my friend.
- Your friend?
- What?
- You said you talk to your friend.
- Mmm-hmm.
The one who lives in the box.
Your friend lives inside the box?
- What?
- He lives in there?
It's a she. A woman.
What exactly does she say to you, Emily?
That I'm special.
Well, you know, you are very special.
You know, I'd sure like to meet her.
Not possible. No one can see her.
Not even me.
Can I have some more?
She's still hungry.
Where's my box?
I got rid of it, Em.
Tell me where it is.
It's not here.
Then go get it.
We're done with the box, Emily.
- I'm calling Morn.
- And tell her what?
- To come pick me up.
- That's not happening.
And if you keep talking to me like this,
you're going to be grounded
the rest of the weekend.
I hate you.
Go to your room.
That's it. Go to your room.
I don't love you.
- Emily...
- And Mommy doesn't love you.
You think
you know everything, but you don't.
You better knock it off. Stop it right now.
Mommy loves Brett now.
He makes her happy.
You don't talk to your father this way.
He does nice things for her!
Something you never did.
- Ow! Daddy!
- What are...
- What are you doing to me?
Daddy?
What are you... Emily!
What are you doing to me, Daddy?
- What are you doing, Dad?
- I'm not doing anything!
Did you just hit her?
No, damn it, I didn't hit her!
Emily!
Em! We need to talk.
Em!
There...
Are you my friend from the box?
No. No.
Because my dad doesn't...
My dad doesn't like me any more.
No.
What are you talking about?
No!
No! No!
Em!
Right.
No, I gotta go.
Judge Simmons has reviewed everything
and is granting the
interim temporary order.
So I can't see my kids?
Based on Mrs. Brenek's report
about the bruise marks...
Stephanie, this is ridiculous.
You know I would never hit her.
Judge Simmons will schedule
a full hearing.
We'll be in touch with the court date.
Thank you.
- Wait. Wait, Stephanie.
- Mr. Brenek!
Can we talk? Just the two of us?
We can work this out, Stephanie.
Mr. Brenek! You can state your case at...
I'm not talking to you.
I'm talking to my wife!
- Steph...
- Don't you touch me!
What were you thinking?
You destroyed this family,
but I won't let you hurt the children.
Just move.
Just move to North Carolina.
I don't want to see you again.
He's clearly unstable.
He's angry and he's confused
and he's taking this divorce
out on everyone around him.
And it's the girls that
are paying the price.
That's why Em's having such a hard time.
Listen, I brought a stack
of DVDs from my collection.
I thought maybe we'd have
a little movie night with the girls.
That's a great idea.
Watch something funny.
Let's lighten the mood
around here a little bit.
Okay.
That's your second glass.
Save a little for dinner?
Hey!
What you got there?
What you got in your hand? Come on.
Can I see it?
Honey, it's okay. Let me see it.
Come on.
Where'd you get this?
Where'd you get this, Em?
It's deliberate...
Em?
I think you should leave.
I think you should leave now.
I don't like you!
Well, you're just going to have to
get used to that, aren't you?
Coach, you looking for the bathroom?
What brings you to my class?
Quite a find, Clyde.
That's just it.
I have no idea what I've got here.
Well, judging by the woodwork,
I'd say it was from Poland, 1920s, '30s.
Probably originated in a Jewish village,
indicated by these Hebrew inscriptions.
I think it says, "Dibbuk."
It's the Hebrew word for
"dislocated spirit."
It's a dibbuk box.
So was it used for something religious?
The more traditional branches of Judaism,
especially in the Hasidic sects,
believe in various spirits,
both benevolent and...
- Benevolent and...
- Evil. Like demons.
A dibbuk box was made with the belief
that the evil itself could
somehow be contained.
Think of it.
If you believed such a thing,
that you could trap a demon.
And now, it's in your hands, Coach Brenek.
Carrying around this curse.
Whoo... Very brave man.
Whoever made this box
certainly had intense convictions.
It's why they concealed this
lock and carved these words.
Basically what they're saying is...
"Warning. Deadly."
"Do not open."
So, don't open it.
- Dad, what are you doing here?
- Where's your sister?
Mom's at the drug store.
She'd freak if she knew you were here.
Hannah, I'm not
screwing around. I need to see Emily.
She decided to stay home.
She's not feeling well.
Dad!
Em.
"Whoever sits in the refuge
of the most high,"
"he shall dwell in the
shade of the Almighty."
"I will say of Hashem,"
"He is my refuge, my fortress, my God."
"I will trust in Him."
"For He will deliver you
from the ensnaring trap"
"from devastating pestilence..."
"With his pinion He will cover you,"
"and beneath His wings
you will be protected."
"His truth is shield..."
"His truth is shield and armor."
"You shall not fear the
terror of night, nor..."
Who are you?
What do you want with my little girl?
You tell me!
What do you want?
Clyde!
What are you doing in here? Get out!
Get out of the house!
I'll call the police. Get out!
What are you doing?
Excuse me.
Sorry.
I get kind of lost when I'm listening.
My name's Clyde Brenek.
I'm looking for Tzadok Shapir.
Yeah, that's me.
- We talked on the phone.
- Thank you for meeting me.
Is that it?
Yeah.
All right.
I'll take you
to see my father, the Rebbe Shapir,
but I must tell you, he's traditional.
Okay.
All right. Everyone's waiting in the shul.
Amen.
My father asks if you could
show us what's in the bag.
Rebbe Shapir wants to know
where you got this.
I bought it at a yard sale.
Did you open it?
Tell us, did you open the box?
- My daughter...
My daughter opened it.
What does this thing want
with my daughter?
The dibbuk
looks for innocence. A pure soul.
It will move back and forth from the box,
searching for a proper host.
The host begins to hear
voices, experience visions.
All of this is the deception of the spirit
to protect the host and drive others away.
The final stage is when the
dibbuk attaches to the host,
the two becoming one.
It will feed and take
until there is nothing left.
It wants only one thing,
that which it does not have.
Leiben.
Life.
It's taking my daughter's life.
How do I stop it?
The only way to stop the dibbuk
is by commanding it back
into the box by its name.
I don't have its name.
This is what I have. I need your help.
I saw this ceremony, an exorcism.
It is too great of a risk.
The dibbuk could come upon anyone
attempting to perform the ceremony.
No.
No, wait. Wait, please.
Someone here has to help me.
It's not my little girl any more.
When I look into her eyes,
it's this thing looking back at me.
But my little girl, Emily,
she's in there, right?
Please tell me she's in there.
You have to help me.
This must be left to the will of God.
The will of God?
If this were your child,
would you leave it to the will of God?
Mr. Brenek?
I'm coming with you.
Why?
Pikuach nefesh.
A permitted violation of a Shabbat law.
A human life is in danger.
I am not only allowed, but required to act.
Let's go.
Em...
What are you doing?
Emma...
Give me that, sweetie.
Emily, what are you doing?
Em's not here!
It's okay, baby. Come here. Come here.
You just stop this right now.
Come here. Come to Mommy.
No!
I'm not playing games now.
Emily.
I said, Em's not here!
Emily, come here, honey.
Em, where are you?
Emily, come here, baby.
Come here.
Em, where are you?
Em?
Emily?
Where are you?
Mom, who am I?
Oh, baby...
Who am I, Mommy?
Her face.
You should have seen it.
I was actually scared.
I've never seen anything like that.
You know, with everything that's going on,
I think we need to have her see someone.
I called a friend of mine.
She's a mental health specialist.
She works with kids all the time.
She said she can see Em
first thing tomorrow morning.
Spend a couple of days giving her a
full evaluation at her facility.
Okay.
You can tell Em that we're just going away
for the weekend.
Okay, everybody, let's go!
Emily?
Brett?
You Okay?
Em?
- Hannah!
- What's going on?
Call 911!
Just...
What's wrong with her, Mom?
What's wrong with her?
There has to be a name.
I don't know. I've searched
every inch of that thing.
The carvings, a prayer
from the Book of Psalms,
the tokens placed inside,
but why is there this mirror?
If the spirit was contained,
it would have to look upon itself,
to be forever reminded
that it turned away from God.
Jesus.
"Abyzou."
Abyzou.
"Taker of children."
Hurry.
I'd like to schedule an MRI right away.
Okay.
Emily, we're going to slide you
into this machine here.
Just think of it as a great big camera.
Lets us take a look inside.
- Am I okay?
- Yeah, baby. Yeah.
Everything's going to be all right.
Don't be afraid, okay.
We're going to be in the other room. Okay?
You'll hear some noises, Emily.
It's nothing to be scared of.
I love you.
I need you to stay very, very still for me.
All right, here we go.
- Can I close my eyes?
- Of course.
We're going to start taking pictures now.
Looking good. Good tissue.
Doing great, Emily.
There must be some interference.
What's happening?
Is she all right in there by herself?
- She's fine.
- Get somebody up here
who knows what they're doing.
What's going on?
Things like this
will happen once in a while.
Oh, my God.
There's something in there with her!
Hey.
Hi.
- Dad, I'm so sorry.
- No.
I saw something...
I saw something in her.
The doctors, they can't help us, can they?
Just, I need you to trust me, okay?
Are you able to get her out?
No. We're going to have to do it here.
Here?
Great.
I hate hospitals. People die here.
Hey.
This is Tzadok. Tzadok, this is my family.
Thank you for coming.
- Can you help us?
- Of course.
What do I look like, a doctor?
It doesn't want me here.
We need a private place.
- Thank you.
There's a physical therapy room down there.
My players use it sometimes.
No one uses it after 6:00.
Oh, baby.
Take these candles and light them.
- How many?
- Seven.
As the others have
done in the past, I have asked you
to put something
from your heart in the box.
It is believed that this
essence will bind the prayer.
This belonged to my grandfather.
The strength of my entire
family is with us.
Hannah? Honey?
Stephanie.
Your wedding ring.
Once we begin,
we must complete the ceremony.
The dibbuk will
do everything it can to stop us.
No, baby.
Even in the face of this evil,
our faith must remain unwavering.
- Okay.
- Please, God.
Oil of two olive trees.
Oil represents light.
Water represents darkness.
May God separate between these two
as only light can dispel darkness.
"Nor the destruction that ravages at noon."
"Put Your hands on her."
"You need only look with Your"
"and the punishment
of the wicked illuminator."
Shut up!
You take me! Take me!
Everybody, put your hands on her!
Cast all fear from your hearts!
Emily!
You die!
Daddy!
You let my daughter go! Take me!
You take me instead!
No!
That is no longer your daughter!
Clyde!
Em?
Daddy, you scared me.
Daddy, you scare me.
- Dad, you scare me.
Take me!
You take me instead!
Em!
Clyde?
Daddy?
Em, is that you?
Clyde!
Daddy?
- Is it okay? Okay?
- Em...
Oh, thank God.
Not right.
This is all wrong.
Guys, this is not right.
Where is it?
Where's the dibbuk?
Abyzou.
Abyzou. Abyzou.
Abyzou!
Clyde!
Hannah!
Daddy!
No! No!
Emily!
I say to you that
He will save you from the ensnaring trap!
He will instruct His angels in your behalf
to guard you in all your ways.
I say to you
in the name of God, leave this flesh!
Abyzou!
I say to the Lord,
my God in whom I trust,
He will save you from
the destruction and pestilence.
Abyzou!
You are cast away from the eyes of God!
Daddy!
Abyzou!
Hannah?
Daddy...
It's okay.
Hi.
Oh, it's just a cough.
Tzadok, hey! I...
I'm calling to say thank you.
Clyde! I was going to call.
Figure out how to get your car back to you.
You keep it.
I am not going to be going anywhere.
How's the family?
Perfect. More than perfect.
So what are you going to do with it?
I'm not sure.
I'm going to speak with my father.
We'll find a safe place for it.
Okay. Goodbye, Tzadok.
Goodbye, Clyde.