- I don't know.
- Seriously, I don't think...
This is stupid.
God, Grace.
Thank you, it's beautiful.
Thanks.
You look great.
How did Dawn take the news?
The break-up and all.
She'll get over it.
Don't you move. Be right back.
Time for the girls
to get a little shut-eye.
This one's for the hippie chick.
Oh, yeah.
Thank you.
Here you go.
Sorry. I was so thirsty.
Everyone is staring at us.
You are so much more beautiful
than you think you are.
You want to go someplace
more comfortable?
You want to go someplace?
I didn't even know the door
was there.
- All right, here we go.
- I don't feel well.
Let me go. Stop.
Mary, help.
What's going on?
Do you think he would
ever touch you?
No!
Willy!
- Get her! She's sober. She'll squeal.
- Willy, get up, man.
Come on, Mary!
Help!
Mary!
Mary! Mary!
Come on, Mary.
We're just having some fun.
- Let's just talk.
- Get away from me.
Hey.
Come on.
It's gonna be all right. Your friends
are okay. It's all right, it's okay.
It's just a little prank.
Come on.
Let's go check on your friends.
You stupid bitch!
Mary?
Mary.
Oh, shit.
I'm sorry.
There you are.
Where's the girl?
I don't know. I thought she
was in here, but she's not.
- Shit.
- She probably passed out somewhere.
Come on, we gotta find her.
That was over 30 years ago,
but her rotting body is still there...
...waiting to be discovered.
Bullshit.
No, it's true. I swear to God. My mom
told me in complete confidence.
Well, complete confidence...
...doesn't mean much when
you drink vodka like it's water.
Shut up.
- Stop it!
- So you don't think it's unhealthy...
...for them to stay home
on their own homecoming?
Not everybody wants to
be homecoming queen.
It didn't hurt me.
You're right.
- And I only wish I could've been there.
- No, you were too old and serious.
Thanks a lot.
That story doesn't make any sense.
I mean, why don't the girls stick
up for themselves? I don't get it.
Maybe if you weren't always speaking
out, like in the school newspaper...
...maybe we'd have dates
to the homecoming dance.
Okay, so you changed your mind.
You think it's fair football players
get academic credit...
...for going to practice?
You shouldn't have published
the picture with the article.
They took the picture as a joke. You
published it out of context, without...
Guys. I've got another ghost story.
That wasn't a ghost story, Mindy.
It's an urban legend.
An urban legend is a made-up story
people keep telling as if it was true.
Like the guy who eats Pop Rocks...
...drinks soda
and his stomach explodes.
Like that bullshit about Mindy's
brother's camp counselor...
...getting his arm stuck in a soda
machine, and it falls on top of him.
That wasn't bullshit.
And it was a candy machine.
- Oh, and like Bloody Mary.
- Who's that?
Supposedly, if you go into
the bathroom and turn off the lights...
...and chant "Bloody Mary" three times
into the mirror, she appears.
Her face is like a corpse.
And if you look at her, well...
...then you have to turn the lights
back on before she drags you in.
In where?
I don't know. In the mirror?
I heard she'll haunt you forever.
That's not even a real urban legend.
That's just like that movie Candyman.
- Well, my story was real.
- As real as your mother's new tits.
What's the first thing you'll do
when you're mayor?
- I haven't won yet.
- But you will.
A lot can happen, so...
But so far...
- What's going on in there?
- I don't know.
Well, the first thing I'm gonna do
is propose a 9 p.m. Curfew...
...on all teenage girls.
I'll keep them off the streets,
keep them safe.
Keep them virgins.
I'm afraid that might be too late.
Bloody Mary.
Who is it?
David.
Asshole.
So, David, you're back early.
Shouldn't you be at the dance?
- I'm sure it's still going on.
- Oh, yeah. Well...
I was there long enough
not to see any of you.
We didn't want to go that
stupid popularity contest.
And why is that?
Oh, because you couldn't get dates?
Yep, that's exactly what happened.
Football team put us on the blacklist.
We could've gone.
We just preferred to stay here
and have some female bonding.
Hey, Mindy. Nice.
- Shut up.
- David!
Oh, and just so you guys
get it right...
... Candyman ripped off Bloody Mary
in the first place.
Not the other way around.
How long was your brother
outside listening to us?
- Long enough to masturbate.
- Not long at all, then.
David.
So how was it?
Just like yours, I'm sure.
You didn't wake up naked in Tijuana.
Just because there's a dead
Mexican hooker in my room...
...doesn't mean I went to Mexico.
Oh, Bill drank all my lemonade.
David, be nice. You know, and you
could call him "Dad" once in a while.
Never happen.
But I still call you "Mom."
Mom, I need 100 bucks.
Do me a favor.
Go wake up the girls.
All right. Just because you own me,
it doesn't mean I'm your slave.
- Go.
- Yeah.
They're already gone.
She's never done this before.
I mean, this is so unusual for her.
- I have to call Sheriff McKenna.
- Okay.
Yeah, Sheriff McKenna.
It's Bill Owens.
Any word, anything?
We're doing all we can.
You have to understand...
... they're not officially
missing for 24 hours.
- Yeah, but they are missing.
- Hello.
That's it, nothing? All right, well,
you just stay on top of this.
All right, look, when
do we call in the FBI?
Our hands are tied.
We'll do all we can locally.
Officially missing for 24 hours.
But they are missing.
Right this way, sheriff.
- Sheriff. Thanks for coming.
- Hi, Bill.
- I appreciate it.
- No problem.
The mountain gorilla.
An endangered species native
to Central Africa. Mountain gorillas...
...live in groups...
...ruled by a dominant male...
...which determines
the group's daily activities...
...and enforces
a very strict social order.
The silverback.
Do you think Samantha
and her friends are okay?
Yeah.
- And consume 20 times
their weight in food annually.
I just spoke to Sheriff McKenna,
and he's got all his men out searching.
- They're gonna find her.
- Sure, that's easy for you to say.
She's just your stepdaughter.
What...?
Sam.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God.
They all say the same thing.
They woke up in the basement...
...of the abandoned old mill
on the other side of the state park.
The door was locked.
Well, that's what they said.
What do you mean?
Well, we're gonna check it out.
They don't remember anything.
Other than that, they're fine. Weren't
harmed or mistreated, nothing.
We ran blood tests and found
traces of Rohypnol in their system.
It's a date-rape drug.
You don't have to worry about that.
We ran medical tests.
They were not abused in that way.
So, what do you think?
Well, it could be the girls' idea
of a practical joke.
You know, for attention.
What happened?
What happened? What's wrong?
What's wrong?
What happened to you?
My mom says that it's all a stunt.
That they did it to themselves.
Samantha will write a story
about it for the paper.
Some people have no boundaries.
Some people need to mind
their own fucking business.
The girls are back.
They were in science class.
Took them long enough.
You'd think twins would have
some kind of sixth sense...
...like I'd know what happened to you.
We're fraternal, not identical.
How you holding up?
It was Buck and his friends,
wasn't it?
He told us they just wanted to talk.
You are butt-white.
- Hey, Roger.
- What?
You need to spend some more time
at that tanning salon.
Hey, girls dig it, man.
He doesn't go to that salon
to go tanning.
He goes to hook up with that chick.
- The one with the big tits.
- Oh, yeah.
Buck.
- What's up?
- Come here. Come here, check it out.
What? Oh, yeah.
I know it was you. All of you.
I know it was all of you.
What did your sister...?
We don't know what
you're talking about.
We were at the dance all night.
Ask our dates.
- Get out of here, loser.
- You little punk.
- Yeah. Get out of here.
- Get out of here, man.
- Get lost.
- You're not gonna get away with this.
- Whatever.
- Oh, I'm scared.
- Come on, get out of here.
- That's what I thought.
- Bye-bye.
- See you.
- We got a problem.
- This is not a problem at all.
Those bitches,
they won't say anything.
Yeah. Take Buck's advice.
What did you get
on your SATs, Buck? Seven hundred?
Total.
What's that supposed to mean?
You're such an asshole.
She needs to relax.
See you later, mama's boy.
Shut up. Shut up.
No way. Shut up.
Yeah. Totally. Shut up.
She did not. No way.
Oh, my God. He's here.
I gotta let you go.
Hi, Roger.
Hi, Betsy. I hope it's okay
I just showed up.
Don't worry about it.
I'm, like, the only one here.
I just wanna catch some sun.
Lay on the bed a little bit,
get my groove on.
Then maybe I could get
some of your sunshine.
Okay.
How long do you want it?
Just leave it on low.
I'm gonna relax for a bit.
I'll get out when I'm done.
I'll be ready.
Totally. Like, yeah, I saw it.
He is so hot.
Yeah, totally. Most people go nude.
Totally.
Yeah. Totally.
No. Totally.
Yeah.
Totally.
Shut up.
Help! Betsy!
Yes way. My past.
I could be president.
What time is it?
Oh, shit. Roger!
Oh, shit.
Roger! Roger! Roger!
- Amen.
Peace be with you.
Thank you, Father.
Samantha?
- Hey.
I brought you homework you might
have missed when you were gone.
I saw how Buck was looking
at David at the funeral.
Heather, you know that David had
nothing to do with Roger's accident.
Yeah.
Listen...
...I know that things have
been difficult for us.
It was so much easier
when we were kids.
God, Sam, we were so close.
What happened to us?
It's funny you should say that.
Why?
Because it sounds like it came
from a TV movie, that's why.
Look, what happened to you was
just a little payback prank...
...and I had nothing to do with it.
The guys didn't mean
to go so far...
...but they were pissed off
you published that photo.
Just a prank?
They drugged us,
and who knows what they did to us...
...after they locked us up.
I sure as hell don't.
How hard was it
to crawl out the window?
That's not the point, Heather.
Look, Sam, there's more.
It's...
- This has all happened before.
- What do you mean?
We'll talk about it tomorrow.
Make sure and do
your history homework.
I'm sorry.
She brought me my homework.
She felt bad. She was cool about it.
Damn it.
- You sure you don't want a ride?
- No, I'm good. Thanks.
Heather!
Oh, my God!
Unit 14, we have a 174...
What's going on?
What happened?
Sam, what...? Sam, talk to me.
What's going on?
Ashes to ashes...
...and dust to dust.
She was in bed. How could they
be crawling out of her face?
I think it's really sick, though.
They were coming out of her face.
Now, I'm sure you've all noticed the
new security precautions on campus.
Every effort is being made
to keep our students safe.
Now, Principal Rosetti
has asked me to remind everyone...
Samantha, dear.
Is something the matter?
No.
Well, as I was saying...
...students who need to speak to
a counselor should tell their advisor.
So how was school today, honey?
I saw a ghost in science class.
Do you really think
that he did it to himself?
Roger Dalton was dumb...
...but don't you think that he would
wake up before he cooked his ass?
What are you saying?
I'm asking if you really think there's
nothing more to our friends dying.
Heather dropped some acid and
just ripped her face off like a mask?
Of course not.
She didn't even drink,
let alone do drugs.
There's something wrong
in our little town, and it has a name.
- Owens.
- David?
Both of them.
They were there both times.
Jesus, Buck.
Murder?
So, what are we gonna do?
Your dad still have
those emergency gas cans?
Get them.
And meet me behind the park
at midnight.
I don't know about this, Buck.
Come on. Scaring the girls
is one thing, but...
Right.
Okay.
I'll be there in 15.
Holy shit, this guy's dick
is smoking. Hey, McKenna...
...better check your beer bottle tonight.
Did you ever hear the story about
a guy who was drinking a beer...
...and found a finger in the bottle?
Look at this.
Someone cut his ring finger off.
- Wild.
- Will you stop with that crap?
That finger is probably
some coyote's lunch.
Yeah, we got EMTs on the scene.
Worthington High School classes
have been cancelled today.
Another student from that school
was found dead.
Although drunk and driving...
... early reports suggest electrocution
as the cause of death.
Tom Higgins,
a varsity football player...
There's something else
going on here.
Heather left this in my
American history book the other night.
I think someone sent this
to Heather as a warning.
This is the same thing
that happened to you.
Only I'm still alive.
Here.
Read the other one.
"Professor at Alpine University kills
students using urban legends as m.o."
Wait, you think there's
a copycat killer...
...that's killing our friends.
No, I just think that Heather
was trying to tell me something.
I need your help to figure it out.
Well, it's about time you asked.
Mary Banner lived here in Utah.
She went to Worthington High.
It says the other two girls
returned home unharmed.
They should still be alive.
See if you can find it online.
Are you smoking crack? This is
dial-up. Let's use the school database.
- School's closed today.
- I have keys to the newspaper office.
Okay.
Let's just get down there
and finish this.
Wait, wait, go back.
- There.
- Wow, déjà vu.
"The two girls,
seniors at Worthington High...
...refused to press charges
against unknown assailants."
Why no names?
Got them. Gina Lotnick, 17, Mary
Banner, 18, and Grace Taylor, 17.
Where are they now?
Oh, that's from '82.
"Local resident Gina Lotnick
died this morning...
...of a self-inflicted gunshot wound.
Miss Lotnick was one of the victims in
the homecoming kidnapping in 1969...
...of which there are no suspects.
Mary Banner, another victim, was
never found and presumed dead."
- Who was the other girl?
- Grace Taylor.
"The only remaining survivor
of that fateful night is Grace Taylor."
Hey, got it. It's not that far
from our house.
Hey.
Hey, Coach Jacoby.
What are you kids up to?
Oh, nothing.
Just some extra credit, you know.
The school's closed.
And that goes for your newspaper.
You're gonna have to leave.
- Now.
- All right, cool. Thanks, coach.
- Hey.
- I just feel like I'm cracking up.
I know it's tough, but we shouldn't
blame this on a bunch of ghost stories.
I don't know what to believe.
These just seem
like awfully big coincidences.
They're odd, I'll give you that.
They're either accidents,
or there's a killer out there.
There's no ghost.
But there is something.
I mean, there's something connecting
this to what happened to me...
...to those girls in '69.
We're gonna find out what it is.
Grace Taylor is gonna tell us.
- This is it?
- Yeah, it's groovy.
Come on.
Power to the people.
Free Angela Davis. What's up?
Hi, I'm Sam,
and this is my brother, David.
- So?
- So we wanted to talk to you.
Miss Taylor,
we wanted to talk to you...
...about what happened
at homecoming 35 years ago.
Power to the people.
Right on.
You take your shoes off.
Have a seat, kiddies.
You want some tea?
- No, thank you.
- Penicillin?
Oh, yeah, we would love some...
...tea.
So, what do you kiddies
want to know about that night?
Well, we were hoping
you could tell us everything.
"Professor at Alpine University
kills his own students...
...using urban legends as his m.o."
There were five of them,
including that devil bitch, Dawn.
Gina and I were tricked, drugged and
left 20 miles from home in the woods...
...all because we didn't
worship them like the rest.
Everyone said that we
just got wasted and passed out.
No one wanted to cop to the truth.
That happened to me too.
I know. I read it in the papers.
But you all came back in one piece.
My best friend...
...never came home.
Get that.
- It's Mary.
- What is?
The murders.
It's Mary Banner.
Looks like urban legend, but it's Mary.
- But she's dead, isn't she?
- Oh, she's dead, all right.
But her energy, her life force,
is very strong.
Always was.
You kids know that nothing ever dies,
don't you?
It just changes form, you know, like
water into ice into water into steam...
...into water into ice, you dig?
Wait, so you're saying...
...a ghost is killing these kids.
But that doesn't make any sense.
Why would she be killing us?
Why not just go after the people
who actually did this to her?
The children will always suffer
the sins of their fathers.
Your friend Heather had a devil-bitch
mother by the name of Dawn.
Well, Mary wants revenge on
the five people who took her youth...
...so she's taking their children.
That's where she's starting.
Who knows where she'll stop.
She has always had to have her way.
Come on, you're not buying this,
are you?
Miss Taylor...
...we need to know the names
of the boys who did this to you...
...and to Mary.
Oh, baby.
I can barely remember
how to tie my shoes...
...let alone the names of our dates.
But they were all
on the football team.
This is ridiculous.
- I cannot believe you believe her.
- I can't believe you don't.
This is as bad as when
you thought there was a vampire...
...living under the porch.
- I'm starting to wonder if I was right.
Kidding.
Heather's mom went to Worthington,
so we can assume she was involved...
...along with Roger's
and Tom's dads.
So we have to figure out
who's next, probably Buck.
Sam, Mary Banner
isn't killing people. She's dead.
It's more likely that Grace Taylor
is doing this.
Look at these.
- Did you steal these?
- Yeah, just look at them.
The handwriting is just like on
the envelope that was sent to Heather.
Grace sent the clippings to Heather.
This is how Heather died.
I saw the spiders,
but no one believed me.
This one's a girl, but the
same thing happened to Roger.
Oh, God.
They're all coming true.
Oh, God. We have to find Buck.
He won't be hard to find.
Let's get out of here.
- Buck, we need to talk to you.
- What?
You gonna write about me
in the newspaper?
- No, I just think that...
- Come on.
I'm sorry that we played
a stupid fucking joke...
...on you and your friends.
But did Roger and Tom
and Heather deserve to die for it?
Do you honestly think
I could kill someone...
...over a stupid, asshole jock prank?
Look, Buck...
...do you know about the kidnappings
at Worthington High in 1969?
That was something that he did
when he was young.
It's like a rite of passage.
- Wait, you're talking about your dad?
- Yeah.
My dad was pissed about the picture
you put in the paper. And the article.
He told me about how he
and his friends would have handled it.
So Coach Jacoby was one
of the boys...
...involved in the kidnappings?
The Mary Banner case?
Yeah, but he didn't hurt her.
He didn't even know
what happened to her.
She just disappeared.
She didn't die like Heather did.
Buck, I'm sorry.
All right, come on,
we gotta get out of here.
Let's go. We gotta get
the heck out of Dodge.
I'm worried about Buck.
Well, he's a source of worry,
I agree.
I think that Buck's dad killed Mary
Banner. I think he's lying to Buck.
Oh, and I'm sure you got this info
directly from Mary Banner.
Well, I saw Coach Jacoby
at her grave after Roger's funeral.
Wait a minute.
You think Coach Jacoby had
something to do with these murders?
No, I mean, not directly.
I just think that...
What? You were gonna
say something.
This might sound strange,
but I think...
She thinks that the ghost
of Mary Banner is killing people.
Guys, if either of you have information,
real information...
...you better stop fooling around
and tell me.
- Just like that.
- Oh, baby.
You're so nasty.
- Yeah, that's it.
- Spank me.
That's it. Oh, yeah.
- So good.
- You love it.
Oh, yeah.
- So big.
- Come on.
- Right there. Right there.
- Yeah.
Shit.
Damn it.
Under.
Okay.
What the hell?
Holy shit.
Oh, Jesus, Chewy,
did you eat another skunk?
- That's right.
- Oh, God.
Don't stop. Don't stop.
Come on. Right there.
You like it, huh?
Hey, don't look now,
but Coach Jacoby's crying.
- Maybe something happened to Buck.
- Maybe someone cut his kidneys out.
- Hey.
- Long time no see, Sam.
Have you guys seen Buck?
- Have we seen Buck?
- Yeah, his dad looks really upset.
Yeah, well, Buck got himself
good and killed last night.
Yeah, I heard he got crushed
under a vending machine.
He tried to snag some free chips,
and then smash.
Did your mother drink
while she was pregnant?
In the news,
they said he got his throat cut...
...by a prostitute
in some sleazy motel.
Wait. Buck's dead?
Maybe you shouldn't be
so concerned with his well-being.
He certainly wasn't concerned
with ours.
Four down. One to go.
Are you still looking for clues?
God, you were fat.
Did you know that Grandpa was bald?
Guess you can kiss
your hairline goodbye.
Yeah, and Grandma has a moustache.
I think Heather was trying
to tell me something.
We know that her mom
was one of the people involved...
...in Mary Banner's disappearance.
Why don't we ask Heather's mom
who the other boys were.
Yeah, and then what?
And then we'll know who's left
on Mary Banner's hit list.
Sam, I appreciate
your community spirit...
...but most people
in this town don't.
- Most people think...
- I'm one bolt short of a nutcase.
That I should have been
drowned at birth.
Yeah, in that general direction.
Where are you going?
We need to talk to the police,
but we need evidence.
I'm going back to see Grace.
Oh, that's smart,
walk straight into the jaws of death.
I don't think she's the killer anymore.
She's afraid to leave her house.
But I think she knows
who the killer is.
- Okay, call me.
- Yeah.
Hello?
Grace...
...are you here?
Shit! You scared me to death.
What are you doing in my house,
X-Man? How did you get in?
- The door was open.
- Oh, yeah.
For the cats.
You're lucky.
You almost got sprayed
with bug spray. Hit.
What do you want? Spit it out.
I really need you to tell me
the name of the football players...
...who abducted you
all those years ago.
Please, Grace.
I wouldn't tell then, I won't tell now.
Did anyone ever tell you
that you look exactly like Foxy Brown?
That's smooth, brother.
Very smooth.
You know...
...anyone who wanted to could have
found out who those boys were...
...just by looking at the pictures
in the school archive.
In the archives?
Right on, Gracie. Thank you.
Damn it.
Oh, my God!
Willy. Willy!
Willy!
Don't leave me in here, Willy.
There's Grace.
Where's Mary?
Hello, Mary.
Who's your date?
There he is.
Holy shit.
No. No, stop.
Leave me alone. No.
Leave me alone!
Grace.
Grace, you need to get a phone
that works.
Grace, please.
Please.
What does Mary want with me?
Mary's visited you too, huh?
Find her.
Find her and bury her.
But I saw her grave.
You saw a tombstone, baby girl.
She's not buried there.
Gina and I looked for her
for years.
Nobody ever found her body.
She could be anywhere.
I think I know where she is.
I hope this is what you want.
Sam!
Samantha!
Hey, it's the Owens.
Leave a message.
David, are you there?
David, if you're there,
pick up the phone.
David.
I think I know where the body is.
I know... I know you think
I'm crazy, but...
This is the one piece of evidence
that we need to bring it to the cops.
When you get this message,
meet me at the school, okay?
You have my keys.
Meet me at the side door.
I forgot to tell you.
Your brother went over
to the school.
Great. He has my keys.
You're just gonna have
to take me in your car.
No way.
I have not been back there
since homecoming, 1969.
Please. I would take my bike,
but it'll take me too long.
No, I can't!
Look at me.
Grace.
Damn.
You have to promise me that you
will bury her when you find her.
David!
David, open the door!
- David!
- Shit.
David, open the door!
David?
I saw someone in there.
- Was it Mary?
- I don't know.
Maybe.
I'm gonna climb through the window.
I'll go around and open
the door for you.
No, hey, I'm cool.
I'll wait in the van.
Oh, damn.
Shit.
Grace, I got her.
Grace, wake up.
Shit. I found her, Grace.
Grace, I really need your help.
Grace. Shit.
Damn, that's some chronic. Shit.
Grace.
Oh, no.
Oh, Grace.
Are you okay?
Oh, shit.
Grace.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
- Hello?
- Bill.
- Bill, thank God.
- Sam, where are you?
- I'm at the cemetery.
- Calm down... Sweetie.
- Your mother... Sam, what's going on?
- What?
I can't hear you. You're in a what?
- I can't hear you.
- Where are you?
I'm at the cemetery.
Fuck. Fucking cell phones.
Bill.
Thank God you're here.
I really need your help.
All right, just calm down
and tell me what's going on.
I found the body.
Now I have to bury it.
Mary Banner's body.
I finally found it, and now
she wants me to bury the corpse.
Here, sweetheart, I got it.
This ground's frozen.
Okay, I just don't want you
to worry about this.
I'll take care of it.
Everything will be fine.
Did you hear that?
That might be Coach Jacoby.
Don't worry about him.
I can take care of him.
Does anybody else
know about this body?
No, just me and David.
Did you say anything
to your mom?
Samantha.
Someone, help!
Someone, help me!
- Did you tell your mom?
- No.
- Help!
- You leave her alone!
Get out of here, baby! Go on!
Willy Owens.
You're gonna go down.
You wait until the city council
hears about this.
Samantha!
Come on, sweetheart, I don't want
to hurt you. I just wanna talk.
Samantha!
I'm sorry I hit you.
L... I have a problem with anger
management, but I'm okay now.
What's gonna happen
to your mother if I go to jail?
Because she won't have
David anymore...
...because David is dead.
You're crazy!
What the...?
Grace.
I...
Far out.
No one is ever gonna believe us.
Samantha.
Follow the tracks down the hill.
Hey, now.
- I fall asleep again?
- Yep.
Bill.
You mean "punk."
They're saying he died
of a heart attack.
I guess something must have
scared his butt real bad.
You gonna be okay?
I guess this will just be
another ghost story.
Something to talk about around
campfires and slumber parties.
Baby girl,
you're the urban legend now.
A decades-old mystery
was finally solved last night...
...when police discovered the body
of mayoral candidate Bill Owens...
...dead of a heart attack
while apparently attempting...
...to dispose of the remains
of Mary Banner...
...a local girl who disappeared
over 30 years ago.
While police refuse to confirm it,
a source tells us...
...that it was Owens
who was actually responsible...
...for Banner's death on that
fateful homecoming night in 1969.
DVD Subtitles
www.GRuPoUToPiA.com.ar