Um, Dr. Dutten,
- my aunt's in town.
- Mm-hmm.
And she's sick, too.
I'm gonna need you to stay late tonight.
- Oh. You are?
- You know, you should probably
text your Aunt Scotty
and tell him you can't make it
to the baseball game today.
Wait a second.
- Okay, look, Scotty and I, we're not-
- Oh, come on, Becca.
- I mean-
- It's the worse-kept secret in town.
Now, that is saying a lot.
Go on.
Get outta here.
Go have some fun.
Thanks, Dr. Dutten.
Well, I don't care what the calendar says.
Opening day-
That's the first day of spring.
No, no, no.
The sheriff never pays for coffee.
Well, that's kind of you, Ben.
But the principal still has to pay
his parking tickets.
- Start him a tab.
- Yes, sir.
Kid throws fast.
Just like he drives.
Nice pitch, Scotty.
Come on, man! Come on, guys!
Strike two!
Whoo! Yeah!
Center field.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Hey, Tommy!
- Stay there.
- What's he doing?
- Boys, get in the dugout.
- Move it off.
- Get off!
- Bring it in. Bring it in.
Get them off the field.
Get them in the dugout, Principal.
Rory. Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey, Rory, we got
a ballgame going on here.
We're playing ball,
and you come out with a gun?
What the hell are you doing?
Aw, Ror.
You're drunk, that's all.
All right? Let's just lay the gun down.
Rory, lay the gun down.
Hmm? Lay it down.
Hell, Rory, come on.
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Rory?
Now, you lay that gun down.
Oh, my God.
I'll have blood alcohol for you in the morning.
A full tox screen will take about a week.
How are you holding up, David?
Peggy here yet?
She just walked in with her boy.
David, perhaps now is not the best time.
Son, settle down.
Hey, Curt.
Uh...
I'm so sorry.
I liked Rory. I liked him a lot.
What was he doing out there?
He had been drinking, that's all.
Rory quit two years ago.
You know how proud he was of that.
Is that what you're saying,
that he was drunk?
- Is that what you're telling people?
- No.
That you had to do it-
had to shoot the town drunk.
You did the right thing.
I need a new blade for this.
Hey, David.
You did the right thing.
You should be sleeping.
Sheriff's Department.
No, ma'am,
we can't comment on that.
That's an ongoing investigation.
No, ma'am, the sheriff
is not here right now,
but I can see if the deputy will-
Amateur.
Sheriff's Department.
Mm-hmm.
That's the medical examiner on line two.
Morning, Jim.
What have we got?
The toxicology reports are in.
The results are negative.
- Come again?
- There was no alcohol-
No, I heard what you said,
Jim, but that's not right.
- Rory was-
- David, we did the test twice.
Rory wasn't drunk.
There was no alcohol in his bloodstream.
We'll get the drug results
back in a couple of days, maybe a week.
Yeah, okay.
- Thank you.
Do you want this car...
Bring it down here.
Ben?
Ben!
Hey.
Hey, Ben. Ben!
Ben!
Hey. You all right?
Don't worry. The, uh...
kids are resilient.
They're gonna be all right.
Yeah.
I'm late. I gotta go.
- Deardra. Bill.
- Hey, Judy.
Little man.
How y'all doing?
Uh, would you mind
taking a look at Bill?
- Sure. What's wrong?
- I don't know.
He's just-
He's not right.
How are you feeling, Bill?
Any pain or discomfort?
Bill?
She worries too much. I'm fine.
Just a little tired.
You got any plans this weekend?
She worries too much. I'm fine.
Just a little tired.
His vitals are fine.
But, you know, I've gotta see a patient
in Cedar Rapids on Monday.
I wanna take Bill in to get a CT scan.
- Monday?
- Yeah.
Let's just make sure it's nothing serious.
- Okay.
- Okay?
You need me, you call me.
Day or night.
- Okay?
- Thanks, Judy.
See you, Nicholas.
- Bye, Judy.
- Bye, Bill!
What's Dad doing?
Wait here, Nicholas.
William!
William?
William, what are you doing?
William!
Oh, God.
Nicholas!
Nicholas?
Nicholas.
Nicholas!
- Nicholas, are you okay?
- Shh, shh.
Nicholas, what happened?
It's Dad.
Wh-Where's Dad?
What happened?
Honey, please, talk to me.
Please.
He has a knife.
Oh, my God.
Stay back.
Stay right there.
William!
William, please, don't do this!
William, please let us out!
Hello.
Mmm.
I'm coming.
What is it?
Number 1, take the full pressure.
All right, team.
Get me some power.
- Oh, my God.
- The garage is lit up, too.
- Deardra!
- Tom, they get out?
Not Deardra and Nicholas.
Just Bill.
- I need two men on that Engine 3 quarter, south side.
- On it.
When we got here, there was
an empty gas can just sitting out front.
And Bill- Well, he was mowing the goddamn lawn.
David, Deardra and Nicholas
were upstairs locked inside a closet.
Bill! Bill!
Bill?
What the hell happened here?
- Oh, my God.
- Judy.
Oh, God.
- Judy, come on.
- No.
- What the fuck have you done?
- Judy, come on.
- Oh! Oh, David!
- Shh.
Oh, God!
Deardra!
Oh, my God!
What the hell?
What you got?
Shit!
Oh, my God.
Russ, you get in touch
with Sheriff Byrnes in Cedar Rapids?
- Russ?
- Uh, yeah.
State troopers are coming this afternoon
to pick him up for transfer.
How long has he been playing statue?
A couple hours now.
The same look Rory gave me.
The same goddamn look.
Shit.
Sheriff's Department.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Slow down. Slow down.
Been there at least a week
by the looks of things.
I'll check to see
if there's any identification.
Yeah.
Do that.
Boys, last I checked,
hunting season ended three months ago.
We was just out taking in a little nature.
- Fresh air is all.
- Guns away till fall.
- Aw, come on, Sheriff.
- What, are you kidding me?
- What's with this guy?
- Well, we got us a pilot.
Where's the plane?
You know, last week,
Travis Quinn was going around
saying he heard something crash
out by Hautman Bog.
- I didn't think nothing of it.
- On account of him being full of shit?
As a general rule.
- Well, maybe there's the exception.
- Maybe.
You said it sounded like a plane, Trav?
Sheriff, about the reward-
Shit. Big plane? Little plane?
What? Come on now.
If you can explain the difference
how those two sound,
- I might be able to figure it out.
- You're full of shit.
He's full of shit.
People only ask for a reward
when there's something to find.
Is it gonna be a big reward, Sheriff?
Travis, you ask about that again,
I'm gonna throw you
out of the fucking boat.
You're not gonna shoot me?
Travis.
Yeah?
Kill the engine.
It was a big plane, Russ.
Why is that?
'Cause we're right on top of it.
Kevin, which way does
the water flow through town?
Nice to see you, too, Dave.
Waste water or drinking?
- Drinking.
- Give me a second.
A plane that size goes down-
nothing in the paper,
nothing in the news.
- Make any sense to you?
- It depends on what the payload is.
Exactly what I'm thinking.
Which is what?
Hautman Bog-
What's that drain into?
- Dwyer Creek.
- Which drains into?
Black Pond. Oh, hey,
you remember monster catfish-
Russell, where do you think
we get our drinking water from?
Treated water comes in from the north,
breaks east-west.
And what house does it get to first?
Uh, let's see.
Rory Hamill.
You wanna shut off
the entire town's water supply on a hunch?
Mayor, I've got three dead bodies
in the morgue in the last 48 hours.
David, take a look around you.
This is a farming community.
It is springtime.
It is planting season.
You turn off the water,
you're gonna kill the crops.
You kill the crops, and you bankrupt
every family in Pierce County.
And that is not based
on some, uh, hunch.
That's a fact.
Water stays on.
Uh, Sheriff,
I'm all for a little civil disobedience,
but, um, I think this one
might cost you your job.
You know what, Russ?
That wouldn't be such a bad thing.
What the fuck?
Shh. Hang on a second.
Well, is he dead?
Well, if he is, he won't mind waiting.
Oh! Jesus Christ!
Did we or did we not request
a transfer for him this morning?
Mm-hmm.
God damn it.
Even better.
- You know what?
- What?
We're in trouble.
Hello?
Jim?
Jesus Christ.
Behind you.
Christ Almighty.
David, I'm not gonna do this.
I can't go to my parents.
- You have no idea-
- And neither do you.
Look, whatever it is,
I can't just leave.
- Are you gonna leave?
- I'm the sheriff.
- I'm their doctor.
- Yeah, well,
if it turns out what they need is penicillin,
I'll call you.
David.
What?
There's somebody outside.
David!
Get on the ground!
This is secure.
All right! Let's go, men! Move it!
Come on. Let's go.
Keep it moving.
Sheriff, what's going on?
- I don't know any more than you do.
- Keep moving, sir.
Please take the first open seat.
A funny thing happened
on the way to Cedar Rapids.
Bastards spiked my tires.
Who are these fuckers, man?
Keep moving.
Everyone must exit the bus.
Keep moving, please.
Let's go, let's go!
Stay in line, sir.
Keep up with the group, please.
Please head into the tent.
- There is no need for alarm.
- Inside, please.
Forward, please.
- Please keep moving into the tent.
- Please step forward.
Let's go.
Keep moving, please.
Hey, can one of you guys
tell me what's going on?
- I'm sorry. You're gonna have to keep moving.
- Sir, come with me.
- Let's go!
- No!
- Russell!
- Don't touch me!
- Coming through!
- The temperature spiked.
- Ma'am-
- What are you people doing?
Judy- Hey, don't touch me.
- Hey!
- Both of you, out!
Let's go.
Keep moving, please.
- Go ahead. This way, please.
- Judy, what does it mean?
- They're checking for elevated temperatures.
- Clear.
Farnum was bleeding from the nose.
So was Rory.
Well, cerebral hemorrhaging-
It's gotta be some kind of virus.
- You gotta wait here.
- Look, I'm a sheriff.
- She's a doctor. We know these people.
- Clear.
Would you just tell us what's going on?
Maybe we can actually help you.
- Take her in there!
- David!
Go, go, go!
David!
Get off me! Stop!
David! Wait! Wait!
Stand back! Now!
- Wait! Wait! Wait!
- Judy! Judy!
Wait!
David! David!
Judy!
David! David! David!
Please.
Please help me.
Please. Please.
Keep it moving.
We got Trayberg scrubbed and ready.
Let's go, let's go.
Please. Please.
Don't. Please. Don't.
No.
No. Please.
Please. I'm pregnant.
Please! No!
Let's go!
Franklin, open these doors!
Quickly, people.
We're getting you outta here.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
- Keep moving!
- Come on!
Let's go, let's go.
Extend your right arm,
please, sir. Let's go.
You'll be given a card.
It looks like this.
Do not lose it.
Keep it moving.
We have an inbound vehicle
coming in from the northern perimeter.
Do you have clearance ID? Over.
We have no ID.
We have gunfire!
It's a civilian vehicle!
- Behind you!
- Right there! Right there!
Keep moving.
Kevin, where's Linda?
- They took her. Judy?
- They took her, too.
They took George and Francine
and Winton Simon
and a whole mess of other people.
- Jake! Jake! Jake!
- Mom!
Let's go, people.
Keep moving. Keep moving.
I'm going back.
They got the whole town sealed off.
Roadblocks on every highway.
Tim Mitchell tried to run one.
They shot him dead.
His entire family.
Keep it moving.
Come up ahead.
David, this here
might be your only chance.
Don't lose it running off
on some fool's errand.
Judy's a fool's errand?
You know what I'm saying.
I'll tell you what, Kev.
Don't ask me why I can't leave
without my wife.
I won't ask you why you can.
We got a breach in the yard!
Got a breach in the yard!
Move out! Move out!
Let's go! Evacuate!
Come on!
Let's go! Let's go!
The crazies have breached
the containment area!
- The military's pulling out!
- We gotta get outta here!
Come on! Go!
Get on board!
- We're outta here!
- Move! Move! Move!
Take 'em out!
On board! On board!
Nice to see you, too, Chief.
Oh, shit.
How'd you get out?
Tom Ellis ran his pickup
through the fence.
Fucking military started shooting.
Townsfolk going nuts.
Before you know it,
people are just running off into the fields.
David, Judy was still inside.
- I'm sorry.
- She's not sick.
She's been running a fever all month.
Russ, she's pregnant.
It's about time.
I'm gonna go get her.
Hoo-fucking-yah.
Let's go to the high school.
Becca? Becca!
Is that you?
Oh, God. Honey-
Honey, are you hurt?
Is this really happening?
It's gonna be all right.
We're gonna be okay.
You don't really believe that, do you?
Shh.
Oh. Shh. Shh.
Please, Principal Sandborn, please stop.
Please, let me go.
Please don't do this.
No. Please don't do this.
Please. No, no. Please.
No!
Oh, shit.
What are you doing? Stop!
No. Please. Please.
- No! N-
- Just get out of here, please.
Stop. Please go. Don't.
- Don't hurt her. Please, just go away.
- Please.
Please.
Please stop. Please stop.
Stop. Leave her alone.
Stop.
Please just get out of here. Please.
No.
No!
Oh! Oh!
Oh, God! Oh, David!
David! Oh, God!
Are you okay?
No, not really.
- Uh, Chief?
- We gotta get to Quik Phil's truck stop on 35.
They're putting people on buses,
and they're getting them out of here.
We're gonna go. Come on.
- Did Peter call?
- Shh.
- That's gonna be me.
Russell, we've got enough problems
without you inventing them.
- That's easy for you to say.
- Did Peter call?
You're at the end of the pot mine.
I'm a half mile from the farm.
- Who's the sheriff?
- What?
Who's the sheriff of Pierce County?
- You are.
- I am. Who's the deputy?
- That would be me.
- You are.
Deputy does what the sheriff tells him.
That's the balance of power.
And I'm telling you,
you're not getting sick,
you understand me?
Did Peter call?
I hope you're right, Chief.
I'm not world leader, but I had plans.
Did Peter call?
Come on.
Let's go.
I'll check the truck.
Fuck.
Aw, shit!
It's booted.
- They all are.
- I'll check those cars.
It's not booted.
Whoa, whoa.
Russell,
get out of the truck.
Just give me a second.
Oh, Jesus.
Go. Run. Go on.
Go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go.
Get down, get down, get down.
Come on, boys.
Come on! Get him!
Come on! Yeah!
Whoo!
Oh, yeah!
- Whoo!
- Run, little man!
Run!
- Get him!
- Whoo!
- Nice shot. Nice shot.
- Oh, yeah!
Huh? Nice shot.
- Oh, yeah! Oh, yeah!
- Nice shot, huh?
Whoo!
Come on. Get him.
Hey, straight through the heart!
- Uh-huh!
- Yeah!
Shit.
- Come on.
- Huh?
Hey, he's gonna dress up real nice.
Come on, boy.
Come on.
Get him up on there.
Good shot, man.
I knew I was okay about that shot.
It's a hell of a walk to Quik Phil's.
I got the old cruiser on blocks.
That piece of shit still works?
Yeah.
I guess you can't boot a car without wheels.
It's seven miles to my place.
It's five if we cut through
the McGregor farm.
Another 20 to Quik Phil's from there.
- I'm fine.
- Good.
Let's go.
They took my blood.
Ran at least one test that I saw.
What if the reason they didn't let me go
is because I have it?
You're pregnant.
That's why you have a fever.
David, you can't know that for sure.
I can, and I do.
If you're sick, I'm sick.
We drank from the same tap.
And I'm not sick.
None of us are.
We are gonna get through this.
What the fuck?
Scotty McGregor.
It's her boyfriend.
Russell, stop her.
- Yeah, I got it.
- David-
We don't have time for this.
You had time for me.
Okay, let's go.
It looks deserted.
Scotty?
- Scotty?
- Get back!
- Drop the fucking gun, Scotty.
- I will blow your head off.
- Scotty, it's me.
- Stay here.
Scotty, don't be an asshole.
We're fine.
Scotty.
Scotty, put the gun down.
Put it down.
Scotty.
Sorry.
Had to be sure.
Yeah, well, that's
a two-way street there, Scotty.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- Scotty, where's your mom?
- Back at the house.
We were just getting some supplies
before we started walking.
The sheriff's got a car.
You two can come with us.
- Are you okay?
- Better than you guys.
- How's your mom?
- Be quiet.
- Get in the barn.
- Go, go, go, go, go.
Russ.
- We have one civilian coming out.
- What are you doing?
- Ma'am, please.
- Stop! Stop!
We need you downstairs.
- Everything's gonna be okay.
- Wait.
- We just need to process you.
- Oh, no.
- Please!
- Okay, I got an adult male.
I just need you...
It'll just take a second, ma'am.
Too late.
Hold it right there!
Scotty!
Okay, light them up.
Okay, let's go! Split it up!
I want a complete sweep of the area!
Take my gun.
Close the back of the barn.
Move, move, move!
Don't kill me, please.
Don't kill me.
Oh, fuck.
How could you do it?
How could you...
- Becca-
- You make a sound louder than this,
and I'll kill you, you understand?
- What the hell was that?
- Orders, sir.
- Who, asshole?
- Whoever gives them- I don't know.
- Bullshit!
- What the fuck is going on here?
All's they said is that there'd been
some sort of accident.
My whole unit got flown in.
We didn't even know what state we was in
till we seen the license plates.
Am I gonna die without my mask on?
Is that what they told you-
If you took your mask off,
you were gonna die?
They just said to keep it on.
Look, um,
I know I don't deserve
any favors from you people,
but if you let me go,
I swear to God I won't say nothing.
I didn't sign up
to shoot unarmed civilians.
- I'll just leave, okay?
- Sit down.
- Put the gun down, Russ.
- Chief...
I'm a sheriff.
That's my deputy.
Look, my wife's a doctor.
She's pregnant.
- Becca here is not even 18.
- When he blabs, they'll find us.
If we don't let him go,
they'll find us for sure.
And besides,
he's not gonna blab.
No, sir.
You gotta give it to him, Russ.
Shit.
I'm sorry about your folks' town.
- Hey, one up!
- Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
Any crazies back there, Babcock?
Babcock?
No. We're all clear.
Good. Military's pulling
back to the perimeter.
Let's go. Come on.
Barn's clear!
- We're secure back there!
- All right, then.
Mount up!
We're moving out!
If what that soldier said is true,
this disease has gone airborne.
We just have to keep going.
Uh, we'll go and get
the car up and running.
- Come on.
- Go.
Hey.
Hey, hey, hey.
It's perfect.
It's a perfect, beautiful morning,
and this is our home.
This is where we were
gonna raise our baby.
We can still do all those things.
Hmm?
Everyone we know...
is dead.
This town is dead,
and it's not coming back.
It's never coming back.
Fuck, yeah.
See if you can find a toolbox.
Okay.
This was gonna be your room.
Judy.
Look, I know this is hard,
but we've gotta keep moving.
This is the gun that killed your father.
Baby.
Peggy- Peggy, no. Not Judy.
No. No, no, no.
I shot him.
I did. I shot him.
Yes.
Peggy, I shot him.
Look at me, you crazy bitch!
That's it.
I fucking shot him!
I did it!
He walked on that field
with a loaded shotgun!
And I'm glad I did!
They should give me a fucking medal!
I finally killed the town drunk!
Oh!
- Oh, God.
- We're okay.
- Baby!
- Oh, my God.
Let me see your hand.
Give me the Betadine.
Yep, that's it. Here.
Shit.
Russell. Russell!
Just making sure.
He's sick, David.
You don't know that.
- You saw what he did.
- Hey, guys.
Come on. We gotta go.
He saved our lives.
That's what I saw.
Hey, you feeling okay?
- She's fine.
- Well, I'm just saying, if she's getting sick,
- we don't wanna be in the fucking car with her.
- Russell, she's fine.
I'm not sick.
You wouldn't know,
'cause that'd be the sickness
- messing with your mind.
- Okay. Russell, that's enough.
Don't lose your head.
What do you mean by that?
I mean, don't lose your head.
What do you mean by that, Chief?
I mean...
She's fine.
Now, just...
Fuck!
- Did he see us?
- I don't know.
- David, honey...
- Aw, shit.
Guys, it's turning around.
- It's coming back for us!
- Shit! Let's go!
We gotta get out of here!
- Go! Chief, let's go!
- The helicopter's coming!
- We can't stay on the highway.
- No.
There's gotta be another road we can take.
- What road? Tell me?
- I don't know. There's gotta be something.
- What road can they not see? Tell me.
- What?
What road can they not see?
What magic road can they not see?
Tell me, and I'll fucking go.
David, I'm just trying to help.
I'm sorry.
- I saw someone.
- Move. Where?
He was back there.
I know I saw someone.
Uh...
- Oh, fuck.
- Shit.
What the fuck?
David, get us outta here.
Oh, shit.
Start the car.
Come on, Chief.
Let's go. Come on.
Get us outta here.
Let's go! Let's go!
Come on!
- Let's go!
- All right!
Come on!
Come on! Let's go!
- Why aren't we moving?
- Why the fuck aren't we moving, Chief?
- 'Cause I can't get any fucking traction.
- Go! Go!
Fuck! Let's go!
Get us outta here! Come on!
I don't wanna die like this!
What the fuck was that?
- There! There! Right there!
- Motherfucker!
- Russell- Russ-
- There!
Oh, shit!
Motherfucker!
Russell!
- Oh, fuck!
- Russell!
I saw movement!
Everything is fucking moving!
Go! Come on! Come on!
- Stop the fucking car!
- Stop! Stop! Stop!
Stop the car!
- Stop!
- Judy!
Shit! David!
Help me here!
Help me!
Oh, God, please.
You're okay.
Becca! Becca! Becca!
Oh, no.
Becca.
No.
That's my truck.
Fuckers spiked my tires.
Shit.
God damn it!
We need water.
I know.
Guys, car coming!
Stay here.
David, what are you doing?
We're taking this car.
- Motherfucker!
- Russ!
What are you- No!
Whoo!
Welcome to Pierce County,
friendliest place on earth, asshole.
Russ, I wanna talk to him.
Okay.
Who the fuck do you think you are?
I'm the guy standing between you and a bullet.
Now, what was on that plane?
What was on that goddamn plane?
Trixie.
Rhabdoveridae prototype.
A- A fucking biological weapon.
- It was headed
- to an incinerator in Texas.
- Whoa. What is this?
You're telling me that you guys
engineered this crap?
It's designed to destabilize a population.
In this case, the wrong one.
Look, fella, we lost a plane.
What do you want me to say?
How about, "Sorry for destroying
your whole goddamn town"?
- What would you have preferred, a global pandemic?
- Wait. Wait.
Take it up with the pilot.
I came here to help.
Help who? Help us?
What- What is the incubation period?
48 hours.
After that, you're either dead
or you don't have it.
Fine. It's day three,
and we're still talking.
So you are gonna help us.
What the fuck!
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
- Oh, my God!
What the fuck is the matter with you?
I said that I wanted to talk to him!
You talked.
Shit.
I'm gonna need that back.
I'll carry it for a while.
- You've been carrying it the whole time.
- Oh, no. Really.
I got it.
You sure?
Yeah.
Russell, we're on your side.
My side? Shit.
I didn't even know there were sides.
- There's not. I'm just-
- Shut up the fuck up!
- Tell her to shut up, or I'll kill her, too.
- Russell, no!
- Judy, stop talking.
- Okay.
Let him think about what he's doing.
Uh-huh.
One, two,
three.
That's how many times
I've saved your life.
Go on.
Walk out where I can see you.
Move!
Fucking heavy.
- Fuck it. I'm gonna confront him.
- No, David. Don't. Please.
If we don't make it to that truck stop,
we're dead anyway.
- Don't, David. Don't.
- Back off!
- I wanna talk to you.
- I will fucking shoot you where you stand.
- I just wanna talk.
- David, stop.
You better listen to me.
- David.
- Put the gun down.
- Final warning, Chief.
- Put it down.
Please? Just put it down.
I just wanna talk.
You and me, man to man.
Come on.
- Shit.
- Okay.
Here's the deal.
Fuck!
Hey.
You remember that monster catfish
I caught last summer?
What'd he weigh, you reckon?
35, 40 pounds.
Shit.
It was a big son of a bitch.
I'm not right, am I?
Can I walk with you guys?
Just a little while longer?
Please?
Shit.
If you cut through there,
you can make it to the highway on the other side.
- They'll see us.
- Nah, they'll be focusing on me.
Deputy does what
the sheriff tells him, right?
You're the sheriff.
Come on, Chief.
I'm done.
I'm gonna die here no matter what.
So let it mean something.
Let it mean that you two made it.
Give me that.
Hoo-fucking-yah.
We got an inbound!
- Hey!
- Attention!
- You have entered a military operation.
- Hey! Hey!
Please identify yourself.
My name's Deputy Russell Crank,
the Pierce County Sheriff's Department.
- Keep your hands in the air and walk slowly.
- It's okay. I'm not sick.
Make no sudden movements
- or you will be fired upon.
- Oh, shit.
We are a live-fire operation.
Get out from behind the vehicle.
You are in breach of
a Level 4 military operation.
Reveal yourself,
or we will open fire.
- Proceed slowly with your hands in the air.
- It's okay.
It's okay.
Now stop there
and get down on the ground.
Stop and get down on the ground!
Get down on the ground now!
- He's down!
- Man down! Cease fire!
Fireteam Bravo, move up.
Alpha Team, stand by!
Let's go, let's go!
Approach with caution.
Movement in tight.
He's still breathing!
Secure that weapon!
Stay on him.
Fuck you for what you did.
Hey! Get an 18-Wheeler Dog
only at Quik Phil's.
Football fans,
show your support this off-season
with our University of Iowa
Hawkeyes Snack Pack.
One jar of hot sauce and one jar of salsa
in a collectible Iowa Hawkeyes helmet.
Available while supplies last
only at Quik Phil's.
It was Grand Central last night.
Nothing satisfies hunger
better than a Quik Phil's Mega-burger.
Take it to go or eat it here
- in one of our panoramic dining areas.
- Wait here.
Hello?
Judy?
Judy! Judy!
Judy, you all right?
Ohh.
They exterminated everyone,
not just the sick.
- Look, there's a rig we can take.
- What's the point?
- If we get out of here, they're gonna kill us, too.
- No.
- If we get to Cedar Rapids-
- David, can you just stop it?
- Can you stop pretending
everything is gonna be okay?
All right.
For Christ sakes.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
You wanna give up?
You wanna sit here and die?
Tell me,
and I will sit here and die with you.
You gonna go get that truck?
Blackbird 2, this is T.O.C.
We are approaching T minus ten minutes.
Confirm status.
This is Blackbird 2...
All units, this is T.O.C.
Be advised we are at ready status.
Proceed to countdown.
Countdown procedure initiated.
We are at T minus ten minutes.
All right. Blackbird 2 is in the air-
Truck!
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
Honey, it's fine.
It's okay.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck.
David, honey,
how's it going there?
We're gonna get there.
Oh, shit. Baby, come on.
Come on. Come on.
David.
God damn it!
David, come on.
- Hurry up.
- God damn it.
I'm sorry. It's okay.
They've gotta be in here somewhere,
David. Come on.
- Just keep looking.
- Oh, fuck me. Just-
Jesus, David.
What are you doing?
Come on, baby. Come on.
David!
David! Quick! Come on!
Let's get the fuck out of here, huh?
The smallest, straightest road
to Cedar Rapids.
Yeah. Perfect.
35, 34,
61- Disengage.
- What happens when it gets to zero?
- 31,
- 30, 29, 28,
- We are T minus 30 seconds and counting.
27, 26,
- 25, 24-
- Faster.
- 22, 21, 20,
- T minus 20 seconds. T.D.S. is active.
- 19, 18, 17,
- You see anything?
- No.
- 16-
14, 13,
- 12, 11,
- Auto sequence start.
- We are T minus ten seconds.
- 10, 9,
8-
- 6, 5, 4,
- Trigger engaged.
3, 2, 1.
Anything?
No.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh!
Get down!
Hey, come on.
Come here. Come here.
Here.
Come on. Here.
- You okay?
- Yeah. I'm okay.
Yeah?
Come on. Come on.
Huh?
Yeah.
Ow.
Oh. Sorry, honey.
Subtitled By J.R. Media Services, Inc.
Burbank, CA
We want to update you
on late-breaking news.
A massive fire in Ogden Marsh
continues to rage,
and high winds are preventing fire teams
from containing the deadly blaze.
Now, information is still coming in,
but what we currently know:
An explosion rocked the Dakon Petrol
chemical plant early this morning,
with eyewitness reports
of a 400-foot fireball that lit up the sky.
We also have reports
of a second explosion
at a nearby truck fueling station.
A perimeter has been set
in an effort to contain the blaze,
and civilians are not being permitted
into that area.