THE ECHO
Subtitles by BISHOP
Listen...
Listen!
Do you hear it?
Go away!
You all have to go away!
No!
It's not in my head.
Bobby.
Bobby, where are you?
Bobby, why aren't you here?
It's happening again.
Shh, shh...
They're after me.
I'm not crazy.
You hear them, don't you?
No.
No!
Well, they're hiring
non-unions...
...down at sanitation,
if you're interested.
There's nothing
in transportation?
Not at the moment.
Do you have any other
job skills?
Good mechanic.
Got a lot of mechanics waiting
for work already.
All right, now what time will I
expect you to call me tonight?
About what?
Well, it says here you got
a board release.
Do you understand
what that means?
I've never done this before.
It means parole
on a short leash.
So you call...
...in the next 24 hours
and let me know...
...where you're parking
yourself tonight.
I'm staying at my mother's.
All right.
You come in every Tuesday
for the next six months.
Now, this is important,
because you miss one...,
...you're in violation.
Does your mother know
you're staying with her?
No.
Well, don't you think
you should call and tell her?
She died while I was inside.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Do you have any other family?
Call him in the morning.
He may have work.
Not a lot of employers...
...want to hire people
in your situation.
Need something?
Helen Reynolds' son.
I left you that message.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Of course, 519.
Wait here.
I don't know where I'm going.
Elevator to five.
Had to go in to change
the locks, you know?
How come?
Well, the police had to break
the door open...,
...you know, when they found her.
I didn't charge you for it,
though.
Thanks.
Going up?
Ow!
Damn it.
What do you mean,
what do I mean?
Where were you?
I was just here
inside the house.
You were just here inside
of the house.
Now, how come I saw you
out by that door?
What are you doing at that door?
You weren't there?
What, am I seeing things?
I really don't understand.
What happened here?
Oh, there's another story again.
No, it's not a story.
She wanted to play.
She can play inside
the apartment.
Why do you have to play with her
out in the hallway?
I'll be right with you.
What do you guys want?
Tell me what's good here.
Listen.
Hey.
Can you excuse me?
Hi.
When did you get back?
A couple days.
Are you here for good?
I hope so.
I'm sorry about your mom...
I...I heard what happened.
Yeah, it's...
You look great.
No, no, I don't.
You don't have to say that.
Maybe a cup of coffee
or something later?
I can't.
I have finals.
School?
You're going to school?
Yep.
That's amazing.
I have to design
an entire line by next week.
It's...
...everything's really different
for me now.
Yeah, maybe another time.
Maybe this weekend, maybe...
I'm working doubles
and school...,
...and, look,
I have zero free time.
I don't think it's a good idea.
Can we get the bill, please?
I'm sorry.
I have to get back to work.
It's good to see you.
You too.
Help me.
See anything wrong?
Got to be a loose
brake pad spring.
You're sure about that?
Guy complained of a rattle...
...when he drives over bumps,
right?
That's right.
You know how to check for
misfires in alignment pressure?
Yeah.
Look, I've got to be honest
with you.
Involuntary manslaughter...,
...that's not exactly
a minor offense, you know?
If I had more to offer you
than my word...,
...I would give it to you, man.
But I'm just trying to put
my life back together.
Pay ain't high.
I don't need much.
If I hire you, I just ask you
to be straight with me.
All right?
It took me a long time
to build this shop...,
...and I don't want anything
risking that.
You understand?
Give me one week,
and I'll show you what I can do.
Come back tomorrow.
Thank you.
All right.
Sir, get up.
It's suppertime.
He won't answer.
Got some plumbing problems,
I think.
Like, I'm hearing noises
in the walls.
Patrol and unit 25.
We get calls.
This is a code four
on First and Broadway.
Code two.
Get 6544.
Great.
Miss Trupiano?
Bobby Reynolds.
Yeah.
Yeah, from high school.
Uh, yeah, I was released.
Is Louis there?
Oh, yeah?
You got a forwarding number
maybe or...
Hello?
She's got the dirty mouth
from the South.
All the way from Pascagoula,
Mississippi...,
...it's Molly Ritter.
You handle all the apartments
in the building, man?
Who's been in mine?
You have the only key.
Everything okay?
I found these.
They're fingernails.
I know what they are, man.
Why...why are they in my place?
Who would keep 'em?
Maybe they belong
to your mother?
Why would she keep 'em?
When did you
speak to her last?
Couple of years.
Yeah, you shouldn't have
to hear this from me...,
...but the neighbors heard
from the police.
Your mother locked herself
in her apartment for weeks...
...before she died.
What?
You got any idea
why she would do that?
No idea.
I started work here after.
I never met her.
But when they found her,
she was in real bad shape.
You never knew about this?
Nobody check in on her?
She didn't have
anybody else, man.
Maybe one of the neighbors
upstairs knows more.
Well, no offense, son...,
...but nobody here wants
to talk to you.
Everybody knows you were
in prison.
People talk.
She was sick, real sick.
Yeah.
You...you gonna check
on those noises?
What noises?
In the walls.
Rusty pipes, I don't know.
They're coming
from somewhere, man.
Well, this is a prewar building.
You know, walls are thick.
There's vents running through
the ceiling.
There's no sound.
You seem to be the only one
hearing things.
- I wasn't there.
- You weren't there?
What am I...
am I seeing things?
I...I don't know what you're
talking about.
Why do you keep lying to me
all the time?
I'm not lying to you.
What, I go to work all day.
I come home and what?
No, just just stop.
Who is this guy?
Stop.
Stop it.
Please.
Well, you're acting like I'm...
what, like...what am I?
Am I the bad guy here?
You're the one that's out...
No, no, no, no,
I didn't say that.
I didn't say it.
Well, what the hell
were you doing there?
I wasn't doing anything.
I don't want to catch you
by that door again.
Are you all right in there?
All right, we'll start you off
with tune-ups.
We'll see how fast you work.
You're also going to bring
the cars in and park them...
...behind the gate every night.
It's freshman work,
but you're the new guy.
You show me you got skills,
I'll give you more shifts
and bigger jobs.
You hear that?
What?
Like a voice.
It's a valve grinder.
Car keys are in there.
What is that?
That's the drop-box.
Don't give keys out till
the customer's paid in full.
You got it?
Had a lot of cars jacked
from this shop.
Can't risk that kind
of nonsense anymore.
Yo!
You with me?
Yeah.
Good.
Get to work.
Two sugars, no milk.
I switched to Sweet'N Low.
Are you gonna knock it,
or you gonna drink it?
You call anyone
from the neighborhood yet?
Yeah, I called around.
Seems like everybody moved away.
Hmm.
People grew up.
Things ain't what
they used to be, right?
Did you think everything
would be the same?
I was hoping
some things would be.
Bobby...
I know you got questions.
No, no,
I don't have questions.
I had questions...,
...had questions for the past
few years.
I stopped asking them
when you stopped writing.
I didn't know if you were alive
or coming back.
Why on Earth
would you just cut me off?
I thought I was
doing it for you.
For me?
Nothing that happened in there...
...was anything that we could have
talked about.
So what did you think
was going to happen here?
You show up out of thin air...,
...bring me coffee,
and I forgive you?
You don't think people deserve
a second chance?
Bobby.
You want to come by
the apartment some time?
Maybe.
I'll take maybe.
Maybe...
...I got to go.
Can I help you?
No.
What are you doing?
Are they coming from you?
The sounds, is that you?
Maybe the woman?
What did you say?
There's a woman who lives here.
I've seen her at your...
You don't know anything
about who lives here, man.
You hear them.
Don't you?
Ah!
What?
Am I the bad guy here?
No, no, no, no,
I didn't say that.
I didn't say it.
Well, what the hell are you
doing there?
I wasn't doing anything.
I don't want to catch you
by that door again.
Do you understand?
Understand?
Do you understand me?
Do you understand?
You're hurting me!
There you go!
Don't you ever do that...
Oh...
Ew.
Listen.
Shh, shh...
Do you hear it?
No, no.
It's not in my head.
Bobby.
Bobby, where are you?
Bobby!
Bobby, why aren't you here?
Oh, it's happening again.
Shh, shh.
They're after me.
I'm not crazy.
You hear them, don't you?
Oh, no.
No!
Going to the lobby?
Hello?
Do you know if he's in there?
Bobby?
Your door's open.
Hello?
You came.
How'd you get in?
Your door was open.
You okay?
Yeah.
Who...who lives
in that apartment?
Nosy neighbors.
I guess they don't feel
too comfortable...
...with an ex-con in the building.
Wow.
Yeah, it's hers.
All this...
all this is hers.
I don't know what to do with it.
Well, it's kind of...
Vintage?
Ugly.
Do you like it here?
Getting used to it.
Everybody here
seems a little off.
Well, it's the East Village.
She looks happy.
I don't think she was.
She was on medication.
It got so bad that, uh...,
...uh, she stayed here
at the apartment for weeks...
...and didn't leave until
eventually she starved to death.
I don't know if it was suicide.
Nobody does.
I can't even go in her bedroom.
It sounds crazy, but I...
...I feel sometimes
like she's still here.
Bobby, it's gonna take time
to heal.
These are amazing.
They're just rough sketches.
What?
Do you ever wonder what would
have happened?
Sometimes.
Do you?
Every day.
What was it like?
Isolating.
But at the same time,
you never have any privacy.
You just hang onto the stuff
you had, you know, before, the...
...the good things.
It's late.
I should go.
Yeah.
It's good to see you.
You too.
Please, somebody help us!
Hang on.
You okay?
Miss?
You need some help
with something?
Whatever it is...,
...I'm right next door
if you need anything.
You need something?
I want you to mind
your own business, okay?
Huh?
Please open the door.
These measurements are incorrect.
Are you sure?
Yeah, look at this.
Senior collection's
going up Friday...,
...and you haven't even sewn yet.
I went to see Bobby.
I saw a woman standing
at his door.
She was crying.
I don't know.
I...I suppose he doesn't owe me
an explanation or anything.
- You still have feelings
for him.
I don't know.
Maybe.
What if I do?
What am I supposed
to do about it?
I don't know what
I'm supposed to do.
Somebody help us!
Come here!
Get in here.
Let Carly go.
Run, baby, run!
Look at me.
Carly...
Carly!
Do what you have to do to me!
Where are you going?
Fuck this.
You weren't there?
What, am I...
am I seeing things?
You okay?
What, I go to work all day.
Here, come in.
It's okay.
Come on.
What's your name?
Am I the bad guy here?
You're the one that's out...
No, no, no,
I didn't say that.
My name is Bobby.
I know you probably don't want
to talk to strangers, right?
But if you tell me...
what's going on in there,
I might be able to help you.
You want to tell me?
You play the piano?
Hey!
Listen to me.
Where were you?
Here, inside the house.
You were just here
inside of the house?
So how...how come I saw you out
by that door?
What were you doing
at that door?
Hey, you want to play
a real piano?
You weren't there?
Come on.
Why don't we make some music
on a real piano?
I remember why I can't able to reach
the pedals...
...but I bet you can.
Stay right there.
One second.
What are you doing?
Don't you dare try
to do that again!
This is crazy.
Stay right there.
He's never going to hurt you
or your mother again.
All right?
Don't you dare do that!
Why do you keep lying to me
all the time?
Where were you?
No, I didn't say that.
Well, what the hell were you
doing there?
911!
What's your emergency?
Yeah, I'm...I'm at 20 Avenue E,
apartment 519.
The guy next door
is beating on his wife.
Do you understand?
Can you repeat the location,
please?
20 Avenue E.
When I tell you to stay in,
you stay in!
Sir, is anyone hurt?
Yeah, I don't know.
Well, just send...
you can't just send somebody?
Sir, I need to confirm
if someone's hurt.
I can hear you in there.
Hug me once, okay?
Open the goddamn door!
Domestic officers arrived.
1026?
Yeah, right down here.
You know the tenants?
No.
They fight a lot.
It got pretty bad tonight.
You see anything?
No, but there's a...
there's a little girl...,
...and I didn't want
to take chances.
The guy is a cop.
Please stand back, sir.
NYPD.
Anybody inside in need
of assistance?
Open up!
Roger that.
This is a joke?
Where are they?
Are you sure this is
the apartment?
Yeah.
I...I just heard them.
It doesn't look like anyone's
lived here in a very long time.
You been drinking tonight?
No.
No!
The daughter just
visited my apartment!
What's her name?
I...I don't know.
And the wife,
the one that was beaten...,
...do you know her name?
She never told me.
Most people know a lot more...
...about their imaginary friends
than that, pal.
You got yourself one hell
of a vivid imagination.
1080, cancel that call.
104.
They were just here!
Look, you know what?
Next time, just don't call us.
Let's go.
Wasting my time, man.
Who lives in the apartment
next to mine?
Why?
Because I just called
the cops on them...,
...and they showed up,
and there was nobody there.
So what the hell is going on?
You called the police on who?
On the guy in the apartment
next to mine.
He's a cop.
Look, I don't know
what you're talking about.
That apartment's been empty...
...ever since I started
working here.
517, right?
Yeah...no.
There's...there's a girl.
There's a kid and her mom...,
...and the dad is abusing them
all day long.
Everybody in the place
can hear it.
Yeah, not everyone.
I've...
I've seen them.
Look, I've walked each and every
hall in this building.
I know every tenant
that lives here.
I've never seen a girl
or a family in 517.
Just you and that guy in 512
live there.
Now, let me sleep.
What?
You're killing me.
Sorry.
We still have two more chapters.
I got to go.
What?
Why?
Wait.
Are you okay?
It was my fault.
What was?
Bobby went to jail
because of me.
What do you mean?
We were at that bar
on Rivington.
Some guy followed me
into the bathroom.
He pushed me
up against the wall...,
...and put his hand over my mouth.
What?
Next thing I know, Bobby...,
...he hit him so hard that I heard
the bones in his face crack.
And he didn't stop.
The more I cried,
the more Bobby hit him.
Al, he killed someone.
I don't know what to do.
I mean, he did all that time.
Maybe he'll hurt you some day.
It's...it's not him.
It never was.
He was only trying to help.
I just want you
to be careful, okay?
Yeah.
What the hell's your problem,
man?
You all right, bro?
Uh, I got blood coming out
of my ears.
How the hell did you
do that, man?
I don't know.
Go see a doctor.
I got to finish my shift, man.
Blood coming out of your ears
ain't normal.
Are you sick or something?
You doing okay?
How do you mean?
I'm not gonna pretend like
I know you...,
...but you been falling apart
since you took this job.
Um, if I try to explain it,
it's not gonna sound right.
When I came out of recovery,
I started over too.
I had a sponsor to talk to
when things got out of hand.
You know what I'm saying?
You need someone to talk to,
or you're gonna fall apart.
Go home.
I'll lock up.
All right.
I'm leaving the city.
I can't stay here.
Why?
I think whatever's...
...whatever happened to my mother
is happening to me.
And I...I just...
I just got to make it stop.
What?
I'm hear...I'm hearing sounds...,
...and I am seeing people
who aren't there.
Bobby,
your mother was sick.
She wasn't crazy.
Something made her crazy.
Maybe you leaving...
...did make her depressed.
You deserted her...,
...like you deserted a lot
of people in your life.
You got tables.
I got to go.
Open the door!
Open the door, please!
I know you're in there!
What do you want?
- Good morning, sir.
- Yeah.
Do you know a Joseph Wright?
He lives down the hall from you.
I just moved in.
Heard anything
out of the ordinary?
Seen anyone suspicious?
No.
The neighbors told us
you just got out of Rikers.
Is that true?
What's this about?
Were you home all evening?
No, I was with a friend.
I may be back
with more questions.
No, no.
You didn't see anything?
Rick, you want to give me
a hand with this?
Yo, Bobby!
You're an hour late.
Sorry, man, there's something
going on in my building today.
We need to talk.
You come by the shop
last night?
No.
You sure you didn't come by...
...the shop
last night after closing?
Yeah.
There was a 300 that came in
for a tire balance.
You remember it?
It wasn't mine.
I didn't do a balance yesterday.
It's gone.
I came in this morning,
it was off the lot.
I called up the owner,
she hasn't picked it up yet.
You got something you want
to ask me, man?
Look, my other guys have been
with me for years, Bobby.
All I got on you
is your history.
But I have a situation
with no other answer.
If that 300 gets returned
in the next hour...,
I won't call the cops.
I don't have the car, man.
No, I'm trying to give you
the benefit of the doubt here.
Call the cops, man.
I don't have the car.
I can't keep you on until
that 300 turns up.
Yeah.
All right.
Hello?
Yo, what's this?
How the hell did this happen?
Damn, man!
Watch the shop.
Are you okay?
Alyssa Foldes?
Alyssa Foldes.
Anybody...
...nobody knows her?
Alyssa Foldes?
You know Alyssa?
It's really important
that I talk to her.
Sorry.
I don't know where she is.
Come on.
You got to help me out.
She put a lot of trust in you.
And you're going to end up
hurting her again.
She can't deal with that
in her life right now.
You don't know
what's going on.
I know Alyssa
never showed up tonight.
I know she didn't turn in
her final.
And I know she's only been
acting like this...
...since you showed up.
Just leave her alone.
She knows about the other girl.
What other girl?
The woman at your apartment.
Did...did Alyssa talk to her?
Don't know.
Just have her call me.
Bobby, you there?
It's Hector.
The city towed
the wrong car, man.
I'm sorry I doubted you.
You still have your job
if you want it, man.
Bobby!
Are you all right, kid?
Hello?
Little girl?
You all right?
Hello?
Where are you?
Little girl?
Help!
Anybody?
Damn it!
Hello?
Mr. Reynolds, do you know
what day it is today?
No.
What?
It's your weekly check-in.
Appointments with your PO
are not optional.
I thought we understood
each other.
Yeah.
Sorry.
Is there something
I should know?
Mr. Reynolds?
I can't talk right now.
Look, let me give this to you
in vivid detail.
You speed your way...
...into the parole office
right now...
...or you illegally violate,
and we come looking for you.
You get me?
Mr. Reynolds?
Help...help me!
I know you're in there!
Please!
Please open the door!
Bobby?
Bobby, can you hear me?
Look, um, those...
...those noises that you heard,
I think...
...I think I may be
hearing them too.
I don't understand
what's happening.
You were trying to tell me
something...
...and I didn't listen,
and I'm sorry.
And I'm going to come
and find you, okay?
Open the door!
Bobby?
Think I don't know
you're in there?
I don't want trouble.
You've been watching me.
I see you in the window.
What are you looking at?
Something happened
on that floor.
You know something, don't you?
There was this family
living there.
One night...,
...the mother, she kept screaming.
No.
Don't!
But nobody helped her.
It doesn't make sense.
You could...you could have
just called the cops.
A lot of terrible things
happen in this city every day.
Either we assumed someone
would call the police...,
...or we were afraid to,
or worse.
Some of us just didn't care.
The next morning,
they were all dead.
It's your fault.
You could have done something.
You let them die.
Any one of you,
my mother included...,
...could have saved them.
You realize that?
Hey, hey, hey!
Wait!
I'm sorry! I can't help you!
Why...why won't they stop?
Hello, Miss?
Is he in there?
I really need to find him.
Anyone home?
Sorry, I...
...the woman who walked
in here, do you...
Oh, my God!
Alyssa?
Alyssa!
I'm so sorry.
Oh, my God.
What did they do to you?
Oh, God.
Please.
911...
What is your emergency?
I...I need an ambulance.
Please.
What is your current location?
Sir?
Can you hear me?
You're doing real good, honey.
Everything's going to be okay.
But I want you to be strong
for mommy.
You got me?
Right.
Let me see that pretty smile.
There.
Hey, what are you doing?
Please don't do this.
Don't do what?
We're leaving.
Why are you leaving?
You know why.
- But you...
- Don't!
You can't leave.
Whoa, whoa.
What?
Don't what?
Shh, it's okay.
It's okay.
Where are you?
Here, here, here,
here, here, here.
Listen, listen.
You just close your eyes...
...and go to that special place
like always.
Nothing else will matter.
Carly, are you okay?
Why are you crying?
What...
No.
I...I really don't understand
what's happening here.
What...what...
Why do you want to leave me?
- Why?
- Hmm?
Look at me.
You did...
you did this to me.
I didn't do that.
Who the hell did that to you?
Go!
Run, baby, run!
Look at me!
Just let Carly go, please.
Uh, Carly...
Do what you have to do to me!
Carly.
I don't understand
what's happening here.
Walter.
It's fricking making me...
It makes me so mad!
It's making me lose
my freakin' mind, you know.
Why won't you just let us go,
please?
Please.
Baby.
I love you so much.
Just say it for me once okay?
Just tell me that you love me.
Just once.
Just say it.
Just say that you...
No, no!
Somebody help us!
Please, someone help us!
Open this door!
Come on.
Please.
No, don't, please.
No, no.
Please, somebody help us!
Come on and help me!
Open the door!
Somebody help us, please!
No, Walter, no!
No!
Walter, no!
Stop!
You've got to stop it!
You mind your own business.
Agh!
No!
Alyssa!
Alyssa?
Oh, it's okay.
It's okay.
Subtitles by Bishop