created by aksub
I remembered a joke.
It's funny.
Okay.
Seorg and his wife
were having sex one night,
when their young son
suddenly enters the room.
Hang on a sec.
Are we going in the right direction?
Olav!
What are we looking for?
Just keep going.
A little bit more or else
we will be flagged on the site.
Okay.
Continue the joke.
The boy gets scared and leaves
running from the room, crying.
The mother says, "Honey!
Now, what should we do? "
You know women...
The father says:
"Let me handle this".
Then he leaves
and goes to the child's bedroom
to say he was joking.
He opens the door and sees
the small bastard
is lying on top of his grandmother,
having sex with her!
Very animated too, rises and falls,
up and down.
Then he looks
for the father and says:
What's wrong, Dad?
You play with mine
so I play with her, right?
Stop!
Is it here?
It's right here.
Don't move!
Turn on the light.
Oh, my God!
Kate!
- Shit.
- Sorry, Kate.
These fellas said that you've been
expecting them?
- Of course, thanks, Hanks.
- Thanks.
Hey, uh...
you forgot, didn't you?
No, no, I just...
Yeah.
He just wanted to...
Actually, this is him.
I'm Dr. Sander Halvorson.
Kate Lloyd.
Yes.
Do you know who I am?
I do.
Adam told me
a little bit about you as well.
He said you specialized
in vertebrate paleontology.
Primarily, yes.
And obviously you extracted specimens
from pack ice.
I've worked on several cold weather digs.
Good.
An old friend of mine,
a colleague of Oslo,
runs a geological research station
in Antarctica.
48 hours ago, his team found something
quite remarkable.
Really?
What'd they find?
We're flying down there tommorow evening
to examine the site.
And I need a paleontologist.
Doctor, I'm sure you can understand that
I need to know a little bit about what
it is I'm being asked to dig up?
There is a structure.
A structure?
- Yes.
- In Antarctica?
And a specimen.
That's all I can tell you.
And I guess I don't have any time
to think about this.
No, I'm sorry. I need
your answer right now.
Well...
I'm in.
Great.
Adam will get you the details
of our departure.
- Right, I'll see you in the car.
- Yes, of course. Thank you.
Adam.
What the hell is it?
You now officially know as much as I do.
But I'll tell you one thing, I
worked for that guy for three years
and I've never seen him this excited.
She US?
Look at this guy.
I mean, how is that even
humanly possible?
I was hoping maybe you could
help me with something?
I can't seem to get ahold of a newspaper
three weeks old
and I'm a man in desperate need
for certain information.
Carter, don't do this to
yourself, man.
And what information would that be?
I want to know how the
Cavaliers are going.
I don't follow football.
It's a basketball team.
They play basketball.
Barely.
They're the Cavaliers, man.
- Sorry, I couldn't help you.
- Nah, that's all right.
Listen, just so you guys know,
whatever y'all are doing,
you might wanna wrap it up
in a couple of days.
Yeah, why's that?
There's a storm moving in.
A nasty one.
Good morning, Griggs.
Yeah, he's right.
And the last place
where you want to be
is cooped up with a dozen
Norwegian guys.
Trust me.
Base in sight of my 1 o'clock.
This is H3 Sea King inbound to Thule.
Do you copy?
Hello, H3 Sea King.
Please, approach from the west.
Landing pad is cleared
Bravo, coming back.
Good to go, Griggs.
- Dr. Halvorson?
- Yes?
- Welcome to Thule.
- Thank you.
Edvard asked you to go
to the site, right now.
Lars is going to drive you.
- Hi.
- Hi. Welcome.
- Please go in the Spryte.
- Thanks.
Hello, sir.
Watch your step.
Brighten.
Edvard!
- You got it.
- Sure, I did.
Yeah, this is Kate Lloyd.
- Columbia paleontology.
- Welcome.
Adam Finch,
my research assistant.
- Welcome.
- Hi.
This is Edvard, my good friend.
This is some of my team.
Karl and Juliette. Both geologists.
- Hi.
- Welcome.
Okay.
Let me show you why you flew
10,000 miles.
Holy shit!
We estimated this has been here
approximately 100,000 years.
We picked up a signal transmitting.
Some kind of distress call, perhaps.
Incredible.
We think the signal
was triggered
when the survivor
exited the craft.
Survivor?
My God.
How long will it take to get it out,
do you know, Kate?
Assuming you've the right equipment,
I'd say...
maybe half a day.
Good.
The ice, should I ask you how fragile
is it?
It's not in a fracture zone.
So there's very little risk of fissuring.
And the ice is quite dense.
So we think
we can get it out in one piece.
Good.
I mean, rough estimates about
6 by 12 feet, 3 and a half feet high.
- Probably some place right around...
- That's great...
Make sure that everyone stays off
the radio.
I do not want any information out.
And the crane... do we have
something appropriate for this?
Yes, it's already there.
It's all set up.
I'm Peder, by the way.
- Peder.
- Nice to meet you.
So, you've gotten it all taken care of.
I don't think you really need me.
What about him?
He's secretly disinterested or...?
Oh, that's Lars.
He does not understand English,
but he works like a bear.
And, as you can see
from the scans,
the ship carved a 200 meter tunnel
into the ice.
So, let me get this right.
You crashed into a glacier...
And then without enough information
you leave the cozy confines of your ship?
Maybe he was hurt and wanted to find
someplace warm.
Well, I guess it didn't find it.
The first night is hard.
- Sorry, I didn't mean to keep you up.
- No, no, it's fine.
I'll never look at them the same again.
What do you mean for transport weight?
To cut it down to a portable weight,
we have to take it from here to here.
Start with 4 inches.
I never believed in this shit.
I always did.
- We're all set?
- Nearly there.
Good.
But before we do,
I'm going to take a tissue sample.
Do you really that's a good idea?
Yes, I do.
I mean the conditions
are so unpredictable
and we don't have the proper equipment.
Sterilization is an issue.
Edvard, what do you have in the way of
a small diameter drill?
Up to 30mm.
Very good.
I think somewhere around here.
Kate.
Just a second.
In the future, don't contradict me
in front of those people again.
- I just thought...
- You're not here to think.
You're here to get that thing
safe out of the ice.
I hope we understand each other.
So, have you ever tasted this before?
- No, I haven't.
- It tastes very bad.
Gentlemen.
Ladies.
After a short but thorough investigation
of our visitor,
I can say, unequivocally,
that I've never seen anything
on any cellular level,
like what we have
in that other room.
Now, the impact of this find...
will be felt
for thousands of years.
From this point on,
the world as we know it
has forever been altered.
You, my friends,
will all be immortalized,
as the people
who made this discovery.
Thank you.
Do you think they're going to pay a bonus
for bringing over an alien
instead of coal samples?
You've got anything better than
this cough syrup?
- Hey, Griggy.
- Yeah?
You want to go out
and get the cabinet stash?
Sure, no problem.
I'm on it.
Where did I put this bottle?
Jesus Ch...
Screw you, man.
Son of a...
It broke out!
What?
It ain't a damn joke, man!
The freaking thing's alive!
I was in the room, man,
looking at the ice
then the freaking thing jumped out!
We search
in groups of two and three.
The entire camp.
If you find it, pull out,
don't attempt anything
on your own.
And be careful...
we don't know what condition it's in.
Griggs, did you leave that open?
- I don't remember.
- Shit.
Hey, just be careful, man. That thing
jumped through the fucking roof.
Jesus Christ.
Help! Over here!
Help! Somebody! Over here!
- It attacked Henrik.
- Come on.
- Jesus!
- In there!
- God, somebody do something!
- Oh my God.
Shoot it! Shoot the fucker, man!
We got to burn that fucker, man! Burn it!
Throw it, throw it!
His blood pressure's low.
Henrik and...
his small children.
Yes, it's horrible.
It's a horrible tragedy.
We're all shocked.
At what happened to Henrik.
But with due respect, we need to examine
the remains before it all disintegrates.
Hey, that was a man.
Not remains.
No, I know,
I'm talking about the creature.
And I'm sure we're all aware
of the importance of this discovery.
This may be the first
and only time...
mankind has been visited
by an alien lifeform.
And as scientists,
we're obliged to study it.
Didn't work out so well
the last time, did it?
I think you should destroy it.
Completely.
I think you've contributed
enough to this matter now.
Oh, really?
Listen, your guy, Olav, back there,
he's in bad shape.
Now, we're gonna fly him back
to McMurdo at sun-up...
and take him
to the military hospital.
And what're you gonna tell them, hmm?
I'm gonna tell them the truth, as crazy
as it sounds.
Kate?
Can you help here?
Come on.
Pull that side up.
His face is encased in some type
of amniotic sac.
The tissue. Looks almost new.
What was it doing to him?
It appears that it was absorbing him.
Some type of digestion.
It's fascinating.
It is fascinating.
- What's the matter? Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
- You sure?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
- Do you need something?
- No, no. I'm okay.
What is this?
Looks like a titanium plate.
Used to reinforce bones
and compound fractures.
Yeah, that's right.
Henrik broke his arm last year.
He had to go to Argentina
to get it set.
So if this was in his arm,
what's it doing out of him now?
That's a good question.
What are you doing?
Took a sample of Henrik's tissue.
I want to find out what this thing
was doing to him.
I think you should take a look at this.
These cells aren't dead.
That's not possible.
Looks like the alien cells
are somehow
attacking Henrik's cells
and then they...
What is that? It looks like
they are transforming...
They're imitating his cells.
Okay, I don't know
if that's what I'm seeing, but...
They're imitating him.
It's going to be okay, Olav.
A doctor will see you in McMurdo.
Kate.
- Hey.
- Hi.
We're leaving.
Once the weather holds up,
we'll be back with help...
as soon as we can.
Okay.
Alright.
- Keep him warm.
- I will.
C'mon, let's go.
Sit down there.
There you go.
Ah, let's get the hell out of here.
Carter!
Carter, wait!
She's flagging us down.
- What's wrong?
- They shouldn't leave.
Carter.
Let's just get out of here, man.
Alright, fuck it, we're landing.
Shit.
Let's take her down.
Is there something wrong?
No, everything's fine.
Probably just forgot something.
We'll be in the air in no time, okay?
Don't worry.
Hang in there.
Something's wrong.
Hailing McMurdo, or any ears on
the emergency channel.
Do you copy? Over.
I repeat, this is Thule Station.
They crashed here,
right behind this ridgeline.
It's impossible to reach them.
This doesn't make any sense.
I mean, they have plenty
of visibility, right?
We're not going after them?
Shouldn't we try?
We need a chopper
to even get close to them.
And there's refueling and hailing.
All this can't be a coincidence.
Radio's dead. It's fucking dead.
The incoming storm.
Fuck.
There's too much interference.
We have four missing persons.
We have no helicopter or radio.
You made a mistake
for bringing these people here.
More people may die.
But, Sander, we don't know
even if they are dead or not.
Colin, Lars, get your gear.
We'll take a snowcat
to the next base.
Lars, do it now.
I don't think that's a good idea.
And why is that?
Because no one can leave this camp...
until we know more about
what's going on here.
- I make decisions about this camp.
- I know, Edvard, but...
Why did you flag down that helicopter?
Because I thought it was in danger.
Why?
I took a sample of Henrik's blood...
and I saw that the alien cells
were still alive.
They were alive and they were copying
Henrik's cells.
Replicating them.
Adam saw it too.
Is that true?
I don't know.
I mean, I don't know what we saw.
I mean, we saw something.
I don't understand.
What are you saying?
That this thing can,
and probably has,
replicated a person.
- What?
- That can't be.
- Who?
- This is insane.
Okay, Okay. Kate? Kate?
Okay! Kate.
This is not the time to be yelling fire.
Let's stop, gather our thoughts,
and discuss this in private.
We don't need
any private meeting, Doctor.
We all want the fucking information!
There's more.
What are those?
I think they are fillings
from someone's teeth.
I found them by a puddle of blood
in the shower.
Puddle of blood?
It can clone cells,
but not inorganic material.
It couldn't copy these, so
it spit them out.
We're wasting too much time already.
Lars?
Listen!
When I went back to check it,
someone had cleaned up the blood.
Someone had wiped it away.
Alright, so whatever it is...
It is still here.
I've heard enough.
Lars, Colin, get the gear.
Ten minutes.
Please, Edvard.
You can't leave.
You can't leave!
You don't know what we're dealing with.
Well done.
Kate?
I don't know
if I should be speaking about this.
I don't want to get anyone in trouble.
Speaking about what?
You were saying...
about someone cleaning up the
blood from the shower.
And that someone here
may not be themselves.
Juliette, please...
What did you see?
After the crash, I think... I saw
Colin coming from the showers.
He was holding something.
It could've been a towel, a rag,
something to clean up.
Kate, I can't say for sure, but
it's just that I s...
He's leaving with Edvard.
We can't let them go.
We can't let any of them go.
I know where they keep
the keys for the vehicles.
- Where are they?
- In that drawer.
- This one?
- Yes.
- How many am I looking for?
- Five.
Three and four.
You said there were five?
Run!
Kate, what happened?
Karl. It got Karl.
It got... Karl.
Kate.
Burn it!
Enough, that's enough.
Burn in hell.
What the fuck's happening to us?
It attacks its prey,
copies it perfectly...
and then hides inside it.
Waiting.
Is it still among us?
It could be any of us.
We got to get out of here.
Yeah, right now.
And it could be getting
a vehicle with it.
You'll be alone.
Vulnerable.
That's exactly what it wants.
Not to mention you'll be giving it
a way out of here.
A way to spread.
It's like a virus.
So what do we do with any virus?
Quarantine.
We isolate it and then we kill it.
Yeah.
We have to rely on science.
Exposing our uncontaminated blood to the
cells of the creature
might create a reaction...
of some kind.
So we take blood samples from everybody.
Yeah, and we test each one of them.
Yes, Adam and I can do that.
Okay.
Lars and I'll disable the vehicles.
We have to trust in this plan.
It's our only chance
of making it through this.
- Is that it?
- Yes.
- No more vehicles?
- Only these.
Okay.
What?
Grenades.
Is everything alright?
Yes, yes, everything's fine.
Good.
- Lars, you're okay?
- Yes.
Kate, we should go.
The storm is getting worse.
Who is that?
Hurry up. They're coming.
The Americans.
It is impossible for a human
to survive in that crash.
We should burn them.
Right here, right now.
- Let's finish them off!
- Peder?
It could be murder.
- It could be survival, Kate.
- Yes, but we don't have to kill them.
Right? We can just lock them up...
until the Sander's test is ready.
Please.
So this is a good idea?
Locking us up?
You need our help.
Warn your scientists they can't handle
with what we saw in that chopper.
For all I know,
you could be one of those things.
It's pretty hard to believe
you both walked away from that crash.
- Yeah, I get that, I do, but...
- We're preparing a test.
And then we figure out who's who.
It's all I can offer you right now.
Damn!
There's a fire here!
Someone sabotaged it.
There's nothing left. Nothing.
Now there's no test.
How could this happen?
It was no accident.
You.
You were in there with him.
You were the last one.
- How are you accusing me?
- Why not?
- He's got something to hide.
- What are you, an asshole?
I was the one working on the test.
I left for 2 minutes!
You just don't want us
to know the truth,
- do ya?
- Bullshit!
This is a goddamn fucking nightmare!
There might be another way.
I think there might be...
another way to tell.
Peder, give me your flashlight.
Now tell Lars...
to open his mouth.
Tell him to open his mouth.
Open your mouth.
That's good.
Lars has fillings.
So he's human.
It can't imitate
inorganic material.
See?
Yes.
Good.
Open.
Come on!
You're next!
Open your mouth!
Okay.
Good.
Right now, it's at least something.
A way to eliminate
some of us.
So I'm gonna get killed because
I floss?
Nobody's getting killed.
Kate?
Kate, come on.
Kate.
Just do it.
Open.
Just go stand over there.
You know as well as I do,
there are too many variables.
Open your mouth.
Open your mouth!
Theyre porcelain.
Go stand with Adam.
Anyone else with porcelain fillings?
Or clean teeth?
It's bloody absurd.
This is wrong.
Jonas, you and Lars go out.
Get Carter and Jameson,
bring them in here, we'll check them too.
But why don't we just leave them
where they are? They can't do anything.
We need to know.
- What?
- She wants us to find the Americans.
Let's do it, then.
Come on!
She is smart.
Yeah.
She is in control now.
Shit, they've gone.
They escaped.
Lars.
Let's go back inside.
No.
We have to find them.
Lars, be careful.
They are not human!
Lars!
Lars Wait.
Lars.
Peder.
Stay calm!
The threat isn't here.
It's out there.
The Americans are the real enemy.
He's right, Peder.
Whatever they're saying right now,
it doesn't matter.
You can't trust them.
Watch them.
Kate!
Come on!
Where are they?
- Where's the rest?
- They attacked them.
- Who?
- They got Lars!
- Peder!
- They took Lars!
- What happened?
- Peder, keep them back.
- We have to help him.
- Stay on them, Peder.
- What happened?
- Peder, they took Lars.
- The enemy is out there.
- We don't know if we can trust them!
Peder, don't listen to them.
Stay on them! Stay on them, Peder!
They're inside.
Where is Lars?
We haven't got Lars.
- Calm down!
- Where is Lars?
I said calm down!
- Where the fuck is Lars?
- Drop it!
- Somebody tell him.
- Peder, don't listen to them.
- Put it down!
- They killed Lars!
Lars is killed.
Burn them! Burn them!
Peder? Peder?
Okay!
I just wanna check my friend, okay?
It's okay.
He was gonna fire.
It's gonna catch fire!
It will explode!
Come on! Let's go!
Edvard?
- Pick him up.
- Okay.
You.
Yeah, you. Help him!
Alright, show yourselves!
Right fucking now!
Everybody in the rec room.
Pick him up, come on.
Sit down.
Not all of us are human.
Just put him over there
on the couch.
Help! Help me!
- My God!
- Get it off him!
What the fuck is this shit, man?
Carter, Carter!
Carter, burn it, man!
There's something wrong with it!
Hold on!
Goddamn it, Carter, burn it!
Look out!
Fuck!
Adam!
- Shit!
- Carter, take it!
Carter!
There's something wrong
with the pressure.
Put some air in the pipe.
Watch out!
Carter!
We gotta get the air up.
No.
God!
No, God!
Carter!
No! No!
I'm with you, buddy.
Carter.
You're okay?
Yeah.
And you?
Not yet, no.
We find it and then we kill it.
I think that was Sander.
Yeah.
- Shit!
- Watch out! God!
Kate, do you see it?
Where'd it go?
There!
Get back!
Don't.
Don't touch it.
You hear that?
Yeah.
Kate!
- Sander.
- Wait.
So what?
He'll freeze out there.
And if he doesn't?
If it makes it out of here...
millions of people could die.
- It's got nowhere to go.
- Yes, it does.
Alright.
What?
What happened to Lars?
We didn't kill him.
Come on.
Run, run!
Kate!
Kate?
So what we do now?
There's a Russian station...
about 50 miles from here.
Should have enough gas.
We're gonna make it back, okay?
Okay.
Let's go.
I'm ganna put this in the back.
You know how I knew
you weren't human...
when you showed up back at base?
No.
Your earring.
It was on your other ear.
Kate?
Kate, what're you doing?
Let's talk about it.
Talk to me.
Kate?
Kate!
No!...
Oh my God.
Hello?
Hello, can anybody hear me?
Edvard?
Lars, it's me.
Hello, Lars!
Lars? Lars, it's Matias.
It's Matias!
- Open your mouth.
- What?
- Do what I say, now!
- It's Matias. Lars, it's me, Matias.
That's no dog.
Start the helicopter, now!
Get it up, get it up! Now!
Come on!