Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
Fraternitas fratrum.
Wait, I'm gonna...
Ah, no way.
♪ Oh, what will I do... ♪
Wait, it was
just here a second ago.
Shoot, I can't find it.
♪ Without you,
what will I do... ♪
Teri.
- Here's yours.
- Aw.
I forgot about it till now.
Got more cheese, bitches!
Oh, God.
- Yes.
- I don't think it's gonna be as good as...
Wait, where's Lindsay?
Um, I think I saw her
at the library earlier.
Oh, my God.
Those are so cute.
That's right,
'cause you can't forget them.
Teri?
Hey, Oona. What's up?
Hey, where are you?
I'm heading to the lot.
Wait, you're not coming back?
I told my grandma I'd be home
for breakfast in the morning.
But I was your secret Santa,
and I got the perfect
Lindsay gift.
- Guess what it is.
- I don't know. What?
Lindsay. Think.
Perfect gift.
Oh, my God.
You told me yours disappeared.
And every girl needs
a little self-care.
Now you'll never need a man.
Well, at least I got something
to look forward to next semester.
Love you, Lindsay.
Have a great break.
Love you, too.
What?
Help! Help! Please!
Let me in, please.
Help me!
Pick up, pick up.
Oh, shit.
Please, help me!
Please, help! Please!
Oh, my God. Thank you.
No.
Please.
I'm sorry. Whatever I did...
No!
Help! Help!
- ♪ J-J-J-Jingle ♪
- ♪ What a beautiful day ♪
♪ For a ride in a sleigh,
got to get underway ♪
- ♪ J-J-J-Jingle ♪
- ♪ Take a little town trip ♪
♪ With a slick little chick
and you figure to click ♪
- ♪ J-J-J-Jingle ♪
- ♪ You're a slap-happy pair... ♪
Claudette, you're killing me.
- I'm up.
- ♪ Oh, what fun it is to ride in... ♪
I'm up.
I have a final in ten minutes,
and I can't find my DivaCup.
How do you lose a DivaCup?
With abandon.
♪ And little baby sister's ♪
♪ Acting kinda perky ♪
♪ But most of all ♪
♪ When snowflakes fall ♪
♪ I know it's Christmas ♪
♪ Christmastime... ♪
Hey, could I borrow
your straightener?
Riley.
What the heck?
I had no idea
you were so good onstage.
- Why am I singing tonight?
- ♪ Jingle all the way... ♪
It should be you.
Where did you find that?
Kris sent it to me.
She, um, said that watching
the woman who inspired our song
would inspire me.
But it just made me realize
I'm the B-team.
"B" as in "brilliant"?
Or "bodacious"
or "breathtaking" or...
I'm running out of "B" s.
Uh, yeah, no.
Uh, barely able
to keep it together
because I'm so nervous?
The day of that performance,
I totally lost my voice
and I couldn't sing.
- What did you do?
- I was doing everything.
I was gargling salt water,
I was drinking tea,
I was rubbing peppermint oil
all over my body, but...
my big sister Becks
gave me this.
It's been passed down
from Mu to Mu for generations,
and it's meant to give
whatever sister has it courage.
I swear to God,
the second I put it
in my hair, my voice came back.
- Whoa.
- Calories, please.
I'm glad to know I'm not
the only one who gets nervous.
Here.
Wait, are you...
are you giving this to me?
Mm-hmm.
As your designated big sister,
it's my job
to take care of you.
That's what I'm gonna do.
Wow. Thank you.
Hey, Mom.
Yeah. Yeah, no, no.
I know I said
I'd call you back,
but it's only been 15 minutes.
Hey, Ri.
I gave you that comb.
♪ Daddy, buy me that,
make my list for Santa... ♪
Here, the dress
I borrowed from you,
all nice, clean, ready for
the orphans' dinner tomorrow.
Hold on.
Is it bad we're calling it
"orphans' dinner,"
since you're a...
Wait, my parents are dead?
I...
I'm kidding.
You can totally call it
the "orphans' dinner."
Oh.
Okay, good, 'cause I thought
it sounded cute,
like Dickensian or something.
Where do you want me
to put this?
Oh, you can keep it.
I never wear it anymore.
Christmas is the time
for looking sexy, Riley.
I thought that was Halloween.
Technically,
it's every holiday.
- Ho, ho, ho.
- Um, can someone figure out
how to turn that thing off?
It, like, woke me up
at 4:00 in the morning.
- Ho, ho, ho.
- Thank you.
I'll leave it here for you
for when you change your mind.
- I won't.
- You will.
I won't.
Bye. Have a good break.
- Grab the duffel.
- Bye, Riley.
After break, man.
It's in the Myers building.
"Men, bonding together,
"invented culture as a defense
against female nature.
"Sky-cult was
the most sophisticated step
"in this process,
for its switch
"of the creative locus
from earth to sky
"is a shift from belly magic
to head magic.
"And from this
defensive head magic
"has come the spectacular glory
of male civilization,
"which has lifted woman with it.
"The very language and logic
"modern woman uses
to assail patriarchal culture
were the invention of men."
Now, who here can tell me
what they think this writer
is trying to suggest?
Miss Stone.
U-Um...
I think that he's saying
that women think
with their instincts
and men think
with their brains,
and that women
live in men's worlds
whether they like it or not.
You said "he."
What makes you think
the author is a man?
I...
It may surprise you to know
that the writer is one
Dr. Camille...
...Paglia.
Now, I just wanted to show you
that there is no way of writing
that is inherently
male or female.
And it's very difficult
for me to do my job,
teaching the curriculum,
which does happen to contain
many white male writers,
when there's a petition
circulating to have me fired.
I have no nefarious plot to
secret away knowledge from you.
There are no "covert meetings"
in hidden rooms
where men discuss
how to bury women.
You, or more likely
your parents,
are paying a great deal of money
for you to study
the proper classics.
And it's my job
to present them to you.
Enjoy your winter breaks.
And a Merry Christmas
to you all.
Hi there. Do you want
to sign my petition against
Professor Gelson
and the ruthless misogyny
of higher education...
Hi. Um, do you want
to sign my petition?
- Uh, sure.
- It's against Professor Gelson.
I don't know.
I just don't really feel like
dealing with my mom right now.
She's just...
It doesn't surprise me at all
that my dad left her.
Anyways, I'm excited to spend
the break with you guys.
A little less excited for the
dance tonight at DKO, but...
Are you sure you're cool
with us doing it?
...higher education. Hi!
Gelson's going down!
Would you like to sign my...
Okay.
50 signatures and counting,
and this is the beginning
of winter break,
when traditionally
no one cares about anything.
You already got the college
to remove the founder's bust
from the
administration building.
Isn't that enough crusading
for one semester, Kris?
- Uh, no.
- Oh.
Calvin Hawthorne was
a racist and a sexist.
He owned slaves.
In the North.
Seriously. He was into
the dark arts and shit.
I read he, like,
killed disobedient women
in ritual sacrifices
to male pagan gods.
Oh, my God, Kris.
You actually believe that?
And it's not like they
destroyed the freakin' thing.
The Dekes took it to their frat,
and now they can
junk off onto it
and no one has to see it.
Everyone wins.
- Where are you going?
- Work.
Ooh, cool.
I need coffee.
I still don't understand
why you want to get him
fired so bad.
Uh, 'cause he went
totally crazy on me
when all I did was ask why his
syllabus has no women on it,
queer people on it,
trans people on it,
- people of color on it.
- Yeah, but, uh, I mean,
are we just supposed
to not study the classics?
Whose classics are they?
'Cause they're not mine.
Will you at least
sign my petition?
You of all people should care.
What happened to Riley is a
completely different thing than
- what happened to you, Kris.
- I am just saying
that she might want
to get involved because
she understands that
if we let men get away with
- this sort of behavior...
- "She" is right here, you guys.
Let men get away
with this sort of behavior,
then they'll get away
with everything.
They already do.
I thought we were sisters.
No? Fine. I get it.
You guys don't want to fight
the good fight.
You don't want to confront
the white supremacist
- patriarchy head-on.
- Kris, come on.
- Split a snickerdoodle with me?
- No, no. Nope.
It's fine. I get it.
I'll sign it.
Excuse me?
Yeah. I mean,
I-I thought it was cool
that you got them to get rid
of Calvin Hawthorne's bust.
It was kind of creepy.
Uh, and the way
Professor Gelson yelled at you
in class was really lame.
Sorry for the wait.
No worries.
I... I don't mind waiting.
Sorry. That was really...
Thank you.
Okay, fine.
Give it to me.
Thank you.
And you know what?
I would love to split
a snickerdoodle with you.
- Excuse me. Sorry.
- Excuse me.
Sorry.
- Oh. After you.
- Thank you.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, you can take this back.
Oh, no.
What's up, ladies?
Can I get an iced coffee?
Excited for tonight?
Brian's gonna be there.
He's coming up from D.C.
to meet the new pledges.
The only place
Brian Huntley belongs
is in jail
for what he did to Riley.
We're going skiing together.
Don't worry.
It's consensual.
Screw you, Phil.
And tell Brian to stay
the hell away from Riley.
Keep the change.
What should we do?
We could pull out,
be conscientious objectors like
Lindsay and the Delta Sig girls
and skip the performance
altogether.
You've been trying to get
out of this for three weeks.
Come on, we're not bailing.
- I'll be fine.
- Are you sure?
It was three years ago.
I can handle it.
What's the worst
that can happen?
Do women say the word "dump"?
I mean, uh, yeah.
I hate these little cutie names
for just taking a shit.
I don't think
we say cutie names, do we?
Is he here?
Did you see him?
I mean, there's
definitely a difference.
I don't know.
That's okay.
- You guys look so hot.
- Smoosh, can you
- take a photo of all of us?
- Of course.
That's what I'm here for.
Ooh.
Oh, daddy.
What are you doing?
Come on.
Yeah.
Whoo. Mm-mmm.
You ready?
Three, two, one.
Cheese.
- Got it.
- I'm glad I wore my push-up bra.
Yeah, okay.
My little documentarian.
I love you so much, baby.
Where's Helena?
Oh, she was pounding
vodka sodas earlier,
but she looked really good.
Are you okay, Smoosh?
Yeah. It's just
an allergy headache. I'm fine.
Seriously, if she screws
this up, I'm gonna kill her.
Says the girl
who projectile vomited
at Sophomore Salad Soiree.
I'm gonna go look for her.
- "Woman."
- "Woman," sorry, who projectile vomited
at Sophomore Salad Soiree.
Fraternitas fratrum.
The founder wills it so.
Watch it, pledge.
Break that, and it's all over.
You'll never be
part of the Deke army.
Fraternitas fratrum.
The power of the founder
compels you
to pledge your loyalty to DKO.
The founder wills it so.
Fraternitas fratrum.
The power
of the founder compels you.
No, stop.
You are so sexy.
- I want you so bad.
- Wait.
Wait. Wait.
Wait.
Phil, wait. Wait.
- Helena?
- Dude, what the hell?
I've been looking for you.
Right, you found her,
so get the hell out.
The girls want to practice
dance one more time.
I-I guess, I guess
I got to, I got to...
We were in the middle
of something.
Do you want me to leave?
You bitches are all the same.
You act like you want it, but
you're all a bunch of teases.
You know, Brian would never
have done what you said he did.
You okay?
I don't feel...
Does vodka mix well
with tequila?
Yeah, get it all out.
Well, that'll be a really nice
Christmas gift for him.
I am such an idiot.
You're not an idiot.
I just thought he was cute.
Should I take you home?
No.
No, you stay here.
You can let the girls down
easy for me.
Will you promise
you're gonna text me
as soon as you get home?
Promise.
- Ooh, ooh, ooh.
- All right.
Oh, daddy.
Where is she?
- I put her in an Uber.
- Is she okay?
She's fine.
She just ate something bad.
What? She did.
Maybe it's a sign
we shouldn't sing.
Ow.
No. Absolutely not.
Are you kidding me?
You've been coaching us
for three weeks,
you know the choreography,
and you sing.
Yeah, but he's here.
It's all the more reason
to do it.
Jesse, what do you think?
I'm sorry, I wasn't listening.
What am I supposed to say?
This way of life
is unsustainable, Riley.
What Brian did to you...
it's awful.
And it's terrible
that nobody believed you.
But you can't just sit on
the sidelines alone forever.
You're gonna keep
shrinking and shrinking
until there's
nothing left of you.
Hmm?
You used to be a fighter.
It's time to be a fighter again.
If not for yourself,
for your sisters?
And now,
the girls from Mu Kappa!
Women!
Yeah!
Rebuild yourself, bitch.
♪ Up in the frat house,
me and you ♪
♪ And you know
what I'm there to do ♪
♪ We're drinking and kissing,
what comes next? ♪
♪ You and I have S-E-X ♪
♪ But ho, ho, ho ♪
♪ I didn't know ♪
♪ Ho, ho, ho, I didn't know ♪
♪ Yes, up in the frat house,
one true fact ♪
♪ And that is that
I got attacked ♪
♪ Up in the frat house,
shit went down ♪
♪ And I'm telling
everyone in town ♪
♪ I didn't lead you on,
for goodness' sake ♪
♪ I couldn't have
'cause I wasn't awake ♪
Yes!
♪ Ho, ho, ho, I didn't know ♪
♪ Ho, ho, ho ♪
♪ I didn't know ♪
♪ Yes, up in the frat house,
click, click, click ♪
♪ What you guys do
in here is sick ♪
♪ There's no more protecting you ♪
♪ No he said, she said
what was true ♪
♪ Don't say that
this was my fault ♪
♪ 'Cause what you did
is called assault ♪
- Yeah!
- ♪ Ho, ho, ho ♪
♪ I didn't know ♪
♪ Ho, ho, ho, I didn't know ♪
♪ Yes, up in the frat house,
click, click, click ♪
♪ You slipped me a roofie
and then your d... ♪
Maybe that'll teach
Brian Huntley
not to rape another girl.
Come on! Hey!
Let's go!
Let's leave. Let's go.
Just keep going.
Look what I got!
I can't believe
I just fucking did that!
Baby Jesus is
smiling down on you, Riley,
and he wants to thank you
for such a good birthday.
- Did you see their faces?
- I was ready... I know.
I was ready to pee myself.
I wasn't even onstage.
- Oh, my God. - I had no idea...
- Riley!
It's the North Pole's
best kept secret.
Oh, really?
- Mm-hmm.
- Hey, uh...
- it's Riley, right?
- Yeah.
Um, that was really good.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
Uh, I was really impressed.
That-that takes guts.
Uh, I'm Landon.
Hey, guys, come on.
Cake. Let's go sneak
into the café.
- Come on.
- No. I should probably go home.
- No. It is midnight on our last day...
- I...
...of our last fall semester
of college ever.
You're not bailing.
Come on. Live a little.
Do you want to come with us?
Uh... nah, I got to...
Yeah. I-I'm-I'm probably
gonna go home any...
Why am I telling you that?
- Like, okay.
- Ugh.
Hey, you know what?
Actually,
screw those Dekes, man.
They suck.
- Uh, they can return the equipment.
- Okay, well, let me
just text my friend Helena,
- make sure she got home okay.
- Okay.
Mm, she already sent
a group text to all of us.
Says, "How is swiff.
"Traking the ampersant
30 train tom.
See you next yeat!"
- So, I think we're all good.
- All right. Let's go.
Yay!
Landon, you can hold this.
Thank you.
Oh, wait. Okay. Uh, f...
I've got one.
Um, why is Santa Claus scared
of getting stuck
in the chimney?
Oh, this is gonna be bad.
Because he's claustrophobic.
- Mm, that's actually not so bad.
- Not so bad.
- Not so b...
- Not so...
It's pretty, it's pretty good.
Are you going to invite
your new friend
over for our
orphans' Christmas dinner?
"Orphans' Christmas dinner"?
It's, like, a potluck we do
for anybody
who's left over here
over the break.
7:00. Are you here?
Uh, yeah.
I don't leave until Sunday.
So... I mean, is that o...
- Are you cool... with...
- Mm.
Okay.
Good girl.
Let's not pretend
like I'm the only one.
I'm wearing a thong
and some other underwear.
I'm not wearing anything.
How come you've never
talked to me before?
You come into the café
every day.
I, um...
I... uh, it just takes me
a while to figure out how to...
approach things.
But don't give up
on me, though.
I... I always
figure it out eventually.
- Mm.
- So...
Hello?
Anyone there?
The star of the evening.
I can't believe you did that
in front of Brian last night.
What?
I don't know. I thought
I'd feel good about it,
but I just feel weird.
Dude. You won.
Enjoy it.
All right.
I got to pack.
My sister... biological...
will string me up
if I'm late for the train.
Promise to
take good care of Claudette.
- I promise.
- And don't overfeed her.
It took an entire year
to slim her down
after last winter break.
Happy holidays, Franny.
Hey, Merry Christmas
from this Jew to you.
Ladies, ladies, ladies.
We've got errands to run.
- Has anyone seen my mitten?
- Hey. He's stressing me out.
He's in father goose mode.
- It'll pass.
- Has anyone seen my other mitten?
- Let's go!
- I think someone was here
- from DKO last night.
- What? Why?
Look, it's the same stuff
that was at the frat.
- Why is all our stuff missing?
- Cheap champagne will do that.
What do you think it is?
Do you think it's paint?
- The dirty junk of frat boy scum.
- No, I'm serious.
I think they're planning
a prank or something.
Ah, right. The classic
painting the cat's paws prank.
They probably took Jesse's crystal,
my mitten
and Fran's DivaCup, too.
Ho, ho, ho.
Okay. If the girth of this tree
isn't how I want it,
I know I'm blaming you guys
'cause you took
frickin' forever to get ready.
We can't control
a girth of a tree.
Well, yeah, you can.
If we got there in time,
there would... I don't know.
Nate, did you get
this door fixed yet?
- Let's go! Riley, come on!
- Coming.
I'm coming.
Ow.
Drive, drive, drive!
Good?
Let's do it.
Claudette?
Are you in here?
If you make me late
for the train,
I swear I'm never
feeding you again.
Ask my childhood hamster.
He's super dead.
Claudette? Seriously.
Where are you?
Sweetheart?
Are you hurt, angel?
Oh, there you are.
Ooh, I like that one.
The tree the guy has.
That means it's taken. Mm-hmm.
Options.
That's a little bit of you, isn't it?
- This one's, you know, humble.
- Mm?
This guy's leaning.
- I think you...
- Humble?
I think this one deserves
a loving home.
- Guys, this one.
- Yeah.
No.
- This is it.
- Kris.
- I cannot afford something that big.
- No, it's okay.
My dad left me his card
so I can spend whatever I want
over winter break 'cause he
bailed on our St. Barts trip.
All right. Let's do it.
- Do you need any help, baby?
- Oh.
- No. I got it.
- Whoa. - Okay.
You're doing the most.
All right.
Keep going. Keep going.
Hello?
Oh, thank God I got through.
- It's Helena's mom.
- Oh, hi, Mrs. Rittenhouse.
Do you know where Helena is?
She was supposed to be here
a few hours ago,
and I haven't heard from her
since yesterday.
I'm a little worried.
Well, um,
I'm not there right now,
but I can check
as soon as I get back.
Oh, would you?
Oh, that would be,
that would be really great.
- Of course.
- Thank you so much, Riley.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
- Okay, bye.
♪ Deck the halls
with boughs of holly ♪
- ♪ Fa-la-la-la-la ♪
- Franny?
- ♪ La-la-la-la ♪
- Oh, shoot.
She must have
already gone home.
- ♪ 'Tis the season... ♪
- Okay.
I need to get started
on the ham.
Can you please lift it up?
Hey, can you
go grab the stand, please?
Helena?
And you go up, up.
Go. Go grab that side.
Hey, it's Helena.
Leave a message
or just be a dear
and send me a text next time.
Hey, it's Riley.
Can you give me a call
when you get this?
Your mom called,
and I'm worried about you.
Love you. Bye.
She's not there.
Her phone's off.
And Lindsay from Delta Sig
didn't get home, either.
I think we should tell campus
security that she's missing.
Okay, let's not forget that
she did have
food poisoning last night
and could've easily overslept
and gotten on a later train.
- She is only a couple hours late.
- Damn, babe.
- Can you hold it straight?
- I'm dealing with something
a little more important
right now, Smoosh.
It's snowy as hell out there.
Her shit probably got delayed.
Please just hold
the tree straight.
Why are you so grouchy
right now?
I'm not being grouchy.
I just want to get the tree up.
- Hold. Okay?
- Okay, look. You just made it crooked.
This is so inefficient.
I love it.
Guys, do I just turn on
the oven and put the ham in?
It seems too easy.
Something doesn't feel right.
Riley.
- Hey.
What are you doing here?
Hello to you, too.
Sorry. I...
Uh, I was just brushing up
to beat you at bad jokes
later tonight.
You okay?
Did you...
Have you been DMing me?
Me?
No.
I... I don't have social media.
I'm freaked out
by all the privacy stuff.
But I'd get it.
Uh, I'd DM you
if you wanted me to.
- I've got to go.
- All right.
Uh, s-still on for tonight?
- Sure.
- Okay.
♪ A brand-new Christmas ♪
♪ The season will be
greeting us anew... ♪
Can I help you?
Um, one of my roommates
is missing.
Helena Rittenhouse.
- She's a sophomore.
- Missing?
- It's winter break.
- I know.
But she was supposed to be
home earlier today,
and her mom called 'cause
she hasn't gotten home yet.
Could just be a delay
of some sort. Snow.
Right.
But... I've been getting
these weird DMs.
Direct messages.
Messages on apps.
Yes. DMs.
Well, I've been getting them
since this morning,
and they're from a Calvin
Hawthorne account, which I...
My sisters and I did
this stupid performance
last night at DKO
kind of making fun of them.
And one of their alums,
Brian Huntley, is visiting.
And you think what?
This Brian Huntley guy
abducted your friend
and is pretending to be
the dead founder
of Hawthorne College
sending you DMs?
No. Um...
But I...
I just feel like
they could be related.
Yeah, well, we need more than
feelings in this business.
♪ Grab some friends
and sing aloud... ♪
Mmm.
May I?
♪ Thank God I've got you
to keep me warm... ♪
Who's Landon?
Excuse me?
Landon?
You asked this person
if it's Landon.
Oh, he's some guy
that I met last night,
but it's d-definitely not him.
You're willing
to accuse Huntley of
locking your friend
in his basement,
but you're sure that
this guy that you just met
has nothing to do with it?
I'm not... I didn't say that
she was locked in the basement.
What are you saying?
I'm saying...
...that my friend is missing.
Anybody home?
Seems like no one's here.
Look, I get
that you're worried,
but I've seen
a lot of these cases,
and nine times out of ten, the
girl's just with a boyfriend.
If she's not back by tomorrow,
come see me.
That's it?
Wh-What about the messages?
I wouldn't worry about those.
Like you say,
they're probably just
pissed about
the little show you put on.
Boys will be... well, you know.
Can I give you a ride home?
No. I'm okay.
All right. Have a good break.
Oh.
I'm sorry.
I was, um...
- No, no. I'm sorry.
- I, uh...
Looking for a comb that I lost.
But I...
I can come back.
Nonsense.
I have a key.
Please.
I promised
I'd let the cleaners in
while the boys
went on their ski trip.
I hope you don't mind
my saying so,
but a few of the boys did
confide in me that the prank
Mu Kappa played last night
went a little bit too far.
I think it only right
Miss Waterson remove the video.
It's online?
Now, which key is it?
Well, I'm not entirely sure
how these things work,
but it did seem to be
heavily watched.
30,000 views or something.
The video she posted of me
garnered less than half that.
Between this
and her petition against me,
it seems Miss Waterson's
passion for equality
cannot be bridled.
Oh, dear.
I didn't mean to bring that up.
It's just...
Hawthorne means so much to me.
This school has
200 years of history.
Many sacrifices have been made
to keep our traditions alive.
I just wanted to make sure
you're aware of
the possible
legal repercussions.
The public accusation
at the end
could be considered defamatory.
Let's see if this works,
shall we?
Ah. There we go.
After you.
I have to go.
What about your comb?
Miss Stone.
♪ Here comes Mary Christmas,
ready as can be... ♪
I can't believe
how easy it was to cook.
I could've been making ham
all my life.
- Babe, can you help me a little bit?
- Mmm.
Since when do you drink beer?
I like beer.
Okay, new game.
Top three animals.
- Go.
- That's a dumb game.
- Well, then you don't have to play.
- Nate.
Okay. Marty, you go first.
Um, I actually can't right now.
I'm a little busy.
Please?
Okay. Fine. Um...
The first one would
probably be an owl,
and then a bunny,
and then an ant.
Wow.
Ant. That's bold.
What's the game?
Okay. Number one animal, owl...
that's how you see yourself.
- I see that.
- Mm-hmm.
Number two animal, um, bunny...
that's what you look for
in a romantic partner.
Not today, apparently.
And then third animal, ant...
that's what you want
in friends.
Why the ant, Marty?
I don't know.
I guess they're strong,
and they're all kind of, like, one unit.
Um, and you can't kill an ant
because they're all
an extension of the others.
That's really poetic.
What the hell, Kris?!
Did you talk
to campus security?
You posted the video
from last night online?
Yeah. Why?
Is it getting views?
Did you watch it
the whole way through?
Uh, I didn't need to.
I lived it.
Maybe that'll
teach Brian Huntley
not to rape another girl.
Oh, God.
- Okay.
- No. Where are you going?
I'm gonna go get Christmas
lights for the dinner decor.
When you guys fight,
it high-key stresses me out.
Look, okay, I'm gonna cut
that part out right now.
It already has, like,
50,000 views.
Well, yeah.
I-I thought the point of
calling out frat boy rape
culture was to inspire women.
We're not inspiring people.
We're pissing people off.
Gelson is cornering me.
I'm getting messed-up DMs
from God-knows-who.
- Helena's disappeared, and now the whole world...
- Wait, wait.
- Hold on. Hold on. No, no, no.
- ...knows that Brian Huntley...
Wait, wait. Back up. Hold on.
You're getting weird DMs?
- Yeah.
- So am I.
♪ ...Mary is,
Santa's sure to go ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Here comes Mary Christmas ♪
♪ Ready as can be ♪
♪ With a smile as bright
as the brightest light... ♪
Okay.
Christmas lights.
What did Gelson say?
- Kris, are you getting them?
- Yes. Just ignore them.
They are boys with heavy
testicles. Did he threaten you?
No. He just made it
pretty clear that he wants you
to drop the petition.
So he thinks
that he can threaten us
and then we'll just drop this.
- Okay...
- This is just getting started!
- No. How about we...
- You're not listening to me!
No.
Bingo.
Let's see.
Shit.
Christmas lights.
Do Christmas lights expire?
Ugh.
Wait.
Let's try these.
Okay.
Helena wouldn't even be missing
if I'd just gone home
like I wanted to instead of
you forcing me
to sing your dumb song.
My song? That was my song?
We did that for you!
I wouldn't have
sung it if you didn't...
You're so,
you're so pushy, Kris!
You never stop, do you?
You just push and you push.
I don't stop
because they don't stop!
Well, not everybody
wants to be like you!
Some of us are
quite happy to...
To just disappear!
What did you girls expect?
- Excuse me?
- I told you something like this
was gonna happen.
Okay? You humiliated
those guys up there.
Of course they're pissed.
And that gives them
an excuse to harass us?
What... If a bunch of
frat bros had gotten up
and sang a song about how,
I don't know,
women were just bimbos
who liked to show off
their tits, then yeah,
- you'd be livid.
- It's a little different, Smoosh.
How? Why are you allowed to say
all this shit about men,
and we're supposed to just
sit here and take it?
Because men have all the power.
Not all men have power.
- Did you just "not all men" me? Did you just...
- Don't.
Not all men are rapists, Kris!
- Okay? I'm not.
- No. Nobody...
But you just lump me in with
the bad ones because I'm a man?
No. Nobody is calling you
a rapist.
- You imply it with your man-hating.
- "Man-hating"?
- What did I say that was so offensive?
- Okay.
Hon, just calm down.
We're trying to have
- a rational conversation.
- "Calm down"?
- Yeah.
- You want me to calm down?! Let's calm down!
Yeah, I want you to calm
down. Okay. You just trying...
- Shut up!
- What would you do if I grabbed you like this?!
- Get out! Get out!
- You know what?
- You need to leave.
- The second I have a good point...
- Leave! I don't give a shit!
- No, no!
The second I have a good point,
- you tell me to leave you?!
- Who are you?!
- Get out of here!
- You know, I should've just
- dumped you last semester...
- I don't give a shit!
- Get out!
- You're hysterical.
Jesus!
Oh, my God!
"I will bring you
to your knees"?
"And you will beg for mercy"?
- There.
- What did you just do?
I said, "Hey, Calvin Hawthorne.
Why don't you come down here,
bite my ass, and make me
a panini on my mom's press?"
Oh, my...
What was that?
Run!
Come on! Come on!
Come on, Marty!
Come on!
Ow.
Oh, shit.
- Oh, my God.
- Shit.
I knew Helena was dead.
I knew.
- I felt it.
- No, we don't know that.
We don't know that.
All we know is
that we need
to get out of here.
Who is that guy?
Could be anyone...
the Dekes, Gelson.
Look, we can sit here
and make a list
of all the guys
that want to kill us
or we could get out of here,
we could get help.
I can't. I can't.
- It hurts too much to move.
- You're okay.
Hold this. I got you.
Where's your phone, Ri?
It's downstairs.
Shit. I left mine downstairs.
Marty's bleeding really bad.
I need to stay with her
and tend her wound.
Riley, we need a phone.
We need to call the cops
and warn all the other girls
- to stay away from that house.
- Okay. Okay. Okay.
I know I wasn't
always on your side.
And I know that
we butt heads sometimes.
- It's okay.
- Um...
And I know that I always
lug Nate around,
but I really love it
when it's just the four of us.
Jesse.
Oh, God.
We've got to find her.
We're ants, Kris.
Okay.
Um, I'll do it.
You just... stay here.
Keep the door locked, okay?
Jess?
Riley?
What are you doing down there?
Wh-Where's Marty?
I, uh, I just, I wanted to apologize.
I... I was having
this intense migraine.
- And I-I feel terrible.
- Nate.
There's someone in the house.
I need your phone.
Where's Marty?
Please, Nate.
She's... she's hurt.
And she needs a doctor,
but I need your phone.
No. Screw a phone.
Get the girls out of here,
all right?
If someone hurts my girl,
it's my duty to protect her.
Show yourself, coward!
This is a man's...
Stay away from me.
Merry Christmas,
boys and girls.
Ho, ho, ho, ho.
Hey. Hey, hey.
Okay. You're okay.
We're here, okay?
Where's Jesse?
Marty.
Nate?
Nate?! No!
No. Oh.
Oh... oh, God.
Oh. No.
What the fuck?
- Get out of here.
- Go.
Go. Go!
I got her!
Come on!
You made your point.
Marty, get back here.
- I just called the police!
- Marty.
They'll be here any second.
Marty. Marty.
If you leave now,
you can save yourself.
Marty.
Run!
No! No! Come on!
- Security.
- 911, attack at Hawthorne College.
- What?
- Report's at 1974 Elm Road.
I'm on my way.
Get to the hall.
Break for the door.
As fast as you can, okay?
Okay.
No!
Freeze!
Why isn't it blood?
I've seen him before.
He's a DKO pledge.
Watch it, pledge.
Break that, and it's all over.
You'll never be
part of the Deke army.
Riley, we have to go
to the cops.
I'm gonna go get Nate's keys,
and you meet me by the door.
Okay? Okay.
This can't be real.
Riley!
Get the keys!
Go!
- Uh, come on.
- Kris, open the door!
I-I got it! Ah.
Kris, hurry, hurry!
Come on, Kris!
Open the door!
I got it!
Come on.
Go! Go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go!
Oh, my God. Okay.
Hey, we're gonna be okay.
We're gonna be okay.
Oh, God.
Who the hell were those guys?
- Something crazy is going on.
- Yeah, no shit.
A bunch of dudes
just tried to kill us.
No, I mean
I saw that guy before,
the night of the talent show.
The Dekes were doing some sort
of ritual with the pledges.
It's a frat.
- Pledges pledge frats.
- No, this felt different.
It was like they were doing
something with this black stuff
that was coming out of
the founder's bust.
It was like...
It was like black magic
or sorcery or something.
So you're telling me
you think the DKO boys
possessed their pledges
in some-some
supernatural hazing ritual?
Well, you saw
the pledge's face.
You saw his blood.
I don't know what he was,
but he was changed.
He wasn't human.
Think about it.
The bust gets brought into
the founder's fraternity.
Brian Huntley turns up
to meet with the new pledges,
and then we all start
getting these messages
from a Calvin Hawthorne
account.
Lindsay goes missing.
Helena goes missing.
Marty and Jesse are dead.
I mean, all of this
leads back to DKO.
I need you to help me.
I need you
to create a distraction
so that I can
sneak into the room
where they were holding the
ceremony and get to the bust,
because that is where
the power is coming from.
Excuse me. What?
A magical bust?
No. We're going to the cops.
What are we gonna tell them?
I would like to remind you
that we just killed three
people who, possessed or not,
are lying dead
in our house right now.
It was self-defense.
Well, you want to count on
the cops believing that?
They didn't believe me
when I told them
what Brian had done to me.
So what makes you think that
they're gonna believe us now?
You don't even believe me.
- Pull over.
- No.
- Pull the car over, damn it!
- Shit, Riley!
Riley! What are you doing?!
Jesus, Riley, stop!
Stop! No!
I thought that
you were a fighter.
Riley?
I was just on my way
to orphans' dinn...
Whoa, what happened?
Riley.
Hey, Riley. What...
Hey, c-can, can I help you?
What-what do you need from me?
Well, you really want to help?
Let us in!
- Is it happening to you, too?
- Yeah.
And to Thetas, Pis and Kappas, too.
We need to go to the cops, now.
- Go.
Go, go, go!
All right.
Uh, he's been Zeta'd.
Uh, you've been Zeta'd.
Yeah. You've been Zeta'd.
Come on.
Seriously?
Hey!
Not cool!
You ruined my mixer!
Hey!
Dickheads!
Come get me,
you pieces of shit!
Morons!
Oh, hey, guys.
How's it g...
Oh, shit.
What do you want, crease?
I want, um...
I-I... I want you
to suck a fat fart
'cause you just got Zeta'd.
I know for a fact
you're not in Zeta.
But you can pledge our frat
if you want.
Just got to go through a...
a little hazing ritual.
Uh...
Got a headache, bro?
That's just the founder
drawing out your true alpha.
Help! Somebody help me, please!
Help!
Helena.
- Oh, thank God you're here.
- You're alive.
Yeah, we have to hurry, okay?
Okay. Okay.
Someone could come back
at any second.
- Did they hurt you?
- No, I think I'm okay.
I'm okay.
I thought no one would find me
and I'd be
trapped here forever.
You're okay now.
You're okay.
Nice work, sweetie.
Fraternitas fratrum.
The spirit of the founder
compels you.
Fraternitas fratrum.
Imagine a world
where you're no longer
sitting in the corner.
You're sitting on the throne.
Fraternitas fratrum.
What's going on?
What did you do to Landon?
He is who he was always
meant to be: a fighter.
A true man.
You see, when your friend,
Miss Waterson,
had the founder's statue
removed and brought here,
the boys discovered something
magical hidden inside.
Towards the end of his life,
Hawthorne foresaw
the threat posed by women.
So he took precautions
in case they strayed
too far out of line.
A master of the dark arts,
he left instructions on how
to create an army of young men
to take our power back.
You're all insane.
No, no.
Not insane, Miss Stone.
Simply men,
tired of seeing ourselves
falsely accused,
our livelihoods threatened,
marginalized and belittled,
reduced to spectators
in our own lives.
Upon graduation,
our army will
venture into courtrooms,
boardrooms and
the halls of Congress
to set the world right.
It was really very simple.
A hazing ritual, if you will.
We read the incantation
inside the bust,
and the spirit of Calvin
Hawthorne filled the pledges,
possessing them with
supernatural strength
and drive.
All we had to do
was name the women
who had stepped out of line,
and these boys
took care of the rest.
Be conscientious objectors
like Lindsay...
...sign my petition against Professor Gelson?
♪ Ho, ho, ho,
I didn't know... ♪
Women who are
willing to be obedient,
like your friend here,
will be spared.
Those of you
who refuse to be compliant
will face the consequences.
Aren't you tired of fighting
against your true nature, Ri?
Just because we're taking
our rightful place behind them
doesn't mean
that we aren't needed.
They needed me
to collect the objects
from the girls
so the pledges would know
who to go after.
I have a final in ten minutes,
and I can't find my DivaCup.
Thanks for the comb,
by the way.
How could you do that
to your sisters?
I'm helping women.
Everything is j...
so out of whack.
It's so much easier this way.
You are a traitor!
This is your last chance, Ri.
You can join me.
We can be good women.
Or...
Or we will bring you
to your knees
and you will beg for mercy.
Still creating problems,
huh, Ri?
You see, you were
given a chance.
You were taught how to grow
into a proper woman,
but you refused to listen.
Now it's time to decide.
Are you gonna bow to the king
when I say "bow"?
Bow.
I said bow, bitch.
You need a reminder
of our power?
Fine.
Baby?
Who put that there?
It's for the cause.
But I did everything
that I was supposed...
He'll do worse than that to you.
Your body, your choice.
I'll bow.
I'll be good.
Yeah, that's right, bitch.
You dragged my name
through the mud.
You lied about what happened
and tried to destroy me.
I told you guys I could
get her to do it. Huh?
Who's the king?! Who's the king?!
Who's the mighty king?!
You took everything from me!
And one day, someone will
tell everyone what you did,
and people will believe her!
See no evil, boys.
You all right, bro?
Absolutely.
You messed with
the wrong sisters.
Wait! Wait. Wait.
Don't you see?
Woman is inextricably
tied to man.
Break us, and you'll
only break yourselves.
We will never be broken.
No!
Hey, Professor.
Suck my...
I'm so sorry!
You were right!
I should've been fighting
this whole time.
Now's not really the time
for I-told-you-so's,
but I did tell you so.
Help me! I've changed!
I totally believe you!
I can make this right!
Bitch, you're gonna die!
I'm so sorry, okay?
That wasn't me.
- They did some magic shit.
- Not now!
Sorry.
Hurry!
- Go, go, go!
- Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
♪ Up in the frat house,
me and you ♪
♪ And we know
what I'm there to do ♪
♪ We're drinking and kissing
and what comes next? ♪
♪ You and I have S-E-X ♪
♪ But ho, ho, ho,
I didn't know ♪
♪ Ho, ho, ho, I didn't know ♪
♪ Up in the frat house,
this one true fact ♪
♪ And that is
that I got attacked ♪
♪ Up in the frat house,
things went down ♪
♪ And I'm telling
everyone in town ♪
♪ Didn't lead you on
for goodness' sake ♪
♪ Couldn't have
'cause I was not awake ♪
♪ Ho, ho, ho ♪
♪ I didn't know ♪
♪ Ho, ho, ho, I didn't know ♪
♪ Yes, up in the frat house,
click, click, click ♪
♪ What you guys do in here
is really sick ♪
♪ There's no more
protecting you ♪
♪ No he said, she said
what was true ♪
♪ Don't say that
this was all my fault ♪
♪ 'Cause what you did
is called assault ♪
♪ Ho, ho, ho ♪
♪ I didn't know ♪
♪ Ho, ho, ho, I didn't know ♪
♪ Yes, up in the frat house ♪
♪ Click, click, click ♪
♪ Slipped me a roofie
and then your ♪
♪ Slipped me
a roofie and then your. ♪
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org