Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Do you...
Do you not know that your bodies
are temples of the holy spirit?
Who is in you.
Whom you have received from God.
You, you are not
your own.
You were bought, you
were bought at a price.
Therefore, honor God with your
bodies.
There will be terrible
times in the last days.
People will be lovers of
themselves, lovers of money.
Boastful.
Proud.
Abusive.
Treacherous, rash, conceited.
Lovers of- lovers of-
Lovers of pleasure rather
than lovers of God.
Having a form of Godliness
but denying its power
Have nothing- have nothing
to do with such people.
They are the kinds who worm their way
into homes and gain control
over gullible women.
"Therefore, we will
not fear,
though the earth give way
and the mountains fall
into the heart of the sea,
though its waters roar and foam
and the mountains quake
with their surging.
Glad the city of God,
the holy place where
the Most High dwells."
"He breaks the bow and shatters
the spear.
He burns the shields with fire.
For persecution or famine
or nakedness or sword.
As it is written.
For your sake we face death all
day long.
We are considered as
sheep to be slaughtered."
Sordico, the genus
purpiceps.
The dark-purplish buds
on this head of wheat
are the so-called sclerotia of
sordico,
from the genus purpiceps.
This indicates the beginning
of the sexual stage...
Once winter is over,
the sordico will sprout
to mushroom-like structures,
which will create the sexual
spore stage,
which takes place throughout
the spring season.
This stage will be discharged
from the fruit bodies
by the fungus and dicem-
- I've got purpose, Jim,
god damn it.
I've got purpose, Jim, god damn
it.
I've got purpose, god damn it,
Jim.
Give me...
Damn it, Jim!
Give me a fucking chance!
Damn it, Jim, give me a, give me
a fu-
- After the
infection takes hold,
the asexual spore stage is
created.
This is called the purpolia
stage,
which creates its spores in a
honeydew-
- A fucking chance!
Just give me a fucking chance!
Poisoning,
caused by sordico of wheat
is referred to as sordicism.
There are two types of
symptoms that can occur
in cases of serious poisoning.
I've got a purpose.
Gangrenous
sordicism
is common in grazing farm
animals.
It causes gangrene to
occur by constricting
the blood vessels that
lead to the extremities.
Convulsive sordicism is
characterized
by disfunction within the
nervous system,
where the animal twists and
contorts its body in pain.
Trembling and shaking.
Typically, when a bovid
becomes infected by sordico,
it must be put down,
and the entire crops from
that season destroyed.
Symptoms of gangrenous
and convulsive sordicism
can occur in varying degrees
in any animal or human
who has consumed sordico.
In the Middle Ages, unaware of
the risks,
the common folk of Europe
rarely made the effort
to remove the sordico from the
wheat,
so the fungal wheat flour was
often baked into the bread.
There are extensive accounts
of these ignorant peasants
suffering from burning
sensations in their limbs,
amputations due to gangrene,
dizziness, nausea, and,
if consumed over a long period
of time, gradual insanity.
These symptoms were titled Godly
flames,
as many considered them
a punishment from God.
A tribulation for the sins of
the people.
- Oh, shit.
- What?
The fucking GPS lost
service.
Did you mess with it?
What do you
mean, did I mess with it?
What are you doing?
I think one of the tires
is low.
- The tires don't feel low.
- Just shh.
It's not
supposed to lose direction
where there's no signal.
Did you touch it?
It's literally like two
and a half minutes away.
I'll get us there without GPS.
That kid is staring at
us.
- What kid?
- On the bike.
What the fuck?
I'm gonna
ask him for directions.
Sam, no.
Sam.
Hey.
Do you know how to get to
Bardwells Ferry Road from here?
Hello?
Rude.
Big weirdy weirdo.
You definitely
messed with the GPS.
Tire's fine.
What?
- What just-
- No idea.
No idea.
Pardon my French,
but I didn't come all the way
down here
to Albuquerque to get fucked.
To get fucked, bucko.
Hey, Jim.
Remember that night in Vegas,
when we met those two broads at
Caesar's?
Well, there's something I never
told you.
There's somethin'...
Hey, Jim.
I'm sorry and please pardon my
French,
but I just get nervous around
cool guys,
and when I got on that plane, I
just-
- You hate me.
Hm?
I've just been crazy
pre-occupied.
It's fine.
I swear, it's fine.
I swear, I swear, I swear.
You hate me.
Yes.
I 100% don't hate you, it's
totally fine.
We're both distracted right now.
I repulse you.
I totally get it.
Hell of a haunch.
Thanks to you.
Yeah, that's what eating raw
and burning 35,000 calories
a month will get you.
Yeah, that and a stomach full
of acid.
Did you take your-
- Yes!
- All right.
Ow, what the fuck,
Rylie?
Sorry!
- What the fuck?
- I'm sorry!
Hello?
- Hello?
Anybody home?
Yeah, what the-
- Shh.
Yeah, who is, who's there?
Sorry if I scared ya.
Can we help you?
You're on my property.
Oh, great.
Sorry if I scared ya!
This is your property?
500 acres.
Between Cedar and Hillside.
Oh, you're kidding.
Nope...
Two of you in there?
Huh?
Are there two of you in
there?
Yeah?
So, do we need to pack up?
Yeah.
All right.
What, what's your name?
Eulis.
What, what was that?
Eulis!
I, I can't-
- E-U-L-I-S.
Oh, Eulis.
Do you know anything that
might be open this late?
Like a motel or...
Not right in town that I can
think of.
There might be something further
north.
Might be something further
Okay.
Thanks.
I'll come back around,
next couple hours.
Make sure you're outta here.
Yeah, we'll be out in a bit.
Make sure to douse that fire.
Yeah, will do!
Get home safe.
Yeah, thank you.
We're probably gonna have
to drive out a couple miles
before we get any service,
but I think I can get
us into town on my own.
Nope.
Fucking nope.
Sam.
Fucking nope!
Sam!
Did you leave the hazards on?
Did I leave the hazards on?
Once we get to the main road
that should bring us into town.
Worst case, we call AAA from
there.
Be home by five AM.
As long as that's the
worst case.
Oh, that's the spirit.
I have 47% battery, how much do
you have?
30.
- Is it on low power?
- Yes.
- All other apps-
- All apps are off.
Brightness all the way
down?
Whoa, what the...
Jesus Christ.
What the fuck?
We couldn't just do a nice day
hike, nope.
Will you just give it a rest,
Sam?
Just, will you shut up?
- Excuse me?
- Just shut up.
Wait.
Sam?
It's okay, I forgive you!
Idiot.
Nice.
- Look.
- What?
There.
What, the light?
No, the darkness surrounding
the light.
God, come on.
Coochie coochie coo!
Oh, my god, Sam.
God, you're really something
tonight.
I'm something tonight?
- Not to mention the five-
- Shh!
- If you shush me one more-
- Just shh!
What's that smell?
- Hi!
- Oh, hi there.
Hi.
We're so sorry to bother you.
We were just wondering if we
could maybe borrow your phone?
See, we were camping a little
ways in, near the wheat fields
and the land owner told
us that we had to leave.
Oh, my goodness.
Yeah, so we were all set to
drive home,
and then our car wouldn't
start and we weren't able
to track down any cell service.
So, we were wondering if
maybe we could use your phone
to call AAA for a jump?
Hi, I'm Sam.
Hi, Sam.
Should...
Oh, please, please!
Where are my manners?
Ah, thank you so much.
Thank you so much.
- Hi, Sam.
- Hi.
- I'm Karen.
- Hi, Karen.
AAA won't do you any good over
here.
Take 'em two-three hours just to
get here.
Not worth it just for a jump.
Now, my neighbor, Pete, he
could be here in 30 minutes.
Settle for a T-bone steak
and a glass of milk for
compensation.
Wouldn't have to spend a nickel.
That'd be great.
Are you sure that he's
awake? It's already-
- Pete?
Karen.
I've got a sweet couple here.
Had their camping trip wrecked
by some scum sucker over by...
Did you get his name?
Eulis.
You-us?
E-U-L-I-S.
Oh, Eulis.
You know a, a Eulis?
Eulis.
Eulis!
Oh, okay.
Okay.
So I'll see you in a bit.
See ya in a bit!
And if you've got your teeth in,
I'll fix ya a cut and a fresh
loaf.
All right, my dear.
Did he say how long he might
be?
Eulis?
Pete.
Oh!
- We don't wanna overstay.
- Oh, please, please, please.
He shouldn't be more than 30
minutes.
Worst case, 45, since he's
gettin' on.
No, that's great, that's
perfect.
Perfect.
Again, thank you so...
Oh, my goodness!
Where are my manners?
You two must be stravin'!
Actually, a little.
Actually, I think we're fine.
Oh, you're a couple of sticks.
Come on, come on!
Come on, Rylie.
You're a stick.
Oh dear, oh dear.
I always overshoot at low heat.
Is there any spinach in the
house?
It gets so hot when I cook,
so I leave it open.
Have a seat!
Hello.
Hi.
Please!
Sit down.
Have somethin' for ya in 10-15
minutes.
You like steak?
Oh, Sam is actually off
red meat as of recently, so-
- Well, I, I-
- How do you like 'em?
No, I'm sorry, he's
actually off red meat.
I had a physical a few months
ago
and my cholesterol is not great.
It's 270, actually.
- Doctor suggested that I-
- He can't have any red meat.
Any dairy, sugar, salt.
Maybe a little piece of
chicken once a month, but that-
- A quarter chicken once a
month.
- He suggested-
- You can't have it.
Bless you.
And I'm actually a
vegan, believe it or not.
Oh, boy.
I take a three and a half,
but an eight feels so good.
I've gotta get 12s.
Oh, perfect.
Do you need some help?
- Where's your restroom?
- What?
Take a left out of the
kitchen,
then a right before the stairs.
So, were you at all
affected by the sordico?
Karen?
- Hey, Karen?
- What's that, dear?
Were you
affected by the sordico,
a little while back?
The sordico?
The cattle deaths, from
the Sordico of wheat?
Oh, right, right.
The sordico.
How do you know about all that?
I'm getting my doctorate in
botany.
I'm doing my thesis
project on the resurgence
of sordico in New England crops
and their life cycle in
this particular climate.
Must've really disrupted
the industry over here.
At least the meat trade.
Oh, sure, sure.
We were one of the top meat and
wheat farmers in the county.
Wow, really?
Now we trade with the farmer
nearby.
Our veggies for his meat and
grain.
Have you ever considered
moving?
You like cardamom?
Love it.
Would you
like me if I wore a uniform?
Great bread.
So, is that your daughter
in those pictures in the hall,
Karen?
Sorry.
Did something happen?
I love Christmas music.
So, is Pete pretty close, you
think?
- Sam, would you like some-
- Hey, Karen?
You think that Pete is pretty
close?
That's 15 minutes
fast.
Wouldn't say more than another
30.
He's gettin' on.
He may look like a chunky monkey
now,
but he used to come in at an
even 400.
Who's that, Pete?
Gunni.
My son.
Got kicked.
By a bull, about six months ago.
Right in the face.
Hasn't been the same.
God, I'm sorry.
Oh.
A little butter won't hurt him.
Thank you.
Left, right, left, right,
left, right.
- So, what do you do, Sam?
- Well, I'm, uh-
- He's an actor.
Oh, really?
- Waiter/actor.
- Actor/waiter.
In between waiting jobs.
He's just getting too many
auditions.
Can never remember the
specials.
I've got the same problem with
scripts.
Well, this weekend, he's
my research assistant.
Was that your bear trap out in
the woods?
Hey, Karen?
Just a nib, Goon
buggy.
Oh, come on, buggy boy, just a
peck.
Just a peck.
Room for dessert?
Whole tray of cupcakes in the
fridge.
Baked 'em yesterday!
Oh, I'm stuffed.
Yeah, me too, thank you.
Oh, Sam.
Tea?
Sorry again, about Pete.
He tends to fall asleep,
just outta nowhere.
Even in the middle of
conversations, sometimes.
- Like a narcoleptic?
- Nope.
You know, we really
don't mind just calling for-
- Oh and if you get a
hankerin' for anything,
go back upstairs!
There's plenty of leftov-.
That's our dog, Earl.
We keep him in the barn, a
little ways in.
Bad with people.
There's no, uh, online or
phone service over here,
but if you're desperate,
you might try a little
further in, that a way.
Cellular phone wise.
I think some sorta
tower might reach there.
Oh, I think we'll be all
right.
Gunni usually sleeps down
here.
I'll keep him up with me
tonight.
Are you sure?
You know, maybe we should
just...
Come in, come in!
Right this way.
Sam.
Got your own bathroom back
there.
You even have a TV.
Think we had a couple of...
Oh!
We really appreciate
your hospitality, Karen.
You've really saved our butts.
♪ Oh my honey, yes, oh my honey,
yes ♪
Yeah, really. Thank you
for everything, Karen.
♪ To the leader man, rag and
music man ♪
♪ Oh my honey, what, oh my
honey, what ♪
Sounds like a cricket got in.
I'll call Pete, first thing.
If he doesn't haul over in 15,
I'll snag his cables myself.
- We really appreciate it.
- Yeah, thanks again, Karen.
Nighty night.
♪ Come on along. I'm goin' along♪
♪ Let me take you by the hand
♪ Up to the man. Up to the man
What?
Ah, shoot.
Sam.
Sam?
Samuel.
Why are you getting dressed?
What, are you leaving?
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Oh, mama.
Window cleaner!
Oh, Jesus.
Jesus.
Oh, lord.
Jesus!
Gunni.
You scared me.
You keep a secret?
I haven't had a grain of salt
in more than three months.
I know.
No red meat, no pink meat.
The occasional fish.
No complex sugars.
No complex carbs.
No starches.
No high-fructose corn syrup.
No refined vegetable oil.
Or sodium benzoate.
No butane.
Did you know they put
butane in chicken nuggets?
No chicken nuggets.
Whoa.
You all right?
Dah... mah...
...Chalk.
Das...
Mah... chalk.
Sorry?
My.
Chalk.
I'm sorry, I can't...
That's magic?
That's.
My.
Chalk!
What?
Yeah?
Sam?
Come on, Sam.
I swear to fucking god.
Sam, consider the consequences.
Sam!
Stop this shit or I'm
breaking up with you!
Sam, I can't tell you how
unfunny you are.
Come on, Sam, just tell me if
it's you.
Sam?
We need to talk.
Well, you know it's cooked,
Jimbo.
It's just still in the thing.
So don't throw any stones.
I've got plenty of license here.
Or baked, or whatever.
Whatever you do, take your
fucking time.
- We need to talk.
- What?
God, what would you do if
this place was on fire, huh?
I feel bad enough about this.
I'm serious, what would you do?
I'd probably be quicker about-
- I don't think you would.
I really don't think you would.
They found a lump.
A what? A what?
A lump.
Oh, cripes.
Where?
In your tum tum.
Window washer.
Of course.
This is so predictable.
I have zero appetite.
Is this place open?
What's gonna happen to him?
Shh!
It's just there are moments
hanging in the ether that could
be mine.
Oh, for Christ sake.
Oh, shoot.
It really
isn't as bad as it looks,
and to be honest,
I think you're being a little
bit of a Letdown Larry.
Oh, I can't talk to you right
now.
"For Chrissake.
For Christ's sake.
I've got purpose."
What a piece of shit.
I love you!
Rylie?
Karen?
Gunni?
Gunni!
Hey, Gunni, open the door!
Hey!
Gunni!
What're you doin' out here, man?
Hey, open the door!
Hey, Gunni!
Where's your mom, bud?
Hey, Gunni, come on!
Let's go, we'll go inside!
God damn it, Gunni!
Hello?
Rylie?
Rylie!
Hello?
Come on, come on, come on.
911, what's your
emergency?
Hi, yes I'm calling
about a girl who's gone missing.
My girlfriend just disappeared.
- We're staying with this woman-
- What's the address, sir?
Yeah, I think it's,
uh, it's Cormorant Way
between, um, I think
between Pleasant Street and
Trouble Street, I believe.
I'm going to
need an exact address, sir.
Okay, yeah, I don't
know, it's a white house.
Sir, I'm gonna
nee...
Hello?
Fuck!
Do you not know that
your bodies
are temples of the holy spirit?
Who is in you.
Whom you have received from God.
You.
You are not your own.
You were bought.
You were bought at a price.
Therefore, honor God with your
bodies.
There will be terrible
times in the last days.
People will be lovers of
themselves.
Lovers of money.
Boastful.
Proud.
Abusive.
Treacherous, rash, conceited.
Lovers of, lovers of the planet
rather than lovers of God.
Having a form of Godliness
but denying its power
Having nothing, have nothing
to do with such people.
There are kinds who worm their way
into homes and gain control
over gullible women.
Rylie.
What's going on?
Are you okay?
Don't get up.
Karen.
What's, what's going on?
Goodness gracious
Karen!
Rylie.
Sam.
We are livin' in a...
Livin' in a time of tribulation.
Eul', darnit with that!
To put it simply.
We have perverted God's divine
love,
through abuse of his gifts.
We were overindulgent in God's
feed,
and so he took it away.
Forcing us to seek a
more immediate source,
so that he may not forsake
us in the end times,
which, my babies, are
nearer than you may think.
But we have been given an
opportunity for absolution.
A second chance to sustain life
entirely
through consumption of what we
can access
of our own flesh and available
earth,
so we may be judged in his
image.
Now, that's what I call mercy.
So...
Came up with a sorta
redemption-type program.
A rationing effort.
We've had a number of
participants
over the years.
I think we've worked out all the
kinks.
Just about.
This little sweetheart's
been with us for a while now.
If there was ever someone
who needed a good sortin'...
Quite the pig.
But from his gluttony,
we were blessed with two cheeks
and a beefy round.
He's also taught us a heck
of a lot about perseverance.
And loyalty.
And now that we're done with his
bottom,
we gotta take from the top.
You've probably been wonderin'
what the heck is in
this thing.
This is our daughter.
My god.
Delilah.
She's given us just about
everything
she's got over the years.
A true model of self-sacrifice.
Come on, girlie.
Oh.
All right, all right.
I'm honin' in on breakfast.
Oh, okay, honey.
It's on its way, my love.
Ah, that's her language.
That blinkin'?
She's sayin' "feed me, darn it!
Feed me that's boy's sweet rear
end."
Let's get this old girl fed.
Shall we?
See how you compare to Buggy
Boy.
Bless us, O Lord, and these, thy
gifts,
which we are about to
receive from thy bounty.
Through Christ, our Lord, amen.
There you go.
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Slow down, darlin'.
She's like, "where the hell's
this been all my life?"
Oh, mama mia!
Yum, yum, yum, gimme, gimme,
gimme.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Pace yourself, darlin'.
Grade-A prime cut, Samuel.
All right.
That'll do for now.
Made from all the brightest
suns of the Universe.
And volumes beyond.
You better believe we're
still aimin' for grand babies.
Bring some sunshine into this
black world.
Goon here seems to be working
with an empty cartridge.
There's another little piece
here, babies.
Goon bug?
Gunni?
Gunni!
One more little piece.
Eulis here was the go-to farm
vet, once upon a sometime.
He performs all our procedures.
We have a little,
little sorta security system.
Eulis?
Eulis.
I've got money.
Money, I have got money.
Money, money, money.
Eulis, please.
Please, please.
- Eulis, come on.
- Shh, shh, shh.
Turn it up, Goon.
Goon bug?
Eulis.
Please, Eulis, please.
This is an
orbitoclast.
Wasn't an entirely unpopular way
of
giving people an overhaul, at
one time.
Please, Eulis, don't do this.
I'll do anything.
Eulis, I'll do anything.
Can't guarantee you
won't try to run off.
Oh, look at Gunni there.
Sweet as a baby chipmunk, and
happy, too.
Truly.
You're not gonna feel a damn
thing.
Well, a little pressure, maybe.
Then it's bright eyes and sweet
smile.
Not gonna make this
any easier,
whippin' around, Pork Chop.
No more strainin', Sam.
Not one more wracked nerve,
darlin'.
Eulis!
Come on!
Bright eyes and sweet smiles.
No, no!
Bright eyes and sweet
smiles.
Shit.
- Help!
Help!
You shut it.
You shut it!
- Help!
You shut it, or she
gets it!
Hey, fellas.
You shut it, or she gets it.
So help me, God.
One more squeak,
and she'll pop him, right
between the peepers.
Yeah, no, it's
been a pretty good year.
Well, it's good to see ya.
It's always good to see ya.
Yeah, yeah.
...come and check it
out.
Hey, Gunni.
Gunni.
Gunni, come on.
Gunni, take off my mask.
Gunni, go up the stairs.
Take off my mask.
Take off my mask, yeah, yeah.
Gunni, take off her mask.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, that's good, Gunni.
Gunni, listen to me.
Take the tape off our wrists.
Un-tape our hands.
Yeah.
Oh, my god, good.
Good, Gunni.
That's great.
Yeah.
Now, Gunni, listen to me.
Listen to me, Gunni.
Cut the tape.
Gunni, Gunni.
Look at me.
Pull out the knife and cut the
tape.
Yeah.
Right here.
Good.
Yeah.
Quicker.
That's it, that's it.
Yeah.
That's good, that's good.
Yeah, yeah.
That's great, Gunni.
That's a good boy.
Help her.
Help Rylie.
Get home safe.
- Take care.
- Uh-huh.
Gunni!
Go, Gunni!
Gunni, go!
Gunni.
Drop her, darlin'.
Gunni!
Go!
Now!
Gunni!
Go get the truck!
Get the truck!
Gunni!
Gunni.
Calling cars
four, three, two, one.
Calling cars four, three, two,
one.
Oh.
I wanna see the bottom of that
plate when I come back up.
Mm, yes.
Oh, my goodness gracious.
"I don't know," I said.
"Stop asking me so many
questions, for cripes sake."
Oh.
"Ah, how can you tell a thing
like that
about a person who's
just standing around?"
I said.
Hi, Sam.
Lunch time.
Let's start with the
yuckies first, shall we?
Get those out of the way.
Open up, darlin'.
Come on.
Just like Popeye.
Oh.
Come on now, Sammy boy.
Open up, sweetie.
Come on, my love.
Just a bite to start.
Come on.
You've gotta eat or
you'll turn into a stick.
Well.
We'll just get Li Li started
on the goodies, then.
Here it comes.
Here it comes!
If we start with the goodies
first,
you promise to eat every
last leaf on that plate.
Well, let me hear "yes, mom."
Let me hear.
"Yes, mom."
Yaaaaaaa
Maaaaaa.
Aww.
Oh.
Tough today.
Like shoe leather.
Oh, gosh.
Oh.
See, now this bit isn't so
tough.
Now, for the extra yummies.
There we go.
"Just stop Sis'," I said.
Let's take a
little break from the grub.
"Just stop."
For just a tick.
That's it.
Okay, my beautiful girl.
Come here, my sweet one.
Come here, my lovely.
Yes.
There we go.
My beautiful, beautiful girl.
Just relax, babies.
Oh, just relax.
Make room for the Lord.
Breathe him in.
Do you not know that your bodies
are temples of the holy spirit?
Who is in you.
Who you have received from God.
You are not your own.
You were bought at a price.
Therefore...
Honor God with your bodies.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull