Duckett! Answer your phone.
My messages are delivering,
so I know you're
fuckin' seeing 'em.
Yo. Seen Duckett?
Yeah, he's inside. He's
fucking off his head.
Bro, he's definitely
on something, eh?
Hey, is Duckett up there?
Who the fuck is Duckett?
Oi! Any of you seen Duckett?
No, I haven't!
Oi. Oi, seen Duckett?
Cole! Get your
brother under control.
- Where is he?
- He's in Jayden's room. Go.
Dude, what's your
brother's deal?
Duckett!
Open the door, man! I'm
not screwing around.
Mate, I'm this close
to calling the cops.
Duckett, open the door
or I'll break it down.
- What?!
Dude, what the hell?! You're
gonna break my mum's door!
Nah, fuck this!
Cole's breaking my
fuckin'... Duckett.
Can you see them?
They're in here.
I'm gonna take
you home. OK, bro?
Pop said you're gonna
hurt a lot of people.
Pop's dead, Duckett.
You're not him.
What are you talking about?
Bro, look at
Duckett. He's fucked!
Are you serious?
Put your phones down!
Put your fuckin' phones away!
Hey, hey, bro...
Everyone fuck off!
It's a knife!
What are you doing?
Get off me. Get off!
- Mum!
Sorry.
No, I am.
I just needed a moment.
Your aunty wants to talk to you.
Yeah, OK.
I've still got her
name in Contacts.
I should take her out,
but I just can't do it.
Yeah, me neither.
You thought about
what you're gonna do
when you finish school?
Mmm...
Work with your dad?
You getting a cold, Mi?
What?
You getting a cold?
Uh, yeah, I think so.
How was today for you?
- What?
Fine.
Hey. Hey, Mia.
- Can you come pick me up?
- Oh, OK, now?
- Where'd you go?
- I was on the phone.
My sister was meant
to be picking me up.
My fat mum's meant
to pick me up.
She's probably off
eating dick somewhere.
Is that Alex?
Yeah, his Snapchats
are so cringe.
He looks like my
mum in half of 'em.
- He looks elvish.
- What's elvish?
You know, like
the fantasy elves.
Shut up.
I swear he stole one
of my cigarettes.
You smoke now?
Nah, I just sell 'em. I
sold, like, two to him today.
He's such a tryhard.
He invited me to
his house to hang.
I thought you hated him.
Eh.
Do you reckon they give
you cancer straightaway?
I don't know. Don't smoke it?
Don't tell me what to do.
Here you go.
Nah.
I hate the smell.
You're a fuckin' foetus.
I need a new best mate.
Put it out, quick.
Riley! You little
feral. Cigarettes?
We weren't actually
smoking them.
He's lying, Mia.
- He's had half a packet.
- Need a lift anywhere?
Nah, Mum's getting here
soon. Thanks, though.
Alright. Call Riley if
she doesn't rock up.
Alright, thanks. Have
fun with your cancer.
- See ya, Mia. See ya, foetus!
♪ I'm gonna swing
♪ From the chandelier-ier-ier
♪ I'm
♪ Gonna live
♪ Like tomorrow doesn't exist
♪ Like it doesn't... ♪
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
♪ I'm
♪ Gonna fly like a... ♪
Um... stay in the car, OK?
Oh, shit.
You poor thing. What do we do?
Do we call a vet?
That's not gonna help,
Riley. I mean, look at it.
We can't just
leave it like that.
Can you at least put
it out of its misery?
OK.
Mia, no, we can't
leave it like this.
Another car will come.
Mia, it's crying.
- Oh! Hey!
Ow. Love it when you
rock up uninvited.
Love it when you forget
to pick up Riley.
Ow!
I'm sorry. I had you on mute.
Ah, cool story.
I'm telling Mum.
No, you're not! Yes, I am!
Thanks for picking him up, Mi.
All good. Come on, Cookie.
Oh, God, you stink!
Oh, you're a smelly girl!
Saw a dying kangaroo.
What?
On the side of the road.
It was in so much pain.
Why didn't you call the RSPCA?
I dunno.
It was almost dead.
I wanted to put it
out of its misery.
Thanks for ignoring
my calls, by the way.
I haven't been ignoring
your calls. I've been busy.
Uh, yeah, busy ignoring me.
- No, Jade, don't. Don't!
- What?
Don't answer it! I
let a kangaroo suffer.
- Daniel...
- I need consoling!
Is that Mia?
- I'll call you back, yeah?
- OK, sure.
OK, bye.
Bye! Bye, Daniel! Bye!
Oh! Alright. I'm consoling you.
- Have you seen the group chat?
- The one I invited you to?
Hayley's video. They're
doing it again tonight.
- No, Mia.
- To see if it's real!
No, not tonight, Mia. I can't.
It was Mum's two years.
That was today?
Yeah.
I just want to forget about it.
And...
I need Daniel to come give
my gucci some attention.
Oh! Daniel's not
touching your gucci, Mia!
He was my boyfriend
before he was yours.
You guys held hands
once three years ago.
- That doesn't mean anything.
- Jade.
It's my mum's
remembrance day. Please?
Daniel can come, too, yeah?
If he's touching my gucci, yes.
- Stop!
Can you give me five minutes?
What am I gonna do
for five minutes?
Oh, I don't know. Wash
Cookie or something!
I don't wanna wash Cookie!
Oh, fine! I will babysit
Riley - the better sibling.
Do not talk about your
gucci with Riley, please.
He has got to learn!
The boy's got to learn!
- Bye.
- Miss you already. Bye.
- Love you.
"Can I help?"
"Yes, Riley, thank
you for asking."
Need a hand?
I'm sorry I couldn't
get to your mum's thing.
I couldn't get off work.
No, it's fine.
How's your dad?
Oh, hey...
You can be honest.
I hate being around him.
He's so depressing.
I'm a bad person,
Sue. Can you fix me?
You're not broken, Mia.
- Whoa. OK.
Ugh, God, I'm dying.
It's just a cold.
You'll kick it.
Thank you.
Riley, get your
shit off the table.
Did you hear me?
Yes, Mum, I'm coming. OK.
Mum? You going to bed?
- You sneaking out?
- Why do you always think
I'm sneaking out or
I'm sleeping around?
You only ask if I'm going to
bed when you're sneaking out.
Is it to see Daniel?
You know, even if it was,
he's ultra Christian.
- He doesn't do anything ever.
- He's still got a dick, Jade.
Is it him you're
sneaking out to see?
I'm not sneaking out!
OK.
God. Night.
Lock the door on your way out.
- Are we sneaking out now?
- Shh!
Bye, Mia.
- Oh, God!
I didn't tell on you.
What? I didn't do anything.
What are you doing?
Mia said I could come.
How could I say no to him?
- You're not coming.
- Alright, then, I'll tell Mum.
Yeah, well, she pretty
much already knows.
What, about you
not picking me up?
Whatever.
- Yo, check this out.
- I swear it's fake.
- Mm, I don't know.
It's 1,000 per cent a trick.
How would Hayley fake
that? Why would they?
Why would they? They're
an attention whore.
They're trying to get
everyone to talk about them
and you've fallen for it.
Sorry for ruining
your phone date.
Apology not accepted.
You'll be pregnant
next month, I swear.
Pregnant? He hasn't
even kissed me yet.
What? You guys have been going
out for, like, three months.
- What is that?
- Even I've kissed Jazzie.
The girl with the horse mouth?
You shouldn't be
kissing horses, Riley.
♪ My City
♪ They won't say
that shit to me
♪ I'm in that town My
brothers is with me... ♪
Only an hour late. Great.
Been waiting for Mum to sleep.
Oh, and we are babysitting
too, apparently.
Fuck me.
♪ Drop through the hood
in Lamborghini cars
♪ I might just give
100 to my dawgs
♪ Thank you for holding it down
♪ I'm sorry if you felt
like there was love lost
♪ They blaming Onefour
for all of the drillings
♪ They blaming us for
what happens in Sydney
what happens in Melbourne
♪ They blaming us for what
happens in Brissy... ♪
Yo. What's up?
Just chillin'.
Cool.
Sick house, Joss.
Yeah.
Oh... Nah, it'll pick
up soon, I'm sure...
How you doin', man?
Boop!
You all good?
Yeah, just...
being weird.
You're not being weird.
You just need to loosen up.
Brrr!
Yeah, just do that. It
looks incredibly normal.
Brrr!
Do that. Brrr!
- Hey, Mia, brrrr!
- Fuck, I love you.
- Jade! Oh!
- Daniel!
Finally.
Um, hi, ex-boyfriend!
Group hug.
- Hold me, ex-boyfriend.
I am lonely. I
am so, so lonely!
You right there, woman?
I'm sorry for dragging you out.
Nah. I wasn't doing anything.
I actually wanted to get
out of the house for a bit.
Wanna come grab a drink?
I don't wanna do it.
- They want you to do it.
- I don't wanna do it.
How you been?
Dude, why'd you
have to bring her?
How you going, man?
- Good. You?
- Yeah, good, thanks.
First, uh, big boys' party, huh?
I don't really know anyone.
You'll know everyone by
the end of the night.
Oh, good.
- She's fine.
- No, she's not fine.
She irritates the
fuck out of me.
She's literally
done nothing to you.
She's so clingy, man.
It's fucking depressing.
Oh! Now she's flirting
with your boy.
They're friends, Hayley.
You keep telling yourself that.
Alright, let's do this!
Yeah, let's fake another video.
I've been waiting for this shit!
Be pretty sick to
hook the kid up.
He's not doing anything, Joss.
Come on, Jade.
Imagine it, though.
Joss, I said no.
Huh. More for me.
Thanks, bro.
I guess, uh, I'll
go first and...
Nah, you always go first.
It's my house. It's
my fuckin' hand.
Duckett gave it to me.
You're a fucking hog!
Does anyone else
want to volunteer?
I'll do it.
You wanna do it? Mm-hm.
- Wanna do it?
- Yeah.
- Do you wanna do it?!
Sit down, Mia.
Better her than me.
- Tie her.
Yes, sir. Hands up.
Mmm, kinky.
What are we playing?
It's nothing, Riley.
Hayley's tricked everyone.
Alright, somebody time it.
As soon as she lets it in,
it cannot go for
more than 90 seconds.
Am I clear?
What happens after 90 seconds?
They'll want to stay.
And if you die while
they're in you,
well, they'll have you forever.
So lame.
Hey, I'm just relaying
what I've been told, OK?
Oh! Fuck, dude!
Trust me... it's gotta be tight.
Candles?
Light the candle
to open the door.
Blow it out to close it.
OK, Mia.
Ah...
Put your hand on it.
No, like, hold it.
Now say,
"Talk to me."
Talk to me.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God, what the fuck?!
Who the fuck was that?
Who was that?!
I dunno, man. It's
different every time.
- Hey, you signed up.
- Where'd he go?
Mia, stop.
No, you didn't do it right.
You gotta say, "I let you in."
No, I'm flipping out.
Seriously, Mia, shut up.
No, someone was sitting
there, I swear to fuck.
OK, I'm proving it.
Attagirl, prove it! Prove
it. That's right, say it.
Do it. Do it.
Do it. Do it. Do it.
Do it! Do it! Do
it! Do it! Do it!
- OK! OK. OK.
Talk to me.
Hey, don't let go, Mia.
- Do not let go.
- I can't look at it!
You don't have to look
at it! Just say it.
- I can't!
- Say it!
I let you in. I let you in.
I let you in.
Someone timing it? Got it.
There you are.
Shh. Shh-shh-shh-shh.
There he is.
They like you.
What?
Oh, shit! Not you, though.
Whoa.
Yeah, Mia!
He's behind you now.
He'll split ya, pretty boy.
He'll split ya!
83 seconds. Joss,
get it off her.
He'll split ya!
- Alright, you've had enough.
- He'll split ya.
He'll split ya. He'll split ya.
Run. Run.
Run. Run. Run.
Run! Run! Run! Run! Run! Run!
- Run! Run! Run! Run! Run!
- 90 seconds, for fuck sake!
Run! Run! Run! Run!
RUN! RUN! RUN! RUN! RUN!
Hey. Hey. You OK?
We went a bit over.
Hey.
That was...
amazing!
That was the best one yet!
Jade. Jade, are you up?
You're not sleeping in here.
I didn't even ask that.
Isn't that what you want?
No. I'm just bored.
Look, Riley, you're not
nine anymore, alright?
Goodnight.
Can you shut the door?
Shut the door!
- Sook!
What a bitch.
Can I hang with you?
It's your house, bro.
Did the hand thing scare you?
A bit.
You gonna have
nightmares, Riley?
I don't get nightmares.
I do.
Like what?
I have this reoccurring
nightmare...
where...
I'm looking in the mirror
and my reflection is gone.
Like I don't exist.
What did the hand feel like?
Mmm...
It felt amazing.
I felt like I was glowing.
I could hear and see
and feel everything.
But I was in the passenger seat.
It felt incredible.
Mm.
How did your mum die?
You know.
Only bits.
She...
took too many sleeping pills.
By accident.
Dad was sleeping on the couch.
In the morning, he
couldn't open the door.
Mm.
Why?
Mum was on the other side.
And there were
scratches on the door
and wood under her nails.
She tried to get help,
but she couldn't.
Jade said you got
depression after.
I was just feeling alone.
No, you can't ever be alone
'cause you'll always
have me and Jade.
Yeah.
It's OK, I don't
feel alone anymore.
Wait. Oh, my God...
- Is it being constipated?
- Are you fuckin'...?
He's won a million pounds!
- You busy tonight?
- You want a turn, eh?
No. Daniel does.
What's in it for me?
My company.
That's pretty cool, I reckon.
No, we can't go to Joss's. His
place is trashed. He's pissed.
My house, then.
I got a party later.
I've gotta be gone by 11.
Mum, leaves at 9,
so... See ya at 10.
Jog on.
Yeah? Yes!
Hi. Is Jade home?
- Why is Daniel at the door?
- Mum, can you let him in?
You'd better not be having a
party, Jade, I swear to God.
It's two friends.
Can you let him in?
What time's everyone
getting here?
- Getting here for what?
- The party.
- Is there a party tonight?
- Don't bullshit me.
I'm... I'm sorry...
Have you got
alcohol in your car?
Oh, no. I don't drink, so...
You're good.
What time's the party again?
What party? The party.
Jade told me. It's
OK. What time?
I honestly don't know
what you're talking about.
The party tonight.
What time is it?
There's no party, Mum.
You are not drinking tonight.
On God, I will punch
you in the face.
Are you drunk?
James.
If there's a party, I'm
definitely drinking at it.
Is that Cookie or you, James?
Will you crack a window?
Jesus, Mum. Knock much?
Mia, if there is
a party tonight,
you are banned from this
house, effective immediately.
OK...
So, you're just third-wheeling
for the night, are you?
It's really humiliating
when you put it that way.
You'd better not be
getting stoned again, Mia.
Oh, my God! Why does your
mum have to know everything?
I know everything.
- I tried weed one time.
You.
My daughter's
vagina - prohibited.
Oh, my God, Mum! Leave the
room before I kill everyone.
The neighbours
tell me everything.
Oh, my God...
- Watch it!
Shut the door. Mum!
I'm leaving it open!
I'm so sorry.
Ooh. That's embarrassing.
♪ I saw your face displayed
upon a crescent moon
♪ That wavers up and down
depending how the petals bloom
♪ Doomed always destitute
Fused through infected roots
♪ Searching for a message
♪ But there's nowhere
left to exit to... ♪
Riley!
Mia!
- Mm! You keen?
I said don't smoke in my house.
Mm!
Hmm... Nice place.
That's an ugly fuckin' dog.
Excuse me.
- I'm thirsty.
So, where'd you get
it from, anyway?
I'll tell you what it is, right?
It's the hand of a psychic. Got
cut off and embalmed. Legit.
A medium, Joss. Not a psychic.
Yeah, this isn't
an embalmed hand.
Yes, it is, Danny boy. The
ceramic shit is put over it.
But if you smash it, there's
an actual hand in there.
- You're full of shit.
- I'm serious.
Apparently it was
the hand of someone
who could connect with the dead,
so everyone around him thought,
let's cut his hand off.
White people shit,
man, I tell ya.
Oi, I heard it was the
hand of a Satanist.
The other hand's just
out there somewhere.
Out where?
Shut up, alright?
- Fuckin' make me!
- You just talk shit.
Alright.
Where'd you buy it? Oh,
nah, I didn't buy it.
A friend gave it to
a friend and... yeah.
- Who?
- What do you want, Daniel?
A fuckin' spreadsheet with a
transaction history or what?
Hold the hand, say "Talk to me"
and ask the spirit your
fuckin' questions, alright?
This is such bullshit.
Oi, Riley, get the lights.
Film me?
Yep.
- Oi, time it.
OK, champ.
You know the drill.
- Say it.
Talk to me.
Whoa!
Oh, what?!
- No way!
- Mate, I don't have all day.
- No. No...
What is it?
OK. OK.
OK.
OK, come on.
I let you in.
Hayley, he's choking.
Hold it.
Hayley, fucking stop
it, he's choking!
Hold it.
There we go.
He hates it when you touch him.
You make him soft.
Yo, this spirit's a cunt.
Oh, fuck!
Oh, shit.
Ohhh!
Oh, no! I can't watch!
Oh, fuck! You OK?
Untie me.
Untie me, come on.
You alright?
Delete it.
Delete it, come on!
Yeah, nuh!
Hayley, please. Hayley...
- Post that shit.
Daniel.
Guys.
Oh, yeah, that was, uh...
That was pretty heavy, eh?
Yeah. You up for it?
Can I have a go?
Sorry...
- After that?
Just get your thot dog
out and no cameras.
♪ La Foule
Hey!
Aarghh!
Let's fucking go!
Mia! Mia!
Time's up, time's up!
♪ Et la joie éclaboussée
par son sourire
♪ Me transperce et
rejaillit au fond de moi
♪ Mais soudain je pousse
un cri parmi les rires
♪ Quand la foule vient
♪ L'arracher d'entre
mes bras... ♪
Talk to me! Talk to me!
What the fuck?!
Oh, fuck, yeah. This
shit never gets old.
Let's go!
I need a shot. Me too.
No way. Come on, Jade.
You're not my mum.
You're not even 18.
You're not even 15. So what?
Jade, please.
- Riley, I said no.
Fuck sakes.
What if we did it
for, like, 60 seconds?
- Mia, stop.
- 60 seconds, Jade.
You don't have to be a bitch
about all things Riley.
Yeah, Jade. You're just so busy
trying to suck Daniel's dick,
you don't give a shit
about anybody else.
OK, no. Why do you want to do
it so much? To impress James?
To come into my room
crying that you're scared
like last time?
Did you tell your
little friend that?
I hate you.
Like you're my favourite
person in the world.
Can't help you, bro. Your
sister's fuckin' boring.
Oh, shit, ooh...
- We should go.
- Yeah.
- 60 seconds. Please.
I dunno, maybe it's
not a good idea.
I actually thought you were
gonna be on my side for once.
Hey... I'm on both
of your sides.
- Obviously not.
- Riley...
60 seconds. Please.
Please.
OK.
What about 50?
OK. 50.
50 seconds?
- Yeah, just get it over with.
- Sign the form, baby!
- Let's go!
- Yeah, boy!
OK, hold up, hold up.
Hands up.
You alright, kiddo?
Yep.
OK. Let's do this.
Riley... gettin' crazy!
You know what to say, boy.
You better not cry
after 20 seconds.
I'll time it.
Talk to me.
What the fuck?
Riley.
It's OK.
Just say it.
I let you in.
Oh, shit.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
I'd never want to hurt you.
I miss you so...
so much, Mi.
I don't want you to hate me.
Mum?
- Hey, that's 50 seconds.
- Please don't close it off.
Mia...
- It's my mum. Please.
I love you both, baby.
I love you too, Mum.
I'm so proud of you.
And I got...
got... got... got...
.. got, got, got...
got, got, got, got,
got, got, got, got...
Oh, my God.
No! No, no, Riley!
- Riley, stop!
Joss, fucking help me!
Get it off him, Joss!
Oh, my God.
Riley! Riley!
Fucking help me!
Oi, help, help, help!
OK, I'm gonna untie him...
Get him on his side...
Daniel, call an ambulance!
No, no, no, no, no, no...!
James, James, get the
fuckin' bag! Hurry up!
Where are you going?
We gotta bounce.
No, we can't bounce.
We've gotta get out of here.
The police are already suss
about the Duckett stabbing.
They're gonna pin this on us.
We let them both do the hand.
We can't just pretend
we weren't here.
We're fucked...
We're fucked if...
We just gotta get
our story straight
and make sure everyone sticks
to it. Don't bring up the hand.
Excuse me. We need
to talk now, please.
Mum, Riley's in hospital.
What? What happened?
He smashed his face really bad.
What are you talking about,
"smashed his face"? How?
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know, I
wasn't in the room!
Stop crying and tell
me what happened.
Three or four minutes,
maybe? I'm sorry, Mum.
Jade! Jade,
frickin' answer me!
Can we talk about this?
Mia.
Dad, I just want to go to sleep.
Can you tell me one thing?
We didn't give him anything.
What happened, then?
I dunno.
I wish you'd just
be honest with me.
Right, because you've
been so honest with me.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means there's something
you haven't told me about Mum.
Isn't there?
Right.
Tell me he's OK.
No offence, I don't
want you here right now.
Wait, Jade. Come on.
Mia.
Sue, I...
Don't!
What are you doing here?
I just... I just came
to see how he was.
He's bad, Mia. He's
really fucking bad.
- Did you give him something?
- No.
Come on. I know you've done
shit before. What was it?
Nothing, I swear.
Look at his face.
What did my son ever do to you?
I... I didn't hurt him.
Go home. Now.
No, please, can I just see him?
You come back here, I'm
gonna call the police.
Sue...
- Jade.
- Just go home.
No, Jade, I'm so sorry...
Mum?
Mum, is that you?
Help me!
- Mum?
Mum?
Mum! Mia!
Mia.
- What's wrong?
Are you OK?
Was your dad pissed?
Yeah.
I'm 18, so the police
didn't call mine.
They can't know.
Where do they think you are?
Cousin's.
I can't go home.
They'll know something's up.
You can stay at mine.
Just 'cause of me and Jade.
It might be...
weird.
Yeah, but...
we're just friends.
It's not like it's
illegal or anything.
I just...
I don't want to be alone.
OK.
I can't believe I spoke to her.
I don't think that
was your mum, Mia.
No, it was at first.
She used to call me
'Mi' all the time.
I mean, how would the
spirits know that?
I feel like they read
what we think. You know?
I mean...
they were in us.
They could know
everything about us.
Or maybe...
Mum was there because she
was trying to reach out.
We could check.
I'm never doing it again, Mia.
Sorry.
Forgot about that.
- I was such a loser.
- You were cute.
Remember when we held hands?
Yeah.
I could feel your heart beating
through your fingertips.
You paid me out 'cause your
hands were bigger than mine.
- And they probably still are.
- No way.
It is. You have
the tiniest hands.
Yeah, I... I didn't
do puberty right.
No, wait, Jade...
Mum.
What's your message
to the haters?
Suck my arse! Mm-hm!
Mum!
Get off me. Get off!
Who's the cutest?
Me. Me.
- Me.
- Who's the hottest?
Who's the best? Me!
Who's the funniest? Me.
You suck!
- Fuck the haters!
Please... No. No, Rhea...
Rhea...
Daniel?
Daniel! Daniel, wake up!
Daniel, wake up!
Daniel!
Wake up!
Oh, what the...?! Mia!
- Stop!
Where is she? Oh,
my God, oh, my God!
Oh, my God, they followed us.
Whoever we contacted,
they followed us.
- What are you talking about?
- She was sucking your foot!
- You had my foot in your mouth!
- What? No, I didn't.
- I'm gonna go.
- Wait, Daniel...
- Mia, stop!
- No, don't leave me!
- No, I'm going.
- Stay with me.
Mum?
Mum.
Please, please, Mum.
Talk to me.
Mum.
Did you...
Did you kill yourself?
No.
Not on purpose, Mi.
Is that the truth?
I'd never want to leave you.
Ever.
I'm here.
Always.
Mia.
Riley needs help.
Oh, your father. Unbelievable.
Can you stay with him, Jade?
Riley.
Riley, please say something.
Riley?
Riley.
Mum! Mum!
No, Riley, stop! Riley, stop!
Stop! Stop!
Stop!
Riley!
Oh, shit!
Stop! Nurse!
Please stop him!
Riley, fucking stop now!
Fucking stop him! Do something!
It was you who took it. You
could've said something, Mia.
Who showed the police the video?
Think it was James.
Least it proves we
didn't touch him.
Police said there's
not a lot they can do.
Has it ever lasted this long?
No.
But we've never been over
90 seconds before Mia, so...
How is he?
Every time he comes to,
he tries to kill himself.
They wanna keep him. What?
The guy who gave
Duckett the hand said
that if you die while they're
in you, they have you forever.
Have any of you guys...
still been seeing stuff?
What the fuck you
mean, "seeing stuff"?
I saw my mum at the hospital.
And another one attacked
Daniel at my house.
Did you see something?
Uh... not exactly.
What's that supposed
to mean, Daniel?
I woke up and Mia was...
I dunno...
sucking my feet.
The fuck?
Jade.
What do you mean,
"woke up with Mia"?
"sucking your feet"?
It wasn't me.
- I couldn't go home.
None of us have
been seeing shit.
We all did it. We
were all there.
Why would you see your mum?
You didn't even let her in.
Wait, didn't Duckett say
they could imitate people?
Wait, who's Duckett?
I got the hand
off him. He, uh...
I met him twice at
some parties and...
yeah, we did the hand shit,
I asked if I could borrow it
and he said I could keep it.
He said he was seeing
them without it.
And then he went full skitz.
Stabbed his brother,
then killed himself.
The brother. Can
we talk to him?
What's up, bruz?
What are you doing here?
We gotta talk about Duckett.
Yeah.
Do you know what
the shit thing is?
He actually thought
he had friends.
You guys always
inviting him to shit,
acting like you cared.
- But you were using him.
- We weren't using him, Cole.
A real friend would've
seen it was fucking him up.
- But you didn't.
Look, bruz, I know it's
a shit time for you,
but we need your help.
Nah, man, I'm out.
Cole.
I know how much it hurts
to lose someone that close.
The people he let in
messed up his head.
If he'd stopped doing
that fucking thing,
they would've left.
My little brother's in
hospital. He went way over.
You let a kid do it?
His body should kick 'em out.
They get weaker the
longer they're in.
It hasn't. Give it time.
They're killing him.
Maybe it's time
you stop fucking up
people's lives, Joss.
What do you reckon?
Jade!
Jade, just wait! Jade!
You shouldn't have
let him do it, Mia!
We all decided it'd be OK.
We didn't decide anything.
We did. We all said...
We didn't say shit,
Mia. That was you.
You let it go for
two fucking minutes.
You sleep with my boyfriend.
What the fuck's wrong with you?
- Jade, it wasn't like that.
- Of course you take her side.
Jesus...
I wish that you didn't force
yourself into my family, Mia.
Um...
Did we blow the candle out?
I don't remember.
What if we opened the door
but we didn't shut it?
What are you saying?
We do it again with Riley but
blow out the candle this time.
You want him to do it again?
The thing that put
him in hospital?
- You wanna save him?
- Don't fucking ask me that.
We have to do something, Jade!
I'll give it back after, OK?
Just burn the fuckin' thing.
Hey, good luck.
Mum's back in, like, an hour.
We'll be quick.
Oh, my God.
Come on, Riley.
Come on, please.
Talk to him.
OK, yeah, blow it out.
Anything?
I don't know. Um...
Maybe if we just try it again.
Mia...
- Just try it again.
Talk to him.
It's not working.
OK. Um...
What if I use the
hand to speak to him?
No.
- What? He's not dead, Mi.
But what if his spirit is
disconnected from his body?
I thought these
spirits were in limbo.
- Maybe that's where Riley is.
- Might not be him.
- What if it is?
- What if it isn't?
This is a bad idea, Mia.
Mia.
Mia, don't.
Riley, talk to me.
Hi.
Is it him?
Is there a boy here?
Him.
Do you know where he is?
Please.
I can take you to him.
OK.
I let you in.
Help!
- Hey. Hey, hey, hey. You OK?
No! Don't touch me!
Don't touch me!
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey.
- It's just us.
It's just me and Daniel.
What happened?
I saw him.
They're hurting him, Jade.
They're not gonna stop.
They're never gonna stop.
Mia.
I haven't been completely
honest with you.
But I want to be.
Your mother...
before she passed,
she left us something.
Something I've been
scared to show you.
Which is wrong of me.
Because it's... it's just as
much as yours as it is mine.
Can I read it to you?
"Dear Max and Mia.
"It's Tuesday today
"and it's raining.
"It's the first
time in a long time
"I haven't felt hopeless.
"In fact...
"I am full of hope.
"I hope you live
beyond your years
"and find absolute happiness.
"I hope you... I hope you
don't hate me for this."
"I hope you find it in
your heart to forgive me.
"I hope you can find
some peace in knowing
"I am no longer in pain."
I'm sorry, Mi.
- It's hers, Mia.
- No.
It's OK.
No, she didn't do it.
She didn't do it,
because she told me, Dad.
because she told me.
She told me. She told me.
- Mia.
Mia. Come here.
Sweetheart.
- She's gone.
I'm sorry I kept it from you.
I didn't want you
blaming yourself.
It's not true.
I'll be back.
What?
- I'll be back, I promise.
- Mi...
I promise. I just gotta... I'll
be back, Dad. I'll be back.
Mi.
He's lying.
Then why did you
write it? I didn't.
Sweetheart.
That's not your dad.
What?
Mia?
That's not Max.
They're imitating him.
He's going to hurt you.
Mia, open the door!
Riley can't stay there.
Mia?
- He's suffering, Mi.
What... what do I do?
He needs to die.
What? Mia?
You have to put him
out of his misery.
No, Mum, I-I-I can't. I can't.
They're never gonna let him go.
- No, Mum, please, no...
I'll look after him, Mi.
Open the damn door!
Help him, Mia.
Let me in!
Help him, Mia!
Just leave me alone!
Mia!
- Mia!
- Help me!
I'm trying!
Mia!
- Oh, my God.
Hey.
Jade?
You OK?
I know what to do.
We can save him.
You know, I actually
think he's getting better.
He woke up for a second.
It's like he was himself again.
I've seen him, Jade.
He's in pain.
And every second
is agony for him.
Just come to mine.
And I'll show you.
Show me what?
You just have to be here, Jade.
Please.
- Just trust me.
- Oh, shit.
OK. I'll be there in 10.
Mia.
I'm... I'm sorry.
No, it's OK. Sit.
I was wondering when
I'd see you again.
You haven't come.
You told me not to.
I know. I was mad.
You had every right to be.
Still do.
No, I don't.
There were no drugs, Mia.
He had a breakdown. I just...
I just... couldn't face that.
I'm so sorry that I blamed you.
I know that you wouldn't
do anything to hurt him.
I love you guys.
You're not Riley's friend,
Mia - you're his family.
It'd mean so much to
him that you were here.
Can I have a minute with him?
Alone.
Of course.
I'm so sorry.
Found me.
Mia!
I am ending this!
You... can't take him.
He's ours.
Where is he?!
You saw.
Why don't you...
touch me?
I want to feel you.
Max?
Jade. Where are you?
At Mia's. She's not here.
- Max needs an ambulance.
- What... No, Mia's here.
What's wrong? What's happened?
She's there?
- Yeah, she's with Riley.
Mum, she's dangerous!
Mia?
Riley!
Hey! Where's my son?
He was in this room.
He should be here.
He was just here.
Well, where the fuck is he?!
Mia!
Mia! Riley.
Riley!
Mia, stop!
Mia!
I'm so proud of you.
Take him, my darling girl.
You're doing the right thing.
Show him the way.
I can protect him.
We'll have him forever.
Riley!
♪ I've seen the look
in her eyes... ♪
Oh...
Did you see what happened?
Riley?
I'm gonna be so far behind.
Don't worry about it.
Dad?
Dad!
Wait, Dad!
Jade? Sue?
- Dad?
Dad!
- Dad, wait!
Oh, Dad!
Dad, wait!
Don't leave me!
Please!
I let you in.
♪ I saw God in a body bag
♪ I got lost in the stars when
they'd cross like a polygraph
♪ Never lie Cardiac
in every line
♪ Insomniac forever
Never go to sleep again
♪ Black lungs from
the falling ash
♪ Giraffe tongue
with a heart to match
♪ Get sawed in half
like the Dahlia
♪ Place pain on
display in Hollywood
♪ Paint it all like
Dali would Face Of War
♪ Fountain pens melting
countenances in a drawing book
♪ A psycho full of
cyclones Eyes closed
♪ I go cold when I fly
low Brains feed on haikus
♪ Isolated in my temples Cairo
♪ Bones jut from their
homes like they're silos
♪ I'm Silent Hill Tell
me where the time went
♪ Kill Pyramids that followed
with the knife gripped
♪ Vice-grips always on the
mind when the crisis hits
♪ Everywhere it's
like a mine I step
♪ I'm an atom
bomb made of atoms
♪ Add 'em up Adam's
apple's rotten
♪ Smashed to apple sauce Adamant
♪ No Adam Eve in anatomy
♪ Only albatrosses
if I have to speak
♪ Another casualty
of the casted wings
♪ Casually I'm high again
♪ Vibrant as a hyacinth idling
♪ So I pretend that
my defence is working
♪ Lurking with the burdens that
still hide below the surface
♪ I know these
things have meaning
♪ Sometimes I don't know
the purpose, introverted
♪ Dizzy from the
disconcerted tizzies
♪ Mr Perfect isn't worth it
Give me what I didn't earn
♪ Put it in an
urn Live and learn
♪ I could never
tell the difference
♪ When I'm
miniature Red alerts
♪ Read aloud like ministers
♪ It's hard to breathe when
you're drowning in the goodbyes
♪ But I'm still here now so
tell me what that look like?
♪ They use a sword to signify
that you're a good Knight
♪ Then use the same one to
kill you and say goodnight
♪ Goodnight, goodnight,
goodnight, goodnight... ♪