Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Hi, you've reached
Tom Dennistoun
of Dennistoun's Design.
Leave your name and number
and I'll get back to you.
If it's urgent,
give Pete a call. Thanks.
You can't control it.
You don't have anything to say.
Your biggest mistake
is believing you can.
You don't know anything.
It's kind of a weird gift,
but I'm sure he'll love it.
Hi, Russ.
Morning, Betty!
He's probably out
walking Friendo.
- You think?
- He never leaves the house,
but I don't know.
He put a new doorknob on.
Check that out.
- That's a start.
- Mm.
We gotta go grab the daisies.
Lilies.
At least the car
will smell nice.
Hey, Charlie!
Charlie.
I guess we'll just see you
at the cemetery.
Okay, man.
Hey, Russ.
You mind keeping an eye
on that thing?
Thanks, bud.
The curb's a little weird.
Give me your hand.
Okay.
- Hi, Mom.
- Hi.
You're coming to the restaurant
after this, right?
No.
I made reservations
for all of us,
- plus Gale.
- Where are we going?
Um, Gale's not coming.
She told me she was.
She was just trying
to be polite.
It's a hard day.
Did you pick the chairs?
Yeah. I think we're gonna...
I think we're gonna go
with brown.
- How's that sound?
- Mm.
I don't know, I'm not making
the decision for you.
The wrong chairs'll throw
the whole day off.
We don't want that!
Hi, you've reached
Tom Dennistoun
of Dennistoun's Design.
Leave your name and number
and I'll get back to you.
If it's urgent,
give Pete a call. Thanks.
You know, you could've
picked him up.
We knocked.
I'll be in the car.
What'll it be?
Ooh, I'm just browsing,
but, uh, Betty,
you want something?
I'm driving.
I'll drive. What do you want?
It's okay.
I don't want anything.
She'll have a tequila soda.
And I will have a double soda.
- Enjoy.
- Thanks, buddy.
Don't know what your dad loved
so much about this place.
The free popcorn.
- Free popcorn?
- Mhm.
- Carl?
- Yeah?
You guys got free popcorn?
Aw, man, that machine's busted.
Shocker.
You think Carl made this?
Fuck, I forgot
to leave this for him.
Don't worry about it,
I'll bring it over.
I'm sure he'll be psyched
to see me.
- Yeah?
- Mhm.
It doesn't matter,
he's not gonna show anyway.
He's gonna come,
he's gonna come.
Grief is...
grief is tough,
it takes time.
How much time does he need?
He's in that house all day.
That's why I'm trying
to get him out.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I got some guys.
Hey, kids.
Oh. Hi.
Hi, Carl.
In honor of your dad.
Thanks, Carl.
A year gone...
...is a year too long.
Thank you.
- Enjoy.
- Thanks.
- Hey, hey, hey.
- I...
To us.
To us. Mhm.
Fires.
Then mudslides?
Bet they didn't plan
on that one.
Oh, what the heck.
Can't control any of it.
You don't have anything to say.
I was buying time.
You shouldn't get close
to people.
Trying to find a solution.
Your brother won't answer,
you won't answer.
Make sure he's almost done
with your father's
house repairs.
Oh, and I hired a DJ.
You'll love her.
Hey, Charlie.
Charlie!
Charlie.
It's Benny, open up.
Hey.
Dammit.
What an idiot.
Hey, Charlie, I'm coming in.
Hey, man.
Friendo!
Hey, buddy.
Just me.
What a slob.
Jesus.
Oh.
Ooh.
Hey.
Happy birthday.
Brought you a new roommate.
Don't even need to water it,
it's fake.
What's going on?
Working.
We missed you today!
Your sister was pretty bummed.
Your mom... well, she's your mom.
Okay.
Forgot to leave the RSVP.
Um...
Feel free to fill it out.
Tough choices.
Lemon chicken or mahi-mahi.
Where's Friendo?
I didn't see him when I came in.
He's in the backyard.
Okay.
The house is looking good.
Devil's in the details,
they say.
Rehearsal dinner is
in a couple days.
You don't have to wear the suit
we brought you.
Just wear something clean.
It'll mean a lot
to your sister if you came.
We only want her
getting married once, right?
And when you get a chance,
give her a call.
I know she'd love
to hear from you.
Okay.
Your coffee is shit, by the way.
I'll show myself out.
But, uh, I'm on my way.
Got a little sidetracked,
but my head's all clear.
I will see you soon.
Order me some egg rolls
and, uh, maybe
some crab rangoon.
Okay, I love you, babe.
Bye.
Charlie?
Have you seen my harmonica?
Should be around here somewhere.
Mhm.
Man, you were conked out
on the couch last night.
Could not wake you up.
Yeah.
You know, my dad used to sleep
on the couch all the time.
He'd be up until
like 1 or 2 A.M.
and wake up a few hours later
and go to work.
Sounds like a dad.
Okay, what's going on?
I've been thinking
about the car,
about selling it.
We just got the car.
Why do we want to sell it?
Dad's car.
Oh.
I mean, it's just
gonna sit there.
Yeah.
You probably gotta...
you gotta talk to Charlie
about that first.
Why we even brought it back,
I have no idea.
I'm not arguing with you.
How much do you think
it's worth?
That car?
It's been in the sun
for a year.
You really should talk
to your brother about this
if you really want
to sell the car.
- It's not his decision.
- It's not yours.
Come on.
Where'd you hide it?
Hamper.
You know what this means?
Don't!
I'm not... I'm not in the mood.
Okay, all right.
I gotta go.
Give me a hug.
Come on, I gotta go.
It's gonna be all right.
- All right?
- Yeah.
It's gonna be good.
I love you.
There's some leftovers
in the fridge
- if you get hungry later.
- Thank you.
Hi, you've reached
Tom Dennistoun
of Dennistoun's Design.
Leave your name and number
and I'll get back to you.
If it's urgent,
give Pete a call. Thanks.
Don't you ever check your mail?
I've been trying you
for a fucking year.
Don't be a fool
like your father.
245-6123.
I won't be calling you again.
This is your Uncle Pete.
Ow!
Charlie?
Are you good?
Yeah, I'm fucking great, Russ!
Come on over here then.
I'll fix us an early supper.
Don't be a hoarder,
like the ones on TV.
If you're gonna stay
in that house,
get rid of whatever
don't make you happy.
Most of it's
at my mom's house,
and I'm not planning
on staying there.
Most of it?
All of it!
Don't leave nothing!
I'm working on it.
My dad left a lot to do.
You done?
I'll do the dishes.
Yes, you will!
I did the cooking.
Well, pretty fair trade,
I guess.
Charlie?
See you tomorrow, Russ!
You finally got back to me, huh?
Listen to me, Charlie.
This thing is going
to destroy you,
just like it did your father.
Leave, before you hurt
anyone else.
You have the address.
Hey.
Seatbelt, please.
32 Hockomock?
Gonna be a long one.
I was almost dead.
A haunted house party.
Friendo?
Friendo!
Hey, buddy!
How are you?
Oh, my...
Hi, you've reached
Tom Dennistoun
of Dennistoun's Design.
Leave your name and number
and I'll get back to you.
If it's urgent,
give Pete a call. Thanks.
Get in here.
I was wondering
when you'd get here.
Want a drink?
Sit down.
God damn, if you don't look
just like him.
Aren't you supposed to be dead?
God damn thing.
You hungry?
Ah!
Ahhh!
Where did that happen?
Huh?
At Dad's house.
Your Dad's house?
That happen before?
Answer me!
Did that happen before?
No.
You weren't followed here,
were you?
Were you followed here?
No.
You hear that?
What was that?
Let's go.
What is this?
These are my brothers.
They listened to me.
Your father would
have been here, too,
if he didn't kill himself.
Let's go.
Let's go!
You need to stay here.
You know that.
Did you hear me?
Can't.
This is our family.
Who we are.
Don't do what my brother did.
I'm going to bed.
32 Hockomock.
How do you even know it's real?
So Charlie knows
I'm coming over?
He knows I'm coming over?
Hey.
Yeah, just get the key from him.
I think this is cool,
I'm glad you talked to him.
Makes me happy.
Soon, you'll be happy.
We will all be happy.
I love you.
Bye.
Hey, Charlie!
Hey!
Good morning.
Hey.
Whoa, ahh!
Oh, God, ahh!
What happened to your arm?
Something scratched me.
What the hell happened, man?
What happened to Friendo?
I didn't think you
actually meant in the backyard.
You know,
you can come stay with us.
I think it'd be good for you.
Get away from this house.
I got some guys,
they could finish it up.
I think you just need
to get away for a while,
clear your head.
Oh, hold on.
Oh.
Hey, hey, what's up, Paco?
Yeah, we're here with the car.
Yeah.
Five minutes, five minutes.
Cool.
All right, yeah.
See ya soon.
Paco's on his way, man.
What car?
The car,
Paco's gonna pick it up.
Who's that, what car?
Oh, fuck.
Betty's selling the car.
It's good, it's good.
That car is bad mojo.
Change is good.
If my mentor,
Humberto,
didn't have to change
the way he ate his food,
he would've never met
the nurse in the cafeteria
at the hospital.
If the bobcat never came along...
All I'm saying is
life is weird, man.
You never know
what's around the corner.
I'm gonna take care
of that wasp nest before...
This isn't the most humane,
but it's the coolest.
Oh, ah!
- Sorry I scared you.
- Oh, hi.
- You're Paco.
- Yeah, I'm here for Ben.
Yeah, I'm Betty... oh, I'm sorry.
I'm actually... I'm not gonna
sell the car today,
and I know you came
all the way out.
All right, so are you gonna
sell it another day,
- just not today?
- I can't sell it right now.
Thanks, thanks a lot.
Fuck!
Oh, great, you made up
your mind about the chairs.
Do you still have Dad's stuff?
Yeah, in the garage.
I think beige will look better,
what do you think?
Uh, sure.
Your voice is so shaky.
This is all just
so overwhelming.
What, the chairs?
No, not the chairs.
I'm gonna tell them beige.
Great.
Okay.
Yeah, we're gonna
stick with the beige.
All set, honey, um, talk soon.
Bye, Mom.
What were you building
back there?
Ah, I don't know.
There are some things
we should do,
and some things you want to do.
But, we shouldn't
do it all by ourselves.
Russ, I think I'm seeing things
that aren't real, man.
Who says it isn't real?
Thanks for letting me
borrow that by the way.
Any time.
Charlie.
What did you think would happen?
What's wrong with you?
Everyone's sad.
Why can't you just get over it?
Hey, good morning, buddy,
I was in the neighborhood,
I was gonna bring you
some coffee.
Sorry about yesterday.
What's going on?
I gotta go.
You know,
the rehearsal's in two days.
Look, you were right,
the house is way too much work.
Get your guys to fix it up.
I gotta get out of town.
You're telling that to Betty.
Okay, fine, let's go,
I'll follow you.
- Let's go.
- No, no, we're gonna
go over there right now.
- Ugh.
- Please get out.
Once you talk
to your sister, I'm out.
We taking the long way, buddy?
Do you know where you're going,
or we just kinda
- playing this one by ear?
- You know,
I can drop you off wherever.
Oh, no, no, no,
I'm good, I'm good,
I'm just, like,
backseat driving, I know.
Just go, we're good.
Let me just, I'm gonna give...
I'm gonna give, uh,
the old battle axe a call.
Let... let Betty know what's up.
Uh, alrighty.
Betty, Betty,
Betty, Betty, Betty.
Ah, this is cool out here.
Hi, it's Betty,
sorry I missed your call.
Leave a message
and I'll call you back.
Thanks, bye
Hey, babe,
just calling, checking in.
Um, sorry for being
a butthead last night
with the garden hose thing.
Um, hope you got some rest
at your mom's.
And she didn't melt your brain.
Um, I'm actually hanging out
with Charlie today.
Going for a little drive.
But, I just wanted to check in
and tell you that I miss you,
and I love you,
and, uh, give me a call
when your phone's not dead,
or turned off, or you're done
being angry with me.
Again, I'm sorry,
talk to you later, babe.
Fuck, where are we?
I can really take a piss break
in a little bit.
Drank all that coffee.
You want me to drive?
I can drive.
I know it's your dad's car,
but I can drive.
Just let me know, you know?
- It's too late for all of us.
- You may start to hear
- this voice in your head.
- You feel like a stranger
- in your own body.
- Hockomock is just
- a place to rot.
- You can't kill it.
- Going there won't solve this.
- You can't hide from it.
- Charlie?
- You'll suffer forever.
- Finish what you started.
- It'll find a way to hurt you.
- It always finds a way.
- This way,
- you two can put an end to it.
- You can't control it.
Stay away from Hockomock,
stay away.
- It will become you.
- It will kill the ones you love.
Is this where
you keep the snacks?
Pull over.
Stop the car!
Stop the car, man.
What are you doing?
Get out of the car.
Get out of the car,
turn the car off,
get out of the car.
I wish I didn't know
you had a gun in there, man.
Hi, guys,
what can I get for you?
Coffee and water, please.
Coffee and water, you got it.
- For you?
- Cheeseburger, fries.
Okay, medium, medium-rare?
- Medium.
- Great, anything to drink?
- Definitely a beer.
- Okay.
- Light beer.
- You got it.
- No food for you?
- No, thank you.
Okay, the burger
should be a moment,
and I'll get
your drinks right away.
You gotta eat something.
Look, I'm sorry
I lost your headphones.
Stupid.
I shouldn't have
taken them out of the car.
All right, coffee for you.
Beer, water.
- May I have some milk?
- Yeah, sure thing.
How much further
do you wanna take this, man?
Me and your sister
care about you.
Look.
Grief is a motherfucker.
You know that.
Before I met your sister,
I was pretty messed up.
It felt like
there was this sadness
inside of me,
and I couldn't shake it.
But, I did.
All I'm saying is
you don't have to do it alone.
You just have to do something.
I do have to do something.
You know that wasp nest
at the house?
I know that you know it.
Well, I've gotten rid
of that thing about
half a dozen times now.
Just keeps coming back.
They keep coming back.
It wasn't a big deal at first.
Just wasps.
But, then it was other things,
like window screens.
The doorknob.
Stupid doorknob.
I don't think it wanted me
to leave the house.
I think it got my dad, too.
I know it killed Friendo.
It killed Russ.
It's gonna kill me.
Kill Mom, kill Betty.
Until I do something.
Okay, cheeseburger with fries.
Excuse me.
Now.
Enjoy.
I need to wash my hands.
That looks pretty good.
- Where's your restroom?
- Oh, it's right around
- the corner to the left.
- Thank you.
Hey, here's your milk,
sorry about that.
Burger tasting okay?
Hm, can I get some ketchup?
- Okay, we have mustard, too.
- Yeah, that's great.
- Dijon?
Okay, get you
another beer as well?
Yeah, thank you.
Yeah, I'll have another.
Leave me a message
and I'll call you back.
Thanks, bye.
Hey, uh, I've been trying
to get a hold of you all day.
It's been a...
it's been a weird one.
Uh, oh, this is Ben.
My phone died.
Um, I don't know what's
going on with your brother.
Uh, he doesn't...
he doesn't seem well.
I'm... I'm worried.
But, um... but, don't worry.
I got this,
I'll take care of him.
So, I'm just calling
to tell you I love you,
and I'll try again later.
Finish what you started.
Disappear.
Hey, is everything okay?
Yeah, I don't know.
Okay, um, we're closing.
Sorry, uh,
can I get you anything?
Maybe another beer, or coffee?
- Yeah, coffee would be good.
- Okay, I'll get it for you.
- Hey.
- Hm?
Do you know anyone
who lives around here?
Well, yeah.
Um, Hockomock?
Hockomock Lane,
do you know where that is?
Hey, Rocco.
Do you know where
Hockomock Lane is?
I'm clocked out.
I'm sorry.
What time do you get off?
- I'm not...
- Could you give me a ride?
- Um.
- Hey, hey.
I'm a park ranger,
I rescue cubs from trees.
My boyfriends gonna be here
in about 30 minutes.
Do you have...
do you have time to wait?
Yeah, that's fine, that's great.
Okay.
Can I get you some milk?
- Sure.
- Okay.
I'll get your coffee.
Pete thought he could trick it.
Fake his death.
Outrun it.
No fucking way.
It found him,
like it found me.
It'll find a way to hurt you,
and hurt the ones you love.
Let's go.
You don't know
what you're doing.
Shut up.
Is he normally this late?
About 15 minutes.
Is that a fucking
cop costume, my dude?
Nick, shut up,
I told you he needs a ride.
Hi, I'm Benjamin.
No smoking in the car, my dude.
It's gotta go out.
Nick, let's go.
- It's going out, let's go.
- Sorry, can we go?
Yeah, we're trying to.
Thanks.
Do you know how much...
do you know how much
further we have to go?
Do you know how much...?
Could I charge my phone,
do you have a charger up there?
No, I'm sorry.
The music's so loud, I can't...
I'm sorry, I gotta...
I just can't hear.
Don't, dude,
are you fucking serious?
- Hey, hey, it's fine...
- I'm just gonna turn it down...
Are you fucking serious, dude?
What the fuck, guys,
what the heck, guys!
- Calm down, calm down.
- Come on, come on, take it easy!
- So unacceptable.
- Take it easy!
- Come on, what are you doing?
- What the hell are you doing?
Stop it, Nick, stop it!
- What are you doing to him?
- What the fuck?
- He didn't even do anything.
- Unacceptable.
- Are you serious?
- What, no!
- He just needed a ride!
Absolutely unacceptable.
My hat!
That's a federal offense!
Ah, fuck.
What are we doing here?
I need you to dig.
What?
Dig.
- You don't know what you're do...
- Shut the fuck up
and dig.
Come on.
Charlie!
Charlie.
Where is he?
Charlie!
Charlie, Charlie, buddy.
Come on.
Hey, just look at me.
Just look at me, come on.
I'm gonna get you out of here,
all right?
I'm gonna get you out of here.
You don't have
anything to say, Charlie?
You shouldn't
get close to people.
There's nothing you can say,
or do anything.
- Charlie?
- You don't understand
your family.
You saw your dad every day.
But, who the hell was he?
- You don't have anything to say.
- Talk to each other.
Charlie!
Ahh, stop, stop!
Stop!
I can't... I can't
do this anymore, man.
Let's just go home.
Charlie!
Close the casket!
Close it!
Close it, god damnit, close it!
We're gonna have a kid.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull