LET THE RIGHT ONE IN
Squeal like a pig.
Squeal!
Squeal like a pig!
The police have many ways
to find out if something's fishy.
Remember the house
that burned down in Ängby?
A house that burned
to the ground.
They found someone in there.
Dead, of course.
In that case
we knew it was arson
because the person
had been murdered.
How could we know that?
Yes?
Because there wasn't
any smoke in the lungs.
That's correct.
How did you figure it out?
I read a lot.
What kind of books,
I wonder?
Newspapers
and things like that.
And now we can talk a little
about drugs.
What kinds are
the most common...
Oskar!
What are you staring at?
Huh?
You staring at me?
You better stop.
Good job, pig!
On the coast,
just a few degrees below zero.
Eastern Svealand-
clear tonight...
intermittent snow flurries...
temperatures ranging
from 20-32 degrees...
Excuse me...?
What time is it?
I don't have a watch.
What's that?
It's called Halotan.
Ricky!
Get lost!
Ricky?
Darned dog!
Ricky!
What are you looking at?
Huh?
Looking at me?
You better quit.
What's wrong with you?
Are you scared?
Squeal then!
Squeal!
What are you doing?
Nothing.
- What are you doing?
- Nothing.
- Do you live here?
- Yes...
I live here.
Okay.
Where do you live?
Next to you.
How do you know
where I live?
I can't be friends
with you.
Just so you know.
Why?
That's just how it is.
Do you think
I want to be friends with you?
I've told you
you have to help me!
Do I have to do it myself?
Say something!
Sorry.
So no one knows
why this boy was murdered.
I understand
that many of you are scared,
but the counselor
will be here all day.
You can talk to her
whenever you want.
Does anyone
have any questions?
If we meet the murderer,
can we murder him?
Conny, that was
unnecessary.
Oskar!
You will go straight home
after school!
And you're not to leave the yard
until I come home.
But it was in Vällingby.
So you think someone
who murders children
can't take the subway?
Or walk a kilometer?
Yes, that would be best...
He's going to his father's
next week...
Murder in Vällingby
MURDERER DRAINED VICTIM'S BLOOD
Senseless massacre in Beirut
No survivors in Arab murders
manhunt for killer continues
Eyewitness identifies murderer
prior to confession
MURDER DRAINED HIS VICTIM
...just coming- hi, there.
I really don't think
the death penalty
has any relevance
in our society.
It's just something
they've drilled into us-
like the Russians
or something-
Are you saying
there aren't any Russians?
Of course
there are Russians.
Never seen him before.
Who's been bitten
by a snake here?
He moved into my building
the other day. With a little kid.
- Should I ask him over?
- Yes, ask him!
What the hell?
In that case...
Things not going too well?
It's screwed up.
You moved into #15?
Why sit by yourself?
Come over instead.
I'm kind of in a hurry.
Mom?
I'm going out
for a while.
Aren't you going
to watch the rest?
No, it wasn't any good.
Stay in the yard, then, okay?
Well, I'll watch
the rest anyway.
You're here again?
Are you here again?
I want to be left alone.
Me too.
Go home, then!
You go home.
I've lived here longer.
What's that?
This?
It's a Rubik's cube.
Is it a puzzle?
Yes.
You want
to borrow it?
Till tomorrow.
I might not be here
tomorrow.
That's okay.
You can borrow it till Monday.
How does it work?
You try to get the sides
one color.
Like this.
You smell funny.
Aren't you cold?
- No.
- Why not?
I guess
I've forgotten how.
Guess I'll see you
Monday, then.
Okay.
Thanks for tonight.
Bye, old pal.
- See you tomorrow.
- Yeah.
- You're the best.
- You too.
Help me.
Hello?
Please, help me.
Has something
happened?
Are you hurt?
- Can you get up?
- No.
I'll carry you.
Can we call somewhere?
Careful.
You don't weigh
anything-
Gösta?
Hey, Gösta!
It's been a long time.
- Jocke...
- What?
Jocke-
There was an animal
behind-
and then I saw Jocke-
and a little kid.
It was here somewhere.
Look!
Damn.
Blood.
It's blood, damn it!
Who the hell did this?
Whew...
How did you do it?
I turned it.
Do I smell better?
What's your name?
Eli.
What's yours?
- Eli?
- Yeah.
My name is Oskar.
How old are you?
Twelve- about.
And you?
12 years, eight months,
and nine days.
What do you mean,
"about 12"?
When's your birthday?
I don't know.
But, like,
when were you born?
Your parents-
they have to know.
You never
get any presents?
No.
You can have this if you want.
It's yours.
I don't get how you did it.
You want me to show you?
Show me.
You have
to start here...
then you take
this side. See?
"He slipped in and out
among the tree shadows.
He ran quickly and quietly
and was careful to avoid the light.
Soon they returned
to watch the gate,
muttering
and swearing.
Bilbo was saved. "
Well then,
that's it for today!
Do you all have the slips
for Thursday's field trip?
Thank you for today.
- Oskar, aren't you going?
- No, I have some things to do.
Samuel Morse
What were you writing?
What do you mean?
Let me see.
No.
What do you mean, no?
Give it here!
Who's gonna talk
to his mom now?
Wait!
Oskar!
I fell at recess.
I fell on a rock.
Oh, darling.
You have to be careful.
Hmm?
Short, long,
long, short, long.
Exactly.
Here.
What happened?
Some kids in my class.
Where do you
go to school, anyway?
Oskar, listen.
You have to fight back.
You've never hit them back...
have you?
Start hitting back now-
hard.
There are three of them.
Then you have to hit
even harder!
Hit back harder
than you dare.
Then they'll stop.
- But if they-
- Then I'll help you.
I can.
Come.
Move over.
Short, short...
S- s-s...
Ooh-hh...
Vuh...
Guh...
Keep the distance!
Not too near, not too far.
Just so. Calmly.
Yes?
That strength training class
in the bathhouse...
can I sign up for it?
You don't have to sign up,
just come.
At 7:00.
You want to?
- Yes.
- Good!
You'll train, then you can go
about 50 times.
At least.
Wait a minute...
Mixed.
Here.
No.
Too bad.
I can... try one.
I'm sorry.
Oskar...
do you like me?
Yes, a lot.
If I weren't a girl,
would you like me
anyway?
I guess so.
Why?
Oskar!
Hi, buddy!
- You're early.
- Hi, Dad!
There are people
who recognize my face
who know I live here,
with you.
- Maybe you shouldn't.
- Where else would you be?
Can you do
something for me?
Not see that boy
this evening?
What the hell?
- Where's Matte?
- Don't know.
Hey! Matte?
Matte!
Time to go home!
Matte?
What are you doing?
Open the door.
Matte!
Let me down!
Help!
Matte?
Turn the handle!
Help!
Help...?
How did you
end up there?
I'm trapped.
...police have not been able
to confirm the identity
of the man who was
apprehended last night
on suspicion of murder
and attempted murder
in Vällingby,
in western Stockholm.
Identification was difficult
because the man injured himself
severely before his arrest.
In sports...
Just go in.
Yes?
Sorry.
I'm looking for my dad.
Is he here?
What's his name?
He's sick.
The police took him.
Where could he be?
Then he's on Level 7.
But you can't
just go in there.
- I can call-
- No.
It's not necessary.
You poor thing.
Can I come in?
Wake up, Virginia.
- A kid!
- What goddamn kid?
Why the hell would a kid
want to kill Jocke?
I don't know.
Jocke was the kindest
person I know.
I'll rip that damned kid
to shreds.
Oskar!
Can I come in?
Don't look.
But say
I can come in.
Come in.
Close your eyes.
How did you get here?
I flew.
Okay.
But you're not
wearing any clothes.
You're ice cold!
Sorry.
Is it yucky?
No.
"Bulleri, bulleri bock
How many fingers
am I tapping you with?"
Eli...
Do I have a chance
with you?
With what?
I mean...
Do you want to go steady?
Oskar,
I'm not a girl.
No?
Do I have
a chance with you?
Can't we just
be like this?
Yes.
Do you do something
special then?
No.
Is everything like usual?
Yes.
- Then you have a chance with me.
- What?
Then we're together.
- Really?
- Yes.
Good.
TO FLEE IS LIFE,
TO LINGER, DEATH.
YOUR ELl
Lower grades, with me!
Middle grades, free skating.
Watch out
for the ice pit over there!
Listen to me!
- Avila...?
- Understood?
Avila...
- it's called an ice hole.
- Ice hole?
I mean, ice hole!
You want to swim?
Are you going to swim?
No.
Teacher, teacher?
I have to go pee.
- Pee over by the tree.
- On the ice?
So what?
It'll be new ice. Yellow.
What are you going to do
with the stick?
I'll hit you-
If you try anything.
Did the pig
suddenly get brave?
I'm going to skate over to you
and push you over.
You won't do anything.
Am I right?
Little piggy...
watch out...
Look.
Come on.
The teacher's coming.
He'll be mad.
So are you just
going to stand there?
What's going on
over there?
Oskar!
What are you doing?
Come on.
POLICE
Yes, it is.
Now he's coming.
They've called from school.
And you can talk to your dad,
because I-
Hello?
I'm okay.
I don't know.
Come up?
We'll see.
Hey, Oskar.
So you're going to swim
after all.
I'm just kidding.
We're not allowed
to be here, really.
This cellar is the best place.
We can do whatever we want.
You know, today...
they tried to throw me
into a hole in the ice...
Oskar-
But I had a stick,
and I hit Conny
in the head
so he had to go
to the hospital.
Oskar...?
Huh?
Hooray!
What were we going to do?
We're going to mix.
It doesn't hurt at all.
All you have to do
is prick your finger.
Eli?
Go!
Get out of here!
Damn it, they had to saw
through that ice.
What the hell
are you worrying about?
Interrogation, and stuff.
Interrogation!
Maybe they'll put me
in one of those rooms...
and shine a light on me-
- Jocke and I, we were this close-
- I'm sorry, I can't do it.
In fact...
it is actually a duty
to testify.
Hell.
I have nothing left...
now that he's gone.
- But Lacke-
- Stop that shit!
Don't give me your
goddamn "Lacke, Lacke. "
You don't
understand shit.
You're cold,
fucking ice cold!
Ow-!
You handled that
just fucking great, Lacke.
Virginia!
Wait!
Can't we talk about it?
Listen-
Help me! Help me!
- Get the fuck off her!
- Help me!
Ginia?
Wait up!
What's going on up there?
- I didn't see that one.
- As usual.
Now I'll get you.
You can always dream.
- We have a guest.
- Hello to you.
So...
you're sitting here
having a good time.
Yes.
So Oskar is here.
Dad?
It's your turn.
Yes, yes.
But we have a guest now.
You have it nice
and warm in here.
So there was some
at home, after all.
TO FLEE IS LIFE,
TO LINGER, DEATH.
YOUR ELl
It went wrong, you see.
I had figured it out
so it would be perfect.
Maybe there was something
wrong with the set square,
or the ruler, or...
Nothing to be scared of, kitty.
And it was more
and more wrong.
And now I walk around
and it feels like-
Awful lot of traffic
this evening!
Come in!
Ginia! Where the hell
have you been?
What are you doing?
I need to talk to you,
damn it!
- We've been so fucking worried!
- No!
I have to hold you.
We've been
so fucking worried.
- Are you crazy?
- Let go of me!
What's happening
with the cats?
- Let us out, you bastard!
- Let go of me! Help!
Oskar, is it you?
Yes.
Are you a vampire?
I live off blood.
Yes.
Are-
are you dead?
No.
Can't you tell?
But are you...
old?
I'm twelve.
Though I've been 12
for a long time.
Are you guys poor?
- You see the egg there?
- Mm-hmm.
If you sold that you could buy
a nuclear power plant.
It's true.
Oh. Sure.
Put your finger here.
Those rings-
where did they come from?
I'm going home now.
I'm going to deliver
chocolates tomorrow.
To earn money?
Um-hmm.
But you can have money
from me.
Here.
Take it if you want.
You've stolen it!
As soon
as they're dead, right?
- It was given to me.
- By whom?
Different people.
I want to go home now.
If I may.
Dad's stamp collection.
His whole life.
One stamp...
80,000.
80 big ones!
Sometimes I tried to be interested.
I said, "I won't tell. "
He just said, "No, there are others.
Thank you very much. "
There isn't a prettier place.
Larks, potatoes-
Lacke,
you have to help me!
Of course.
- That child.
- Yeah?
She must have infected me.
I don't want to live.
Good morning!
This looks good-
you'll be able to go home today.
Good.
I'll just open this...
and take a little blood sample.
There.
- Sir?
- Yes?
Could you open
the shutters, please?
Sure.
Give me the cap.
Give it to me!
Are you stupid?
- Hi.
- Hi. What's up?
Can I borrow the keys?
- Why?
- I'm going home.
Sure. Here.
Thanks.
- Hi.
- Hey.
You have to ask me in.
What happens if I don't?
What happens
if you come in anyway?
Is there anything
in here?
Tsk-tsk-tsk...
Tsk-tsk-tsk.
No!
You can come in!
Who are you?
The same as you.
What?
"What are you
looking at, huh?
Are you looking
at me?
Then squeal like a pig!
Squeal!"
That was the first thing
I heard you say.
I don't kill people.
No...
but you'd like to,
if you could.
To get even.
Right?
Yes.
Oskar, I do it
because I have to.
Be me a little.
Please, Oskar...
be me a little.
You can borrow
a dress from my mom.
Oskar, can you open?
Coming!
I'm in the bathroom.
Hl! I'M IN THE BATHROOM.
PLEASE DON'T COME IN.
DO YOU WANT TO MEET ME TONIGHT?
I LIKE YOU SO MUCH. - YOUR ELl
No!
Huh?
Let go! Let go!
Thank you.
Oskar...
I have to go.
WHO MURDERED THE MAN
IN THE ICE?
Hello.
- Oskar, are you there?
- Yeah.
It's Martin.
Teacher was wondering
if you're coming to practice tonight.
How come?
Don't know.
He was just wondering.
Maybe he wanted you
to come.
I don't know...
By the way...
I think it was good,
what you did to Conny.
He needed it.
Damn,
he's good at acting!
- You think so?
- Yes.
You coming
to training tonight?
POOL
Hi, Oskar.
Hi.
Hey, Oskar.
Hey.
Now we'll start
water exercises.
Hurry up!
Come on, Oskar!
Vamos, vamos!
Uno, dos, uno dos-
keep going!
What? Damn it!
Call the fire department!
Fire!
Get out of here!
Out!
Do you know who I am?
- Yes.
- Good.
Then you understand.
We're going to have
a little contest now.
You'll stay under water...
for three minutes.
Do that, and it's just
a little scratch.
If you don't...
I'll cut out your eye.
An eye
for an ear, okay?
But... it's impossible.
That's your problem.
Three minutes.
Breathe now!
Five...
four...
three...
two... one.
- Jimmy-
- Shut up!
- Let's get out of here.
- Shut up, I said!