Were they in Korean or English?
Or what? I couldn't tell.
I couldn't tell.
I thought that they
were arguing in Korean.
Can you turn off
the lights in the bathroom?
- Yeah.
Oh God, of all
the times for this to go down.
Do you want to open the windows?
- No.
They're taking
someone through the alley.
It's too dark, I can't see.
It looks like a woman.
Okay look at this.
This must have something to do
with what happened last night.
This is down the block
from my apartment.
More blood.
So this is further up the block.
Look at this.
Something big went down
last night.
Something crazy happened here.
What the fuck
happened last night?
- What do you think?
-Creepy.
It's a coroner.
There you have it.
Murder in Koreatown on my block.
Got a little gruesome pic here
from the crime scene.
Okay so she was 26.
This guy was 31.
I'm gonna see if I can find
any of these neighbors,
see if anybody knew these people.
I just figure...
Maybe this is an interesting
thing I can make a video about.
And what I don't
understand also...
Okay. Lets just see.
Hold on one sec.
Okay. So let's do a little
recap of what happened.
Oops.
So there was a scream
out there in the alley.
And then...
The police took her through
the alley back here.
See right back there
there's the alley.
They took her through
there and then
all the way through
my apartment complex.
Now what's weird is that
her apartment complex is
way down there.
Uh, way down the block.
So I guess the thing
that's so weird to me
is uh what she was doing
so far down in this
part of the alley.
And then also...
Uh... I'm wondering about
the blood that was
down there on the corner
even further away
from the crime scene.
Okay, so I made this little
map here just to
sort of illustrate
just how far away
she was arrested from
her apartment,
the scene of the crime.
And also look at how far away
this blood that I
found on the front street
is away from the
scene of the crime as well.
So we'll be getting to the
bottom of this real soon.
- Here we are at the
scene of the crime.
I'm just gonna hang
out here for a little bit.
And see if anybody uh comes out.
And I'll ask them
If they know anything
about what happened.
So I'll be here.
Well it seems like
everybody's at work
or doing something right now.
So I'll take a little walk
around the neighborhood,
give you guys a tour,
a flavor of the city.
- Fuck you nigga.
- Fuck you.
Fuck you
motherfucking niggers man.
Don't steal again.
- Don't come again!
- Call the
motherfucking police bitch.
- Why you stealing?
- Call the motherfucking police.
Shut the fuck and
call the police.
You know it's not
really going my way today
I think it's a little hot
and everyone's inside or at work.
But I'm gonna come back out
a little bit later or tomorrow
and check back in.
You have a question for me?
- A question for you?
What kind of question
should I be asking you?
- It's your movie, I don't know.
You're the one
that asks the questions.
- Are you gonna try to murder me
like that lady murdered her husband?
Promise? - Only if you're bad.
- Only if I'm bad?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Okay this guy sleeps right here
on the uh...
like in front of
my apartment building.
So he probably saw
what went down.
I'll ask him a little bit later
when he wakes up.
Did you see anything like...
there was a guy out here
he was bloody and stuff
- No.
- You didn't see anything?
Okay, so you don't
know what happened?
- No.
- Okay. Alright. Well thank you.
- Alright.
- Okay.
Okay here we are back again
another day at the
scene of the crime.
You know...
Let's see here...
Maybe I can get in
and check on this place.
Let's see here.
Let's see here
Okay. Well it's locked.
I probably shouldn't
be doing this anyway.
Well I'll just hang out here.
And uh see
If I can find any
of these neighbors
without trespassing.
So you didn't know her?
- No, no actually I just moved
in not too long ago so...
- Oh really?
Yeah so I don't really
know anybody there.
- Okay.
- To be honest, but uh...
- Where'd you move from?
- But yeah, from
Florida actually.
- Oh really?
- Yeah yeah.
- Alright, murder in your new
apartment complex, welcome to LA right?
Yeah right.
- Um.
Okay well do you think that
any of your neighbors
might know anybody
or like know any
information about it?
Like I said, I mean
I just moved in and
I don't really know anybody
- Okay you don't know anybody
- Yeah. To be honest,
the neighbors aren't that friendly
they kinda keep to themselves.
Oh actually there,
I think there is one lady that...
she lives downstairs who
might know something.
She talks a lot,
she's an old lady so...
Okay. Um.
Do you think there's any chance
cause there's a gate over there
um you can see it's locked.
Do you think maybe
I could come...
you could bring me
in there with you?
And uh, I could try to
talk to her a little bit?
Uh, I mean...
I dunno.
That might be a little much.
- It's too much.
- Yeah cause it's
it's kind of a sensitive topic.
- Okay. Uh. Well how about this?
Do you think I could get your number
and maybe you could ask that lady?
- Yeah. Yeah sure.
- I'll give you a ring later?
- Yeah hope it helps.
- Alright. Thanks buh bye.
Okay.
- God bless you.
Thank you. God bless you.
Thank you.
I heard a scream.
Like I said
I can't talk about it right now
- Okay. Um....
Do you think
we could talk later? Or?
- Maybe, I don't know.
Now is not a good time.
- Okay.
- Alright. Okay thank you.
I think I'm going to call it a night.
People really aren't that friendly
they don't want to talk
to me but that's okay, so...
Uh... - You're crazy
- Well I'm not that crazy...
- Yeah.
- Okay but, okay so what do you...
you don't...
You just don't think
it's a big deal?
Or what's your?
- No. I mean I think it's like
I mean obviously it's a really
crazy thing to happen just...
right down the street from us
which is a little...
you know... unsettling.
...A little?
Why was she
so far back in our alley
I guess that's my question.
I mean...
It could be anything.
Like it could just be some...
small piece of evidence that
that she needed to show them
relating to the crime,
I mean who knows?
- She freaked out and ran I guess?
- Yeah like she
could've ran there or
- Well...
- I mean..
- I don't know.
- Well what about the blood...
In the front you know over on uh
Pico and Menlo.
That's like really far away
from their apartment complex.
- It's possible that he got got
stabbed more than once. Right?
And...
It's possible that if you're stabbed
without being life threatening
you're just kinda
bleeding all over the place, right?
- So she stabbed him
over at Pico and Menlo?
And then ran back,
he ran back to the apartment.
- She chased him with a knife.
It could be. Yeah.
Right? I mean.
- Well I don't buy it.
-I don't know. I don't think it's.
I think the case is closed.
I think you're overreacting.
I mean what do you think happened?
- I don't know what happened.
That's why I'm making...
that's why I'm doing this.
Cause I need to know.
- I dunno I think you're gonna
drive yourself crazy
trying to figure this out.
I think you just gotta give it up.
- Well I just,
I'm just getting started. So...
So one thing, I...
Uh...
You might be wondering why
you're not seeing my face.
Uh, but...
I'm a little bit camera shy...
I don't really know
if I want anybody to know
uh...
who's making this project. So...
Here is... the alley.
This is where they
arrested the murderer.
Okay, this is
the back of the apartment
where the body was found.
This is also where
the uh murderer
at some point came though this
uh little back part
down to the alley right here.
Some I'm just gonna hang
out in the alley a little bit
and see if I can't catch
some of these neighbors.
Hey excuse me.
Yes sir? - Uh...
I'm making a little video
about a murder that took place.
Uh....
So you don't really
know that much else
about what happened? Or...
- No I don't.
- Okay.
Alright, well uh...
Do you think your wife
knows anything else, or?
- No.
- Okay.
Alright. Well uh,
Thank you very much
for talking to me.
- Thank you.
- Alright have a good day.
- Okay.
You don't know anything?
Okay, uh...
Do you speak English?
Uh not very much? Poquito?
Okay so you don't know anything
about the murder that...
- No man.
- No nothing?
Okay. Alright.
Okay thank you.... Okay.
- No that's okay.
...No no no, please please.
Please.... No no.
- Okay thank you.
Okay, finally... Excuse me.
Um... I'm doing a little uh
Documentary kind of thing
about a...
a murder that happened
over in uh this
apartment complex
Do you live in
that apartment complex?
- Yeah I do.
- Um...
Do you know
the lady who murdered her husband?
Did you know them?
- It's really sad I mean
she was a sweet lady
I don't know
anything what happened.
Okay you don't know what happened?
- No.
- But she was really nice.
- Okay. Were you there
the night of the murder?
- Yeah I was there. I mean...
I was home.
- Okay. Um...
But do you know why she did it?
- I have no idea.
- You...
- I mean it creeps me out.
- Okay. Yeah. It is pretty weird.
- It's really sad.
I don't want to really
talk about it right now.
Okay. Do you think
it would be possible if
maybe we talked a
little bit later about-
- I doubt it, no.
- No I don't want to talk about it.
- Okay, you don't want to talk about it?
- No.
- Okay. Alright. Well uh...
Thank you very much I appreciate it.
- Thank you. Ciao.
- Okay. Have a nice day. Okay.
Well that weird, uh I had it pulled up.
Okay. Well...
Here, have some... window.
I was looking into
getting the police report.
And it's a no go.
It's not happening.
There's a trial coming up
And basically the only way for me
to get a copy of that is if I had been
a relative of the deceased
or if I was a lawyer
somehow involved in the case. So...
Uh I haven't really
tried to track down
any of these people around uh
this little apartment here.
Near the corner
where I found the blood.
I've just been walking
up and down the block here.
You can kinda see maybe where
they cleaned it up a little bit.
But the rest of the blood is gone.
It's been cleaned up at this point.
So...
I hope you
can hear me over this...
Helicopter.
Eh...
Anyway so at this point...
I haven't found anybody
who knows what the fuck
happened here uh...
I might as well be like the only
person other than the police
who knows anything about
the blood that was over here.
Wow.
- It's a different world
when you wake up early boo.
- Well no, it's not about that.
- I'm kidding.
If you can't tell...
Part...
the reason I'm making this is...
Part of the reason I have
so much time on my hands
is because... uh...
you know I lost my job...
several months back... uh...
You know it's just...
It's tough getting back
into the swing of things and...
and dealing with... the uh...
constant rejection...
The world gets you down you know?
It's beating down on you every day.
And you know...
You know that's why uh...
doing this project
has been sort of like
a breath of fresh air for me because...
you know... its...
given me a little bit of a reason...
to wake up in the morning.
So you used to work with Tae right?
- Yeah. Well,
I knew him as Andy.
- Okay so how do you feel
about his death?
And the... - Its...
It's terrible. Um its...
super tragic...
I... it's the last person
that I would expect
something like that to...
you know, to happen to them.
- Okay. And so did you know
his wife as well?
Or? - Yeah.
Yeah I did. I had um...
I met her a few, a few times.
She was kind of quiet...
but seemed very sweet.
And it seemed like they had
a really good relationship overall.
And so like what happened?
Or why do you think she did it?
I don't know man.
Shit got really weird
right after they moved into
that new place a couple months ago.
- Okay, and how so?
- He... I dunno he just...
would have like weird
sort of expressions on his face.
He seemed like really tired like
he wasn't getting a lot of sleep.
It seemed like,
he didn't say it exactly...
but it seemed like
they were fighting a lot...
which had never happened before.
I know moving can be stressful.
But it was way more than...
than that...
Something was wrong.... Okay.
Uh, that's two people now
that have confirmed...
that the murderer
was a very nice lady.
Something doesn't ring about
the idea of a nice woman...
just, I dunno, snapping,
and killing her husband.
I mean, I guess murders happen but...
something about it
just doesn't add up.
- He was uh...
and someone put a chair for me
because I'm homeless.
And he came by and
graffiti'd it over and over.
And no, I don't know his name.
And I asked him
"what are you writing?"
He wouldn't say.
Then he pretends
he doesn't speak English.
That he only speaks uh...
- I'm the property manger, why?
- Uh well... Actually, uh...
Do you know anything about
the murder that happened here?
- As far as I'm concerned it's over.
- But you don't know about why
there was blood on the
front of the street or why she
was arrested so far back in my alley?
- I have no idea about that.
Look...
You can't keep filming here.
I'm gonna have to call the cops
cause the tenants
keep complaining about you.
- I'm not trying to
be disrespectful I just have
a lot of unanswered questions
about this murder.
- You're not gonna find anything.
- Yeah but...
Okay well...
- Look, you can't film here.
- Well...
- Put down the camera and go home.
I guess it's just...
It took a second
for it to really like
sink in what this means...
But uh... You know...
If I'm banned more or less
from the property...
where the victim was found...
Then this investigation
is like over.
I... you know... it's just...
Maybe I should
give this fucking thing up
and go look for a job.
Maybe it's just not right for me.
Who would've thought
that it would be this hard
to just find one person
who knows something more...
about what happened than
we already know.
You know, the world's not a fair place.
In case you didn't know, okay. So...
You know, just cause...
you know I deserve a
little something from this...
from all the the time
I've been putting into it.
You know, maybe I'm just
the world's worst investigator...
uh, failure at life...
I should just go
jump off a fucking bridge.
How am I supposed to go on
with my life if I don't know about
what she was doing in the alley.
And...
why there was blood on the front
of the street. Okay?
So now I don't really
know what to do
and I just wanted to tell you...
my confidant uh...
in this project...
So I just...
- I'm sorry. I mean...
Maybe it's just time to give it up.
Well, what about the
blood on the street,
you know I still have a lot
of unanswered questions.
I feel like it's not...
going anywhere.
And I feel like those things
are just...
random coincidences...
- Yeah we've it been over before.
I mean, I know you've been hating
on this project since the beginning.
It's okay, you can admit it.
I don't care.
- I just feel like it's not,
there's not point.
And I just think that
you're wasting your time.
-Ugh. Okay.
Well, maybe I'll just
sleep on it.
And maybe tomorrow
I'll just give it up and start
looking for a job.
- Is it good luck,
or is it bad luck?
-I hope it's good luck.
I just had the weirdest dream.
It was his face.
Right in front of me.
It was like staring at this picture.
And...
There was all this writing
that was in Korean.
And...
I have no idea what it said...
But it was like...
One of the most
weird dreams I've ever had.
And...
I just don't know
what to make of it.
- The bible says
hell is the whole salvation.
Hell is the accepted path.
Jesus Christ. Son of God.
- What you do with Jesus.
The call of God is to repent,
turn around.
Repent, turn around.
Believe in the lord Jesus Christ
follow righteousness and holiness
and you can escape the damnation of hell.
If this hasn't already been
a weird enough morning...
Look at this...
I just passed this.
And I need to get a shot of it.
Okay... Look at this.
Now this is going to
sound totally crazy but...
I feel like this message
is written for me because it's...
basically identical to
what I saw in my dream last night
and I would love to know
what the fuck this says....
because I am freaking out
right now.
There's no way it's just
a coincidence that I
stumble upon this writing that...
came to me in a dream.
And now it mentions
the pastor story.
And I happen to see...
A street preacher pastor kind of guy...
And... Okay...
This is already weird enough right?
It gets way crazier.
Okay. I've seen...
this guy...
maybe it was one of his friends,
I've seen him before.
Now look at this.
I took this video
the morning of the murder.
Maybe it's not the same guy.
But they're obviously...
you know... coordinated.
So what the fuck is happening here?
- So here's my question.
Can you get one of your friends from work
to help translate this for me?
Please?
- You have to
give this up, it's, this is insane.
- Just get her to come...
- I thought you
were done with this already.
- Well, I
said I would sleep on it
and I slept on it and a bunch
of other shit has happened.
So, now I'm not done with it
until I get this translated
and then maybe I'll be done with it,
or I will be done with it.
I promise, okay, just ask.
All you have to do is ask her.
It's gonna be great.
Okay so while I've got this downtime
waiting for our translator this weekend,
if I was gonna prioritize
what I need to be doing,
looking for somebody who
knows about the blood
that was on the front street
is the most important part
of my investigation.
So, I'm just gonna, I'm gonna stake it out
and I'm gonna find
somebody and that's that.
- Some... some... blood on his
hand, for sure, I saw that.
- Okay.
- He was like leaning
over kinda holding his side and...
I saw that. And I was like,
"Does this guy need any help?"
"Should I be concerned?"
I kind of approached him
and he just ran off.
He didn't want any help.
It was weird, man.
- Well... Which way did he run?
- He ran back that way.
- Okay, well.
- You all right though?
You doing all right, man?
- No no no I'm
- Look, okay,
here's what I don't understand...
Cause he was murdered down there
and he came, he ran this way?
- He did, but uh...
- Well, what did he look like?
Tell me what the guy looked like.
- Well he was an older, he was an older,
older, older like Asian guy,
probably like 5'6" or
whatever, but I'm not sure why....
No no he was...
- Why you're asking all that.
- No, he was younger.
He was a young tall guy and he,
are you sure you got a good look at him?
- 100% man, but you kind of, you know,
you're kind of scaring me a little bit.
You're looking kind of,
kind of nervous, man.
- No, no, no. Just...
- Hey, bro, see, I'm
trying to help you out
but you're kind of,
you're coming on a little strong.
You want me to call somebody?
- Dude I'm doing fine.
- You want me to call
somebody for you right now?
Okay you know what?
You don't know what you're talking about
You're full of shit, okay, all right.
So, as you can see I've been
busy trying to work through
all the details and I'm just wondering,
is it possible that I was
wrong about this third person?
Could there have been a
third person involved?
I guess that would really answer
a lot of the questions I have here.
I was just searching the
Internet for this case
and Mi-Sun Yoo, who is accused
of murdering her husband,
she claimed, she said to
the police that there was
a third person there that
broke into their apartment
and committed this murder.
So, I think now it's almost certain
that there was a third
person involved in this.
This guy, the apartment
manager, was so defensive.
He definitely fits the description,
short Asian guy, older.
So, you know, maybe this is like
the big break in the case
that I've been looking for.
Okay, I'm just, I'm keeping my distance.
So, I'm not technically near the property
but I'm gonna stake this
place out for a little bit
and see if I can find
this apartment manager.
Okay well, I'm just going
back to my apartment now.
It's a waste of time at this point.
I'm gonna come back a little bit later
in the afternoon and try to catch him
when he's coming home from work.
Okay so, I just heard back from
this guy with some bad news.
The old lady at his apartment complex,
I won't be meeting with her
because I've already met her.
Voila, this is the "old
lady" who's probably like 40.
And then the other bad news is that
this apartment manager guy,
he's been confirmed now
that he was out of town on
the night of the murder,
so that's double dose of dead ends
and that's how my day is going.
Look at this weird light, so anyway.
Hello?
Weird vibe today.
So, I don't even know really
what I'm gonna do now.
And I don't want to put all
of my eggs in one basket
but I really have a feeling.
And it's hard for me to explain really,
but I have a feeling like this graffiti
is possibly the missing
link and maybe there's
a piece of evidence in there that's really
gonna point me in the right direction.
So, we got the translator coming tomorrow
and I can't wait to see what she says.
I totally spaced that I had
seen this graffiti before.
On the couch, there's
the lady with the couch,
the homeless lady.
Look at this, like this
weird Jesus fish thing.
So, I think this is the same guy
and we'll try to get
this translated as well.
So, she didn't tell you about the murder
or anything like that? Or...?
- No.
- Okay so,
actually it happened to be
at this apartment complex right here.
And there's all these like, sort of like
weird inconsistencies
about like what happened with it.
So, I found this graffiti up here that I,
and there have been these
street preacher kinda guys,
and I uh, I don't know.
I just feel like it all is, you know,
like working together in some way.
You know?
- Okay.
Oh, no,
it used to be right there.
This is, oh shit.
Anyway, I think there's another one
that's like just down the block.
You're okay if we go check that one out?
- Um. Yeah.
- Okay cool, all right, oh, man.
I'm sorry about that.
We walked all the way
over here and it's gone.
Well, it used to be
right there and there was
a homeless lady that
used to live here, too.
And I don't know, hey,
you didn't see any,
there used to be a couch right here
with some like graffiti on it.
- What is it?
- A couch.
- A couch?
And a homeless lady
that used to live here.
- Yeah there used to be a
couch over here, what happened?
- I don't know what happened to it.
- You looking for the couch
or you're looking for the lady?
- Both actually.
Well, we've got her here.
She was gonna translate what
was written on the couch.
Okay, it's been gone?
- The lady comes at night time.
You find her at night time.
- Okay alright.
- In the day time,
I don't know where she at.
- Okay, all, right, well thank you.
Anyway, so yeah, this whole month or so
has been pretty crazy
because I've been looking
into what's been going
on with this murder and uh...
Okay, hold on, oh shit.
Okay, wait, there we go, all right.
Um...
Let's see.
- Well, he's talking
about a Korean pastor.
He's saying let's try to avoid him.
- Avoid who though, the pastor?
- Yeah, I guess he's
just telling everybody
to avoid the pastor as much as possible.
I mean, he seems kind of not all there,
like he's not making any sense.
- Okay, there was
another one right down here.
It's gone of course.
Let me just...
Okay well...
Okay sorry.
I just thought that it
might still be still under there,
but it's not.
I have video of that other one.
Do you think maybe we
could just go, oh sorry.
Do you think that maybe
we could just go
back to the apartment
and you can translate
maybe from the video?
Or, would that be okay?
There was another one. - Yeah.
- Okay, it's fine?
Okay, yeah, let's go back, we'll go back
and we'll just, yeah, we'll
translate from the video.
And I just, I wonder if it was here.
Hold on one second.
It's so thick, it could
be on any of these.
Okay, well, pardon the mess.
Okay, we'll go back to the
apartment and we'll just,
we'll go back to the apartment.
Okay, all right, let's just
go back to the apartment.
She's not that happy that I'm
still working on this but...
Sorry it's taking so long.
Okay, this is the one, this is the couch
the homeless lady had right next to her.
So, what's, what in the hell does it say?
- Bungeoppang,
bungeoppang is a old Korean dessert.
So, she wrote,
she drew a little fish.
It's a dessert that looks
like the shape of a fish.
- Well, okay,
hold on, there's another.
There's another, it's the pastor's story.
- Okay, this is insane.
The guy is talking about
the same pastor again,
but this time it seems like
he's mentioning other names
and they're saying that they're bad men.
He's saying that the pastors are bad men.
And he kind of just rambles on like
none of it makes sense.
I think he's, I want to
say he's not all there.
He might be mentally ill.
I'm pretty sure he's homeless.
- It's gotta
have something to do with what...
with what I'm working on.
You think?
- How?
- It's, it's, it's
not just a coincidence.
This all has, it's all
coming to a head somehow.
I just have to figure out how.
- I think you're reaching
and I don't think has...
- Okay, well,
you don't believe me then...
that's two.
One, two, I guess we're done.
You can go now,
I'll go in the bedroom.
My fucking girlfriend is gonna kill me,
but I feel like, like I have
to come back out tonight.
I'm telling you, I have
a feeling that tonight
I'm supposed to go out
here and find...
the lady with the couch or
find the guy who wrote the graffiti
or find something at
one of these key spots.
And I know it's gonna happen.
So...
Back here at the scene of the crime.
Back here where the blood was.
No couch, no lady.
I seen her fucking every day probably
for the past five years
and then out of nowhere
just the day that I need to find her
she's disappeared off the
fucking face of the Earth.
If I could just find the guy
who wrote this fucking graffiti
then I could sleep well tonight.
But it looks like
it's just not happening.
Back here in the alley
where she was arrested.
It's the last stop of the night.
Okay, look, I don't like
to be sneaking around
doing things behind my girlfriend's back
but basically I just
lied to her and told her
that I was giving up my investigation
and... I'm not.
Because there's something
else that's at play here.
I'm gonna make a big video tomorrow.
Sort of uh, explain something.
I just... I had the dream again.
I've taken some time
to collect my thoughts
and I wanted to make a video
to come clean about something
which might shed light
on my behavior lately.
I want to explain an aspect
of this investigation
that I haven't shared yet.
You didn't do it to play a trick on me?
- Why would I do that?
- You promise?
- Of course, I
wouldn't even think of that.
Pay for it, Bobby ain't bothering me.
You got it all coming on you.
- It's as if something
has been trying to communicate with me
and it's been giving me
a very distinct feeling
that I've only had once before in my life
when I was a child and my
mother died unexpectedly.
I woke up in the middle of the night
and I knew the moment that she passed.
I can't explain how but I felt it.
And it's the same feeling
that I've been having lately.
And it's part of the reason
I've been so persistent
in my investigation.
I haven't felt the same
since I first dreamt you,
Tae Kyung Sung.
I don't even know how
to say your name right
but I feel such a deep connection to you.
So, if it's you that's trying
to communicate with me,
I choose to communicate
back that I'm here to help.
But as I'm reaching a dead end,
I ask for your help in return,
for your blessing to continue
and for something that points
me in the right direction
so I can bring closure for us both.
Hey. - Hi, how are you?
- Good, do
you mind if I film this?
- No, go ahead.
- I've been
doing an investigation into a murder.
And it's possible that this guy who was
murdered is trying to communicate me,
with me from the, from beyond the grave,
and I just came for a
reading, or for your help
if you're able to... - Okay.
My reading is $20.
- Okay, here's the twenty bucks.
So, you're a real psychic?
- Yes, I am.
- Okay.
- I've been reading for 40 years.
- Okay, so, can you
- Let's see what my cards tell me.
- Okay.
- You know, what
I would advise you is,
because this person is
trying to contact you
from the other side...
- So he is?
- Is making you feel discomfortable.
Sometimes people's minds,
okay, work differently,
because maybe sometime in your past
or sometime in your childhood,
maybe you lost somebody,
or wanted to be with somebody
or was trying to contact somebody
and you couldn't and
maybe what you feel is that,
that is confusing you and troubling you.
And maybe you should just let it go
and not pursue it further
because it might cause you
more drama and make you
feel more discomfortable
in the future.
- Well, look,
I just, I have to know
what the answer to the inconsistencies
about this investigation are.
Do you know about this
stuff, like, what's?
- Well, you know son,
psychics feel
and sometimes know a lot of things.
Okay?
But sometimes to pursue everything in life
is not always the best thing.
- Well, what
does he want though?
- There's no telling
what this person wants.
- Is there anything I can do
to figure that out?
Or anything you can do?
- Well, you know, son,
there are a lot of things
that a person could do,
but I would suggest to you
just to leave it alone.
Just leave it alone.
Just try to be strong and positive
and don't listen to anybody or any voices
that tell you to pursue this.
- How do I get him to stop
if I'm not supposed to go on with this?
- You know, son, let me tell you.
Sometimes the signs that you
see are not put there for you.
Maybe you just think that
they're there for you
and the signs are telling
you this, but they're not.
I'm suggesting to you,
give it up, leave it alone.
- Okay well I-
- Don't pursue it.
- Okay, I'm gonna go.
Maybe she's just right.
You know...
What's fucked up is she clearly knew
about my mother dying when I was a kid
and that connection that I felt.
That this is the same thing
I'm feeling right now.
I'm just, why can't I, what's
wrong with me finding out
what's happening around here?
I mean, I just want to
know what's going on. Okay?
Okay now look at this. Okay?
How am I supposed to ignore this?
Okay?
This is clearly written for me.
I know that the pastor
and the pastors are bad. Okay?
I know that the pastors are bad men
and I'm supposed to avoid them.
I understand the warning, but why?
I feel like the reason
that this message is here
is maybe to get me to come
back to the scaffolding
and find the person
who wrote the graffiti.
I'm coming back tonight.
I'm gonna stake it out
and we're gonna settle this
once and for all.
This graffiti from earlier,
somebody's ripped it down.
Is this supposed to
be another sign for me?
I'm telling you, I have
a feeling that tonight
I'm supposed to find this guy.
I'm supposed to meet him here.
Uh. It's happening tonight,
it's happening tonight.
I think this guy has taken
the night off tonight. So...
Well, if it's not gonna be the guy who
wrote the graffiti then it's gonna be...
you know, the person whose blood was
out on the side of the street
or it's gonna be the lady with the couch
who's come back from the dead.
Again, the blood.
I know I'm not even
supposed to be here but
the scene of the crime again.
Still no couch, still no lady.
I'll go to each and every place
that I can possibly find anybody tonight
and I'm just gonna keep
on going back and forth
to these spots until I find the person
that I'm supposed to meet. Okay?
Back here in the alley
where she was arrested.
You probably can't hear me over these
fucking helicopters either.
Jesus fucking Christ, go away.
Am I supposed to meet you here?
- Am I supposed
to meet you here?
- I don't know, you tell me.
- Do you know anything
about what happened with the murder?
- Do you know anything about
what happened with the murder?
- You're just gonna repeat
everything that I say to you?
- Yeah.
- I think I'm
supposed to be here with you.
- Time out, are you making a movie?
I've been to 'Nam,
cut me a break.
Jesus Christ, it was a murder?
- It was a murder.
A woman murdered her husband.
- Oh, man, what the fuck is going on?
What town is this by the way?
- This is Koreatown.
- Oh, Koreatown, no wonder.
Jesus Christ.
A lot of murders happen in
Koreatown that people
don't even know about.
- You were here in this alley
the night of the murder?
- Hey, buddy, I don't know.
I must have been if that
was the purple flash
was the murder weapon fire discharging.
If it was, I don't know for sure.
I didn't hear a sound,
but I saw the light.
But it was purple in color
and it was up that way,
up into the sky from inside
that garage over there.
- And it has
to do with the murder?
- I guess, if that's what
you're investigating.
But I saw three figures inside the garage
during the flash.
I got keen eyes.
I've been to 'Nam.
So listen, buddy, I'm
telling you the truth.
Do you doubt my word?
- No.
- Okay, that's important news.
Since Cambodia, it's called
the People's Outdoor Court.
It's as good as in the court of law.
- Where did it
come from, which garage?
- The one back there, one
of the, how many of them are?
- Will you point it out?
Will you point it to me?
- Four or five, that one over there.
- I can't see anything.
Which one was it?
- One of them.
I don't know which one it was.
- His name was Tae Kyung Sung.
- Oh, I know
that guy, Tae Kyung Sung.
I know him personally from overseas.
- How'd you meet him?
- No, he was one of our group.
- I believe
that the spirit of the man who was killed
has been communicating with me
from the other side
- Okay.
- And leading me toward,
The... whatever he wants me to see...
- The other side of the poetic wall
- Yes, that's true,
probably true.
Lots of ghosts are like this.
They don't even realize they're dead.
They don't even know they're dead!
- Do you think that
we've met here for a reason?
- I think more than one reason.
I think we're meant to be here together
to solve this problem.
Do you think I'm going
on the right direction here?
- The right direction
with your investigation?
- Yeah.
- Oh yeah, I
think you're right on target,
locked on, ready to fire, as
they say in the Air Force.
Push the red button and you got them.
- Anything else?
- It's all coming down on you, buddy.
- What's coming down on me?
- Well, I
heard somebody say that today.
That's the only reason I mentioned it.
It's almost over.
I'm an expert witness.
I've been a witness before,
especially in Cambodia
where we did people's court.
In the evening, just before supper.
- I can't
overstate the significance
of last night and there's
a lot that went down
and a lot to decompress.
All of my suspicions have been confirmed,
that something else has happened
and there's weird shit going
on in this neighborhood.
You know, I feel validated right
now in this pursuit,
like this stuff really has
been happening for a reason,
like I've been chosen for something.
Something went down in this alley.
Something big went down in this alley.
I'm gonna find out what it was.
The reason that she was
arrested so far back here
in the alley is because her garage,
this must be her garage up here.
I'm just gonna...
This is sketchy as fuck,
okay well, something,
something went down in this garage
and I'm almost positive
this is her garage.
I have to come back tonight
and see what's in there.
I have to know.
Can I do that?
Am I gonna get in trouble?
I'm almost positive,
this has been triangulated
that there was a third person here
with the blood and whoever it was,
was in the garage with the
murder victim and the murderer.
Who was this third person?
I have to do this before
my girlfriend gets home.
It's not even dark out yet, I don't...
Let me get, hold on, I have
to turn this flash off.
It's too bright, okay.
Oh shit.
Okay, there's people up there.
This is too sketchy.
I...
There's no way I'm
breaking into this garage tonight.
I'm done filming for the night.
My girlfriend will be home any minute.
I need to go in the garage
But I'm gonna do through
the proper channel.
So, I put in a search with the city
for the property owner's information.
So, I can just contact the
landlord of this place.
It will be a couple days
so I asked this guy, Jack,
maybe he can give me
the information faster.
And if not, there's one other
thing that I really need
to get done right now,
which is I just realized,
so this guy, the guy from the alley,
I talked to him for hours
and I forgot to ask him
one of the most important questions
which is if he knows
anything about the pastors.
And it's really weird
it just kinda like slipped my mind.
And I'm almost sure that he
lives in one of the alleys
adjacent to this, to my alley.
So, I'm gonna go find this guy
and ask him a couple more questions.
I don't know where he goes when it rains.
Yes.
- It is?
- Yeah.
- How's it going, my friend?
- Is it still raining?
- No, it stopped raining.
- Yeah, I remember now,
you were talking to me
about your girlfriend being
murdered or something like that.
- Well, it was
about my neighbor's murder...
- Oh man, it's a wicked
town, man, it happens.
- Well, so but, I just,
there are two things so...
Well, first of all, you really saw
the three people in the garage?
- I told you the truth
about what I witnessed, sir.
- Okay, so you weren't just
liquored up or something?
- No, I'm...
- You really saw it?
- I was wide awake. I saw what
I saw and I told you what I saw.
- Okay, well,
do you know anything
about the pastors? By the
way, that's the reason...
- Pastors, I never met a pastor.
I haven't met a pastor.
- Okay, so you
don't know anything about that?
- I've met preachers but
I haven't met a pastor.
- - It's a little bit...
- Nobody with a official hat on.
- Okay, it's too crazy for me
to really tell you about
if you don't know already.
- I just don't know about it.
- I just had
a repeat of the same dream
and this time, this is
gonna sound so weird,
he reached out and he grabbed my arm.
And now, look at this.
You see that?
It looks like a burn or something.
Okay, this is new.
I am getting a really weird vibe today
and I don't like it.
You know, this is making me nervous.
I feel like these guys
are following me around
and I already know that they're bad men
and to avoid them, so I'm
just gonna turn around
and walk the other way.
I just have this very weird
paranoid feeling right now
like something is out to get me.
See, they are, they're
following me around. Okay?
I almost wanna just go up to the guy,
ask him what the fuck he wants from me.
I just want to know who they are,
what they want from me
and what they have to
do with the murder.
You see this from earlier?
You see this reflection?
It's like the next level
of weird shit going on.
Look at this.
They all look at me at the same time.
Okay, one more time.
What the fuck?
Great so now we got chicken sacrifices.
Just a beautiful day in the neighborhood
where people have been
sacrificing chickens apparently.
Everything is fine in
Koreatown right now.
Everything is peachy keen.
This is horrible, oh my God.
The guy who I interviewed...
uh the actor who just
moved here from Florida...
he killed himself.
Does this look like the kind
of guy who kills himself?
I feel horrible.
I feel like this is my fault.
Burn update.
It's not getting any better.
This I don't like at all.
I just want to fucking...
one second.
So, the landlord
of their apartment building
lives in the building behind
me, this building right here
which he also owns.
And he has a store in Koreatown as well.
And I'm gonna go there right
now and ask him some questions.
What the fuck is this place?
- Hello?
- Hi.
- Yeah, are you the landlord
of 1100 Menlo Avenue?
- Yes.
- Yeah, I have
some questions because
I'm doing an investigation into the murder
that happened at your apartment complex
and the suicide that just
occurred a couple days ago.
- Excuse me, what this?
- Uh, it's a...
- What's that camera?
- Okay look.
I'm not filming you.
There's something fucking weird
going on in your apartment complex
and I have information to believe
that it all is centered in a garage.
Do I have your permission
to enter the garage?
- Please.
- Okay, do I have your
permission to enter the garage?
- No, no, please, please leave.
- Why not?
Why can't I enter the garage?
- Because I know nothing about that issues.
- Okay, well
you don't think it's weird
that people have been dying
at your apartment complex?
- I'm asking you to put the camera down.
- Okay, I'm putting it down
but why can't I go into the garage?
Give me a clear answer.
- I don't know,
just, I don't like to...
I don't like you to be involved
in this anymore.
- But why don't you
want me to be involved in it?
I just have to know the truth.
Okay?
Just tell me, where were you
on the night of the murder? Okay?
You fit the description of this third man
who was in the garage with the
murder victim and his wife.
- Okay, I need to call up the police.
- Okay, well, call the police
and bring them here and then
we're gonna go to the garage
and we're gonna find whatever
evidence is in there.
- You're bothering my business.
Okay?
- Yeah, there's nobody in here
except for her and who the fuck
is that fuck is that, by the way? Huh?
- Please, I am asking you to leave.
- Okay...
- Please leave.
This guy is one of them,
this guy is one of them.
He is one of them, he is one of them.
- Are you one of the pastors?
- Get out. Get out.
Where were you on the night of the murder?
- I'm asking you to get
out, okay, just get out.
- This guy
is one of the pastors!
It's a cult or something, it's
a cult, it's a cult!
Fuck.
I know he's hiding
something in the garage.
I know he was there on
the night of the murder.
This guy might as well be
the fucking ring leader
of this organization or
whatever the fuck it is.
This is what I'm worried about.
Okay?
It's possible that I've
been misinterpreting
this whole thing and
the man who was killed,
that he has been warning
me this whole time
and either the guy who
was murdered wants me
to go to the garage and
find out what's in there
and expose the truth so
that way no one else is hurt
or it's like I'm being lured into a trap.
Okay?
It's the middle of the night.
I don't want to wake up my girlfriend but,
that's gotta be the
landlord's apartment building.
Something really fucking crazy
is going on in this neighborhood.
I think that I've figured
out a pattern here
and it's not good and it
all has to do with how
I found out about this.
Okay, so, I had the dream.
I saw the graffiti.
I saw the pastor and the lady
with the couch went missing.
Okay, let's fast forward
a couple days ago.
I had the dream with the burn.
I saw this Satanic graffiti.
I saw the pastor and
this guy kills himself.
Okay?
It's the time in the middle that is
a little bit off with this pattern.
I don't know if anybody died that night,
but I had the dream, I saw the graffiti,
and who did I see that night?
Who told me about the purple light?
And who led me toward
investigating the garage?
Okay?
Do you get where I'm going here?
I have to know.
Hey,
Now I'm gonna ask you a question
and I want a truthful answer from you.
Are you one of the pastors?
- Yes.
- Leave me alone.
- I will.
- Don't talk to me anymore.
I don't want to see you in my alley.
I should have known from the beginning
and I am just way in
over my head right now
and I am just fucked is what I am.
I don't even know what I'm gonna do now.
I feel like there are two factions
fighting for control over my mind.
And this investigation
has to end right now.
This is my last video.
I don't give a fuck what's in the garage.
I'm never going back to that alley again.
Thanks for watching.
I can't sleep.
I just... need to stand here
and watch over her.
I feel like if I don't
then something horrible
is gonna happen.
Like they're going to
come get her or something.
I'm spending some quality time
with her this weekend.
And I'm going
to ignore this investigation.
And unless
Tae Kyung Sung shows me
a true proper sign
then this investigation is still over.
My relationship is in shambles.
My life is in shambles.
And I need this to end.
I'm done.
Hold on a sec.
Holy shit.
What's wrong with you?
- No look we
have to go right now okay?
Why? I'm waiting for my food.
Wait why? - We're not safe here.
- What's wrong with you?
- Okay fine I'll meet you out front.
I haven't really
finished my investigation.
Wait, no no no. Just stop,
I haven't been
completely honest with you.
And I have to show you I haven't...
- No. Stop.
Just stop filming.
Stop filming this.
Somebody else has to see this
because I'm not...
No, you do care. Okay?
Because it has to do with our safety.
And what I've seen tonight
with one of the pastors...
- No. Stop filming me...
- Means that something bad
Is gonna happen tonight...
- No. Stop...
And I'm the only one
who can stop it.
Okay?
- No. Stop filming. Stop filming me.
- The spirit of
the guy who was murdered
has been communicating with me
and his presence
is here right now and I can feel it.
Okay?
And I have been chosen
to stop whatever bad
is supposed to happen tonight
from happening. Okay? Do you...
No. No, just, you've gone insane.
He's here.
Tae Kyung Sung.
If this is you
and you're trying
to communicate with me
show me a sign.
Whoa.
Are you seeing this?
Do you believe me now?
Do you want me
to go to the garage?
Is there a piece of evidence
there for me to find?
I have to break in there...
- Please don't go.
I have to go.
Hey buddy...
Come on over. Hey everybody
check it out man,
I'm talking to the rats.
Don't worry I can hear you.
You're sloshing your feet too.
Must be wet up there.
Hey buddy down here.
Why don't you come down
here and join us?
Stay out of trouble for a while,
warm your cockles.
Look buddy I got some
really good news for you.
You're this close to
nabbing the crook.
Hey I know what,
let's talk a walk upstream a bit.
Look there goes a couple of rats.
Hi Suzie...
Anyway uh yeah,
let's walk up the shelf a little bit.
Hobo's hit your row.
Why don't you break into
that garage over there?
You might find something
that'll help you.
It's the perfect
time, it's raining.
They'll never know.
They won't even
see fingerprints if it's raining.
Go to the garage.
Break the lock. Open the door.
Go inside.
Make sure you collect
the evidence you need
and then get out of there.
And then it's sealed.
For your humanity's sake...
Do it. Do what we recommend.
We don't mean
to tell you what to do
like a 'straw boss'.
But please, take our advice.
It's King Kong crying
over your dead soul if you don't do it.
I'm going to pass out.
Okay I just woke up and I have
a huge fucking problem which is that
And I don't know
where my girlfriend is.
I don't remember exactly
what happened last night but...
I think that she's mad at me at she's...
left.
Something fucking bad happened...
Something really bad fucking
happened and I don't know what to do.
It's just really not like her
and she won't answer my calls and...
I don't know
what the fuck happened last night.
All I know is...
I heard that wretched voice
coming from the sewer.
Where is she?
Are you down there still?
Hello?
- Hey it's Jen,
leave a message or send me a text. Bye.
I feel like I saw
the landlord in the garage
and he assaulted me.
So as soon as it stops raining
I'm gonna go pay this guy a fucking visit.
Look at this...
Do you see this crack...
Hold on let me turn on the light here.
Do you see this in my ceiling?
This crack in my ceiling!?
This doesn't make any sense. Okay.
At 10:08 is when I
recorded the video
of my encounter with the
landlord in there.
And then at 11:09 I left the garage,
I ran out of the garage...
What the fuck happened to
me in there for an hour?
Okay? What did he do to me?
Hello?
Uh who are you?
I'm John. - Uh yeah
I'm looking for the landlord who
I saw last night in the garage
before my fucking girlfriend
went missing!
- Last night happened something very bad.
- Uh yeah well where's the landlord?
He's... he's dead. - How?
-I don't know, maybe a suicide.
- He's not in here?
- No, he's not here now.
Do you know what's going
on in this neighborhood
with the pastors or any
of this other bullshit?
- I don't know.
It's okay?
- No it's not okay. Okay?
He's really dead?
- Yeah he's really dead.
The feeling I had with him is gone.
And all I feel now...
is nothing.
- Hello?
- Can I help you?
- Yeah my name is Sam,
I'm a friend of Jen's. I just wanna...
come in and talk to you for a second.
- Do you know where she is?
- I don't that's why I want to talk.
- Uh...
How do you know her?
- I'm a family friend.
- Look if you don't
know where she is
then there's nothing
you can do to help.
- Open the door please.
Her fucking family thinks
I've done something to her.
I haven't done anything to her.
I don't know what happened okay?
I don't know where she is.
What the fuck am I going to do?
- Fuck.
He's coming upstairs.
Okay. Here we are going to file
a missing persons report for my girlfriend
at the request of the police.
Well the police
think that I'm crazy.
Uh yes, there's some weird
supernatural occurrences going on
and my fucking girlfriend
has gone missing.
What do you think the first
thing that comes out of their mouth is?
Well where were you?
What were you doing?
Surely there's gotta be somebody in this
town who can help me with this problem
somebody who knows something
more about the pastors
somebody who can
help me find my girlfriend.
- Stay away. Stay away.
- Just, I can't give you a reading
there's nothing I can do!
I can't sleep.
I'm going right now
to try to find the guy from the alley
and when I find him,
I'm going to do this to him
I'm gonna go
smash his fucking face in.
Okay great now
this guy has gone missing too.
The guy from the alley
is now officially missing
because this is
where he used to live
before he started
talking to me from the sewer
Now look at this. Okay this alley
is blocked off by a bunch of rubbage.
How is this possible?
- Hallelujah!
Holy shit.
Hey!
- I don't know what to do.
I almost forgot she was gone.
The police are out to get me.
Like what the fuck do you do
when the police are out to get you?
They're searching my garage.
She's not in there, I already checked.
I know she's not fucking in there.
The next logical conclusion
they're going to come fucking arrest me.
I'm so fucked here.
Holy shit I'm fucked.
The only thing I can do is try
to find the guy from the alley again.
He's the only person who
knows anything about what's going on here.
If I can't find the guy from the alley,
I'm going back to my apartment
and I'm going to go hang myself
before the police arrest me.
- I hear you coming.
- Hello?
Come on buddy get over here.
- How do I get to the other side?
What do you want from me?
- I don't want anything from you, not me.
- Well who does?
- You got any beans? Refried beans?
- How do I get my girlfriend back?
- How about a tank of propane?
- You might have to wait another lifetime.
- How do I get her back?
- Get her back?
You can't bring back the dead.
Are you some kind of saint?
- Who says she's dead?
- I didn't say so...
- I didn't do anything to her
- Any of you rats so so?
We didn't say so.
We ain't accusing you of nothing.
We're the people's court.
We're fair and just.
- How did you get down there?
- We're not...
You're accused
of murdering someone though.
Or so we hear...
- How did you get down there?
- I come down a secret passage.
My own passage.
Everyone has their own
separate rabbit hole you know.
- How did you get
into the sewer the other night?
- Well you're here now. How did
you get down? Through the manhole?
Did you do something to her?
- I didn't do anything to her.
- Do you know about what happened to her?
- I've been down here for months.
- What is happening?
- I'm just withering down here.
- What happened to me in the garage?
- What happened to you in the garage?
- When I went to the garage.
- Oh...
- I saw a glow
that lasted for a minute.
A purple glow coming from the window.
So maybe you killed
her maybe you didn't.
Maybe you killed her in
an absent minded state.
- I didn't kill anybody, I'm innocent.
- Well that's what you remember...
Maybe you did it
in an absent minded state.
I think you did it though.
I think you did it.
Cause you were in that place
and anyone who...
Even an innocent person is guilty
once they're in there
of killing someone
close to themselves.
There's a long history of that place,
that particular garage is haunted somehow
it's cursed even,
that people who go in there commit murder.
They could give you time
they could give you life
if they really wanted to.
You stay here we'll give you free life.
You wanna stay?
Stay outta trouble?
Stay with us.
- You're guilty bud.
You're guilty as charged.
Unless you present evidence
to the contrary.
- I didn't do anything
what are you talking about?
What do you want from me?
- Just do
what we recommend, we're doctors.
Doctor's recommendation:
go to the garage...
and find the evidence you need.
This garage is haunted!
It's run by the pastors!
It's a portal to hell!
People are talking to me
from the sewers!
There's a portal to hell
in my neighbor's garage!
It's cursed, run by the pastors!
They talk to me from the sewers!
My girlfriend's gone missing!
My neighbor's garage is cursed!
There's a portal to hell inside!
It's run by the pastors!
They talk to me from the sewers!
Now my girlfriend's gone missing!
I didn't kill her!
What do you want from me?
It has become clear
that I have traveled
to a new distant world.
And I am rapidly approaching the end
of my investigation into
into the murder of
Tae Kyung Sung.
There is no one left to help me.
And it's only a matter of time
before the police arrest me.
My only recourse is to present
the evidence as clearly as possible.
This will be my last video.
When I'm finished,
I will ship the footage to a friend
along with my notes.
Because if this information
doesn't get out...
More people will go missing...
And more people will die.
I have discovered
a series of pictures on my phone
which I do not remember taking.
Pictures that helped me crack the case.
At the end of this recording
I will share them.
But first...
I'll take one last walk
to those familiar places.
Back to their apartment
where Tae Kyung Sung's body was found.
The man who communicated with me
from another world...
maybe the one I'm in now.
You touched me and I felt you.
But I'm afraid I
felt something that wasn't true.
I'm now confident that
his only communications were warnings.
Like the burn on my arm
Where he reached out...
with whatever last bit of energy
he had left in his former world.
In a last ditch effort to save me.
And everything I felt after that
like the wind blowing in bathroom
the night I was
lured into the garage
wasn't coming from him at all
it was coming from the pastors
or maybe the garage itself.
Back to the scaffolding
where I found the graffiti.
Where I was surprised to
learn that all those messages
were most likely written by the landlord
even after he was dead.
Which seems impossible
but not here.
He prayed on my curiosity
Knowing that I would take the bait
his shiny shoes gave him away.
I believe he brought the shopkeeper
and the shopkeepers mother
from Africa to be sacrificed next.
I want to believe that I saved them.
Back to where I found
the blood on the front of the street.
The landlord's blood.
Also known as the mysterious 3rd man.
Who after a skirmish
with Tae Sung and his wife
in their apartment
Stopped to check on his wound
spewed his blood
then ran home.
Back to the alley where she was arrested.
Where the pastor
spoke to me from the sewer.
Where she ran after
realizing what had happened.
And finally...
Back to the garage.
Where there exists some sort
of evil entity
or portal to hell or new dimension
where your worst fears come true.
Speculating about
it is pointless.
It is impossible to understand because
it is an illogical hateful place.
But I am certain that
there are more of these places.
And more pastors who tend to them
as part of a supernatural cult.
To enter alone is not enough.
I believe a pastor must be present
for the ritual or whatever it is,
to occur.
The landlord served this function
on the night of
Tae Kyung Sung's murder
But the couple fought back
because they were strong...
much stronger than me.
But not strong enough
to fend off the pastor's spell
which caused Misun Yoo
to stab her husband.
Apparently in an absent minded state.
But not without
stabbing the landlord first.
So now I'll take one last trip
back to those familiar places.
Back to where his body as found.
Back to where I found the blood
on the front street.
Back to the alley where she was arrested.
And back to the garage.
Armed with new regretful knowledge.
The evidence that
helped me crack the case.
The pictures on my phone which
I don't remember taking.
And now I know the truth of
what happened to Tae Kyung Sung...
and my girlfriend.
Subtitles Diego Moraes(oakislandtk)
www.opensubtitles.org