Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
MINISTRY OF CULTURE
CINEMA FUND
MINISTRY OF CULTURE - CINEMA FUND
NMG STUDIOS
STS
ORBITA-4 SPACESHIP
A million, million, million scarlet roses
From the window, from the window,
from the window you see
A million, million, million scarlet roses
From the window, from the window,
from the window you see
Who's in love, who's...
Won't you sing with me?
Or should I inform Mission Control
that the commander's psychological
condition has worsened?
-Go ahead.
-Alright.
Then let's sing something you like.
You know, I used to kind of like
that part about the roses...
You see.
...a couple months ago.
What's happening, Cheget?
Ready for undocking.
The system is functioning normally.
Pressure CA 730 BO 730.
Roger! Everything according to schedule!
So here's my plan!
When we get out of recovery,
I'm going home.
To my elevator, then my apartment.
I'll take off my shoes
and go straight down the hallway
to the very end...
And turn on the hot water.
And then just a tiny bit of the cold.
-Alright!
-And climb into the bath.
And just let some jerk knock on the door!
Just let him knock!
What about you?
I'm going to Rostov.
-What do you have there?
-Business.
Some dame again?
I know you!
Mr. "Beloved by women and children".
You can't tell me?
Temperature 23 degrees.
Command issued to open the latch hooks.
Copy, Cheget!
Latch hooks open.
Controlling the departure
of the TC from its station.
Initiating full disengagement.
We’ve undocked successfully.
I'm watching the station.
Copy!
Well, it'll be like this...
I'll lay there in the bath. I'll get out,
dry off with a towel.
I'll put on cologne, of course.
We'll dress up nice, wife on my arm,
and on the 14th we'll head to a concert
at the Zheleznodorozhnik theater.
There, just for me,
she'll sing:
"A million, million, million scarlet..."
What was that?
I don't know. Maybe the utility module?
I don't see anything.
-We're looking out the windows!
-Yes sir.
Oh you stinker!
Come on, come on, come on!
Come on, my dear.
Just a little more.
Well, you don't say!
Kostya!
SOVIET KAZAKHSTAN. 1983
MOSCOW. RESEARCH INSTITUTE OF BRAIN AMS USSR
How much longer?
-Hello!
OK, colleagues. We may begin.
This is a straightforward matter...
I propose we skip the introductions
-and move directly to the interview.
-OK.
I hope you don't mind.
The sooner we finish this
unpleasant business the better, right?
I'm not in a hurry.
What's that supposed to mean?
Tatiana Yurievna, we are not your enemies.
We know your methods.
No one will accuse you of willfully
inflicting injury on a patient.
But you will have to acknowledge
some degree of negligence.
Negligence is failure
to fulfill one's duties.
-I did what was necessary.
-You nearly drowned your patient.
I temporarily cut the oxygen supply
to his lungs.
He was improperly diagnosed.
The standard therapy would not
have succeeded.
You held him underwater
for nearly a minute.
The boy is seventeen.
The last two weeks his mother has visited
every office in the Health Ministry.
Then deal with his mother.
His psychogenic seizures are rooted
in her overprotection.
For now I blocked them.
They will return
if you can't keep her under control.
Tatiana Yurievna,
let me explain the situation to you
so you will have no illusions.
Now you only have two options.
Either acknowledge your guilt
and accept dismissal
or we will be forced to send your file
to the public prosecutor's office.
The conversation will be
very different there.
I did the right thing.
Tatiana Yurievna!
Can I have a word with you?
I answered all your questions
at the inquiry.
I am not from the Health Ministry.
To the contrary.
My name is Semiradov.
I would like your expert opinion.
You personally?
Or your entire task force?
It's about a patient.
I must ask you to come with me.
Bring him here
and I'll give you my opinion.
If you can do so within two weeks,
before I am dismissed.
I would be glad to, but it's impossible.
I came to ask the mountain
to go to Mohammed.
Are you asking me? Or is that an order?
I don't believe in orders.
It's in the human nature.
Orders are not effective
for highly intelligent people.
Interesting. Isn't that anti-Soviet?
Possibly. I'm not a politician.
You could say we are colleagues.
I run something like a research institute.
I'm also interested in neuropsychiatry.
I think you will find this case
very interesting.
Otherwise, I will bring you back.
Oh, and I will take care
of the review board.
You have my word as an officer.
How's the weather?
Any crosswind expected?
-Nothing serious.
- I know.
Help yourself!
There'll be no fancy cafeteria
once we land.
That's the one thing even I can't change.
I would like to see his medical history,
if it is not classified.
I'm sorry, but we haven't prepared one.
Would an oral report suffice?
Surely you have heard about
the recent Orbit-4 landing?
I read about it.
We had to sanitize the media report.
We lost radio contact with the crew
a day before they landed.
It appears there was an incident in space.
Our patient is the commanding officer,
Konstantin Veshnyakov.
He is suffering from episodic amnesia.
Do you want me to sign the nondisclosure
agreement now or when we arrive?
Nondisclosure agreement?
Apart from the amnesia
and physiological symptoms, suppose
the cosmonaut simply lost his mind.
The Soviet people probably
don't need to know
that their national hero
has lost his mind.
So where is the paper I should sign?
SOVIET KAZAKHSTAN
ALL-UNION SCIENTIFIC RESEARCH INSTITUTE
You have access to 90% of the facilities.
You can move about freely.
After you receive security clearance
you may enter the restricted area.
At my count,
with each beat of the metronome
you will experience a pleasant drowsiness.
One...
Two...
You feel a pleasant warmth
spreading through your body.
Can they see us?
Three...
Tea? Coffee?
Our staff work non-stop, day and night.
Four...
-Tea, thank you!
-Five...
Everything has become hazy.
You are on the spaceship.
I’m on the spaceship.
What do you see?
Something...
Something huge,
dark blue...
-A whale...
-No.
No, once more.
Tell me your name and rank.
Robert.
Duvall... D...
Field marshal Robert D Duvall.
Is that a joke?
Doctor, did I doze off?
Konstantin Sergeyevich...
We can’t make progress
if you won’t help me.
You see, Yan Leonidovich,
only the mentally strong
are sent into space.
Unfortunately, I cannot be hypnotized.
This is sabotage.
I will report you.
Yan Leonidovich Rigel.
Research Director of our institute.
Pleased to meet you.
There’s nothing to be pleased about!
The situation is despicable.
Comrade Colonel!
What happened to Averchenko? Is he alive?
If I’m guilty, give me a trial.
Otherwise, let me go.
Do you hear me?
I’m going on a hunger strike! Understand?
What do you need from me?
To begin with,
I would like to know your opinion
of his condition.
Look at this!
Well, isn’t this something new!
Did Semiradov bring in reinforcements?
I’m Tatiana Yurievna. Good evening!
The evening certainly is good!
Comrade Colonel!
Finally!
Your Rigel makes me almost want
to kill myself.
Would you like tea?
Thank you!
I haven’t seen you before.
I just arrived.
I was asked to assess your condition.
Is that your toy?
Yes. Mine.
I play with it from time to time.
Even in prison
I observe cosmonaut traditions.
You take personal possessions with you.
Can you tell me what happened?
Again?
First I prepared for spaceflight,
and then we launched.
I completed my assignment,
and initiated the landing procedure.
After that, I can’t remember anything.
I ended up here.
You can find the details in my testimony
and MCC files. Have you read them?
Not yet, but I certainly will.
Tatiana Yurievna.
Forgive me if I’m wrong.
You don’t make the decisions here.
No, I don’t.
And you can’t discharge me.
No. But possibly I can help you.
That’s right. I’ll even tell you how.
Call my mother in Moscow
when you finish here.
360-73-44. Lidia Sergeyevna.
When you call,
tell her you’ve seen me and I’m fine.
She’ll be worried.
Okay, then.
You should just go home.
I feel fine.
A cosmonaut’s health is always good.
Don’t worry about me. I managed fine
in space and I’ll manage here too.
May I?
It was nice meeting you.
Are you going to examine him or not?
I already did.
He has PTSD.
The tactile sensitivity
in his hands is diminished.
His sensory receptors or peripheral
nervous system may be damaged.
But considering you have kept him
prisoner here,
it’s to be expected.
If it were to be expected,
we wouldn’t have put him in isolation.
Well, everyone plays their own games.
Is that all?
You promised that I could leave.
Cosmonauts are not the only ones
who need my help.
Of course.
A helicopter leaves in the morning.
Show Tatiana Yurievna to her room.
The institute cafeteria offers
three meals a day.
Good to know. But unnecessary.
I’m here for one night only.
Comrade Semiradov must
authorize your departure.
-You don’t have an exit pass yet.
-There will be one tomorrow.
Who are they?
They are inmates.
Brought in to do hard labor.
Room 108. At the end of the hall.
Do you have a room closer to the stairs?
I get up early.
You are the only one here.
How can I help you?
-I’d like to place a call to Moscow.
-We can only place local calls on base.
Only Comrade Semiradov has
access to an outside line.
I see. Thank you.
Thank you!
Please, go.
You’re still awake. Excellent!
-Has it been long since you had dinner?
-I’m not hungry.
When was the last time you ate?
I don’t remember. About 4 hours ago.
Would you like to see it up close?
What is it?
I don’t know.
But it’s clearly not terrestrial.
-It lives in Veshnyakov?
-Yes, but Veshnyakov’s better than ever.
The creature enters and exits
without harming its carrier.
-But what does he think?
-He doesn’t have any idea.
What?
Try to understand. We don’t know
what exactly happened in space.
We sent two into orbit,
yet three returned to Earth.
Where is the other cosmonaut?
He died.
How?
Like a hero.
I promised you this would interest you.
My mission is to find out what happened.
Yours...
...is to find a way
to separate parasite and host.
Or, sign the nondisclosure agreement
and return home.
Why did you entrust this task to me?
I’ve never worked with your office,
with classified material... Why me?
Because of the boy
you almost drowned.
You sought someone
who is ready to take risks?
Listen, I have no interest in the process.
Tatiana Yurievna, I need results.
I found out you saved him.
The only one who stepped up and saved him.
Please.
Do it again.
I need a professional
who can save a hero.
I need to see all the videotapes
of the creature
and Veshnyakov’s testimony on the landing.
All notes and analyses.
Two sessions a day for an hour each.
After landing, Veshnyakov was sent
to a rehabilitation facility.
On the very first night, that creature
emerged and attacked a medical technician.
We had to bring him here
for safety reasons.
So far, we have been unable
to find a safe method to separate them.
The parasite has succeeded in establishing
a bond with Veshnyakov.
We tried to remove it.
But without it,
Veshnyakov’s vital signs deteriorate.
For it, he’s kind of a spacesuit
against a hostile world.
At the same time, the creature gives him
a phenomenal capacity for regeneration.
Veshnyakov was seriously injured during
landing, yet recovered in just two days.
While incubating, the parasite takes up
just thirty centimeters.
It fits in his esophagus and stomach,
increasing the diameter
of the cavities by 30%.
When it exits,
it exudes a toxin that relaxes
Veshnyakov’s muscles and knocks him out.
It can expand from its tubular form to 1.5
meters in length, once it ingests oxygen.
Then it coils up and returns.
The length and diameter
of its head constantly changes.
For now, it resides outside of Veshnyakov
for about 1 hour and 40 to 50 minutes.
It exits consistently between
2:40 to 3:10 at night.
Parasite or symbiote?
That’s enough, Konstantin Sergeevich!
I can do more.
After your injury,
you should take it easy.
Although the speed of your recovery
has been phenomenal.
-How do you feel generally?
-Fine.
I have a tickle in my throat.
Probably I caught a cold.
If it continues to bother you, tell Rigel.
Okay. See you tomorrow.
Tired out, guys? Go home!
Can anyone tell me the whereabouts
of Veshnyakov’s son?
If I'm not mistaken, they lived in Rostov
when the boy’s mother died?
Is that the only thing you want
to know right now?
Yesterday did you see clearly
what we’re dealing with?
What does it feed on?
The same as what Veshnyakov eats.
Yan Leonidovich, let’s be clear.
I’m not after your job.
Or your Nobel Prize.
You have access to the patient,
our analyses, and video recordings.
If you need anything else,
ask Comrade Semiradov.
Uh-huh... Alright...
Hello, is this the orphanage?
I'm looking for a boy of 7 or 8.
His last name may be Veshnyakov.
But not necessarily.
Where are you going?
Into everything! Oh, this business!
I leave for a minute, and you run wild!
If I tell Margarita Mikhailovna,
do you know what she'll do?
Don't you have anything to say?
I'm talking to you.
March to your room!
Friends, I believe caravans of rockets
Will race us forth from start to star...
Don't you like my singing?
I'm sorry, it's for them.
You know,
there are no greater fans of space songs
than jaded ground personnel.
In space we sing other songs.
Which ones, for example?
Any old nonsense.
The melody is the important thing.
A million, million,
million scarlet roses...
You're drawn to me, right? Admit it.
You probably asked to come
to the base yourself. Am I right?
The people who brought me here
think you have lost your mind.
What do you mean?
They think you killed
the spaceship co-pilot.
What is she doing?
During landing, an event occurred in space
that led to the death of Averchenko.
Or, perhaps you killed him.
You see, Comrade Semiradov can't
let a hero who's insane
go free into society.
Perfect.
So, it seems I'm a murderer and insane.
Surely you know
not all crazy people look crazy.
Listen, doctor!
You're a sensible person.
I prepared for this flight for years.
Something went wrong,
and I don't remember what exactly.
And that's why they put me
behind armored glass.
Can you tell me
why are they're holding me here?
Can anyone explain?
I'm not a spy
-or a wild animal!
-But who are you?
What do you mean?
Well, Konstantin Sergeevich Veshnyakov...
Who are you?
Read my file.
I'm a hero of the Soviet Union.
I could never understand.
A grenade attack on a tank is one thing,
but you sat in a tin can
at the expense of the government
for a few weeks.
What's heroic about that?
What are you saying?
By the way, about your file...
Why did you abandon your son?
Let's be clear.
You never married
the mother of your child.
After her death,
you could have adopted him.
But you wanted
to be a part of a space crew!
An illegitimate son could blemish
your otherwise perfect reputation.
This is why the boy lives in an orphanage
near Rostov.
Am I right?
I also grew up without a father, so what?
Did it prevent me from becoming a hero?
Heroes don't abandon their children.
You know what, Tatiana Yurievna?
I like your pretty face.
But from now on,
I prefer that idiot Rigel.
Thank you, the session is over.
Have you lost your mind?
What the hell were you saying in there?
Who gave you the right?
Test his endocrine profile. Do it now.
Do it!
Yesterday I thought
his reactions were a bit too slow.
It could be his hormone levels.
This can be tested
after a severe psychological stress.
The glands empty into the blood stream.
The results of today's tests will show
how and what the creature
inside of him feeds on.
Even if it's like photosynthesis!
This has no relation to our mission.
We need to remove the parasite.
Comrade Semiradov.
Please order Comrade Veshnyakov
to be transferred
to the medical unit during daylight hours
and allow him to associate with civilians.
We should attempt
to recreate his normal life
to obtain a realistic clinical picture.
"Please order!"
What is this?
A reward for good behavior?
We wanted to help you...
The Cuban representatives confirmed
the meeting took place as anticipated.
They expressed their gratitude
to Secretary General of the CPSU,
Chairman of the Presidium
of the Supreme Council of the USSR,
Yuri Andropov and the entire Soviet
nation for their hospitality.
The Soviet people were equally excited
to welcome back our cosmonauts from orbit.
At last, Kirill Averchenko and Konstantin
Veshnyakov have landed safely.
The heroes are in a rehabilitation center
where they will recover
from their long stay in weightlessness.
In approximately three weeks,
the world will welcome the heroes home.
In brief...
All-Union competitions
between the country's strongest skaters
concluded in Alma-Ata...
What are you doing here?
I owe you an apology.
I provoked you intentionally to measure
your hormone levels under stress.
Okay then,
I'll see you at tomorrow's session.
Goodbye until then.
I didn't know about the child.
She never told me.
A week before the flight,
they called me
from Rostov. She had died.
The little guy has no other relatives.
He's in an orphanage.
They didn't even tell me his name.
I thought,
when I return, I'll go get him. Or...
... maybe I didn't think anything at all.
What would you have done in my place?
I don't know. I don't have children.
Tatiana, tell me why you're here.
Not to cure me of amnesia.
What do they want from me?
You can't say or won't?
I can't.
But I'll do all I can to help you.
Do you think you can help me?
Try moving closer.
Try not to say anything
while I'm working.
Don't worry! We already confirmed
it has no auditory receptors.
But I do.
What are you doing?
Tatiana Yurievna, what are you doing?
Is this thing even working?
-Tatiana Yurievna, what are you doing?
-Can you wait a minute!
-Well, then. If you're finished...
-Raise the glass.
What?
Raise it!
Are you certain?
Yes.
No! It's too...
Then put on a protective suit.
Get her out of there!
We have a shortage
of flower shops around here.
I picked what I could.
-How do you feel?
-I'm fine. Thank you!
You are truly a brave lady.
Now at least we know what not to do.
Veshnyakov isn't fully unconscious.
I see...
Can you be more specific?
That toy reminds him
of the guilt he feels towards his son.
Do you mean the creature
reacted to the toy
because it means a lot to Veshnyakov?
I mean the creature
and Veshnyakov are a single entity.
They share the same conscious mind.
The creature partially blunts
his memories and social skills.
Every night it spends
a few more minutes longer
outside Veshnyakov's body.
At some point it will no longer need him
like a butterfly sheds its cocoon.
We have to do something.
We need more resources.
He must be taken to Moscow.
To Moscow?
Tatiana Yurievna,
why do you think we're not there now?
We know nothing about this creature:
whether it's a grown specimen
or a nymph that might grow
into something that dwarfs us.
I am obliged to preserve
the ability to destroy it,
if it becomes uncontrollable.
We are risking the life of a human being.
A cosmonaut.
A hero of the Soviet Union.
A hero
is prepared for anything.
Including self-sacrifice.
Every day I send fake reports
on our accomplishments
to Moscow.
What he eats.
Details of his pulse, feces, mood.
Anything I can make up.
To avoid the order to destroy him.
I should be court-martialed already.
I hoped you were also ready
to do anything.
May I?
-Yan Leonidovich!
-What?
Doesn't this alarm you?
Maybe there's been a technical mistake?
Veshnyakov's hormone levels
are radically different
at morning and night.
At night he appears to get much worse.
I keep wondering,
when does he get that boost?
I'm not an endocrinologist,
Tatiana Yurievna.
Do your work and figure it out.
You edited parts of the videotapes.
Don't tell me this creature eats
what Veshnyakov does.
What are you feeding it? Pigs?
If I'm leading an investigation,
why is everything hidden from me?
Isn't that enough for you?
Do you want my advice?
Go back to Moscow while you still can.
Forget what you've seen here.
When the review board comes,
we'll all be reported.
Will you torture him with hypnosis
for the review board?
I know what's keeping you here!
You want a Nobel Prize.
You won't make any progress without me.
To do so, I need access
to all the information.
There is no need
for Comrade Semiradov to know.
What, are you serious?
Open the gates!
Don't waste your chance.
The battery lasts
for only about ten minutes.
Where are you taking me? Why am I here?
No!
Don't!
Light!
Stop the camera!
Before he was brought here,
the creature attacked a medic.
You saw the video...
...but you didn't see
Veshnyakov's vital signs.
His condition immediately
improved after the murder.
We tried feeding it everything -
from lab rats
to pigs.
And then
Semiradov ordered that one convict be sent
into the enclosure.
Veshnyakov's hormone levels improved.
You got me thinking about hormones...
Did you see how it behaves
in the enclosure?
It doesn't just need to kill.
It's important for the victim to see it
and become afraid.
The highly developed human brain
releases a lot of cortisol when afraid.
On this planet, we are the champions
when it comes to fear.
This creature
essentially feeds on cortisol.
We are on the edge of a great discovery!
If we combine forces...
Rigel! You're killing people.
Not me,
this is all Semiradov's doing.
What, do you think I'm a monster?
You're not a monster, you're a coward.
A highly adaptive and hardy specimen.
You can't stay here any longer.
It's a terrible place.
They're gonna kill you.
Let's go.
I can't.
-Go to Astra.
-Listen to me.
You are not a robot, but a human being.
Don't you understand?
Let’s go.
Good morning!
Morning!
To be honest, I prefer war films.
Or ones about spies.
What movies do you like?
Don't you need to get back
in shape after your injury?
Want to go for a run?
What, are we going to run
around in a circle, like gym class?
We'll push the TV into the corner.
I received permission
to exit the compound.
You look good in sports clothes!
Did you ever think to try track and field?
No.
We should try when I'm released.
We can no longer
compete professionally,
but why not try amateur sports!
Listen to me carefully!
You brought back a passenger
from outer space. It's inside of you.
They feed people to it alive.
We can separate you from it,
but we have to find someone
who can inform the government!
Can you hear me?
-Are you being watched?
-I don't know.
-At night? Did they assign you a guard?
Find out!
If not, meet me at 1 AM in my block.
That's all, Dr.
I'm exhausted.
Time to sleep!
You also can't sleep?
You're not allowed in the hallway.
I know.
What a life, right?
I can go into space,
but not into the hallway.
Konstantin Sergeevich.
What do you think,
-is anyone out there?
-Where?
In the sky.
Do you believe in God?
I believe in what I can see.
I didn't see God there.
You know what?
I say it's your break time.
Come watch a movie.
They gave me a VCR,
but it's boring to watch alone.
I'm not allowed.
Come on!
Konstantin Sergeevich, I'm not allowed!
And the entire planet will enjoy
the pure air!
Come on.
What's wrong?
-I'll stay by your side.
-I am all alone.
-That's not true.
I was produced to no purpose.
I don't get it...
Amusing, right?
My whole life I dreamed of having
my legacy displayed in a museum.
Can you feel what that creature feels?
I am that creature.
Without morals or obligations.
I feel everything it does.
I remember everything in minute detail.
Everything it sees, stays with me.
You knew from the beginning!
Why didn't you say?
Why do you think?
If Semiradov knew,
he'd never let me go.
My co-pilot Comrade Averchenko.
Help me, Tanya!
To hold on just two more weeks.
Just continue on as you have been.
Semiradov will have no choice.
A review board will arrive from Moscow.
We'll be released.
But before then,
he should not know that I...
I don't want to end up like him.
It will kill people for two more weeks.
How can you endure that!
What would you have done in my place?
Smashed your head in against the wall?
Yes!
I didn't decide to feed it people.
I can't be responsible for that.
I haven't endured so much,
just to die out here in the steppe.
My mother lives alone
and I need to get home.
I must survive.
I need to collect my son.
Now I understand why that creature
chose you and not Averchenko!
You mean I'm a monster?
And you, a princess?
While you all sat cozy and warm
in your offices,
I prepared for this flight,
a heroic accomplishment.
And now you all tell me I should die.
It's your dinner time.
Where are you going? Such a pain!
You haven't killed yourself yet?
Give it to me.
You saw it, huh?
He is like a little animal.
I don't seem to remember this one.
He's from which group?
The invalid group.
Just take a look at his feet!
This one's a nutcase.
Look, he scratched me to blood.
Comrade Colonel.
You may go!
You and I, Tatiana Yurievna, never got off
to a good start.
I should have told you everything.
What in particular?
That you feed people
to that creature alive?
We don't know how much
that creature will adapt.
The victor will be the one
who can control it.
We must learn to control it.
Is that the only thing you care about?
Weapons?
Yes.
Do you know why we need weapons?
Weapons guarantee peace.
A pack of dogs would tear
each other to pieces.
In order to live in peace,
they need one leader.
You feed it people.
People...
Sergey Gennadievich Kovalyev.
Born in 1952.
Convicted by law 103, 117,
77 part one.
He raped and killed his neighbor,
a 12-year-old girl.
These are not people!
People are those who died in Angola
and who die in Afghanistan now.
These are fodder!
If the authorities find out,
they'll court-martial you.
Yes.
We don't like initiative.
But doctors and soldiers sometimes
must make difficult decisions.
Victors are not judged.
I'm ready to take responsibility.
You're the same, Tatiana.
You don't know me.
You...
You don't know yourself.
Come on, I'll show you
the feeding up close.
No need to sit in the back
of a car with binoculars.
Comrade Semiradov.
She allowed herself to go too far.
But it was for the greater good.
Yan Leonidovich, doesn't your conscience
trouble you at night?
M...me?
You showed her the feeding session.
You disobeyed an order.
Please, don't!
I'll find another way.
In the short term, unlikely.
Open up!
I'm not afraid...
It's me.
A million, million, million scarlet roses
From the window, from the window you see
Who's in love, who's in love
A million
A million scarlet roses
From the window, from the window...
It adapted.
Now it can hear.
He transformed his life into flowers
For you
Who's in love, who's in love deeply...
No!
Can Veshnyakov control it?
No.
Not yet.
I need results, Tatiana Yurievna.
You must learn to control him.
That will be difficult without you.
Let's forget our differences
and work together openly.
I take full responsibility.
You can say that I forced you.
If things go well,
we'll have an amazing weapon.
Will you help?
Tatiana Yurievna!
Do you know why it chose Veshnyakov,
and not Averchenko?
He was in the early stages of cancer.
With a kidney tumor
that caused Addison's disease.
We couldn't detect it prior to lift-off.
But the creature could.
His body suppressed
high concentrations of cortisol.
That's why it couldn't establish
a complete symbiotic bond.
Come here.
Metyrapone and Trilostane,
four milliliters...
[Latin] And some strong sedative.
[Latin] At 2 AM. By the medical unit.
Trilostane?
[Latin] Tonight.
We will attempt an escape. With you.
[Latin] Not me.
Be a man, after all.
You're a scientist, not any old doctor.
Look here.
See the tongue?
Don't be afraid, Comrade Rigel.
[Latin] Help us.
If you escape, say he made me do it.
Or if you don't, that I didn't know.
Thank you, colleague.
You helped me a lot.
Are you allergic to Buspironum?
Me? I don't think so...
You... What...
What are you doing?
Make up your mind, Comrade Rigel.
You didn't know or you were forced?
Watch the door.
We have little time,
so listen carefully.
No review board is coming here.
Semiradov will do anything
to keep that creature here.
I know how to separate you.
Why did you enter the enclosure?
I could have killed you.
But you didn't. You like me too.
This is a mix of hormones.
It will imitate the effects of Addison's
disease, which Averchenko suffered from.
The injection will force
the creature to exit you.
Without you,
it can live no more than an hour.
You'll survive much longer. We just
need to make it to an emergency room.
And if you are wrong?
If it's already acclimatized?
We'll be letting it go free!
We'll give you a shot,
when we get a safe distance away.
Where there's no people.
It's weaker in the sunlight.
No.
We just need
to make it to a real hospital.
I'll be able to think of something.
I'll find a way out of this.
Why?
Tatiana, you don't understand.
I don't need to be taken anywhere.
The creature doesn't harm me at all.
To the contrary, it saved my life.
You don't believe that.
Leave already!
I'm not afraid of them!
Be afraid of me! It chose me!
It is not you.
It's me!
It's my punishment!
I abandoned my son.
I chose space instead.
I deserve this, you understand?
That's all. Go!
Lyosha!
What?
His name is Lyosha.
Aleksei Konstantinovich Romanov.
He'll be seven next week.
There's a car by the enclosure.
They'll kill you here. Come with us.
Don't worry. I'm a highly adaptive
and hardy specimen.
Thank you!
This Dr. Rigel, from Base ALFA 4.
Please, connect me
to the operative on duty.
I have very important information.
-What is it?
-They're in the enclosure.
Veshnyakov and Dr. Klimova.
Send the response team.
Do not shoot Veshnyakov. Terminate her.
Stop!
Veshnyakov!
Take two steps to the right! Lie down!
Drop your weapons
and no one will get hurt!
-Don't shoot!
-Fire!
And he... he ordered
they be listed as victims of a fire.
But those people were killed outright.
For now, there are seven victims
from the convicts.
Did you have enough time?
Did you manage to call them?
You're no hero, Yan!
I could tell immediately.
You have no resemblance to them.
But you'll have an honorable death.
Out of respect
for your scientific endeavors.
The syringe!
No.
-Not yet.
-The syringe.
Come on!
Faster!
Run!
Fire!
If you find the fugitives, take
all possible measures to detain them.
-Pull over!
-Get out of here!
As you were!
Kostya!
Sorry!
What are you doing?
Your condition worsened!
You won't survive without it.
We can still leave...
We can do it!
Have you changed your mind,
Tatiana Yurievna?
I was mistaken.
They can't be separated.
They have become fully symbiotic.
They'll die without each other.
Well, no matter.
Everyone makes mistakes.
We won't let them die, right?
Do you know what your problem is?
You try to save everyone!
But that's impossible.
You must always choose.
He's gone.
We can separate you.
We'll try in Moscow.
It'll be OK.
I know.
We'll think of something.
I already have.
ROSTOV-ON-DON
Why do you keep coming back
here like a bee to the flower?
Why won't you lie calmly?
Why this running?
Why on earth do you need those?
Where are you going like that?
Do you have parents?
Go on!
But just play around the complex, OK?
Or they'll take away my award.
Hello! Tatiana Klimova.
I'm here to adopt Lyosha Romanov.
No problem!
God loves everyone.
I've done this sedentary job twenty years.
And it's fine.
You're going to be alright, little fellow.
I'm not a boy.
My name is Tanya.
So you're Lyosha?
Hi.
SPUTNIK
DIRECTED BY EGOR ABRAMENKO
OKSANA AKINSHINA
PYOTR FYODOROV
FYODOR BONDARCHUK
ANTON VASILIEV
PRODUCED BY MIKHAIL VRUBEL,
ALEXANDER ANDRYUSHCHENKO
PRODUCED BY FYODOR BONDARCHUK
PRODUCED BY ILIA STUART,
MURAD OSMANN, PAVEL BURIA
PRODUCED BY VYACHESLAV MURUGOV
CO-PRODUCER
ILIYA DZHINCHARADZE
EXECUTIVE PRODUCER
MIKHAIL KITAEV
DEVELOPMENT PRODUCER
ALINA TYAZHLOVA
WRITTEN BY OLEG MALOVICHKO,
ANDREY ZOLOTAREV
DIRECTOR OF PHOTOGRAPHY
MAXIM ZHUKOV
MUSIC BY OLEG KARPACHEV
PRODUCTION DESIGNER
MARIA SLAVINA
COSTUME DESIGNER
ULYANA POLYANSKAYA
MAKE-UP ARTISTS
VALERIYA NIKULINA, ALINA NAZAROVA
PRODUCTION MANAGER
DENIS POPOV
ASSISTANT DIRECTOR
OLEG ROMANOV
FILM PRODUCTION MANAGER
MARIA KARNEYEVA
STUNT COORDINATOR
OLEG CHEMODUROV
POST-PRODUCTION PRODUCER
YEKATERINA LEE
EDITED BY
ALEXANDER PUZYREV, EGOR TARASENKO
VFX BY MAIN ROAD POST
SOUND BY FLYSOUND
DI COLORIST
ANDREY MESNYANKIN, C.S.I.
BUTTERFLY EFFECT PROMO AGENCY
PROMOTION PRODUCER
DARYA SKUGAR
CEO VODOROD PICTURES
ALEXANDER VRUBEL
CEO ART PICTURES STUDIO
DENIS BAGLAY
PR ACTIVITIES
MARIA DALAKIAN
CFO - JULIA DZYADKOVSKAYA
COO - VASILIY YUDACHEV
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org