It's been 4 weeks since
I asked for a nanny.
If you tell me you're still
looking, how should I respond?
I told you many times, I
don't care about paying more.
I said it's urgent for work.
Please look for a nanny properly.
Ina, our new home is
really quiet and has clean air too.
The doctor said it'd be good for you.
Once you live there,
you'll grow to love it.
Sweetie.
That doll there,
it's a limited edition.
It was really hard getting it.
You should be thanking me.
WRITTEN AND DIRECTED BY KIM KWANG-BIN
Ina!
Yeon Ina!
Sweetie!
You can't run off like that, I
looked everywhere for you.
Ina, that's our new home.
Do you like it?
You should've come early.
You missed Ina getting the award.
You know about my new project.
It's a state of emergency.
Do you even know what
your birthday gift to her was?
It's this necklace.
She wears it everyday
since I told her it's from you.
Honey!
Panic attack isn't something
that gets better with some rest.
It needs constant care.
Or you'll have seizures again.
Set an alarm and medicate regularly.
I can take care of myself,
but Ina's not getting better.
Is she in bad shape?
She won't even lock eyes with me.
She'll get better in clean air environment.
Architect of the Year
You moved there for that reason.
It's just frustrating, I'm
doing everything possible.
The last resort would be
the art camp I mentioned,
but you two will be apart,
so I don't recommend it.
You're in treatment too,
that's what worries me.
I'm more concerned with her.
Dad, watch me run!
Okay, my little star, do your best!
Yeah, listen to me.
Wasn't I supposed to handle
everything from concept to finish?
But you're never here.
I'm not saying I won't go!
It's because of the kid!
Listen, this is a unilateral
contract termination.
Am I wrong?
Let's talk face-to-face,
I'll come to the site.
Happy birthday to you!
My lovely Ina,
happy birthday to you!
Blow out the candles,
or I will.
No way!
- What was your wish?
- Secret!
- You won't tell me?
- Nope!
Ina!
What happened, sweetie?
Did you scream just now?
I didn't scream.
Is everything okay?
Yup.
Can I come in for a bit?
That's weird.
You really didn't scream?
Nope.
Where did you get that doll?
It was in here.
- In there?
- Yup.
Hold on.
You know that doll I
bought you recently?
I think it'd be more
fun to play with that.
Dad, can I keep this?
Someone else
played with it, it's dirty.
Give it to me, I'll throw it out.
I want to play with both dolls.
Are you really okay?
Yup.
All right.
Sleep early.
Okay.
Thank you for the meal.
Dad, can I play in my room?
You want to?
I like this house.
I got a friend too.
That's great, Ina, thank you.
Why is Hyun-sang in the conversation?
If we share the design, the
concept will get tangled up.
What does he know about galleries?
He hasn't even done a 2-floor cabin.
While you were on leave,
he did a gallery in Jeju.
He's doing well, like
you in your prime.
Honestly,
they just wanted him,
but I championed you.
What a load of crap...
The boss is asking,
how an architect designs
when he's not even on site.
It's all been agreed to!
I'd come down as
soon as I find a nanny!
It's been over a month now.
We're out of time.
Why is he here?
Yeah, that's odd.
Why is Hyun-sang
here? Out on a stroll?
So it's already been decided.
No way, dude.
I'll come down, so get rid of him.
What?
I'll report to the site!
Stop moving!
Don't fool around!
Hold on!
Ina, what were you doing?
I was making a song for you.
Wanna hear it?
Ina.
I have to tell you something.
Remember how I said I was designing
a museum in Tongyeong?
That job is starting,
so I need to work at
the site for a little while.
A nanny will stay here with you.
How long?
About 2 months?
But I'll come home
every weekend to see you.
Can I come with you?
I really want you to come with me,
but it's a construction
site, so it's bad for you.
If you're understanding
and help me out,
I'll buy you a present.
You were gonna do whatever you want.
Why bother asking?
Honey.
I'm not doing whatever I want,
I want to find a way together.
But if you always give
me an attitude like this,
I don't know what to do.
Could you try to understand
and think in my shoes?
I'll think about what you want.
Ina, let's talk again.
Ina, it's late, get to bed!
Decide if you'll come
or not by tomorrow.
How is the art camp treatment done?
They'll start with
isolation treatment.
Will she be okay?
Being away from me,
since her mom's gone too.
It won't be easy, but what can you do?
It's too much for you.
They take only a few kids,
so you'll need to donate.
Think about it.
Where are you going?
Ina, I'm going to the site for a bit.
I'll be right back.
You said we'll talk again.
Can't think of what to buy me?
Ina.
Let's talk tonight.
And that doll in New
York, I ordered it.
It'll arrive soon.
Do you know how old I am? I
don't need those dumb dolls.
Ina.
You said you liked that doll.
And why are you talking
like that to your dad?
Why do you decide what I like?
Then tell me what you really like!
I don't need anything.
- Calls himself 'dad'...
- What?
- Ina.
- Let go.
Let go! Let go!
Let go!
D'you ask for a nanny?
Yes, hello, I was just heading out.
$150 for a day.
Okay.
Do-hyun, that donation
to the art camp,
how much would be enough?
They're pretty well off.
The kid's in her room, doing whatever.
No wife.
Who knows, maybe she ran off.
He stashed all the expensive stuff.
It's so my style.
Hey.
This is Mr. Park.
- Good work.
- It's so nice to meet you.
- This is Mr. Kim.
- Great to meet you.
Good to meet you, sir.
- Shall we go inside and talk?
- Sure.
She's screaming and
smashing shit in her room.
She doesn't eat no matter what I make.
She'll wise up when she starves.
Crazy little bitch!
She started today, how
could she just leave?
Stop giving me a load of shit.
I'll head home tonight,
so keep her there till then.
If she took the money,
she must be responsible!
I can't go right now!
Okay.
Talked to art camp
director, send her next week.
I want to go too,
take me with you.
Come with us...
We'll take you with us...
Missing Child: Yeon Ina, female (11)
Thank you all.
She's not my daughter.
She's been missing for a
month, and you got nothing?
It's killing us too.
Nothing comes up at all.
That nanny I hired,
Ina disappeared
shortly after she left.
Let's investigate her once more.
We checked the dash cam
from the car she drove that day,
and we even did a lie detector test.
She's clean.
Please go home and wait.
You've been telling me to
go home and wait for a month!
Are you investigating properly?!
Why the hell are you
lashing out at me?!
- All done.
- Okay.
All right, Mr. Yeon,
please look at the camera.
You can speak freely about Ina.
Hello, I'm Yeon Sang-won.
This is my daughter, Ina.
She's 11 years old,
and she disappeared about a month ago.
I really want to find
her, please help.
We scoured all security cams,
and dash cams in 3km vicinity,
but we did not see any traces of her.
Her mother died in a
car accident last year,
and she lived with her dad.
According to people around
them, they weren't in good terms.
While filming, we stumbled
upon a dozen pill containers.
They're all used to
treat mental illnesses.
The medication shows his
illnesses must be serious,
and he may be experiencing
overlapping symptoms.
He was so fixated on work,
to the point that I felt bad.
Maybe because he took some time off,
he looked nervous and anxious.
Unfortunately, many of
the missing child cases
are linked to family members.
Remember the Mi-jin case
we introduced 3 years ago?
There are many similarities
between these two cases.
Perhaps this is the point
where we need to look at
the case from another angle.
A girl who disappeared
from inside her home,
where could she be now?
We're waiting for your tips.
Is this Behind the Story?
Her dad is suspicious.
Man...
There is no Internet connection.
Tada!
This is a gift from dad.
A butterfly necklace!
It's so pretty!
You love it that much?
Do you want to thank dad?
Thank you, dad!
Who are you?
Hello, you called for
an internet technician?
The door was open.
This house is so big,
I'll need to look around
to find the problem.
This house is humungous.
Are you an artist?
Or are you making a house?
I've always wanted to
live in a big house like this.
But my family was poor.
It's not here.
How do you clean a house like this?
You'll tire yourself
out doing it alone.
Do you get a maid?
Really high ceiling too.
Do you get really high heating bills?
I'm sure you get government
subsidies for solar panels,
but you can't tell how
efficient those panels are, right?
How much is it per square foot?
Higher than Gangnam?
You can ask the real estate agency.
Could you just get
to fixing the internet?
There are cable problems
out here in the country.
So the EMF...
So I'm using an EMF
detector to check the condition.
Is this how you fix the internet?
May I?
Sure.
Excuse me?
Could I get your business card?
Wait a minute, that's not important,
I'm about to solve the problem.
I checked the terminal
box just in case,
and someone had cut the cable.
What did you say?
Didn't you call for an
internet technician?
Sir, could we be civil
and talk about this?
Listen to me, will you?
Wait a minute!
Who the hell are you?
Don't take it the wrong way.
I needed to check something,
I'm here to help you.
Are you from the TV show?
I'm not getting fooled twice.
I'm calling the cops.
Didn't Ina's personality
change before she disappeared?
Acting weird, talking to herself
or screaming in front of the closet.
How did you know that?
Ina isn't the first child to
disappear in her house.
32 kids have disappeared since 1998,
and I've been at it for 10 years.
If you Google 'Exorcist
Heo', you'll find me.
I've been blogged many times
and went on TV shows too.
Exorcism at your service
Exorcist Heo Kyung-hoon
When it comes to exorcism,
I'm pretty much No.1 in Korea.
Top class fame and skills
but with reasonable rates,
like this.
Take a look at this first.
They all disappeared from their homes.
Playing, doing homework, sleeping,
they all vanished without a trace.
They drew those drawings.
They all point to a child.
A girl named Hyun-soo disappeared
like Ina 20 years ago.
Her parents set up this ritual
to find out if she was dead.
You saw her, right? That's my mom.
A few parents of the
missing kids said so,
that they saw her.
I think she was trying to warn them,
trying to stop it
from taking the kids.
Shall I continue?
She killed my mom, took the children,
and now Ina too.
It's her.
The source of everything,
a demonic child.
How am I supposed to take this in?
Does this make sense to you?
A ghost took my child?
You're just trying to
get paid for a ritual!
Are you out of your mind?!
Get out, leave.
Don't believe me? Okay.
I'm the only one who believe you.
Everyone thinks you killed her.
If it's delayed any longer,
she'll be lost forever.
Wait.
Can you really find her?
Yes.
Spirit of the living remains
in the underworld for 49 days,
so-called '49-day memorial rite'.
It's easily explained in the
movie Along with the Gods.
You didn't see that movie?
Never got to.
I thought you were cultured.
In any case, Ina has only 3 days left.
3 days.
This is a detector that finds
objects with wavelengths
beyond quantum mechanics.
When ghosts appear,
this reacts to them.
So where exactly is Ina right now?
Realm of the dead.
We call it the dark realm.
It means...
- Let me take a page...
- Don't tear that.
Jeez...
Take a look.
Realm of the living is
separated from realm of the dead.
They share the side.
They're stepping on the same space,
but they can't see each
other because of the border.
But if the resonance
frequency is in sync,
they can see each other.
They can cross realms.
Like the movie Interstellar.
The shaman exorcism is like
scrubbing the radio frequency.
It's often called 'possession'.
This happens frequently,
so I need protection.
There is a breed of ghosts
that are especially malicious.
Like the demon we're after.
They find people who sync up
and drag them to their realm.
The victims lose their memories over
time, and are left with only malice.
They become the Blinded.
Once they lock eyes,
they'll swallow everything,
they're horrifying beings.
What can I do to find her?
We have to capture the
demon to get her back.
Beat it up or negotiate,
whatever it takes.
The child demons are
subconsciously drawn to dolls.
When they hold the straw
dolls with my blood on them,
it'll generate a tingly sensation.
It's like a trap.
This creates a boundary,
these are all money.
Value of these talismans
shot up lately!
So yeah, these are expensive.
Watch carefully, it'll come out soon.
Have you tried this cup noodle?
It feels so genuine.
It has real fried tofu.
Who cares about fried
tofu, does this really work?
Yes, of course.
Be patient.
Did it figure us out?
Why isn't it coming?
I hear something.
Huh? It's Ina's violin.
My ears...
She's a bold one.
Was Ina here?
Not sure about that.
We'll try once more,
with a big doll drenched in blood.
She's really something.
Sir.
Which singers does Ina like?
BTS? BLACKPINK?
Bands that kids nowadays like.
You don't know? Who's her best friend?
You really don't know much about her.
You two don't talk?
That's not right.
I absolutely hate silence.
I actually hate being talkative,
but I talk a lot because
I hate silence more.
So, how should I address you?
Whatever you feel like.
Then...
Mr. Yeon?
No, since you retained
me how's 'boss'?
I'd rather you call me Mr. Yeon.
What should I call you?
General Manager Heo,
GMs work the hardest.
I'm thirsty, let me raid your fridge.
I could use a beer.
GM Heo.
GM Heo!
Dad...
Dad!
Mr. Yeon, close your eyes.
Close them now!
We didn't set the trap, she did.
The Blinded can only see
those with opened eyes.
So don't open them and
get out of there quietly.
Stay still for now.
Completely still.
Now, do exactly what I tell you.
Keep your body low,
and turn right slowly.
No, left from there!
Mr. Yeon, stop!
Don't' move.
Don't move and stay right there.
You're almost there, just hang on.
You're so close, don't move a muscle,
I'll be right there, don't move.
Goddammit...
Mr. Yeon, get out of there.
Just come out!
All the beings in heaven,
and sprouted on earth,
slay the treacherous
and cunning ghouls,
repel a 10 million ghosts,
push away all evil,
strike down with all your might,
and dissipate energy of the vile...
You're...
Missing Child Cho Myung-jin (11)
Heo!
What happened?
That was embarrassing...
- It was Myung-jin...
- Myung-jin?
In Surgery
Missing Child Cho Myung-jin (11)
Chungcheong Province,
Jujin District, near Gyunbaek...
Gyunbaek Real Estate
I'm not sure, got another photo?
That's all.
He looks like an ex-con.
Did he steal money from you?
His child went missing.
Is that so?
Sorry for what I said...
Wait, a missing child?
Could it be that Sangdong man?
There's a man who lives
alone in Mt. Sangdong,
he's famous for all the
weird stuff around his house.
From what I hear,
his kid went missing.
Kyung-hoon...
It's mom... mom...
Find mom...
- Defibrillator!
- Yes, doctor!
Hello?
Excuse me!
Is anyone home?
Who are you?
Are you Myung-jin's father?
Please leave.
I have some questions about her.
Are you a cop?
No, sir.
My daughter also disappeared.
I think it's related to
Myung-jin somehow.
She disappeared while
sleeping in the next room.
My wife went out to look
for her, and never returned.
I searched her for 10
years before giving up.
And spent another 10
years trying to forget her.
I don't want to dig up
the past, please leave me.
Did anything happen
before her disappearance?
This might sound weird, but
did her personality change,
or maybe she talked to
herself in front of the closet?
Why do you think I live up here?
It suffocates me to see kids,
why do you think I live
in complete isolation?
My apologies.
Do you know anything about this doll?
Why is this... But how?!
Why are you here?
Why did you come?!
I'm not gonna die!
You won't get me!
This can't be here.
I have to burn it...
Dad...
Myung-jin...
Sir?
Hello?
Honey...
It's okay...
What are you doing?!
Just hold on...
You go on ahead and wait for us.
Sir, please...
I'll be...
right there...
Dad! Dad! Please let me out!
Dad! I'm really scared!
Mom! Dad!
Over 1,000 shops have
closed down or are on sale.
In Seoul alone...
Please let me out, dad!
Let me out, dad!
Mom! Mom!
Please let me out!
I'm sorry!
Dad!
Myung-jin.
Breathing doesn't
prove that we're alive.
Dad, please help me...
When we are reborn,
we'll be happy, with no debts.
Dad, I'm really sorry...
Please let me out, I'm sorry...
Rather than living like this...
we'll be happier dead.
I'm scared, dad...
Please!
Please, I'm sorry!
Dad!
Help me...
I saw Myung-jin's memory.
You and Myung-jin's
frequencies must be in sync.
Then you can see
each other's memories.
Her resentment turned her into a demon,
and she's been gathering
other kids in pain.
It all makes sense now.
You resented Ina, no?
Be honest for a moment.
Work always meant more than her,
and you wanted her to go away.
Get to your point.
Kids know everything instinctively,
whether someone
truly loves them or not.
Buying her some dolls
can't hide your feelings.
All missing kids have
something in common.
They're scarred by their parents:
assault, verbal abuse,
and abandonment.
Same thing with Ina.
How painful would it have
been to live with a dad
who wanted her gone.
Imagine her loneliness.
Her sorrow called for Myung-jin.
So it was me who sent her away.
- Mr. Heo.
- Holy craps...
What is it?
About that frequency,
so you're saying if we're in sync,
I can see and enter their realm?
Right, if you're in sync.
When I had that panic attack, you
said I was in sync with Myung-jin.
Does that mean I can meet Ina?
What do you want to do?
We're running out of time,
let me enter their realm.
No way, it's too dangerous,
you'll get hurt.
I don't care if it's too dangerous,
there's no other way,
unless you got a plan.
Help me get there.
You have no idea what you're saying.
Once you're there, you
could get stuck and die.
Plus, you'll ruin my exorcism career.
You're asking the impossible,
it's just not doable.
Sorry for bringing up money,
but I'll pay you whatever you want.
So help me get there.
I want to see her, please help me.
Jesus...
I'll protect you with a ritual,
but you'll have no
longer than 30 minutes.
If you don't come out before
then, remember the Blinded?
You'll turn into that and
stay in the underworld.
It's okay, let's try it.
All right, let's try it.
How to worsen your panic attack?
That's a weird question.
Could you just trust me? Please.
Cho Myung-jin (11)
If there's a high
intake of caffeine pills,
you'll get a panic attack,
and at worse, death,
so be absolutely careful.
Remember that I've warned you.
Are you ready?
My symptom will start soon.
Myung-jin created that realm,
so anything can happen,
she'll do whatever
it takes to stop you,
so be prepared.
I'm bringing my daughter back.
Stay alive...
and pay me for my service, got it?
Depends on your performance.
This fire is linked to you.
If the time runs out, or if you die,
this fire will go out.
Seung-hee...
Wait, honey!
Look what you've done to Ina.
Ina is dying.
Die!
Ina!
Seung-hee...
Honey, are you okay?
Baby...
Ina...
Ina?
Protect her no matter what, okay?
Seung-hee! Honey!
Sweetheart...
No! Seung-hee!
Ina...
Ina!
Why are you here?
Myung-jin, I came to get Ina.
Why? This is what you wanted.
You wanted to throw her away.
That donation to the art camp,
how much would be enough?
Back then, I...
Ina will soon live with us here.
Myung-jin!
Please let her go...
Please let me take her back.
Myung-jin,
what happened to you that day...
I saw it all.
That's why you brought
other kids here, Ina too.
The last thing you heard that day...
I don't want to hear it!
Rather than living like this...
We'll be happier dead.
Do you trust me?
Mom!
Mom...
I want to live...
It's all grown-ups' fault.
It's my fault.
It's all my fault...
Don't lie to me!
It's mom...
Don't forget, find mom!
Mom...
Ina, honey!
Kill him.
Ina, please snap out of it.
Everything belongs somewhere,
you will find out where god is.
Ina, please...
Ina!
Myung-jin?
Here you were, my baby.
Mom?
How scared must you have been?
How painful...
I should've protected you...
I'm so sorry, sweetheart...
I only waited for you.
- Mom...
- Myung-jin.
You can rest with me now.
Ina.
Ina...
Myung-jin...
Mom!
Mom...
Mom! Mom!
Mom!
Myung-jin.
Mr. Yeon, hurry, there's no time.
I'm really sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Ina!
Ina, wake up...
Ina...
Dad...
Dad, I want to go home.
Ina, let's go home,
we'll be right there.
Let's go home.
Mr. Yeon!
She still doesn't remember
the underworld?
I hope she doesn't ever remember it.
How's the new house?
It's good enough for us, very cozy.
That's great.
If you want to use a credit
card, there's a 10% surcharge.
If you blog about me, I'll
give you free talismans.
Total: $205,000
Ina!
Hi, dad!
Hop in, little miss!
It's okay, baby, he's a good man.
You'll have to revise this.
I'll just ignore it.
Subtitles Diego Moraes(oakislandtk)
www.opensubtitles.org