NETFLIX PRESENTS
Do you know why I'm here, Eric?
Your parents called me
because they're worried about you.
Want to tell me what's wrong?
You can trust me.
I've helped kids like you.
There are other kids like me?
Of course.
Let me guess.
You're sad
because you had to leave your school
and your old house, right?
Eric, it's normal to be angry.
I don't like moving either.
But this is a very pretty house.
And you'll make new friends soon,
and it will be just like before.
Tell me, why do you have
so much trouble sleeping?
They always wake me up.
Who wakes you up?
The voices.
"Voices"? Your parents?
And what do the voices say?
Sometimes they ask me to draw things.
Eric, do you hear them right now?
Yes.
And what are they saying?
I can't tell you.
What's wrong with him?
He has a lot of imagination.
And the voices he says talk to him?
Your son is a very intelligent boy
who's had to get used to playing
and talking by himself, that's all.
And why can't he sleep?
Sara told me
you buy houses to resell them.
Yes, that's right. We renovate them.
It's likely because of the instability
from so much moving.
That can cause anxiousness
and trouble sleeping.
It makes total sense.
There's a chance of showers.
Everywhere else will be
partly cloudy with lower temperatures.
A front will move in from Algeciras
bringing rain across southern Spain.
You're fucking kidding.
Dad, can you hear me? Over.
Dad here.
You have to say "over," over.
Dad here, over.
Can you get my ball out of the pool?
It went in there again, over.
On my way, over.
It's good you waited outside.
I don't like you to go in alone.
If it goes in again, let me know.
-What's that for?
-This?
Know what an infestation is?
The flies that live in my fireplace?
I don't think it's just your fireplace.
But don't say a word to your mom.
She'll kill me for buying an old house.
Eric.
It's bath time, Eric!
Come on, buddy.
See if you can steal it.
Come on.
He hates you…
You didn't rinse yet?
-I did.
-Come on, tip your head back.
What's this?
Were you playing with the cats?
I told you not to go near them,
you could catch something.
-Mom?
-What is it?
What is it?
Does Dad really hate me?
Where did you hear that nonsense?
I asked you a question, Eric.
Dad.
Dad said that? When did he say that?
On the walkie-talkie.
Don't lie.
Dad loves you very much, you know that.
Don't you?
Come on, it's dinnertime.
I've got your number in my contact list--
There's a man stuck to your back.
We're joined by Germán Domingo
for the release of his latest book,
titled Sounds from The Great Beyond.
How do you know an EVP is authentic?
They are voices that come
from a place with a lot of pain.
Believe me, when you hear a real one,
it's something you'll never forget.
How many of the EVPs
you've analyzed are real?
Very few.
Almost none, I'd say.
Most come from humans.
They're voices
from the street or the neighbor's TV.
-Dani.
-Yes?
Is it true real EVPs…
Did you scold Eric
or say something to him?
No, nothing. Why?
-Why these recordings don't have…
-Never mind, forget it.
…oscillations in the waveform
is something we haven't figured out.
You heard the psychologist,
there's nothing seriously wrong with him.
Once he makes a friend at school,
he'll be fine.
Sometimes he says things…
I don't know.
I think he's mad at me.
I'll try to get organized
and have more time to spend with him.
That would be good.
Don't worry.
Damn it.
Shit… Damn gate.
Not now. Let me sleep, I'm really tired.
What is it, sweetie?
-Please don't! Please!
-Easy, it's OK.
Please!
Easy, you're OK now.
-Please!
-What is it? You're OK.
Eric? What's the matter?
I don't know.
Honey, come here. It's OK.
It was just a bad dream. It's OK.
Dani… your hand.
Damn it.
Jesus, what a disgusting house.
-Why are you here? What happened?
-He got expelled.
-What did you do?
-Nothing.
What do you mean "nothing"?
He hid in a closet and when the principal
went to get him, he bit him.
-Does that seem normal?
-Why did you do that, partner?
Dr. Carol will come
every day starting tomorrow.
The doctor is dead.
-Where did that nonsense come from?
-The voices told me.
Go to your room
and start your homework, go on.
I can't do this alone, Dani.
I'm sorry. I'm truly very sorry.
If there's anything we can do, just--
I understand.
I understand. Goodbye.
What happened?
Her car went off the road
shortly after leaving here.
How did he know?
How could he know?
Someone must have
told him at school, right?
What's going on, Dani?
I don't know.
Can I come in, partner?
-I brought you a sandwich.
-I'm not hungry.
You have to eat something, come on.
Eric, before I came
in your room last night…
…you were talking on the walkie, right?
-To who?
-To you.
I didn't talk to you, partner.
It was your voice.
Go on, finish your sandwich.
Am I crazy, Dad?
You're not crazy at all, son.
You're just confused from the move
and all this mess, that's all.
I don't like this house.
Didn't you want a house with a pool?
I don't want to swim there.
Why don't we move somewhere else?
Until your mom and I fix it up,
we can't resell it, so…
Remember how well the last one went?
-We made a killing.
-Exactly, we made a killing.
Is Mom still mad at me?
She'll get over it, don't worry.
Go on, eat.
Dani…
The pool gate.
Is someone there?
It's too late to play.
We're doing this again?
Eric!
Are you sure
you don't want to come too?
It'd be good for you
to get away for a few days.
I have to finish as soon as possible.
Give your parents my regards, OK?
What will we do with the house?
I don't know, Sara.
Right now, I don't know.
I can't live here.
And what do you suggest?
I don't know if you've realized,
but all our money is invested in this.
All of it, Sara.
Take care.
Hurry up, we're getting wet.
Mom, look.
It's cool, right? Incredible.
-It is so big.
-Come on.
Wow, it's really big!
Yes, but there's a lot to fix.
Can we keep this one?
Yes, for a while. Then we'll see.
You know how this goes.
Three, two, one… Ta-da!
Wow, it's really cool. It's so big!
And it's your room.
-Seriously?
-Yes.
-What color should we paint it?
-Can we hang up my drawings?
Yes, just like the last house.
Drawings all over.
Downstairs too, in the kitchen.
Dad, can we go swimming in the pool?
-Have you seen the water? And it's cold.
-Then we'll clean it.
Or I can take this room.
-No.
-No?
-Hi, honey. How are you?
-We can decorate that tree over there.
I'm really sorry
for how I acted this morning.
I didn't want to argue.
-Seriously?
-Yes.
-Yes, there or there.
-Talk to you later, OK?
-It's huge.
-Can we have a barbecue?
-Yes, of course.
-I love you.
I don't think he likes this room, huh?
-I do like it!
-No.
-I do, Mom.
-No, you don't like it.
-Yes.
-No.
He doesn't like it. We'll take this room.
Are you sure you like it?
-Yes.
-See? You don't like it.
The robot doesn't like it either.
He doesn't want to stay here.
I'll take this room.
Hello?
Sara, what is it?
What's wrong? Is everything OK?
Yes, why?
I couldn't understand your message.
There were weird voices, like screams.
I don't know, it scared me.
-Are you sure you're OK?
-Yes.
The service here is bad, maybe that's it.
Alright.
Listen, I'll call you later, OK?
OK. I love you.
I love you too.
Hi, honey. How are you?
How are you?
Dad, help!
-For Javier.
-Javier.
Yes, thanks a lot.
It's an honor. I have all your books.
SOUNDS FROM THE GREAT BEYOND
-Thank you.
-Thanks a lot.
-You're welcome.
-Yes.
Well, I'll leave you to it.
TO MY WIFE, WHO'S WAITING FOR ME
ON THE OTHER SIDE
Excuse me, who should I dedicate it to?
To Daniel.
Here you go.
Are you a fraud, Mr. Domingo?
-What was that?
-Is what you say in your book true?
Look…
I've published over ten books
on electronic voice phenomena.
If I didn't believe they were true,
I would have wasted my entire life.
I need you to listen to a recording.
Send it to me, my email is in the book.
I need you to listen now, please.
My son just died.
I think I recorded his voice.
I know it's hard to accept
the loss of a loved one,
especially a child,
but you're clinging
to something that won't return.
I'm asking you, please.
You're the only one who can help me.
Look,
this isn't how these things are done.
The waveform doesn't change
when the recording is playing.
Your book says that's a sign
that the EVP is real.
Isn't that right?
You think this one's real?
-Did you see the file I sent?
-Yes.
It may have been tampered with.
Why would a father fake
the voice of his dead son?
I don't know, Dad.
You just get so excited and then…
I have a feeling that this one is real.
Fine.
CIVIL GUARD
DO NOT ENTER
Should I unload?
-Is that a joint?
-It sure is.
It's a rolled cigarette.
As smart as you are,
I don't know how you can still smoke.
-Thanks for coming so soon.
-It's my pleasure.
Ruth, this is Daniel…
Velasco. Daniel Velasco.
Pleasure to meet you.
I'm so sorry about your son.
-Shall we go inside?
-Yes, of course.
I apologize for the mess,
but I'm sure you understand
it's been a tough few days.
Don't worry about it.
-Is anyone else here?
-No.
My wife is with her parents.
Is there a more secluded room,
a basement or something
for me to set up in?
No basement,
but there are many empty rooms.
What's this?
My son said someone talked to him on it.
In fact,
he said it was my voice he heard.
I understand.
In the recording, it sounded like
my son was shouting asking for help.
Do you think
he's trying to tell me something?
It's possible.
But I'll warn you,
the message may not be pleasant.
What do you mean?
Look…
I am sure that…
what comes after death
isn't what we've been told all this time.
Are you saying
my son is somewhere horrible?
He was only eight.
What could he have done to deserve that?
And is it any less horrible here?
Wars,
children starving to death, disease…
Why wouldn't it be the same there?
I can't tell you your son is
in heaven surrounded by angels, Daniel.
I'll tell you what I know,
and what I know
is we have to be ready for anything.
If my son needs help,
I'm willing to do anything, Mr. Domingo.
How did it happen?
Couldn't he swim?
He knew how to swim.
The police think he must have gotten
caught on a branch trying to get his ball.
But I know that's impossible.
He never came in alone. He didn't like it.
Don't ask me why, but I have a feeling
something else happened that night.
-Everything OK?
-Jesus!
Sorry, I didn't mean to scare you.
Don't worry, I'm just a little jumpy.
That's not the best trait
for this job, is it?
This isn't my job.
I just help my dad occasionally.
What's all this for?
For studying sounds
that the human ear can't hear.
Sounds from The Great Beyond,
like your dad's book.
Well, unlike him,
I don't think they come from the dead.
I'm sure the voice
I recorded was my son's.
How's it going, honey?
Everything is almost ready.
We can start whenever.
Then let's start.
Point towards the corner.
Are you getting anything?
No, nothing is registering.
Dad, I really don't think
we'll find anything.
Patience, sweetie.
Without patience,
we can't discover anything.
Are you enjoying this?
What's so bad
about enjoying your work, Ruth?
I don't know how Mom could stand you.
Dad.
What is it?
Tell Daniel to get out, he's interfering.
-Ruth.
-Yes?
What's going on?
You can't be seeing Daniel.
Of course I can.
He's in his son's room, I can see him.
I can see him too and he's outside.
You see something
in the boy's room, right?
This is really strange.
Can you hear that?
Yes.
It's coming from upstairs.
I'm going up.
Please be careful.
Can you see it?
Is it still here?
Dad.
-Ruth? I'm losing you.
-Dad…
-Ruth?
-Dad, do you hear me?
Ruth?
I'm losing you, Dad…
Dad, can you hear me?
Yes, I can now. What is it?
You have to get out right now.
What's going on?
It's right in front of you.
This is incredible.
Who is it?
I wish I could answer that, Daniel.
You were there. Didn't you see anyone?
I didn't see anyone or anything.
You're saying
there's a presence in my house?
Well…
Accept it for what it is,
a paranormal phenomenon.
You recorded that figure.
A thermal figure, Dad.
And to record a temperature,
it needs a physical body.
Just because we don't understand…
it doesn't mean it isn't real.
We have to try again tomorrow.
Germán.
Who's there?
Is that you, honey?
Come on. Come here.
Come on.
I'm waiting for you.
Hello, my love.
I'm dreaming.
Does this feel like a dream?
I bet you don't know what I'm making.
Sit down.
It's been so long.
Have you missed me?
I miss you every day.
You look the same, Sofía.
There had to be some advantage.
I've been waiting
for this moment for so long.
Haven't you?
I have too.
No.
We'll be together again.
Don't be afraid, my love.
Dad! What are you doing?
What the hell are you doing?
What are you doing? Daniel!
Dad, look at me! Dad!
Daniel!
What are you doing?
UNKNOWN CALLER
Hello?
Mom.
Who is this?
It's me, Eric.
Who is this? Is this a joke?
Mom, you have to come help me.
Eric?
Eric.
Mom, please. That man wants to hurt me.
What man?
A man Dad brought over.
Eric, where are you?
I'm hiding in my room, under the bed.
Hurry, pleas--
Eric?
Daniel!
Have you ever seen this?
Never.
I think I read about it.
What does it mean?
I don't know.
But… I don't think we can trust
what we see or what we hear.
It may all be a trick, Daniel.
A trick by who, Germán?
I don't know, Daniel.
Look…
I'm afraid the voice you recorded…
…may not have been your son's.
I'd recognize my son's voice anywhere.
-Why are you here?
-Who is that?
-Why didn't you call?
-Who is he?
Germán, a friend. He's a writer.
Sara, wait.
Come inside.
Come on.
You're from the house
with the voices, right?
You shouldn't go back there.
The voices know things about us,
they trick us,
and before you know it…
it's too late.
Eric?
Sorry my wife was so rude.
This has been very hard on her too.
Here it is.
I knew I'd seen it before. Look.
What is this?
What does it mean?
It's a threat.
It was used in the Middle Ages to warn
outsiders they were in her territory.
-Whose territory?
-A witch's territory.
It's this house.
It seems there was a court here
300 years ago.
A court, here?
The Inquisition.
Yes, they must have tortured and killed
dozens of innocent women here.
It's hard to believe
someone deserved to be burned.
But even though it was usually
an injustice, evil has existed--
Sara!
Dad, are you OK?
Sara! Hold on.
Sara!
Have you seen them argue lately?
Not really.
Like I said before,
I've only known Daniel for 24 hours.
Yeah, sure, if I remember anything,
I'll let you know.
If you remember anything, call us.
-OK.
-Thanks a lot.
Honey, I want you to see this.
Dad, we have to talk.
I think I know where to find
the remains of the people tortured--
Dad, listen to me. We have to leave.
-I'll get our stuff.
-But Ruth…
You heard the voices too.
They're here.
they're trying to tell us something.
I've been looking for this
my whole career.
We can't go now. Don't you get it?
I can't leave.
You're doing all this
because of Mom, right?
What do you mean?
What happened?
Dad, tell me what happened.
I think I deserve to know
why she did what she did.
I'm not a little girl anymore.
You're still my little girl.
It's over, we're leaving.
I hope one day you realize running
from everything isn't always the solution.
Dad, come here.
What is it?
No!
-What did I do?
-It wasn't you.
What was that?
-Daniel!
-Shit!
-What?
-She's here!
-Daniel, easy.
-Can't you feel her?
-I hear her everywhere.
-Nobody's here.
I'm telling you she's here!
Easy, it's OK. Nobody's here!
Nobody's here.
Look at me, Daniel. Nobody's here.
Easy, nobody's here.
It's OK. Look at me.
It's OK, Daniel. Easy.
Everything is OK.
Alright.
How do you live with this?
How do you live knowing your son
is asking for help and you can't help him?
Knowing you'll never really know
what happened to your family?
How the hell do you live with this?
It's not easy, Daniel.
I can assure you.
It's all my fault.
I asked them to come here.
Now I'm alone.
You're not alone.
Look…
I think I know where we can find…
…the root of what's happening
in this house.
If this was a court,
the people killed here
have to be hidden under our feet.
I think I know how we can get in.
Jesus.
What the hell happened to her mouth?
The Holy Inquisition believed
the punishment
should fit the crimes committed.
If the crime was blasphemy,
lying, or manipulation,
the torture was applied to the victim's
mouth so they couldn't use it anymore.
Kill her!
Witch!
You'll pay for your crimes!
It was her voice.
That's why they tried
to silence her forever.
All her rage has been
locked up in here all this time.
According to tradition, the only way
to destroy a witch is to burn her.
Here, take this one.
It won't be enough.
-I must have another.
-I'll go down, we have to hurry.
-Where's Daniel?
-He'll be right down.
You stay here.
-What? No way--
-Listen to me, Ruth.
You asked for the truth
about your mom's death.
You want to know why she killed herself,
you want answers?
Well, I don't know, Ruth. I wish I did.
I dragged you here
and I can't lose you too.
Promise me if I'm not back in ten minutes,
you'll leave this house immediately.
Promise me.
Fine.
No!
Dad!
Dad, are you OK?
Dad?
Daniel, is that you?
My baby.
Don't you remember me?
Mom, is that you?
You've grown so much, my love.
You're a woman now.
Come here, I want to see you.
I was very sad
because you didn't say goodbye to me.
You didn't come to my funeral.
Dad wouldn't let me.
I'm very sorry I couldn't be with you,
sweetheart.
But you're here now, we're together.
Come here.
Give me a hug.
Don't you want to hug your mom?
You're not my mom.
How could you say such a terrible thing?
Come, my love. Give me a hug.
No!
Don't let him do it, Dani.
If you let him, we'll disappear too.
I miss you both so much.
I miss you too.
Why don't you want to be with us anymore?
Dad.
Ruth.
Fight, Ruth.
You have to fight, honey.
Don't make me do it.
What's going on? What happened, Dad?
-You're hurt! Come on!
-Alright.
Let's leave!
Come on.
Careful. Watch your head.
Dad, I have to treat this, OK?
Dad…
How are you?
I'm fine, honey.
Do you think it worked?
I hope so.
But we're not staying to find out.
I can imagine
how you must have felt all this time.
But I needed an answer too.
That's why you started all this, right?
I always thought…
…there was something dark
behind your mom's death.
When she left us
in such a horrible and senseless way,
I understood evil exists
and it lies in wait.
And if that's the case…
…maybe good spirits
are nearby too, right?
So, now what?
Now you can live your life.
-Or maybe…
-"Or maybe"?
A few days ago…
…a friend who's a priest emailed me.
He wants me to interview a girl.
An exorcism?
I'm sure it's an untreated illness,
but you never know.
Sure.
Well, you need to rest for now.
And I need a week-long vacation.
Dad, help me!
Please let me go.
Mom!
No!
Let me go, Dad!
Please help me!
Daniel?
Ruth!
Daniel!
Hail Mary, full of grace,
the Lord is with thee. Blessed art thou…
Lord, hear our prayers
and don't allow our enemy to defeat us.
-Unleash your wrath on the beast.
-…now and at the hour of our death.
-Why am I here?
-And release your servant
so she is no longer prisoner.
Now and forever…
In the name of the Father,
the Son, and the Holy Spirit.
Amen.