Damn,
was that the brakes?
I just
want to be clear
on the last thing I'm hearing
'fore I die.
Imani, I didn't have time
to bring the truck in.
Mm-hmm.
And that's a good thing.
That means we got work.
This job
came up last minute.
No, a good thing is not dying
in a fiery crash.
Not gonna happen, Imani,
so just cool your jets.
Oh, you laughing
at that?
Oh,
is the new boy
allowed
to laugh at that, boss?
Oh, boy.
New guy can laugh
at whatever he wants
as long
as he carries his weight
and wears
the company shirt.
So what do we think?
I think we're gonna need
a bigger truck.
Work order says
one person's living here.
Let's get to work.
Think this dude's
a priest?
What?
Those are baby angels.
Stupid.
Yes?
Good morning.
Uh, Mr. Mueller?
Call me Vern.
Alright, Vern, um...
We're here
to facilitate your move.
Excellent.
Come in.
Come in, please.
Vern: You would like
to take a look around
before you get started?
Yeah, um, Imani,
show Carlos the ropes.
Uh, get the boxes,
the bubble wrap,
and the cart
from the truck.
And, Carlos,
get the shirt on, alright?
Got it.
Please, sit.
Can I get you
something to drink?
I'm fine standing,
thank you.
You -- You run a tight ship,
Mr. Schillinger.
I must say,
I'm -- I'm very impressed
with the way
you the way you, uh --
the -- the way you handle
your employees.
Right.
Yeah, I'm just doing my job,
Mr. Mueller.
Can I get you
to sign that for me, please?
Right.
No, you're good.
Relax, Imani.
You're doing just fine.
Imani, mira,man,
I'm grateful for you
hooking me up with this job
and everything,
for reals.
I need you to look me
in the eye right now, man.
What?
I'm 100% serious
when I tell you
that I'm notworking in
no haunted house today.
Stop.
Why are you laughing?
Look at it!
Man, just because
the original Crypt Keeper
is living here
in Grey Gardens
don't make
this shit haunted.
I get that reference.
No, I'm -- I'm good.
Trying to be a good role model
for my daughter.
Good. No drugs in here.
Schillinger ain't about that.
Nothing that's gonna
get you in trouble with
your parole officer.
Hey, speaking of,
you and Schillinger
have a --
an interesting relationship.
Yeah,
that's my boo.
Man, you know the hustle.
Who else
gonna give ex-cons
a good,
solid job like this?
Yeah, you're right.
He's a good guy.
Damn right.
He went to prison,
managed to
turn his life around,
and that ain't
no easy thing to do.
Bro, odds are
stacked against us, man.
Yeah.
History repeats itself,
lest we stop it from doing so.
Kind of like his motto
or whatever.
Yeah, that's deep.
Yeah.
I like that.
Schill's all about
second chances.
He a second-chance
motherfucker.
'Sides,
work ain't that bad.
Damn sure beat be bouncing
at the club -- too many fights.
Not the best move
when fighting's
what I went in there for.
Alright, get out of here.
Geez.
Oh, shoot!
How do I get me
a tool belt like that?
Oh, you got to earn this shit,
motherfucker,
and you can start
by taking some of them boxes in.
Get, get, get,
get to work.
You've got to earn
this shit, motherfucker.
I'm just gonna take a belt.
You got to --
Forget that.
Thank you.
So, your home is a bit larger
than expected,
but we should have everything
out by midday tomorrow.
Well, I'm sorry to say,
but that won't do.
Why is that?
I told the new owner
I would be out by morning.
We'll do our best
to accommodate you,
but I can't make
any promises.
It's a very large home,
and there's only
three of us here.
Let me be
very clear --
It is in
your very best interest
to see that the first
and the second floors are packed
and shipped by first light
tomorrow morning.
The basement and the attic
are not your concern.
I will
handle them myself.
That is
four times your rate.
Uh, that's a bit
unconventional.
But we love
four times our rate.
Indeed.
You should listen
to your worker.
Well,
this workeris in.
What about you,
Carlos?
I think my lady would be happy
with the extra cash,
but it seems like
a lot of rooms
and we don't -- we don't know
what's upstairs.
I'm not so sure,
Vern.
Fine.
Here is
another thousand dollars.
It is imperative
that the move happen tonight.
Schill, come on.
Let's do this.
Okay, Mr. Mueller,
you got a deal.
Good.
See that these boxes
are on the truck by morning.
They will be.
Hmm,
I-I got no signal.
It's a very old house,
constructed mainly
of stone and brick.
Yeah, makes sense,
I guess.
You'll get a chance to, uh,
text her on break, Carlos.
All nighter,
huh?
Looks like it.
Let's get started
in here.
It's a lot of furniture.
Let's get it covered,
get it onto the truck.
Uh, Vern, you might want
to take a few steps back.
Can get a little crazy in here.
I will be downstairs,
Mr. Schillinger,
if you have any questions,
and, uh, just knock.
He can call me a worker
all he want.
We gettin' paid,
ladies.
We're only getting paid
if we make the deadline.
Let's work.Let's get it.
Come on. Shit!
Gosh.
Hey, jefe?
What's the protocol
for when a doorway's being
a tight little butthole?
Uh, the protocol's never
say that again, like ever.
Okay, my bad.
Hey, but for reals,
what do we do?
Let's move this back
and out the way.
Yeah, door's gonna have to
come off its hinges.
First, we got to close it.
And then let's see.
Need a
flathead screwdriver.
Just get that lodged
right up in there, like so,
and, uh, yeah,
that's it.
Think you can
handle that?
Okay.
Bro, that was like two seconds,
man, three tops.
Glad you're impressed.
Hey, I feel like
you're kidding,
but I'm for reals.
I-I'm impressed.
You just smile at me?
You smile?
He's got teeth.
Alright, we're going two
on this one, Carlos.
Okay.
Think you are strong,
huh?
Uh, alright, let's call it.
Let's make it lunch.
Keep it to 20 minutes.
Still got a lot to do, right?
Yeah.
Fuck it.
So what you boys
spending your share on?
It's going to my daughter's
college fund.
Well, alright, Oprah.
What?I'm just sayin',
Oprah always
openin' up a school.
I'm for reals.
My daughter is gonna be
the first one in my family
to go to college.
That's pretty decent
of you, Carlos.
I'm just
fucking with you.
You're a good dad.
Just doing my best,
I guess.
What about you,
Schill?
Uh, yeah,
first priority
is getting the brakes fixed
on the truck.
Whatever's left over
will go back into the business.
Alright, let's take
a little time to use the phones,
and then we've got
to get back at it, alright?
Hey, man, come on!Carlos!
Is that
what I think it is?
Yeah, I guess some of
that money
should go towards
laser removal.
So you a skinhead?I was.
Not anymore.
I needed protection
in jail.
Fuck. Fuck!
Are you for reals?
It was easy
to rally around hate.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
"Rally"'s the right
fucking word.
But I don't practice
or believe in
the Brotherhood's
hate anymore.
But you out here
calling it a "brotherhood."
Look, I'll tell you what
I told Imani a long time ago.
If you want to leave,
I get it.
I'm out.
No, no. 'Los, 'Los.
Look,
I wouldn't be here
if I didn't trust this man
with my life,
and I wouldn't have
brought you in, either.
So why
you still got them?
Honestly,
I don't feel like
I deserve to be free of them.
Got to earn clean skin.
Yeah.
I ain't got clean skin,
neither.
I sold it at first.
Then I started using.
Then they
took my daughter away.
So yeah.
I'm saving my money
for her.
Sure, man.
Yo, can I ask you a question --
about your tats?
You got to be 100
with me, though.
Sure.
Why they so shitty?
Some skinhead with bad breath
and needle ink did it.
Alright, Imani,
how about you?
Care to share?
No, I'm good.
We just had
a raw moment in front of you.
Now's your time.
Cool. No.
Yeah, no?
I mean,
I'm at peace with my past.
Some dudes just deserve
to catch these hands.
I'm zen.
Yo, 100%, you're not.
200% you're not.
Fuck you.
Uh, alright,
we've got to get back at it.
We still got a lot
to do.
For my first day,
I'm doing pretty good, huh?
Yeah, you working your ass of.
I know.
I can give you that.
It's almost midnight.
Yeah,
we're making decent time.
Place is huge, bro.
Yeah, alright, I'm gonna
get going on the bathroom.
Carlos,
you can go in the library,
and, Imani, get to work
on the kids' room, alright?
Kids' room?
Yo,
the kids are 80.
Alright, come on.
I'm gonna do
a quick sweep downstairs.
I'll be right back.
Hey, hey,
you need help?
No, it's just
a quick sanity check.
You guys get going.
Something I can help you with,
Mr. Schillinger?
Uh, I suppose this is
the off-limits basement.
Yes, that's right.
All handled.
Nothing needed
from you here.
Something else?
No, I was just noticing
the lock.
Ah, yes.
The crest --
lock seems pretty old,
safe to say.
Mm, yes.
You recognize it,
uh, the crest?
It looks familiar.
Is it German?
Oh, very good.
Yes.
Uh, you have
seen it before?
I'm not sure.
Ah.
Well, something about it
must have caught your eye.
Maybe I've seen it before
and I just can't place it.
I am impressed.
Very few people
would recognize it,
an old German lock
like that.
Uh,
are you a collector?
No.
Oh.
Well, then, I wonder
where you have seen it.
Something else?
No.
I'll get back to work.
Very good.
Uh,
do let me know
if you have
any more questions.
Must admit,
I'm suddenly just
as curious as you are.
This shit is creepy.
Hey, Carlos!
I'm gonna be done
with my room in 30, 45 tops.
Imani, it's not always
a competition!
But I will
crush that time.
Yeah, we'll see.
Ow.
You ain't in a haunted house,
I promise you.
It's just it's an old man,
fucking just doin' his thing.
Book box.
Whoa, hey.
Carlos,
it's just me.
Yo, I'm sorry, boss.
It's -- It's this house.
It's Vern. It's --
I'm just jumpy.
Yeah, well, I think
there's reason to be jumpy.
Oh.
It's like an actual nightmare
that you just said that.
Something's just setting off
alarm bells,
so just keep your head
in the game for me
and let me know if you see
anything weird.
Jefe,I've seen like a thousand
weird things since I got here.
Alright.
And I'll let you know --
anything weird.
Alright.
I know you've been hustling.
Let's see if we can pick up
the pace even more, okay?
I just want
to finish this job
and get the fuck
out of here.
Roger that.
Okay.
Alright. Okay.
And what I was saying
is you need to use
a smaller book box, okay?
Books are heavy.
Trust me.
You got it,
boss.
Fuck that.
Small books in a big box,
baby.
And one big book.
This thing.
The fuck?
Come on!
This dude
ever heard of a Kindle?
Oh.
Why's it in German?
Come on, man!
Hey, yo, boss, come here, man!
Something weird, man.
Anything weird, you said,
right?
Yo, boss, hurry up!
The fuck,
Carlos?
You said
anything weird, right?
Look at that.
This dude's
got a ton of this.
It's everywhere,
man.
Aah!
The fuck
you grabbing me for?
You know you don't sneak up
on a sister like that.
How do you let your whisper
louder than your yell?
Guys,
my gut's not sitting right.
I-It's this place,
this client.
Say less.
What you want to do?
Maybe we just
call it and leave.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ooh,
that's fucking with my coin.
Look, I get it,
but we all could use the cash.
Alright.
I think if we tackle
this together, we can do it.
We double time it.
Are you shitting me?
Imani,
Vern's the type of dude
that pushes around a stroller
with a fake baby in it.
He can push
whatever he wants in a stroller.
If the money's right,
the deal is real.
Let's just finish this shit up
and get out.
Yeah, Carlos, look,
my gut's going haywire, man,
but we really don't got reason
to call the cops, right?
I don't know.Think about it.
Is this man dangerous,
or is he just strange?
The dude's a freak.
Okay, I agree, and look,
it's my job to protect my crew
and I don't
take that lightly.
So if you want to go,
you just say so and we're gone.
But I say
we get this job done fast.
Get that money.Man is like 100.
It's three of us.
We'll be alright.Come on.
That tuition ain't cheap.
Alright.
Let's wrap this shit up quick,
alright?
Yeah.
Money makes me
do crazy shit.
Cool first day,
by the way.
Got a screwdriver?
Yeah.
Fuck!
What you find?
Don't!
It's just a suitcase.
Shit.
But it's little.Jesus.
Yo, hold up.
You told me
I could call it.
I'm calling it.
Let's go.
Don't open it.
It's birth certificates.
Twins.
Let me see.
The actual human teeth.
This is not happening.
This is not happening
on my first day!
Some actual World War II shit
right here.
See?
This dude could be like 100.
Fuck! Fuck!
Come on.
Shh. Be quiet.
It's coming from
up there.
Old-ass Vern told us to stay
out the fucking attic, remember?
Yeah, yeah, she's right.
We got to get the fuck
out of here, man.
What do you think
is up there?
Monsters.Monsters.
Look around.
It's kids.
Yeah.
We got to call
the cops.
Sure as hell do.
Imani, get outside
and make that happen.
Carlos,
you're with me.
Let's do this.
We got this.Okay.
Shit, it's locked.
Hey, Imani, let me get
your screwdriver.
I got it.
Yo, Imani,
that was badass.
Come on, baby.
Shit!
This is my exit cue.
I'm gonna outside
and find a cell signal, okay?
Yeah.
Alright.
Well, hey, hold on,
let me get that flashlight.
Alright, Carlos,
you're on watch.
You hear anything,
you hide, okay?
Yeah,
I got you.
Vern?
Oh, geez!
Man, yo, Schill!
Schill, Schill,
Schill, Schill!
Aah! Schill!
Schill, help me, man!
Don't leave me!
Schill!
Jesus!
Oh, my God.
Are you okay?
No.
What the hell
is this place?
I don't know.
But you do.
You knew something was way off
right when we started this job.
You know more
than you're telling.
I'd just be guessing.
Okay, go.
Holocaust experiments,
the Angel of Death.
What does that
even mean?
Josef Mengele.
He was
the Angel of Death.
He was a Nazi doctor
who was performing these --
these horrible experiments
on the Jews
in the concentration camps,
genetic stuff.
He was --
He was obsessed with...
Yo, what?
He was obsessed
with twins.
Oh, shit, twins?!
So, what, this dude Vern,
he's a relative or something?
Or a copycat, uh,
some nutjob continuing
his experiments, I don't know.
Oh, come on.
Who's up there?
Forgive
my general appearance.
Everything was packed
for the move.
Usually,
I assure you,
I am much
more professional.
Imani: No, man,
come on, please.
I really did intend
to have you in my home
only as movers,
but then, you did not
obey my instructions.
And my -- my instructions
were very, very explicit.
And, well,
this became inevitable.
Guys, help!
Please, help!
No, no, no, no,
the walls are reinforced.
Your friends
cannot hear you.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
Carlos, Schill, help!
I was always very fascinated
by the ocular region,
and the procedure
which I will now administer
will harvest
one of your eyes.
You sick fuck, no.
No!
No, no, no.
I cannot --
I cannot allow you
and your friends
to leave this house,
but instead of this whole thing
being erased,
I will put you
to very good use.
Hey, hey, it's okay.
We're not
gonna hurt you.
It's okay.
We're here
to help you.
Carlos.
No, no, no, no.
We got to help her,
okay?
Hey,
what's your name?
Shit.
Carlos, do you have that marker?
Okay, hey, look, here.
Here, here, here, here.
Anne.
Okay. Hi.
I-I'm Albert,
and this is Carlos.
Anne, Anne, Anne, is --
is there anybody else here?
Where?
Carlos, Schill!
No, no.
You will become
part of my work.
What work?
Oh, many cultures
have acknowledged the --
the power of the eye.
Yes, and something that is
fascinating to me
is a tribe
in Africa --
they -- they consume
the eyeball for vitality.
But I found that the enzyme
of the optic nerve --
it must be injected
rather than ingested
in order
to prolong life.
No, no.
Mm, decades of trial and error
have taught me
that the -- the specimen --
that would be you --
must be alive
in order for the optic nerve
to -- to release the enzyme.
Where are my friends?
Where are my friends?!
Oh, they -- they will be here
very soon, I assure you.
No!
No, no, no,
man, please, please!
Please, no!
No!
No, no, no,
no, no, no.
No, man, come on, please.
Please, no.
No!
No, you --
No, no, no, no, man,
no, please.
Fuck you!
No, no, no, no, no.
Shh, shh.
It is very quick work for me
at this point.
Aah!
W-What do you think,
Carlos?
Carlos,
we've got to help them.
look at me.
We need
to get them to the truck.
Right.
Okay,
you take this flashlight.
Anne, alright, here.
I'm gonna
give you my shirt, okay?
Take this, Anne.
Okay, alright, I got you.
I got you.
It's alright,
it's alright.
Just gonna get you
to the truck.
Okay.
Just come with us, okay?
It's okay.
Shit.
We need to find
another exit.
What about Imani?First things first,
we need to find
an exit route --
uh, windows,
a rear door.
Anne?
Oh, shit!
I see you have met
Anne and Sarah.
Mr. Schillinger,
please release my girls.
You piece of shit.
You do this to children?
I'm gonna kill you.
Ah, well, if that is where
you would like to set
the tenor
of this discourse...
I will match it.
Carlos, Carlos.
Son of a --
I'll kill you!
No, Carlos,
you stay with the girls.
She's not dead,
Mr. Schillinger.
No, there is still
another eye to harvest,
and I need her alive.
She may experience
extreme fear.
It's okay.
It's okay, come on.
You must come to my lab
for harvesting.
Otherwise,
this is all for nothing.
They need
medical attention.
No,
she needs myattention!
these are children!
They're not experiments!
They're just like us!
Nein!
They are not
just like us!
No! Schill!
Schill, come on.
Schill,
no, no, no, no, no.
It's alright,
bro.
We just
got to put some --
Stop the bleeding,
man.
It's alright.
Come on, man.
Come on.
No.
Anne...
I do not think this man
is who you hoped he was.
Hey,
where you going?!
Anne!
I knew it.
Breathe, breathe, breathe.
Concentrate, concentrate.
Breathe slowly.
I can't.
Can't what,
man?
I knew --
I knew there would be
a reckoning.
I can't do this without you,
man, come on!
Shit, come on, man!
Please!
Help -- Help --
Help the girls.
No, please, no.
Shit.
Come on, Schill!
Come on, man, come on!
Oh, shit.
Fuck you, freaks!
Ah, finally...
you reveal yourself,
Mr. Schillinger.
Huh.
Hey, Sarah.
Hi, hi.
Aah!
Go on!
You can't get in, can you?
You can't get in, can you?!
Ha!
Aah!
You have made
a truly terrible choice
for your hiding spot.
It is the room I use
for my failed experiments.
Zyklon B.
It will only be
a few moments,
and it will take effect.
Help!
It is a shame
it has to come to this.
I really...
would like to have
used all of you in my work.
Auf wiedersehen.
Aaah!
I died.
I know I died.
How?
I brought you back.
You're to help
with her.
Why?!
I am a doctor
and a scientist.
This is
my life's work.
Why didn't you just
let me die?
I deserved to die.
"Deserved"?!
No.
No, no, no, no.
No, we do not
have to hide anymore.
This is our time,
my friend.
I know who you are.
Yes, I do.
You have been hiding,
but now you are amongst
your people here.
I am nothing
like you.
Oh, well,
your -- your tattoo
seems to tell
a very different story.
It's prison ink!
That's the story!
That's it!
No, no, no, no.
This -- This is not the sign
of a follower.
It tells me
you were a leader.
Yes.
I have people
on the inside,
mutual friends.
What do you think
you know?
Oh, Heidelberg.
Cass Vogel,
his brother Friedrich,
Simon Hesse.
Need I go on?
No, it is not a coincidence
that you are here.
I scouted the right man
for this job.
Who are you?
Who are you really?
I am
Dr. Joseph Mengele.
That's not possible.
Absolutely not possible!
How?
I showed you.
The same way that you yourself
have cheated death.
It's not possible.
It is a serum
I created
harvesting
viable subjects.
In this
particular case,
it was
your schwarzworker's eyeball.
Imani?
Schill?
This dude's fucking crazy.
Imani,
you're alive.
Are you okay?
I have one fucking eye,
Schill.
Hell, no,
I'm definitely not okay.
This is fucked up,
man.
Who is this psycho?
Schill?
Ah, your friend knows more
than he's letting on.
Tell her the truth.
Imani,
don't listen to him.
The hell
is he talking about, Schill?
Do you know what
this, uh, this tattoo means,
the eagle
on his chest,
the story it tells
about the man who wears it?
Man, yeah,
I know all about that.
Prison makes a person
do wild shit to survive.
Nothing new to me.
So you believe that this, uh,
this was earned in prison?
Shut up!
Imani,
you know me.
Don't listen to him.
Yeah.
Yeah, I do.
Have you ever noticed
how -- how this tattoo is clean?
Professional?
Not like the others,
not roughshod?
Man,
they all look like trash to me.
Ah, but this was
long before he went to prison.
What is he talking about,
Schill?
He did not find
the Brotherhood in prison.
No,
he was already active.
This tattoo means
he was a deputy,
not exactly
a low-ranking position.
Schill,
I'm dead serious.
Why is this man
talking shit about you?
Because it's true.
No.
No, no, no, no, no!
It can't be!
Imani --
No,
it can't be right!
We were supposed
to be friends, man!
You told me
this was some prison shit!
We arefriends.No,
if we were really friends,
you wouldn't have lied
to my fucking face!
I wasn't lying
to you.
Man.
Oh!
I get it, Schill.
I'm straight.
You feel
with that white guilt,
here comes Imani
to make you feel better.
Fuck out here!
I was the only guy
that took a chance on you!
An angry Black female ex-con
who's unemployed!
Remember that!
Remember where you were!
Oh, so you saved me now,
huh?!
Is that what
you're telling yourself?
Fuck you, Schill!
I hope I helped your weak,
white Nazi ass
feel better
about yourself.
Fuck you.
You should've stayed dead,
motherfucker!
There comes that rage.
There's that rage
we all knew was inside of you!
Yeah, you keep talking.
You just keep talking.
I'll fucking kill you myself,
swear to God.
Strapped to that table?
What are you gonna do?!Just keep talking.
Keep talking, that shit, Schill,
and you gon' find out.
Fuck.
You were right.
About?
I am who I am.
This world will never
let me be anything else.
I read about you.
I know about
your experiments.
I need to know how.
Show me.
Mm.
An appeal
to my vanity.
Hitler saw the Jews
as vermin,
but the Jews
considered themselves
to be chosen.
And they were right.
Yeah.
What?
The trauma they have
experienced over the centuries
made them stronger
as a people,
and therefore, their -- their
enzymes were much more potent.
And Imani?
Why use her
for this serum?
Her people, too, have suffered
similar trauma, yes.
And they --
they carry the enzyme,
and Imani is,
oh, an exemplary producer.
The girls in the attic.
Ooh...
The girls.
Yeah.
Well, the more trauma
they suffer,
the stronger
the enzymes...
...the longer I live.
The house,
the move...
never was a buyer,
was there?
No.
Too, uh, too many Jews
have gone missing.
And now
I'm being hunted,
so I have to
relocate quickly.
I was tipped off by a member
of the Brotherhood.
We have many well-placed
brothers these days.
Don't we,
Mr. Schillinger?
Yeah.
I will now harvest
the other eye,
and then I will
terminate her, and, uh...
We must move now.
I-I need to see
how it's done.
I'm weak.
I'll need your help,
but...
I need to see
how it's done.
Hmm. Well...
I suppose, uh...
I suppose there is
a certain honor in that.
I heard you.
Watch it.
Imani!
Imani, Imani!
That's the Angel of Death,
motherfucker!
We worked hard
for this.
We've got to find Carlos
and the girls.
Okay.
What?
No, no!
Imani!
Violence --
I abhor violence.
Nein!Oh.
No! He was my baby!
I created him!
We got to get the hell
out of here.
What's that?
No, no, no. No.
Shit.
No, no, no.
Fuck!
Anne!
Can't do shit with
broken legs, can you?
Imani!
Fuck you,
Nazi piece of shit!
We will never die.
Help, help!
Help us, please!
Help!
You idiot, you.
You stupid, stupid,
stubborn man.
Fine.
Do it,
but you cannot kill all of us.
No, we --
we are too strong now.
You are one of us.
No.
No, I'm not.
The proof
of your belief
is -- is etched
into your skin!
It's your blood.
Aaah!
You...
You think you can kill
our legacy,
just carve it out?!
No, no, no, you cannot.
It is too big for you
to just -- just cut away.
You -- You think
you can kill
what has risen
over the decades?
You think you can kill
our legacy?!
Well, come the fuck on!
Come on!
So you, uh, stabbed me
in the chest with that needle.
For what?
So we can live to fight
another day, my friend.
I told you --
Schill's a second-chance
motherfucker.
Straight up,
Imani.
Hey, come to think of it,
both you motherfuckers
owe me and my eyeball
your lives.
You're welcome.
Thank you,
Imani.