My dad...
My dad is a police officer.
He is strong, kind,
and like a superhero.
He helps those who get
lost or lose something.
He works really hard for everyone.
I would like to become a
police officer just like my dad.
Hey.
The criminal is Koji Tanaka, age 29.
Previous convictions for
robbery and abduction.
He's kidnapped and held
a female passerby captive.
He has barricaded himself
in an abandoned building.
There is no time to
consider the circumstances!
Those of you in the riot squad,
don't go easy and please kill him off!
Divine punishment!
Secured!
It's an engineer!
Ruka, it's an engineer!
Tokyo Gore Police
The police force of Tokyo
has been privatized.
Tokyo Police Special Riot Squad
Osamu Mifune Squad Leader
We will protect you.
The crime extra-territoriality
law is our ally.
We have no mercy for criminals.
Serial killer Yoshiki Takahashi
Murdered 15 kindergarten children
We will protect you.
Tokyo Police Corporation.
Serial killer Yoshiki Takahashi
Dead
Privatizing the police will lead
to more plentiful lives for us.
For a better society
Tokyo Police Corporation
Ruka always shows no mercy.
She's definitely a model hunter.
There's no mistake. This one
is definitely an engineer.
Within these past few years...
These so called "engineers,"
criminals who have
remodeled their bodies
to turn into ferocious, fiendish
murderers, have increased in numbers.
An engineer's main characteristic
is that when they're wounded,
their wounds become a dangerous weapon.
Also...
a key-shaped tumor is
always found within the body.
To kill an engineer, you have to destroy
or sever that piece from the body.
Where did they come from?
What is their objective?
The only thing that is clear is
that I have the duty to hunt them.
Because I am a police
officer, an "engineer hunter."
Privatizing the police will lead
to more plentiful lives for us.
Tokyo Police Corporation.
Privatizing the police will lead
to more plentiful lives for us.
Tokyo Police Corporation.
Privatizing the police will lead
to more plentiful lives for us.
Tokyo Police Corporation.
Bar lndependant
Welcome.
What would you like?
Orange juice.
I'm on patrol.
So hard-working.
You're always so serious.
What happened?
You're bleeding.
Are you okay?
Let's go to the hospital.
Let's go!
What are you guys doing?
Stop wandering around!
Don't ever come around here again.
Are you okay?
Mama, are you open?
I'll come back another time.
I'm sorry. I'll leave.
It's okay.
You have a righteous job, right?
Then you should sit here boldly.
Ruka, there's trouble!
Come back to the station immediately!
I have to go.
Privatizing the police will lead
to more plentiful lives for us.
For a better society
Tokyo Police Corporation
Happy birthday, Ruka!
Happy birthday!
Plus, congratulations on your
achievement of hunting 50 engineers.
You have acquired a single badge.
Congratulations!
Yeah!
The Shouwa seesaw.
It's a sad conclusion.
If you close your eyes
the flower hangs and sways.
The night butterfly.
Palm of the white hand
on your chest.
If we decorate it gently...
When my father, a police
officer, died at his post,
the chief of this station
raised me like his own daughter.
To me, this place is the same
as a home with a waiting family.
It was supposed to be the same...
But...
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Here, Ruka.
Happy birthday.
Thank you, Dad!
Come on, hurry. You, too.
What are you saying is wrong?
What are you doing?
What are you saying is wrong with me?
It's okay. It's okay, so...
Please! Please, just tell me,
will you?
Let go of me!
What are you saying is wrong with me?
It's okay.
Don't worry.
It's okay. Calm down.
Did it hurt?
It was so good.
Do you want to do it again?
W-What is it? I didn't.
This was consensual.
Extension fee.
Much appreciated. The next
is also here at 307. Hurry up.
If it goes over even one
second, it's an extension.
I even made a "10-minutes left" call.
I was using a vibrator, so I
couldn't hear the phone vibrating.
Hurry up and go!
I'm sorry.
Come on.
You're absolutely right.
That doesn't matter.
Just hurry up and pay!
Thank you for waiting.
Yuka, right? I understand.
Then may I have the hotel and the time?
Okay.
Okay, in 30 minutes.
I understand. I will make the girl
head over. Please treat her well.
Yuka, in 30 minutes, SM play.
Don't be saying you don't
want to do things that hurt.
SM play is good money,
and you know that.
Right, right.
You just have to do it.
You want to do kinky stuff?
There are cuter and
younger girls for that.
How about Yoko?
I can call her right away.
Also, from now on, please
make reservations by phone.
There is a website and
a cell phone site too.
I'm not available.
I'm...
America Yokocho
You. Yes, you. What's up
with these documents?
Commit suicide by seppuku, hara-kiri!
Yes, I understand.
I'll commit hara-kiri.
If I was brave enough to
stop the hara-kiri, then...
If I had the courage to
say I couldn't do it...
If I was able to say my own self
was more important than my job...
Ah, he's done it!
Hara-kiri is also suicide.
Stop the Hara-kiri
Heaven's Punishment
Incident occurrence.
Scene of the crime is the
Tokyo subway Miyama station.
Again...
Once again, the body of a prostitute
has been discovered.
She was broken, cut into pieces
and packed up into a small box.
There wasn't even a drop of
blood at the scene of the crime,
but there was testimony that
they heard a security buzzer,
so the location of discovery and the
crime are thought to be the same.
Engineer?
Yeah.
With the cases so far...
Our point of view is that engineers
are generally simple berserkers
and they usually don't think
of evidence or their safety.
But the criminal this time is
carrying on everything pretty calmly.
It's definitely the same criminal.
Even though he's an engineer, this guy
is definitely trying to pick a fight.
If a newcomer like that has shown up,
it means he's trouble.
Ruka, we're counting on you.
Let's go stylish with wrist-cutting.
It's cute!
The design is cute.
When you cut, it doesn't hurt that much.
The blood becomes tastier.
Die!
No, no!
Wrist Cutter G!
New product!
It's a cutter with a cute design.
It hurts! It hurts!
I-It's a mistake.
Ouch!
It's a mistake!
I-It's a mistake!
It's not me!
You have the wrong person!
I think that's enough!
It's not me...ouch!
Please, it's a mistake!
Ouch!
It really is a mistake!
Please forgive me!
It's a mistake! It really wasn't me!
An act of molestation
is clearly a crime.
Remember...
Everything...
It cuts well. It cuts well.
The Japanese sword of Kohka.
It cuts well!
It cuts well. It cuts well.
The Japanese sword of Kohka.
It cuts well!
It cuts well. It cuts well.
The Japanese sword of Kohka.
It cuts well!
I thought they stabbed each other.
There isn't any particular
abnormality in your body.
For now there's evidence.
Once you catch your breath...
...stop by the autopsy room.
Let's go.
From this part of the face,
we didn't find the key.
But with this much evidence left, we
should be able to identify it right away.
Granted that it's still alive
after losing half of its face...
It's definitely an engineer.
Engineers...
We have to kill them by any means.
They are
humanity's new enemy.
Yes, I agree.
Extermination is the only answer.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
You should rest today.
Bar lndependant
Akino Miyama.
Died at the age of 24.
It says that he committed suicide.
Oh.
His parents also died
before and after that.
This college...
What's the KGE Laboratory?
That's the laboratory this one was at,
but it's not there anymore.
For now, I need the
laboratory's contact address.
There are countless numbers
of them in the whole country.
Please print it out.
Okay.
Thanks.
The number that you have
dialed is not in service anymore
and has been changed.
The new number is...
I'm sorry, but please check
the number again and redial...
KGE Laboratory
Branch Locations Listing
Fly to the right.
Fly to the left.
Fly south.
Fly north.
Go away...
I am an able eulogist...
About Megumi's disappearance...
...no one knows.
Are your siblings,
family, and friends safe?
Are they exposed to
the threat of a madman?
This is not fiction.
For those of you that cried
yourselves to sleep, you can relax now.
Remote execution.
The government is the
ally of the victim.
Government lnformation
The volcano erupted, and
the rain of ash poured down.
The snow of death falls and accumulates.
Everything is buried under rubbish.
Akino Miyama
Like ruins...
Just like this town of cruelty...
How everything is going to be buried...
Ruka
Am I also going to be buried?
Haruka Yoshioka
Recorded by: Akino Miyama
Subject: Haruka Yoshioka
There is something I
need you to look into.
Haruka Yoshioka.
Find all apartments under the name
Haruka Yoshioka in the last 10 years.
Haruka Yoshioka
Address Listing
Ah, so tired.
I can't do all-nighters anymore.
Hey!
Is anyone here?
At times like this,
I wish I had speed.
This feels so good.
It soaks into my body.
I wish I had never been born.
You guys...
If you're going to end up like me,
then die while you can!
For our future. Now
recruiting police officers.
Tokyo Police Corporation.
At the show hut
the light comes on.
It's what that child put in.
Hanaichimonme.
I don't understand words.
I cannot hear you.
If you are lonely,
you should come eat some tsuruko.
you should come eat some sushiko.
A moon with wrinkles
cuts through the night.
With the dripping device
it draws the red down.
The hide and seek
that child was watching.
There is a night that you don't know.
Let's gather flowers Hanaichimonme.
I bare your secret.
Did you forget the gold fish's eyes?
My feelings, do you know them?
Come on, let's fight with soldiers.
Number 31.
69!
Thank you.
In use
We will be starting human
body-restructuring surgery.
What! Hey, hey!
What!
No!
Stop!
You like being chewed on, right?
Take this.
You will become one of us.
Welcome to the world of engineers.
Haruka Yoshioka
Address Listing
Old lady bit my leg and it's satisfied.
Older brother licked me,
so my eye has a sty.
Are you really going to do it?
Yeah, I'm going to do it.
That guy made me incomplete.
For a better society
Tokyo Police Corporation
That guy made me into the devil.
Before the night ends...
Before I fall to hell...
With a red light bulb dangling.
Let's go out.
Let's go kill.
Pomegranate tastes
like blood, tastes like sin.
We are incomplete lemons.
The two of us makes
one whole lemon.
Yesterday, the bird
that I had as a pet
died spitting out blood.
Its small beak was dyed red,
without knowing the sky, it died.
Where did my little bird go?
Where did my purity go?
A canary that forgot its song.
A canary that lost its virginity.
Let's throw them away
to the back mountain.
I know
about Hirohito,
that you are not a virgin.
I know.
You slept with Masako.
You slept with Old Lady Matsuki.
You slept with Anesa.
I know.
What is resistance?
You and I shall
never be tied together.
You are useless!
From here on...
...we're going to have an engineer hunt!
If they are even a little suspicious,
kill them all without mercy!
All of them!
It took quite a while.
Congratulations.
Come on, come on...
Here, sit down.
The man with a license to kill
A long time ago,
there was a man with a license to kill.
He was a sniper for the police, and
his shots never missed the target.
Once, he aimed from
the summit of Mt. Fuji.
Once, he aimed from Tokyo Tower.
He was able to kill the
criminals every time.
The moment the criminal's
eyeballs fluttered in the air,
the man savored a supreme sensation.
Even to a man like this,
there was a family.
He had a wife and a young boy.
One day, another order
to kill came to him.
The target this time was a criminal
who barricaded himself inside a building.
The man resigned.
He was barely paid any of his severance.
That is what an organization is like.
His son continued to grow.
The mother worked hard
until she no longer could.
Their son's mind structure was so
different that he was called a "genius."
He said that he wanted to study the
specific field of genetic engineering.
But there wasn't that kind of money
in this family to let their
son get the education he wanted.
That was when the man's old
boss showed up in front of him.
We want you to kill
a certain individual.
That was what the boss said.
And the man took that request.
That individual was the leader of the
group against police privatization.
He was also another police officer.
When the man succeeded in
the murder of the leader,
that man was also killed.
And his spurting blood
was poured down on his son.
At the time my father was murdered,
I was at college studying
the genetics of murderers.
We collected genes from
murderers all over the world
to research and to lower
the occurrence of crimes.
However...
My father was killed
right in front of me.
And my motivation changed.
I took all the killer genes
they had stored at the lab
and injected them into my body.
I couldn't forgive them.
The ones who killed my father.
I planned to turn myself into a
complete killer and seek revenge.
But...
I fell into a state of confusion
and stood on the lab's rooftop.
Then I jumped.
When I regained consciousness,
I was in front of an enormous door.
Did I die?
Strangely, I didn't
have any sense of fear.
The next moment,
I woke up in the hospital.
The professor said that
it came out of my head.
I researched it.
The more I researched, the more
I came to see how amazing it was.
It surpassed all other killer genes.
So I reproduced and cultured it.
That's when I started coming
up with an innovative idea.
The man who killed your father is dead.
So at this point, personal
revenge is meaningless.
The problem is the man who
ordered your father killed.
And in addition, killed my father...
Just to protect the
enterprise called the police...
The first thing is to kill that man.
This isn't revenge.
It's preparation for a revolution.
Remember...
The time that we
were showered with our fathers' blood!
Against privatization!
I will become the king of murderers!
I will unite this country.
That is, the country of engineers!
We will not lose to anyone.
You and I are allies.
We are comrades.
Let's fight together!
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
That's right. That's the best.
Right?
Thanks a lot for telling me.
You insane bastard...
Kill anyone that resists.
Rock out, everybody!
Mt. Fuji
Tokyo Tower
On sale right now!
The Japanese sword of Kohka.
It cuts well!
Right now, we Tokyo Police are
the ones with the advantage.
Continue as is and keep on
killing, killing, killing!
Please stop, Master!
Welcome home, Master
You...
You are impertinent!
Who do you think I am!?
That hurt!
I like killing Japanese.
That's the right side.
Don't lick that.
Right.
You work too slowly.
This is the left.
Left.
Don't underestimate the Chinese.
Privatizing the police will lead
to more plentiful lives for us.
For a better society
Tokyo Police Corporation
You came to kill me, huh, Ruka?
You remember now.
I had no choice with your father.
He was very much against
privatizing the police.
It was for the organization, no...
I meant to protect this
huge corporation called the police.
Your father was in the way.
As atonement, Ruka,
I gave you shelter at a lodging house
and raised you to become the
strongest engineer hunter.
Right?
But life is full of irony because
you've sunk to becoming an engineer.
Ruka, you've become an engineer, huh?
I'm half disappointed and half happy!
Bingo!
You perverted bastard.
It's over already!
Easily, easily!
The engineer hunter...
...has become an engineer, huh?
Game over.
The end.
Ruka...
Can you...
Can you kill me?
I was the one who raised
you with great care.
Engineers are our enemies!
We will definitely annihilate them!
Once we wipe out
the engineers completely
our power will become much greater!
This one, here...
I have raised her with care.
A prisoner...
And this one...she's different from you
in that she will never betray me.
Manic-depressive
Prisoner 639
Are you okay?
Are you going to repay
kindness with evil?
I don't remember raising you
to be a rude girl like that!
You devil!
You allowed an engineer to rape you.
And fell to the level
of becoming their slave.
I have no intention of showing
any sympathy to a woman like that.
I don't need any sympathy.
Even if this body has
been taken over by a devil,
as long as I am myself,
I will not become a devil.
Because I am
a police officer who
protects the citizens.
I will not forgive your evil deed!
Here I come!
I wonder which one of us is a devil.
I will not lose!
I am the one who's going
to change Japan!
Here I go!
Ruka, we're not done yet!
You engineer!
Go to hell!
Chief...
For all your hard work...
Thank you very much!
The Self-Defense Force
has also been privatized.
The Tokyo Police Corporation has
taken over the Self-Defense Force.
We will protect you.
The crime extra-territoriality
law is our ally.
We have no mercy for criminals.
Serial killer Yoshiki Takahashi
Murdered 15 kindergarten children
We will protect you.
We, the Tokyo Police Corporation.
Serial killer Yoshiki Takahashi
Dead
The new Tokyo Police.
From now on, we will be making a
great effort to become everyone's...