- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Little bitch!
Give me that bag. Oopsy-daisy.
Ow!
- Knock it off! Get off, Kenny!
- What do we got here? I'm gonna take that.
- Get off him!
- What the fuck?
- You're such a stupid fuck!
- What'd you just call me?
I called you a stupid
fuck, you stupid fuck.
Hey, don't touch her!
Hey, I don't need your help, okay?
That's all you're gonna do? Out
here by yourself, teach me a lesson?
You got held back, didn't
you, Kenny? Twice, I think.
You think that's funny?
No, I think it's very sad, actually.
I only mention it because
that would make you over 18.
If you were to beat me up, which I'm
sure you could, it would be child abuse.
So if you don't want to wind up on some
registry, I suggest you back the fuck...
Do you have any idea how
much trouble you're in?
I'm looking at homework here for
at least 15 different students.
Are we really not gonna discuss
that I have an ice pack on my face?
Nurse says you'll be fine.
So no interest in why a teacher
found me sprawled out on the ground?
Mia Sutton says she saw you
walk into a beam out back.
How do you think we found you?
All right. I get it. I'm in
trouble. All I'm trying to say is,
you have the chance to stop the people
who make things hard for everybody.
You gotta see the big picture here.
Light...
some people might look at
you, a kid in your situation,
losing your mom the way you did,
and they'd cut you a little slack when
it comes to these behavioral issues.
Well, I don't believe in that.
Detention. Two weeks. Get out of here.
Hey.
Oh! Hi. I'm awake.
I was just like a tree
or a plant or something.
I'm heading out for a moment. Don't
fall asleep or it adds another day.
"Rule one: The human whose name
is written in this note shall die."
Whoa.
"Rule two: This note
will not take effect
unless the writer has the
person's face in their mind
when writing his or her name."
Ah!
Hello?
Help! Help me! Help! Help!
Holy shit! Holy shit!
What the fuck?!
Shall we begin?
Okay.
Relax, Light.
You're asleep.
You're asleep and you're
dreaming of some eight-foot-tall,
demon-looking motherfucker.
Oh, yes.
A dream. I like that.
Dreams are places you
can have fun, right?
It's all in your mind,
so why not enjoy it?
Shh.
Listen.
Get off of me!
Go, check it out.
- No!
- Come on! Come on!
What?
Kenny, no! Let me go! Get off me!
You're so disgusting!
Get the fuck off of me!
- Ooh! While you're down there...
- Aw, it sucks to be you.
Now we could, in this dream of yours,
take care of a situation like this.
We just put Kenny's name down...
and see what happens.
Yeah.
- Nah.
- Get off! You're such assholes!
I know you want to.
Go on.
Help her.
I don't have a pen.
It's a good thing you have a pen.
Ah...
Good. Now as long as we're
playing, let's do it right.
There's no need to stop at "who."
I'm sorry. What else is there?
How.
For a beginner, not bad at all.
Now...
watch.
Give it back!
Ah!
Now listen. I need to separate
the wheat from the chaff.
I think you might be
capable of great things,
but if you don't think you
can handle it, that's fine.
Just put the note somewhere,
leave it alone for seven days,
and I'll find it a new home.
How can this be possible?
It happened. Just like that.
And if this is possible,
imagine what else you could do.
- He a friend of yours?
- Who?
Kid in the accident.
Oh. No, I don't think he
was a friend of anyone.
Want to talk about it?
No.
We should talk about why
you were still at school.
Oh, yeah, that wasn't a big deal.
I just wrote a couple papers
and then got detention.
You don't think cheating's
a big deal? That who you are?
No, um...
Actually, I only got caught because
I was trying to break up a...
Know what? Doesn't matter.
You wouldn't understand anyway.
Because you're just that
smart or I'm just that dumb?
Because this is what you do. Instead
of trying to solve real problems,
you look over people's shoulders
so you can bust them for bullshit,
like not turning in
their reports or whatever.
A gun is only good as its aim, son.
I make sure people can trust our aim.
Just once, it would be nice
to think that you actually...
I mean, you're a cop.
How do you sleep at night
knowing you watched while a guy
like Antony Skomal walked away?
You think I just watched?
If I was a cop and some
guy ran over my wife,
I'd be pretty pissed off if his
dad paid his way out of jail.
He killed my mom, he nearly
beat his girlfriend to death,
and you just sit there
saying the same bullshit
- about how people better trust your aim...
- I'm gonna assume you're still raw
by what you saw today at school,
and that's keeping you from
thinking before you speak.
I suggest you stop talking.
"Rule 64: Each page of the note
contains the power of the whole note."
"Rule 95: Anyone may
write names in the note,
but only the keeper can possess it
for more than seven days." Jesus!
How many rules does it take to...
"Don't trust Ryuk.
He is not your pet.
He is not your friend."
- Hey, kid.
- Ah!
It's pronounced Ree-yook.
Ryuk.
Oh. Hi.
Sorry for the mispronunciation.
Ryuk, what exactly can I
do with this Death Note?
What exactly did you have in mind?
Well, it says that I can
specify the manner of death.
If I can choose how they die, does
that mean I can actually control them?
Every human spends the last moments of
his life in the shadow of a death god.
If we so desire, we can
influence those moments.
There are, of course, limitations.
"Rule 20:
A subject can be influenced for no more
than two days leading up to his death."
Two days? Your fingers are huge.
"Rule 28: Each death must
be physically possible,"
so no shark attacks while
someone's on the toilet.
As much as I love that idea.
Uh, where did it come from?
The history of the note is
as long as history itself.
But who gave it to me? I
mean, did you give it to me?
The last keeper of the note passed
away. It fell to me to find a new one.
- What if I didn't want it?
- You may pass it on.
Or better yet, I will.
- How would you do that?
- I told you!
When the note is separated
from the keeper for seven days,
I find a new one.
Who wrote those warnings
about you in the margins?
Oh, is that what we're gonna do with
the note, Light? Rules and warnings?
_
The name and the face
is all you have to have.
Turner.
Yeah, no, it's fine. What's going on?
Say that again.
You gotta be kidding me.
All right, yeah. I'll see you in a bit.
All right.
Hey.
Hey, uh, one second.
Come in.
Hey, what you up to?
Uh, just fell asleep on my desk.
I just got a call.
Our friend Antony Skomal is no more.
Impaled himself on a steak knife
in the middle of a restaurant.
- Holy shit.
- Yeah.
You seem happy.
Probably shouldn't be, but yeah, I am.
Your mom...
she always was kind of a hippy.
And we didn't see eye
to eye on everything.
She was damn sure right about one thing.
Karma's a bitch.
Sorry about what I said... you know.
Love you, son.
I love you, too.
- Go, go!
- Yeah! Watch your feet!
You in mourning?
In... Uh, what?
Our friend Kenny.
Oh, yeah. It's terrible
what happened to Kenny.
You don't have to lie to
me. Kenny was a sociopath,
and just because he's dead
does not make it a tragedy.
- Right.
- I just wish I'd seen it.
I heard his head spun
all the way around.
Actually, his head exploded
into a million pieces.
- In case you're wondering.
- You saw it?
Mm-hmm.
- I'm Mia.
- Oh, hi.
I know that you're Mia,
actually. I already knew that.
I know that you're Light
Turner. I already knew that.
Yeah.
You knew that I'm... You know my name?
So are you gonna tell me
what you saw, Light Turner?
Why did you get me put into detention?
I'm sorry.
I, uh... thought you could
use some medical attention
and I wasn't aware of the fact
that you were carrying around
a stockpile of illegal
papers in your backpack.
Is that one of them?
Hmm? Oh, no.
"Death Note"? What is it?
- What is what?
- Your book.
Uh, I can't tell you.
- Okay.
- Do you really want to know?
- Sure.
- Okay, then I'll tell you. I just...
Follow me.
Please tell me this
isn't your poetry journal.
When you see him, try not to
freak out. I freaked out a little.
See... who?
Behind you.
It's okay.
What are you talking about?
Only the keeper of the note can see me.
"The human whose name is written
in this note... shall die."
- Your poetry sucks.
- It's not poetry.
Um, will you just read the last entry?
"Kenny Doyle decapitation"?
I have, and...
I'm gonna sound crazy,
but I have a death god.
- I'm gonna get out of here.
- No. No, don't go. Trust me.
You of all people are
gonna want to see this.
Authorities received a 911 call...
Okay, we can work with that.
Overheard a violent argument between
Mr. Brode and his ex-wife earlier today.
Things escalated,
as several gunshots were also heard,
and the situation is still unfolding.
Authorities are standing by.
Seattle police and Seattle SWAT
trying to de-escalate the situation.
This is live coverage
of the hostage situation.
- Okay. Watch.
- Police are now confirming the hostages
- are Brode's ex-wife and children.
- Hope you know what you're doing.
With his violent history,
police are hesitant
about moving in on this situation.
You stupid bitch! You fucking stay
there, you snot-nose little douchebag!
It appears that James Brode
is exiting the storefront.
It looks like he has released her.
That's definitely a good sign.
- Holy shit.
- Oh, my goodness.
Uh, folks, we are trying
to get more information.
I hope no children were watching this.
This is obviously
very upsetting footage.
In case you're just tuning in,
the man holding his family hostage
just saluted to cameras before
being run over by a rogue SWAT truck.
We apologize for these
disturbing images...
I killed him.
I guess I should feel
guilty, but I don't.
That woman and her kids are only alive
right now because of what you did.
What is there to feel guilty about?
Thing is, I know what it's
like to get fucked over.
Some asshole killed my mom and...
got away with it until I got this book.
I just keep thinking, I mean,
why should it just be for me?
I mean, all the people that make
life miserable, make life dangerous...
I can reach them now.
Do you think that I'm crazy?
If anything, I think
you're not crazy enough.
- We could change the world.
- "We"?
Like "we" as... as in us?
We're getting an update live...
The police are extremely hesitant...
Can I kiss you?
You're not supposed to ask.
What am I supposed to do?
The note was filled
with names when I got it.
Whoever had it before us,
what did they accomplish?
Just small-time killings,
revenge, petty crimes?
I think we can do a lot more than
just settle some random scores.
How about this guy?
I don't want people to say
they're scared of it or horrified.
What do you want them to say?
I want them to say... "Thank you."
Look at those people.
- They're a bunch of sheep.
- No, they're not.
They're looking for someone
who's not gonna let them down
the way cops do and politicians.
And that's why they have you.
It's bigger than me.
It's bigger than us.
What they want...
is a god.
So let's give it to them.
Let's give them a god,
let's make a name for him.
A god that never lets anybody down.
It's not gonna solve a few
crimes, it's gonna solve all crime.
A god that scares the
shit out of the bad guys
until they don't want to be bad anymore?
A god who inspires hope that
things can actually change.
Kira.
Kira? What does that mean?
It means "light" in Russian and Celtic.
Wouldn't you be worried they
could trace it back to you?
No. How could they?
It also sort of means
"killer" in Japanese,
so if they're looking, it's
gonna be on the wrong continent.
Who or what is Kira?
That's the question facing
baffled investigators today
as death row inmates in six different
continents were found dead in their cells.
Each victim left behind the same
message written in perfect Japanese.
It reads, "Lord Kira has
returned to punish the wicked."
None of the victims
actually spoke Japanese...
I think I got one.
Reports are that the
previously elusive leader
of the terrorist movement blew
himself up in front of his men.
Kira is apparently
behind the bizarre deaths.
Five members of the cartel
apparently threw themselves
in front of an oncoming train.
Kira is responsible
for all of these acts
that are happening right now.
The globalists will have you believe
that Kira's the New World Messiah
here to right the wrongs of our time.
This is another bid by the super
elites to sweep the rug from under us
and shape our reality by
what can only be described
as one of the greatest false flag
operations in the history of covert ops.
Fear they will be punished by Kira
has led to a series of wanted criminals
literally turning themselves in.
Kira's had a bigger impact on
crime than anything I've seen.
I don't wanna say our job's
gotten easier, but look around you.
News out of Japan tonight
where Kira has apparently struck again.
More than a dozen were found
dead in a Tokyo nightclub,
a scene authorities described
as "incredibly gruesome."
What can anyone tell us about Kira?
And perhaps, more importantly,
can anyone stop it?
And should they?
_
It makes no sense.
The Nakamuras and the Inagawas
have had a truce for over ten years.
How would Kira even know about them?
- Because I tipped him off.
- What?
I've had access to law enforcement
databases for some time.
I've been seeding the
names of obscure criminals,
waiting for a hit.
And now... we know
who we're looking for.
How long since you've slept?
Forty-one hours.
And you're certain of your conclusions?
Yes.
The insulin spike from the candies will
focus your mind for final consideration.
When it fades, you
will sleep for one hour.
Wear these to properly
prepare your body clock.
I've been contemplating
several different strategies.
I honestly don't know
that I'll be able to sleep.
- Sleep is key to strong thought.
- Yes.
Would you mind singing a song for me?
Of course.
♪ You're out of the woods
You're out of the dark ♪
♪ You're out of the night ♪
♪ Step into the sun,
step into the light ♪
♪ Keep straight ahead For
the most glorious place ♪
♪ On the face of the
Earth and the sky ♪
♪ Hold onto your breath
Hold onto your heart ♪
♪ Hold onto your hope ♪
♪ Walk up to the
gate and let it open ♪
Investigation, since when? And why
are you just telling me this now?
Because I just got added last week.
Knowing you'd have this sort
of calm and thoughtful response,
I can't imagine why I
didn't bring it up sooner.
What part of terrorists
killing each other
and criminals turning
themselves in bothers you, Dad?
Why exactly are they doing that, son?
- They're doing it because of Kira.
- Right, and who is that?
How does Kira get to decide who lives
and dies, who's guilty and innocent?
Is there a complaints department if
I don't like one of Kira's decisions?
Or would complaining get
me put on Kira's list?
Is that what everybody
at the station thinks?
Well, it's safe to say I'm
ahead of the curve on that one.
Hey, how do I look?
- Good.
- All right. See you this afternoon.
_
- Turner.
- Just got a call from the FBI.
Apparently, they got someone
who wants to speak with you.
- Oh, yeah? And who is that?
- They're not really saying.
Just said he helped them out before
and he's got a theory
on the Kira situation.
- I just got the case. What does he want?
- I have no idea.
They said he's a little different.
In fact, they'll probably
send a representative...
Detective Turner?
I am to meet with Detective Turner,
local head of the Kira investigation,
in his office at 9:00 a.m.
Call you back.
- What can I do for you?
- I am Watari.
Your fellow officers did that?
Cops don't like it when
you go after other cops,
but, apparently, they hate it
when you go after their god.
They support Kira?
Kira's doing away with
the "Most Wanted" list.
These guys wanna throw him a parade.
But now that rumor has it
Kira's a cop, it's in my world.
The idea that Kira is associated
with law enforcement is not a rumor.
It is a fact,
uncovered by the individual I work with.
- Oh, yeah, and who's that?
- He goes by the letter "L."
L is real?
You're familiar?
Yeah, I hear things.
That giant smuggling
ring in Eastern Europe,
practically handed to
police on a platter.
L would like to speak with you
regarding the Kira investigation.
- Okay. When?
- Right now.
- Hmm, Detective Turner.
- What is this?
A one-time offer.
I'd like to assist you
in the capture of Kira.
Why me? The FBI, CIA have
hundreds of men on this.
I've been in communication
with Interpol and the FBI,
but I believe you have
something they do not.
What's that?
An in-depth understanding
of potential suspects.
Why would I have a better understanding?
The FBI thinks the killer
is operating out of Japan.
Because of the name Kira.
Ah, but the name is an
intentional misdirection.
He wants us to believe that he's
Japanese, operating a half a world away.
He's not.
Kira's in Seattle.
Shall we help one another?
"Justice for the Wicked." What is this?
It's a site for Kira worshipers.
They put up names of
people that deserve to die.
Holy shit.
Rapists, pedophiles,
human trafficking, murder.
This guy killed four
people in a house fire.
I don't know. How do
we know that it's real?
What do you mean?
What if somebody fucked your girlfriend
and you put him on the list to kill him?
What would you do if some guy fucked me?
- Oh, I'd kill him.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- You'd kill him?
But that is the reason why we can't
kill people based on website rumors.
It's not like that.
These are real people with real
problems, and they've been ignored.
They need our help.
Figured you'd be older.
And that I'd be able to
see more of your face.
Yes, well, I find I'm not in a
very trusting mood these days.
I took the liberty of moving your
evidence to a more secure location.
Oh, I can see that. Were
you gonna let me know or...?
Wow, this is very, very impressive,
James. Your men must be proud.
Ask your partner how my men
think about me these days.
So you did all of this yourself?
Even more impressive.
Please, James, have a
seat. Rest your glutes.
Mm-mmm. You've made two mistakes.
This is zero day, Kira's
first recorded murders.
But previously, on April 15th,
convicted felon James W. Brode
had taken his wife and children hostage.
I remember that. You
think that was Kira?
Initial speculation was that
his behavior was drug-related,
but lost in the ensuing
crush of Kira activities
was the fact that Brode's
toxicology had come back clean.
The stand-off had never
made national news,
and it was only broadcast
on local Seattle stations.
- So that's how you knew he was here.
- I infiltrated your network
in order to ensure that there
hadn't been a data breach.
Prior to my access,
the network was intact.
Did you just hand me evidence
you hacked the Seattle P.D.?
I handed you evidence
that whoever Kira is,
they have access to the
database from the inside.
Kira's one of ours.
Here's a cross-reference list
of officers and their access
as well as the dates of Kira activities.
The Federal Administration has agreed
to make resources available to us.
We can begin seeing who was where when.
- What are you gonna do?
- I'd like to start by speaking with Kira.
Sure you are.
- Hey.
- Light, turn on the news.
The individual known as Kira,
as I'm sure you're aware, has
taken credit for over 400 deaths.
Oh, shit.
While we don't know how
he kills his victims,
we do know how he chooses them.
Prior to these deaths,
all of the victims have had their
identities released to the media.
This would suggest that Kira
is not some omnipotent force.
He's a person...
like you or me.
He is also a coward.
A child wielding power
he does not understand,
mistakenly believing in doing
so, he's at no risk to himself.
He's wrong.
Kira, if you're watching this,
know that I am coming for you.
Unless, of course, you'd
like to kill me right now.
Now I'm rooting for this guy.
Would you shut the fuck up?
No?
Well, in that case, Kira,
I shall be meeting you
face-to-face very shortly.
Who does this guy think he is?
What the fuck was that?
I have a theory.
Kira cannot kill by simply sight alone.
He needs a name and a face.
Every victim we've seen
so far fits this pattern.
So you antagonize him on purpose?
While withholding my
identity from the record.
Now, we know that he wants
to kill me but is unable.
And what if you're wrong?
Then, James, I'd be dead.
Either way, we'll have
gained valuable information.
He always pull this kind of stuff?
You guys getting close to catching Kira?
Oh, I'd say the haystack's down
to a hay pile. Still a lot of hay.
I saw the press conference today.
Who's that guy on TV
with the turtleneck?
You like that look? I'm
thinking of taking it myself.
Hmm.
Goes by L. He's an
independent investigator.
Wow, so you don't even
know his real name.
About the only thing I know is
he's got some handler named Watari.
Really likes ice cream.
He's connected an awful lot of dots.
Do you think he's connected
the dots because he's Kira?
I don't think so.
He has a history of cracking big cases.
Besides, I think you can tell when you're
sitting across from a killer like Kira.
Right. Of course.
What happens when they catch Kira?
Well... he's murdered over 400 people,
so, my guess...
it's probably gonna be a fight
between those who want to hang him
and those who want to dissect
him and figure out how he did it.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
You put someone on my kid?
We agreed that everyone with access
needed to be thoroughly vetted.
I did not see it prudent to
have you investigate yourself.
What? We're not talking
about investigating me.
We're talking about
having my son followed!
I investigated you prior
to offering my assistance
and concluded you are not Kira.
As for your son, he may
have access to databases
around which we have
centered our search.
Therefore, deserves the same scrutiny
as anyone else that fits that criteria.
- No, he's a kid!
- Yes.
- A particularly bright kid.
- You know what?
If you had any questions about
my son, you should've come to me.
Here you go.
Even if they're suspicious, I
don't see how they can prove it.
I think we just go quiet
until they stop following us.
- What do you mean "go quiet"?
- Stop fucking around with the Death Note.
Is that what you think we're doing?
Come on, Light. Just get rid
of them. All we need is a name.
- I'm not gonna do that.
- Not gonna do what?
- I was talking to Ryuk.
- I like this one, Light.
- She has wonderful ideas.
- What'd he say?
Ryuk? Not much.
- We're good. They're trying to stop us.
- We don't kill innocent people, Mia.
Even if I wanted to, which I don't,
taking out the guy following us
will only indicate that it's me.
You'd have to get rid of all the agents,
regardless of who they're following.
They wouldn't know who it was,
but they'd know what happens
when you fuck with Kira.
- Can't believe you're saying this.
- Cant believe you're not.
Then I guess we're really
fucking lucky that it's my book.
Kira has been strangely
inactive of late,
something authorities
are eager to point to
as evidence their investigation
is gaining momentum.
However, Kira supporters
have begun to criticize police
for suppressing its activities,
as a small but noticeable
spike in global crime
has become apparent in the absence of
recent activities from the phenomena.
Are you leaving?
Yeah, I've got some work to do.
There's a guy on the news
who killed a couple kids.
I thought maybe we
could make some popcorn,
take some names down for later.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Director Pearl. These just
came in from the field offices.
Tell them to keep surveillance
on all the potential...
Assistant Director Pearl is
dead. Heart attack, just now.
We need to contact every
FBI agent on their team.
This is Franks.
Agent Franks, your team
has been compromised.
Drop what you're doing and get to
the nearest hospital. Right now.
Agent Franks?
Agent Franks, can you hear me?
Twelve FBI agents
mysteriously commit suicide.
Some sources say it
was the work of Kira.
This is the first time Kira
has attacked law enforcement.
- Slow down for one second?
- He did it! Son of a bitch killed them.
- Ryuk?
- There's so many rules in that thing!
There must be some kind of loophole.
What's he gonna do if you go after him?
Maybe you just need to
take a minute and relax
and see if this was the best
thing that could've happened.
No.
Ryuk!
You think I'm some dog, Light?
You can just snap your
fingers and I'll come running?
- Did you kill those FBI agents?
- What do you think?
I decide who dies, you obey
me. Those are the rules.
- Who do you think wrote the rules?
- Whose side are you on?
There are no sides, only the game.
And I knew eventually you
wouldn't be able to handle playing.
I asked politely, but
you didn't hear me.
Let the note go.
Look at the strife it's causing
you and your little girlfriend.
Let me find it a new home.
We'll be free of each other.
I'm not gonna give the
note to you or anybody else,
and if you fuck with me again,
I'm gonna put your name in it.
You could try.
But I warn you, there are
four letters in my name.
Most anyone's ever gotten were two.
Mm.
We interrupt this to take
you live to an announcement...
- What the fuck is he doing?
- By James Turner,
local head of the Kira investigation.
Oh, shit.
Those of you that harbored any
illusions about what Kira really is,
the cold-blooded murder
of a dozen FBI agents
should lay bare his true nature.
Kira is a cowardly criminal thug
concerned only with self-preservation.
Not only is he unworthy
of the veneration and celebration
he's received in certain circles,
as of today, he's not
even worthy of our fear.
Understand this, Kira.
You may strike me down,
but another one will
stand up and take my place.
Why would he do that? He's
forcing Kira to retaliate.
And another for as long as need be.
We will not waiver.
- Because he's not afraid.
- We will not submit.
And we will not fail.
Where is it?
What? Are you out of your
mind? That's my fucking dad!
Yeah, and he just dared us to
kill him on live television.
Think people are gonna be on their
knees if he can talk to Kira like that?
We're not killing my dad!
This is over! Ryuk fucked us!
We're not the good guys anymore.
What happened to the boy that
wanted the world to get what he got?
Think about your mom, Light.
Either Kira stands up
or they hunt us down.
If you want out, then
just get the fuck out!
So you just want to quit?
I don't know.
Well said, James. Tell me, are
you truly ready to give your life?
If that's what it takes.
How long will it take
him to decide, I wonder?
What's going on?
Let me take this.
- Turner.
- This is L.
Just making sure you hadn't died.
Still here.
Excellent. Carry on.
I'm really proud of you.
Understand this, Kira.
- You may strike me down...
- Sir?
- But another will take my place.
- Light Turner is Kira.
- And another and another...
- How long since you've slept?
for as long as need
be.. Thirtyone hours.
- We will not waiver. We will not submit.
- Sleep is key to strong thought.
- Trust me.
- And we will not fail.
Nothing's gonna change once I wake up.
Hello, Light.
Oh, um...
You're the guy. You're L.
Yeah, well, it's not my real name.
But I'm sure you're
painfully aware of that.
What are you doing here?
Following a lead. You?
Um... I was just... I'm leaving.
I wonder if it was a difficult decision.
If what was a difficult decision?
Sparing your father's life.
Sorry, what are you talking about?
You must've known it would implicate you,
yet you couldn't bring yourself to do it.
I'll admit, I always
wondered if you had a line.
I guess it's fortunate for us,
the line you finally decided to draw
points so clearly in your direction.
- So you really think I'm Kira.
- No, I know it.
If you're so sure, why
haven't you just arrested me?
Because I don't do check,
Light. Only checkmate.
- But we'll be there soon enough.
- Great. Until then, enjoy the gelato.
Assuming you can eat through
that thing. And I'll just, uh...
Can I ask you something?
Yeah.
How do you think he does it? Kira.
I was hoping you could shed
some light on that for me.
I have a theory.
I think that it's some
form of remote viewing
coupled with maybe some latent psychic
ability of some sort. Am I close?
So you really have no idea, do you?
Well, I have several ideas.
Eventually, you'll tell
me which is correct.
What if it turned out
that all arresting Kira did
was give that power to someone
else, someone potentially much worse.
You're suggesting the ability
is somehow transferable.
I'm suggesting maybe what you
and the person you're after want
isn't so different.
Maybe they're as ready to see
the killing end as you are.
And if that were true, perhaps
now would be a good time
to start helping them
instead of hunting them.
Helping...
Hmm...
You know what I think, Light?
I think you want to make a deal.
Good deals are made by those
in a position of strength.
Criminals, such as yourself,
never make those deals.
What they do is wait until
they're caught and then they beg.
I'm not begging. I'm telling
you that you don't understand.
Let me put this in terms
you're more familiar with.
A man kills 400 people.
He tells us that it's complicated,
that he's misunderstood.
Do you think that Kira would hear
his excuses or walk him off a bridge?
Think you're better than me,
but you're trying to kill Kira!
- Kira, Kira, Kira!
- I do not kill, Light!
I don't even carry a
gun, it's distracting.
What I do is bring people to justice.
But the form it takes is their own making.
A consequence of their actions, not mine.
You're the one who flew into the sun.
I'm just here to make
sure you actually burn.
- Well, if that's how it has to be.
- It is, Light!
You know that as well as I do.
There are no draws in this game.
- Please, you have to forgive me.
- It was my dad, Mia.
If I could take it back, I would.
I promise. I was just scared.
Do you think I'm not scared?
I'm a fucking cheerleader, Light.
Nothing I do has ever
mattered until I met you.
I made a mistake. If I could
take it back, I would. I just...
I wasn't ready to lose you.
I love you.
L showed me his face.
I'm gonna get his name,
and I'm gonna stop him.
That's Watari. He's L's right-hand man.
If anybody's gonna give us L's
real name, it's gonna be him.
All right.
"Watari becomes obsessed
with revealing the true identity
of the detective known as 'L.'
For the next 48 hours, he will cease
all communication with the outside world,
except to update what he learns
to the number 206-555-0166.
At 7:00 p.m., on October 12th, he dies."
You didn't say how he dies.
- It doesn't matter, it's dealer's choice.
- What?
Huh? Oh, I was talking to Ryuk. Sorry.
- So kill his friend to get his name?
- No, I'm not gonna kill Watari.
That's the best part.
Rule 89 says:
"If the person who writes
a name destroys its page
prior to the death being carried
out, the target will be spared."
So if I burn Watari's page
before October 12th at 7:00 p.m...
then nothing bad happens, right, Ryuk?
Only one name can be removed
from the Death Note by burning it.
Get this one wrong, you
won't get another chance.
I only get one page to burn.
- Hello?
- My name is Watari.
- This information is not known to me.
- I'm sorry. What do you mean?
I took responsibility for L
only after he left the St.
Martin's orphanage in Montauk
where he was one of the Rochester wards.
One of the... Sorry,
what is a Rochester ward?
They were orphans
trained since childhood
to become the greatest detectives
the world had ever seen.
- You've gotta be kidding me.
- I am not.
For their first test, the wards
were placed in a conditioning vault.
Those who retained their
sanity after seven months
were initiated into the program.
L joined at six, the
youngest candidate ever.
Okay, but what was his name
before the vault or whatever?
That name exists now
only in their records.
Okay. Okay. Watari, you
need to go there right now.
I should like to rest first.
Sleep is key to strong thought.
No. You don't have any time to sleep.
You have 48 hours to get a name.
What happens in 48 hours?
- You just need to go right now.
- I will go.
- Leave him alive, it's a loose end.
- You don't need to help, Mia.
Of course I do.
I'm not gonna leave you alone in this.
Continental America
from Seattle to New York
will be departing from track three.
I'm telling you, I
wore an actual top hat.
- And was that with your wife or...?
- No.
Frankly, she wouldn't have been
caught within ten miles of me.
I didn't get this cool until much later.
Hello. Nice to meet you. Leave.
What are you doing here?
We have a critical issue that
requires discussion immediately.
- Kids, give us a couple minutes.
- Sure.
No, wait, wait, wait.
Not you, Light.
The discussion concerns you.
How?
Watari has disappeared.
I've known him my entire life.
He has not, would not, could not leave
without me being sure of his plans.
- Okay, let me make a call.
- What is it that you want?
- Sorry, I don't have any idea.
- I get that this has got you upset.
Your son is Kira, James!
What?
Don't know why you haven't been
able to put one and one together,
even despite him
having spared your life,
but it does not speak well to
your deductive abilities at all.
It's time to leave.
- I'm not going anywhere.
- Wanna fucking bet?
I have a search warrant
and a team of men outside.
So, as I said, I will be staying.
You? You have managed a strong move.
Now, provided that you
return Watari to me safely,
I'm willing to put your position
of strength into account.
I'm sorry about your friend.
I'm sure he'll be fine.
Damn it! You don't have...
You have crossed the line!
Force me to do the same and I
assure you you will not survive!
You threaten my son again,
I'll fucking kill you!
Get the fuck out of here!
Tear this place apart! Tear it apart!
- You okay?
- Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Has nothing to do with you, son.
I knew he was off the minute I met him.
You know what happens when they find it.
It ends up my book again, Light.
And guess what name I'm gonna suggest
we start with when I find it a new home?
Is there...
anything I need to know?
How do you do it?
- How you handle all this?
- What do you mean?
How do you handle having everybody
against you? You're screwed either way.
Yeah, one way or another,
we're all in the middle.
Things are never black and white.
Sometimes you just...
you just have to choose
the lesser of two evils.
♪ And the sky ♪
♪ Hold onto your breath
Hold onto your heart ♪
♪ Hold onto your heart ♪
♪ Walk up to the gate ♪
♪ And look up ♪
He's coming out of the house right
now. I want a car on him. Every move.
- Hello.
- Where are you? What's taking so long?
- I'm on my way to St. Martin's.
- Well, how much longer?
I hope to find it within
the next few hours.
Find it? You don't know where it is?
It was never intended to be a
place that was easily accessed.
Okay, just hurry.
This is a reminder.
Time is running out to purchase
your Winter Dance tickets.
- Hey.
- This is for tonight.
Also comes with this. You're
really gonna stand out.
You really think I give
a shit about Homecoming?
Look in the hat.
They're never gonna stop following you.
We're gonna end this once and for
all, but I need you to trust me.
- Can you do that?
- Yeah.
What do you want, Light?
You're not some sadist.
There's always some flimsy
justification, some reason that...
Get me the New York field office. Now!
I've asked Brandon here to dance with
me for one. Is that cool with you?
Hey. Where are you?
I've located the records
room, but need more time.
Only got a few minutes.
Is it there or not?
I am confident it is here,
but I cannot yet say where.
Fuck it. Fuck it. Fuck it.
Forget it. Just forget it.
No! Mia, what did you
do? Where's the page?
- Watari, you have to run right now! Okay?
- Watari!
You have to run away
as quick as you can!
- Someone's here.
- Okay...
Just go to them right now
and ask for their help.
I am obsessed with revealing
the true identity of...
Yes. It's here.
- What does it say that it is?
- L's true name...
- What does it say? What is L's real name?
- Sir! Answer me!
Are you Watari?
- I am Watari.
- Watari.
Fuck! Fuck!
Ah, you said dealer's choice.
Why didn't you tell me
the page was missing?
But then what would you
and Mia have to talk about?
I told you I like her a lot, Light.
I know you're probably upset...
but if you freak out,
they're gonna be all over us,
- and that's not gonna end well.
- You killed him.
No, Light.
I saved you...
from yourself again.
Because every time things get hard,
you leave me to do the real stuff.
Oh, my God, it was all you.
Ryuk never found a loophole.
You were the loophole.
You don't get to feel
superior for being a pussy.
I did what I had to do... to protect us.
"Agent Raymond Young...
will write the names of all the
other agents of the Kira task force
in the Death Note, placing each of
their faces in his mind as he goes.
When he's done, he will join
them in climbing to a rooftop
and leaping to his death."
If you want out, you're out. All I
need is for you to give me the book.
Are you insane? Do you think that I'd
ever let you near that thing again?
You didn't read it.
What did you do?
"Light Turner's heart
stops beating at midnight."
No... you're trying to kill me?
You're going to officially
pass the book to me.
Then once I'm the keeper...
I'll burn your page.
That's why I couldn't let you save
Watari. You can only burn one name and...
I wanted it to be yours.
There are so many fucking rules.
Now go get my goddamn book.
Did you find Watari?
This is Detective Turner.
I want every unit looking
for the individual known as L.
He should be considered
armed and dangerous.
And I want my son put in protective
custody until he's located. Now!
Let's go! This way! Move, move!
Fuck!
Agh!
Be on the lookout for Light Turner,
last seen in the vicinity
of North Seattle High.
Ah!
Hey!
Hey, man!
Ah!
Light!
Hey, asshole!
Move! Move! Move! Move!
Hey!
Hold it right there! Stop! Repeat...
Whoa! Hey!
Hey!
Sorry! Sorry! Sorry!
- Light!
- Ah!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Didn't I clearly explain what would happen
if Watari wasn't safely returned to me?
Wait! You need to understand how it
works, okay? Or you can't stop it!
I couldn't stop it!
Death can be handed out
through a fucking calculus book!
- You're stalling!
- No, I'm not! I swear I'm not, okay?
I'm just gonna turn
around really slowly.
Okay. I'm gonna reach into my bag.
Don't move! Do not move!
This man is Kira. I'm
working with law enforcement.
In order to capture and eliminate...
Lord Kira.
Yeah. Yeah.
Out of my way!
Come on! Let's go! Come with me!
Where the fuck is the book, Light?
- Come on!
- We're actually closed, guys.
Take us to the top! Nobody
else gets on, hear me?
Here. Want the book? Get in!
- What the fuck is your problem?
- Take us to the top! Now!
Hit the button!
We gotta stop doing this. We
gotta stop doing all of this.
It's already done!
Let's run away together and
never use the Death Note again.
I don't want to run away!
Now give me my fucking book, okay?
Take it! But...
just remember what it's done.
Not just out there, but to us.
If you love me...
If you love me, then you gotta trust me.
Don't take the book.
Because if you do...
you'll never see me again.
I love you so much.
You do?
- Light!
- Dad?
Light!
No!
What?
What did you do?
You put my name in it, didn't you?
It was if you took the book. I
thought I could convince you not to.
Are you kidding me, Light?
- You put my name in the book! I got mad.
- Are you kidding me?!
You said you love me! I thought
you wouldn't take the book!
Light!
Light! Light!
Oh, shit!
Ryuk! I take it back! I take it back!
Here, just hold on! Don't let go!
Please don't let me
go! Don't let me fall!
Four new killings.
And every one of them identified by
the news media in the last 48 hours.
I understand you think this
means Light cannot be Kira.
You think he's knocking
people off while in a coma?
I'm not exactly sure how it is...
Apparently, you have enough highly-placed
allies to keep you out of jail.
But none of that's gonna
help you if we see you around.
Was there a calculus book
seized at Light Turner's house?
Don't take off!
Come in.
Hey, Dad.
What's wrong?
It was you.
All along.
What are you talking about?
In your room.
At first, I couldn't figure out how
or why it'd gotten out of my safe.
Then it hit me.
James Brode wasn't the first victim.
It was Antony Skomal.
How?
Do you really want to know?
Dr. Norman Ludlam,
known for sexually assaulting
female patients under sedation.
On the night of October 12th,
Norman Ludlam is present at the pier
when two individuals fall from
the Northwest Ferris Wheel.
He rescues the male
suspect from the water
and manages to revive
him, saving his life.
Using his connections at the hospital,
Ludlam keeps the suspect in a
medically-induced coma for two days.
At the end of this period,
he leaps to his death from
the roof of the hospital.
Aaron Peltz. Mailman, retired.
Molested nearly a dozen children
over the span of 20 years.
Peltz retrieves the Death Note
from the river on October 12th.
Each night, Peltz fills in the
blanks with the name of criminals
who appear on the news.
On day two, he returns the
Death Note to the Kira suspect,
and then commits suicide.
Mia Sutton is killed when she accepts
the Death Note from her boyfriend.
As the Northwest Ferris Wheel
mysteriously collapses...
she pulls the page with my
name on it from the note.
And it is ultimately consumed by fire.
Although her boyfriend
lands safely in the water...
Mia strikes the shoreline...
dying instantly.
I made a lot of mistakes.
And then I tried to fix
them, but it didn't work.
I thought it was simple at first: I
was just gonna kill all the bad guys
and the good guys would
win, but it wasn't like that.
It's like you said...
sometimes you gotta choose
the lesser of the two evils.
Which one are you, son?
What?
You humans are so interesting.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --