Mr. Blackwood?
Sir?
Mr. Blackwood, I'm sorry.
You did ring, sir?
Come down.
I'm so...
So very sorry.
I didn't see the steps.
They made me do it.
I didn't...
If I want to see my child again,
I must comply.
Mr. Blackwood.
Please understand.
Precious teeth. Beautiful teeth.
Ransom for my boy.
Yes.
Daddy.
I brought you something more to eat.
Not children's teeth like you wanted,
but please accept them
in exchange for him.
Children's teeth.
Oh, no, that's the best I could do.
And they're my own. You see?
My own.
Please. Give me back my son!
Yes, your son is down here.
Reach for him.
Son? Son!
Son!
Grab my hand!
We've now begun our descent
into T.F. Green Airport.
Please return to your seat,
make sure it is in...
She's landed.
What do you think? Too much?
No, it's perfect. Just like you.
There's my girl.
Sally?
Wow! Look how tall you are!
What are you, 17 now?
Dad, you know how old I am.
I know. I'm being silly.
- Hey.
- Good morning, sir.
Thank you.
Come on.
Sally, this is Kim. Kim, Sally.
Hi, Sally. It's nice to meet you.
I love you. I love you.
Thanks.
What about a picture?
You got your camera?
It's good to see you.
Good morning, Rhode Island!
- Everything okay?
- Yeah.
We've got fog this morning
and a slight chance of a shower later on.
Smell that fresh air, kiddo?
Sure beats the smog of LA, huh?
I have to call Mom now.
Just press one and the green.
Hi, you've called Joanne
and the magical Sally! Leave us a message.
L.C. delivered the flooring.
If it rains, I'm afraid it's going to warp.
Well, just put it in the garage.
Sally, say hello to Mr. Harris.
Nice to meet you.
Come take a look at the house.
Mr. Harris. Mr. Harris,
would you give me a hand...
- How's it going?
- Good.
- When do you think you'll be finished?
- No problem.
Good, huh?
- It smells funny.
- You should have smelled it before.
They had moldy newspapers everywhere,
and dead pigeons all over the floor
and poop.
- Lots of it.
- It's Jacoby's office.
Mr. Jacoby.
Oh, hey, Michelle. Sorry.
I don't know. Hold on. I'll check.
You got the photographs?
I like to draw, too.
You work here?
No, Sally, I live here.
I'm the interior designer.
Do you know what that is?
Of course you do.
You see all the animal
paintings and friezes?
They're by Emerson Blackwood,
a man who once lived here.
He was a very famous wildlife painter.
Hey, Sally, look.
You want to try?
What do you have there?
- I found it.
- That's mine.
It was my grandmother's.
When I was little, my mother gave it to me.
My mom gave me to my dad.
Sally?
You want to see your room?
What do you think?
Kim and I worked really hard
to get it ready. Check this out.
It's pretty great, huh?
It looks better at night.
How long am I staying here?
What did your mother tell you?
She told me I was coming to visit.
But then she packed all my clothes.
She didn't explain anything to you?
- No.
- Sally.
Your mother and I are worried about you.
She thinks that maybe you're feeling sad
and she thought that...
Well, we thought that perhaps a change
might be good for you and that you could
come and live here with Kim and me
until we finish the work on the house
and sell it.
Then we could move
somewhere else and...
Sally? Come on. Open the door.
Come on. Let me in.
Are you going to marry her?
That's between Kim and me.
Mom said you only liked her
because she was young.
But she isn't. She's old.
Sally.
Open the door.
Come on, sweetheart. Open the door.
Sally, please, let's talk about this.
Look, I know...
I know it must be tough.
You've had a long flight,
and it's strange being in a new house.
I want to go to bed now.
Okay.
Don't forget to brush your teeth.
You'd be a terrible poker player.
You've been ironing that shirt
for half-an-hour.
She sure didn't take to me.
I wouldn't take it personally.
She's like that with everybody.
Those pills she takes, what are they?
Adderall, I think.
Jesus.
That's her mother for you.
That woman medicated our dogs.
So, what about Jacoby?
His assistant said he still
hasn't looked at the new photographs yet.
- He's had them for a week.
- I know.
We're still in the running,
and he's still coming to the dinner.
- He should just give us the cover.
- Yes, he should.
He gave it to the Spencer restoration
two years ago
and you have done miracles here.
We have done miracles here.
It's not all about me.
Thank you.
These are new?
- Yeah.
- Great.
If we get the cover of
Architectural Digest,
we won't need to take
out another bank loan, will we?
You know what your
daughter told me today?
What?
She said your wife gave her to you.
Kids say all kinds of
things they don't mean.
It couldn't have gone any worse today.
I feel like the evil stepmother.
The evil and very old stepmother.
Let's not forget the old part.
Because I was kind of thinking
you were looking a little ancient.
- Oh, yeah?
- Oh, yeah.
The stuffed bear? What was I thinking?
Come on. It's great. She likes it.
I saw it in her room.
On her bed?
Well, above the bed. Hanging by a noose.
That's okay.
Nice sign of affection, I think.
Sally. Her name is Sally.
Sally!
What do you think?
Yeah. Looks great.
- Have you seen Sally?
- Yeah, she's on the bench.
Sally!
It is not safe for you back here.
Hey. What's going on? Everything okay?
Keep her out from the back of the house.
She could fall in.
We'd be in a hell of a mess.
I didn't do anything.
There's pits. Old wells.
It's dangerous for a child.
Mr. Harris is right, Sally. He knows.
His grandfather worked at the house.
- You shouldn't be back here.
- But I found a basement.
There is no basement.
Easy, Harris. I'll take her. It's okay.
It's there! It's right there!
There's a reason
this house is called Fallen Mill.
The English had a mill here,
and it fell into a sinkhole.
That's why most of the houses around here
don't have basements.
This one does.
- You may want to check this out.
- It's unsafe for a child.
Pull on that.
Look! I told you it was here!
Can you believe this?
This is definitely hollow.
I'm going to get some tools.
- You sure you want to do this now?
- Of course! You kidding?
We can fix this easy if we have to.
You may want to step back.
Mr. Hurst, I...
There's a door in here.
Where did you put the old house keys?
They're in your junk drawer in the office.
Okay.
Have a look.
Oh, wow.
- You be careful, Sally. Okay?
- Okay.
How the hell did we miss this?
That must be the garden window.
It's all of his paints and old
color pencils. This is amazing.
Wow. Alex, look at this.
Harris, did you know about this?
This place isn't safe. Especially for kids.
It's okay. I'll keep an eye on her.
This must be where Blackwood worked.
I found another door.
- Look at these sketches.
- It's an ash pit, I think.
Yeah. It's bolted shut.
These are incredible.
Okay. Let's go, Sally.
Come on, Sally. Let's go.
Sally, come on.
This must be like King Tut's tomb for you.
Which is why we shouldn't be touching
anything. This stuff must be valuable.
- She's gone.
- No, she will come back.
They always do.
Yes, they always do.
I don't think that's important, Alan.
No, I just need to make sure I get
the paintings and furniture
back in time for the dinner.
You told me you could.
Come on.
How long have we known each other?
I'll write you a post-dated check.
Hold on.
It's either walnut or mahogany,
I think. Yeah.
There you are.
I thought maybe we could bake scones.
I promised Mrs. Underhill
we wouldn't make too much of a mess.
No. That's all right.
What have you got there?
My doll. And my drawing stuff.
Looks like it's just you and I
baking scones today.
I made sandwiches for everyone.
Sally, open the grate.
Yes, open the grate. Set us free.
Who are you?
What do you look like?
We've been locked up for so long.
Set us free.
Come down.
You'll see what it's like down here.
Wait a minute, will ya?
There's other children down here.
They're just like you.
Come and play with them.
Sally?
Sally.
What are you doing down here?
- I heard something.
- Rats, probably. It's time for dinner.
- It was a voice.
- Really smart rats, then.
No! Listen.
Nothing. Come on. Let's go, kiddo.
- I forgot my bag.
- Hurry it up, then.
Sally, now!
We can get this tomorrow. We can't
get the rest of these for two weeks.
What about the burnt umber?
It's much warmer,
and we can get it for half the price.
You not hungry? Sally?
Don't you like rice?
Mrs. Underhill made apple pie for dessert.
Apple pie has gluten, and Mommy says
gluten is bad for my concentration.
Oh, come on. You love apple pie.
We can worry
about your concentration tomorrow.
Mommy says no gluten.
What's your mother filling your head with?
- How about some chocolate milk?
- No.
- I'll make something else.
- Hold on.
Sally, you need to eat this,
or you can go to your room. Okay?
Good night, Dad.
What?
- Did that work on you when you were a kid?
- She's testing us, Kim.
That's what kids do.
Who's the parent here?
Certainly not me.
I didn't mean that.
No. You're right. I'm not a parent.
- We talked about this, remember?
- No, you told me about this, Alex.
I'm not sure
I'm ready to be anybody's mother.
I had a hard enough time
getting over my own childhood
to have to deal with somebody else's.
Listen, will you help me with this, please?
I realize this is terrible timing,
but I don't have a choice.
I can't just send her back.
That's not what I'm asking you to do.
Apple pie.
Thanks.
- Hello?
- Hi, Alex. It's Joanne.
- Hi, Joanne.
- Can I speak to Sally?
- No, you can't.
- Why not?
Because she's asleep.
We're three hours ahead, remember?
What were you thinking not telling her
she was going to be living here?
You and I had a conversation.
I asked you if you wanted me to tell her.
Don't do this every time I have...
You're the one who wanted her here.
I love you. I love you.
Did you just speak to me?
I love you.
The light, it hurts us.
Yeah. Turn out the light.
I love you.
Turn out the light.
We want to be friends.
Where's my doll?
With us. Sally's doll is with us.
Who are you?
We're your friends.
Friends?
Where?
Come down to the basement
and play with us.
Where are you?
What are you?
Hungry.
Very hungry.
I have food.
Let me see you.
I won't hurt you, I promise.
Sally?
- What are you doing under there?
- I'm looking for my doll.
- Looking for what?
How about Teddy instead?
No. That's all right.
- Did you lose a tooth?
- That's not mine.
- I found it.
- You found it? Here in the house?
Yeah.
Can I call Mommy now?
No, it's too late. She's probably asleep.
I don't think you should keep this.
It's not very sanitary.
What about this light? Should I...
Leave it on, please.
All right, well, sleep well.
Sally, would you do me a favor?
Would you try to, maybe,
be friends with Kim?
- Yes.
- Thanks, kiddo.
Kim, have you seen my razor?
We have to leave in five minutes.
- Yeah. Have you seen my razor?
- Here, take mine.
Five minutes.
My dress.
Sally. I want to talk to you downstairs
right now.
I cannot believe you cut up Kim's clothes.
I didn't do it.
- I didn't do anything. I swear.
- Stop lying.
It was a horrible thing to do.
And it was dangerous.
You could have cut yourself.
What did you use, my razor?
Let me see your hands.
- It's mine.
- What is this?
Where did you get this?
- Let me go home.
- You can't go home.
Just let me go home.
I'm sorry about this.
She's never done anything like this before.
She's obviously very angry about something.
Alex, that is not anger. That is fear.
We need to go. Mrs. Underhill,
Kim and I have an appointment
at the historical society.
We'll be back this afternoon.
Sally, we're going out.
Listen to Mrs. Underhill
and do what she says.
And you think about
what you need to say to Kim, okay?
Sally.
Are you there?
Did you cut Kim's clothes?
Do you have my dad's razor?
You have to tell me the truth.
If you want to be friends.
I won't be angry.
Sally's not angry.
They're angry.
No, I'm not angry.
They don't want to, but we do.
Come down here, Sally.
Come down and play.
You said you were hungry.
Do you like raisins?
We said we liked them.
See? Delicious.
Delicious. Yeah.
So delicious.
Did you do something bad?
You have to answer if
you want to be friends.
Yes, friend.
Sally?
What are you doing
down here in the dark?
Were you talking to someone?
Is there someone here with you?
No. I'm all alone.
There's nobody here.
Why don't you go help Mrs. Underhill
make lunch?
Go on. Off you go now.
That's right. Up those steps!
Quick as you can, now!
Harris. You old fool.
I swear. I didn't tell them anything!
No.
No, please!
Get away!
I had an accident! Call for help!
Don't look.
I could hear screams down there.
- Noises.
- Did you see anything?
He asked me to leave the cellar.
It was so dark in there,
he must have stumbled.
- Mr. Hurst, thank God!
- What happened?
- Are you William Harris' employer?
- Yeah.
There's been an accident.
- Are you okay? Where's Sally?
- I'm sorry. She saw him.
I tried to cover her eyes,
and I was too late.
- Where is she?
- She's in the garden.
I am sorry!
Sally?
Hi.
Are you scared?
Do you want to talk about it?
Is Mr. Harris going to die?
No, Sally.
He is going to be okay.
Can I show you something?
This is my favorite part of the house.
Blackwood loved nature.
He imported these fish from Japan.
And so did we.
They're called koi.
They're considered magical.
Badgers can spot them
against the mud at the bottom
because of their bright colors.
So what makes them special
is also what makes them vulnerable.
They have to be tough.
And you, too, Sally.
I didn't touch your clothes.
I swear to God, I never touched them!
- I didn't touch them.
- Sally.
I didn't! Didn't cut them, I promise.
I don't care about my clothes.
I can't really tell. 1804, I think.
It's hard to see.
The coin is pretty worn down.
She probably found it
in Blackwood's studio.
I don't want her
going down there anymore.
I'm worried about her, Kim. It's not safe.
- This is Joanne.
- Mommy?
Oh, sweetie, it's you! How are you?
Can I come home?
You want to come...
The sashimi. Stuart, the sashimi.
- I don't like it here.
- You what?
Honey, don't fret. It's so beautiful there.
You just need to get used to it.
But it's cold.
- Honey, what?
- My bed is too big.
- Sweetheart.
- And I think I'm getting sick.
You're not getting sick.
It will take a little tiny bit of getting used to,
but you are going to be so happy there.
Okay? I promise. You'll get used to it.
I got to go, honey. Mommy's got to go.
I'll see you soon. Bye!
Kim?
- Don't leave.
- What's wrong?
Even when I'm asleep.
And don't turn off the lights.
I'll be right here.
Come on.
Kim?
I love you. I love you.
Daddy! Daddy!
Daddy, please!
Daddy!
Sally, what's the matter?
I don't want them to come anymore.
Who, Sally?
The little things.
They live in the basement.
They gave me the silver dollar.
They said they wanted to be my friend.
But they're horrible and mean.
- You just had a nightmare.
- Don't say that!
It's okay.
My bear.
Look what they did to my bear.
Your dad tells me art is your
favorite subject. I wish I could draw.
Drawing is easy.
The other kids can't do feet and hands.
When you say "the other kids,"
do you feel they're different from you?
My doctor back home asked me that.
What was your answer?
Okay. Let's start with something easier.
What's your favorite color?
What is that? Purple?
Black.
How about these little things you saw?
What do you think they are?
Fairies.
Or gnomes.
But scary ones?
And you say they know your name?
They talk to you?
Yes.
What do they say?
They want to play with me.
Is that all?
They say my parents don't love me.
Can I go now?
Just a few more questions, okay?
There is a lot of anxiety in that little girl
and a deep belief that she's not wanted.
I believe that's what's triggering
these fantastic episodes.
She told me she found a little tray filled
with teeth right inside that fireplace.
Yeah. She found a tooth,
but that doesn't mean anything, does it?
She's constructing this elaborate fantasy
about wrinkles, claws, fangs.
She's individuated
each one of those things,
her imaginary world, its inhabitants.
It's as detailed as any
I've ever encountered.
What do we do?
I'd like to try her on a
stronger medication, for a start.
I'll ask her doctor in LA to send me a copy
of her charts.
You call my office,
make another appointment.
Okay, great.
Meanwhile, I'll give you something
to help her sleep.
I'm going to be late. I can't believe it.
If we don't get the extension on this loan,
we're not going to get the paintings
or the furniture back on time.
We forgot the invitations
for the historical society.
Maybe we should just
postpone the dinner.
Kim, it's Architectural Digest.
We have to get the house on the cover.
- I know.
- If we don't,
I'm never going to get my career back,
and we're not going to sell the place.
- How often have we talked about this?
- What about what's been happening?
Harris? That was an accident.
- I'm talking about Sally.
- It's all in her head!
It's real to her.
It doesn't matter if we see it.
- Come on!
- Calm down!
I'm going to walk. It'll be faster.
I'll see you back at home.
I'm not sure how lucid he'll be.
He's pretty heavily sedated.
Mr. Harris, I know this is difficult,
but I need to understand something.
I need to know what Sally saw
so that I can help her.
Is she out of the house?
No.
Out.
She needs to be out of there.
Why?
Why was that room sealed up?
Grandfather.
Your grandfather closed it up?
- Yes.
- Why?
After...
After what?
Blackwood.
What about Blackwood?
Lot 1134.
Public library.
Get her out of the house.
The library will be closing in 15 minutes.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
- Can I help you?
- I'm looking for the librarian.
Lot 1134.
Emerson Blackwood, Special Collections.
One sec.
Right this way.
Can't remember the last time
anyone requested these. They're beautiful.
I'm a designer.
I've been working at Fallen Mill.
Wow. Now, that's a privilege.
Personally, I think Emerson Blackwood
rivaled Audubon.
Come across his mural?
A mural? Where?
There in the house, supposedly.
If you do, I'd love to see it.
Hello?
Now, it's pretty ironic, really.
For a committed realist, someone who
insisted on drawing only from nature,
to do these at the end of his life.
I've looked at everything by Blackwood,
and I've never seen any of these.
You wouldn't.
The family made it a restricted donation.
- These may never be published.
- Is it possible to get copies?
I'll see what I can do.
"Wrinkles, claws, teeth?"
Have you ever read Machen?
Arthur Machen. Welsh.
He believed in fairy folk,
these ancient entities
from the netherworld, predating mankind.
Blackwood quotes him extensively.
Here, that line. There.
"One life must be taken."
These creatures had to take one human life
every time they emerged.
to replenish their ranks.
Many of these creatures fed on the bones,
the teeth of young children.
And then there's a truce, a pact of sorts,
between Pope Sylvester II
and these ancient beings
in the year 999.
In exchange for human teeth, they start
leaving silver pieces under the pillow.
Now, this is the last known drawing
by Emerson Blackwood,
made shortly before his disappearance
and the loss of his child.
His child?
Blackwood's only son vanished, lost.
Not long after, Blackwood himself
disappeared without a trace.
No!
No! No! Please!
Sally, what's wrong?
Sally, open the door!
Oh, my God!
Dear, thank goodness you're home.
- Where is she?
- I put her to bed.
She wouldn't stop screaming.
Sally?
Kim!
She's not down here.
I think she's run away.
She's done it before.
Once she tried to walk all the way back
to LA from our family home in Boston.
I wouldn't be surprised
if that's what she's doing.
I went and visited Harris today.
Blackwood had a son. Did you know that?
And when he was eight, he disappeared.
And Blackwood vanished a few days later.
Why are you telling me this?
A lot of what Blackwood wrote
at the end of his life,
it's awfully close to Sally's story,
gnomes, creatures, all of it.
Kim, don't tell me you believe this.
Something terrible happened
in that basement.
- We need to leave.
- What are you talking about?
Put a million miles
between us and that house.
Every cent I have is in that house.
And you're saying that we just walk away?
I accept that
my daughter has problems, okay?
Thank you. We all know that.
But they do not involve
monsters in the basement.
There she is.
Come on, Sally. Get in the car.
Sally, please, just tonight,
and after the party we'll talk, okay?
Four, three, two and one.
There.
After the party, I will get you out of here.
No matter what. I promise.
- Sally!
- No.
I took it from them.
- You can't have this.
- They stole it. You don't understand.
- I need it to fight back.
- Absolutely not.
Please!
Nobody believes me.
Sally, I trust you,
and you can tell me anything at all.
They don't like bright lights.
Those things.
They don't?
Then I have a good idea.
Mr. Jacoby, I am so
glad you could make it.
- Alex, call me Charles.
- Charles.
- My wife, Evelyn.
- Hello, Alex.
It's a pleasure. Come on in.
The house looks absolutely fantastic.
You've done a remarkable job.
Well, thank you.
- We'd love the nickel tour.
- Of course. That's the whole point.
The foyer, obviously.
The mahogany, we shipped from
the very same vendor
that Blackwood used in London.
It's been in business since 1865.
You know Bill from the heritage board.
Easy, Sally. Not everybody
wants to have their photograph taken.
So, Alex, where's Kim?
I think she's still upstairs.
Why don't you step into the library,
grab a drink, and I'll join you in a moment.
Kim, hey, what's going on?
Her drawings.
They're exactly Blackwood's sketches.
Yeah, I'm sure she probably saw
your photographs and copied them.
No, she didn't.
Kim, please, Jacoby's here.
- Alex, this is your daughter!
- I know.
This is serious!
Just because you keep denying it
does not mean
- it's not happening.
- Kim, I can't do...
Excuse me, Mr. Hurst.
When should we serve dinner?
Ten minutes, please. Kim, everybody
is waiting. Will you come downstairs?
- We can talk about this later.
- No.
- I have proof, Dad. Look!
- Not now, honey.
- Please!
- Not now. Come on!
Welcome, everybody.
Please, have a seat.
If I could just say a few words
to all of you friends of Fallen Mill,
both big and small.
Thank you for joining us this evening.
It means a great deal to us.
Every aspect of this restoration
has followed the exact specifications
and materials used
in the original construction of the house,
including the wood assembling techniques,
the layout in the kitchen,
even the lacquering process
for all the timber.
It's something Kim and I are very proud of,
and I'm sure all of you,
with your vast array of expertise,
will appreciate the attention to detail.
The art you see on the walls, the friezes,
even the furniture that you're sitting on,
has all been meticulously chosen,
reassembled or restored,
depending on its condition,
to, I think, truly represent the essence
of the Blackwood collection.
So, thank you to the heritage board
for their assistance,
and to the historical society,
and, of course, to our guest of honor,
Charles Jacoby.
Your interest in our projects is nothing
short of inspirational. So, thank you.
And finally, to the house itself.
May its newly restored life be long
and happy.
I guess not everybody is a fan
of tonight's menu.
Poor Sally. No one believes you.
What do you want?
Please just tell me what you want!
We want you!
Daddy! Daddy, please!
Daddy!
Sally?
- Daddy!
- Sally?
Daddy, they're in here!
Open the door!
- Charles.
- What's going on in there?
No! Get off of me! Stop it!
Sally!
Sally. Sally.
Look at me. Sally, look at me. Look at me.
Picture, I took a picture.
- I think we better call it a night.
- I think we should.
It's okay. It's okay.
Alex, can I talk to you?
I feel like I have no idea what to do.
I love my daughter, Kim,
and I love you.
I love you, too.
We should go, right?
- I'll get Sally ready.
- I'll get the car.
- Will you put this in the car?
- Yeah.
Kim?
Hi.
Where are we going?
We're going to go to a hotel downtown.
We're going to get you out of here.
Alex?
It's okay, it's okay.
A life will be taken.
One life must be taken.
Sally.
Sally!
Child's teeth!
Kim?
Daddy?
Kim!
Kim! Please.
Kim.
Wake up, please!
Wake up, Kim. Wake up, Kim.
- Wake up, Kim.
Wake up, Kim.
The key. The key.
Kim, please!
Daddy! No!
Kim!
Kim, please!
Sally?
Sally? Sally!
Kim!
Let go of me!
Don't make me go in there!
Kim! Please!
Kim?
- Please, Kim!
- I'm here, Sally!
No, please!
Sally!
Kim?
No! Go away!
Hold on! Hold on! I got you.
Keep them away, Sally. Use the light.
Use the light.
Kim!
Get him.
No! Please!
- Get away from me!
- Get off of me!
When I cut this rope, Sally, you run!
Please!
You run! You got that?
No, what about you?
- No! Please!
- Be strong.
Kim!
No!
Sally?
Sally, are you okay? Sally.
Alex?
Kim!
Dad?
Daddy?
Daddy.
Please!
That's far enough, Sally.
I love you, Kim.
They will find us. They will find us
and hurt us. We must fight.
No, we will go deeper, and we will wait.
They will forget, and others will come.
When will they come?
When will we get them?
Soon, soon.
- We have all the time in the world.
- Yes.
All the time in the world.