Record it all, God damn it!
Rosso, record!
Okay!
Okay, let’s check.
Connect!
From now on we record it all.
Don’t disconnect
until we’re finished.
-Finished what, chief?
-’Till I say so, okay?
-Anything else?
-No. We’re going in.
Fuckin’ great!
Rosso, let’s check.
Mini cameras in.
-Martos, in.
-Make me look handsome.
We’re working on that.
Now I’ve got you, Rosso!
Chief, in.
-The signal is failing.
-As usual!
How much time have we got?
3 minutes.
Let’s check weapons...
The area is sealed. The usual
protocol, inspect and recognition.
-We’ll get orders when we get there.
Orders from who?
From whoever gives orders.
Shit, let’s make it easy.
Easy? No shit!
We’ll have to use this.
Here.
Hell!
So the infection is for real?
-So it seems.
-Fuckin’ masks again!
-You too, Rosso.
-Shit!
How many times are you gonna check?
Okay, guys, get ready.
Chief, can you turn the light off?
I’ll check the searchlight.
Larra, Argentinean and from
the Valencia soccer team.
I have been since “El Matador”.
Who is “El Matador”?
You don’t know? I won’t stand up
‘cause I don’t fit.
Maria Alberto Kempes!
-We got backup lights?
-Assault, three.
You’re from Granada and for the Barca.
Yes, but don’t compare.
Rivaldo, Romario, Koeman,
-Kily, Pirjo...
-That’s enough!
We’re arriving.
There seems to be action.
...fuckin’ great...
Take it all.
Battering rams, flares. Everything.
Sir, who carries the battering ram?
-I will. Fuck you!
-come on, guys!
I only asked...
Enough! Okay, let’s go, go, go...!
Attention, attention,
leave the perimeter!
Sir!
This is the situation.
We know there is
a contagious infection.
We’ve quarantined the building.
A technician from
the Ministry is going in
to see if he can find out
what’s going on.
Your mission is to escort him.
-This is Dr....
Owen, Ministry of Health.
A pleasure.
No one’s gone in or out?
2 hrs. ago a Ministry Dr.
went in to
try and control this,
but we lost contact 70 minutes ago.
The people infected seem
to show a certain type of
aggressiveness.
The symptoms are similar to rabies.
We have at least
two deceased inside,
and one is a cop.
-Hold it, hold it!
-You’re going in?
You’re going in?
I need to go in with you.
My wife and daughter
are in there.
Get him out of here!
They have a fever.
I went to the drug store...
Rosso, we’re going in.
-Thanks,
-Let’s go!
Be careful in there.
You know, guys!
Fast and easy!
-Fast and easy, sir.
-Fast and easy!
-We need an authorization.
-Authorization granted.
Rosso!
Let’s go!
Main door locked.
Don’t touch it!
What the fuck...?
The virus is not in the air,
just in fluids, blood and saliva.
You can take it off,
there’s no danger.
-So why’d they force us to...
-Pure show.
We must keep this confidential.
What do we do, chief?
Out!
-Are you sure?
-We’ll start upstairs.
-Let’s go!
We must reach the penthouse.
We think the infection
started there.
All clear!
This is too calm.
Let’s keep going.
Chief, chief, doctor.
Doctor, upstairs.
Make way.
Go on.
-And you?
-I need to get a sample.
-We should have controlled downstairs.
-There’s no time.
Let’s go.
Hold it!
Rosso, cover me.
Stop, stop!
It’s here.
We must go over it.
Be careful!
Battering ram!
Ready.
Larra, light!
-Control the door, Martos.
Okay.
We have to secure this place
but above all, don’t touch anything.
If in doubt, let me know.
Martos, how’s that going?
Done.
Okay, you’ve heard.
Let’s get to work.
-Rosso, you stay there.
Okay.
Whatever he says.
You know how it works,
extensive documentation,
so record everything.
What are we looking for, exactly?
You just record.
Give me some light here.
It’s still hot.
The enzyme has proven
to be extremely contagious.
They’re very nervous in Rome.
Carboni called this morning.
He ordered me to stop it all.
But the insect bites worry me.
I think they are mosquitoes.
Record the walls, everything...
They are afraid it’s too late.
Dear God, I’m your humble servant...
There’s something here!
Let’s go!
Martos, check it out.
Be careful.
Up we go!
Rosso, tap in.
In.
Report.
Looks like a junk room.
Nothing, just shit.
Clear.
What was that?
It seems as if
we’re not alone.
So it seems.
Let’s go check it out.
No! Our priority is
to examine this place.
Yes, and see if there are
any survivors.
I remind you that
I give the orders here.
come on, come on!
Martos!
Go, Martos!
Go, go!
You are making a mistake.
What is that?
Martos.
Larra, cover.
Rosso... cut in.
In!
Martos, report.
It comes from here.
The door is open.
I’m going in.
Okay, but be careful.
It seems all clear.
Okay, go on.
It’s here.
Be careful.
Martos, Martos!
Someone seems to have had a party.
Okay, come back here.
What is it, Martos?
What is that?
What’s going on there?
Hang on, Martos!
We’re coming!
-Where?
-It’s over there!
Martos!
What happened,
where is that thing?
-Careful!
-Martos, no!
Martos, take it easy!
It’s us!
-Get it off me!
-Fuck, Martos!
Martos, what the fuck are you doing?
Get it off, Larra.
Holy father!
Look at this servant of yours, and
send your Spirit to him.
Christ’s blood breaks all bonds,
all influence on this body.
In the sign of the cross,
free us of our enemies, Our Lord.
By your cross, save us.
What shit is this?
Larra, fuckin’ help me!
What should I do?
You record. Keep on recording.
Make way!
-Shit!
-I can’t take this!
I just can’t!
Why’d he stop now?
What did he do?
What shit is this?
We have to go back
to the penthouse.
We must get the fuck out of here!
That man was okay 5 minutes ago!
What sort of a virus does this?
I recommend you limit yourselves
to carrying out your orders.
You recommend...!
The way things are now,
we can’t guarantee your safety,
nor ours either.
This is way too big.
I remind you that no one is leaving
until I give the order, and
you know how it works,
voice recognition.
Now you listen to me!
I’ve just lost, or whatever,
one of my men.
So start telling us all you know
because clearly you know more than me.
Chief, relax.
Okay, okay, but let’s go upstairs,
we’re not safe here.
Let’s go, let’s go!
Larra, the door.
Okay.
Now you tell me what the fuck
happened down there.
It’s not just a simple virus.
We just fuckin’ saw that!
This is Tristana Medeiros.
At 11 she began giving signs
of being possessed.
The Vatican checked it and
the case was accepted.
Possessed by what?
A diabolic possession.
Father Albelda took charge
of the girl.
It was a perfect chance to study
the physiological symptoms
of a diabolic possession.
If we could isolate
the chemical essence, we could
find an antidote.
What the fuck’s he saying, chief?
What the fuck are you saying?
It all had to be very discreet
that’s why they chose this place.
I can’t believe this.
You can’t be serious.
We seemed to have
achieved it, but
something must have gone wrong.
This is fuckin’ shit!
This guy’s pulling our fuckin’ leg!
Who the fuck are you?
We were told you were from
the Ministry of Health.
Don’t be a fool.
Answer! Who the fuck sent you?
It has nothing to do with them.
They don’t know
what’s really going on.
They’re not in charge here.
What a fuckin’ joke!
Chief, the guy is a priest.
A priest, chief.
-Sons of a bitch!
-They tricked us!
This is a secret operation.
No one should know.
You either.
What are you going to do?
What?
Kill us after we’re finished?
What are you going to do,
you son of a bitch?
Be sure no one will believe you.
You’re right!
What will we say,
the building is infested with what?
Possessed people.
Demons.
Chief!
Shit... Shit!
Hey,
I don’t care what happened here.
I’ve just lost a man
and all I want is to get
out of this fuckin’ hell now!
So...
tell me what we must do...
and let’s get this the fuck over!
As per reports,
there should be a blood sample
of the girl,
the original blood,
that’s what we want.
We need it to find
the antidote.
Let’s finish searching here.
There was a door at the back.
come on, Larra!
come on, come on, come on!
I’m coming, I’m coming.
come on, Rosso!
It’s there!
Yes... it has to be here.
come on, come on.
Doctor...
This has no way out.
-This doesn’t make sense.
-There’s nothing here.
What shit is this?
Get back, get back!
These are your experiments?
What is this?
Relax!
Relax? These are children!
They’re children!
Fuck!
Where the fuck did they
send us, chief?
Relax.
I’m relaxed, chief.
Larra! Larra!
Relax, okay?
What is this?
Relax, Larra!
Fuckin’ relax!
Relax. Relax, okay?
Okay, it’s over. There’s nothing here.
No! We must go on!
That blood must be somewhere.
I don’t get it.
-Nothing here!
-It has to be.
Chief!
-Shoot!
-Get it off. Get it off me!
Don’t move...
Careful!
-Chief, what was that?
-I don’t fuckin’ know!
Relax, everyone take it easy!
Let’s go...
The ceiling, the ceiling!
Where has it gone?
Chief, chief!
Get away!
Be careful!
Don’t come closer. Back!
Back, back, Rosso, back.
-Shit!
-Freeze!
Don’t come closer.
The ceiling, watch the ceiling.
Turn it around, carefully.
Okay, get back.
Who the fuck is he?
Albelda, no doubt.
Chief, there’s something here.
I think it’s a duct.
A duct, of course.
Bravo, Albelda, very smart!
That blood must be up there.
We must...
Get it off!
Get it off me!
Okay, shoot, aim at his head.
Aim at his head!
Shoot it, shoot it!
Okay. Shoot at the head!
-It’s under control.
-It’s just a child!
-Just a child!
-No!
No, it’s not.
Rosso...
Larra, check the ceiling.
It’ll hold up.
Doctor!
Take good hold.
-Be careful!
-Shit!
Be careful!
-What do you see?
-Just a moment.
Rosso, cut in!
In.
Larra, be very careful.
Don’t worry.
Shit...
See anything?
There’s something here.
What is it?
It’s like a freezer.
And it seems to work.
The test tube! Get it!
-It’s got a label.
-What’s it say?
C28, M03, T. Medeiros.
We’ve got it.
Now bring it here.
-What’s going on?
-I don’t know.
What is this?
come on, get out of there,
Larra, get out!
Come on, Larra, out you go!
Are you okay?
Fuckin’ great.
Now give it to me.
You have her blood.
Now let us out of here.
No, not until we’re sure.
I must check it.
But check what, fuck?
It’s quite clear there.
Medeiros. What more do you need?
That makes no difference.
I told you, I must check it.
You already have, Medeiros!
Doctor!
My omnipotent God, see my
distress and come in my aid,
Jesus, image of the Father,
splendor of the eternal light.
Hold this. Very carefully.
What the fuck’s he saying?
...comfort for the abandoned,
you who came into this world
so compassionate of me,
who went down to the hells,
who resurrected amongst the dead,
free us from our enemies,
have compassion of us.
It has reacted, we’ve got it.
Hell!
I’m sorry. It was burning.
What now?
That was the only one we had!
Fuck!
-Voice recognition requested.
Owen.
-Recognition confirmed.
-Go ahead.
We have seen civilians at a window.
What do we do?
No one is to leave.
I repeat, no one is to go
outside until I give the order.
Roger!
What now?
-Keep on looking.
Oh, come on.
-Larra, the door!
-Yes, chief.
No one’s out of here until
we finish the mission.
That’s clear.
What’s not so clear is...
Watch it!
Stay clear!
Get back, Larra!
Hey, who the fuck are you?
-How did they get in?
-They’ve got a camera.
Catch them!
Catch them? What for?
They’re not going anywhere,
you said so.
You know what
a secret operation is.
No cameras can be around.
That’s an order!
-come on, come on!
-God damn it!
Hold it! Freeze!
Move it, fast!
Let’s go!
-Where the fuck did they go?
-I don’t know. Move, move!
Larra, check.
Larra, report.
All clear.
It seems they’re not here.
In any case,
they’re not getting out.
All clear.
Make sure.
-What is this?
-I said in the head!
-Shit!
-Larra.
Fast!
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
Fast, fast, move it!
Here, use it!
Over here, the door!
It’s open.
This will hold.
What are they doing?
Leaving.
-Larra, Larra... fuck!
-Cut in Rosso.
-In.
-Shit!
Larra... Larra... Situation.
Larra!
I’m in front, chief.
Stay there.
We’ll get you out.
Hold on. As soon as it’s all clear,
we’ll go get you.
-Ma’am, hold it.
-Shoot.
-Hold it.
Okay, okay, okay...
Larra, get back!
come on, do it!
Take cover. Take cover.
The clip, chief!
I’m out of fuckin’ ammo!
Take cover, quick!
The window, the window.
Shit!
Okay, okay.
Keep cool.
The gun.
Listen, the pistol.
You still have ammo.
You can do it, Larra.
You can do it...
Larra, what are you doing?
Larra... Larra!
Larra!
Chief...
We’re getting out.
Give the fuckin’ order.
We’re getting out!
Incorrect voice recognition.
We’re not finished,
we need the blood.
There was just one sample,
you said so.
Now it’s lost.
It’s all over.
We can get a new sample.
That’s bull shit.
You said it had to be
the original blood.
The girl Medeiros
began the contagion.
The evil resides within her.
We must find her and
take a sample.
It’s the only way.
We don’t even know
if she’s still alive.
Enough!
We’re leaving.
Do you have kids?
What about you?
What?
Would you shoot them
in the head given the case?
If this virus got out of here
we had better have an antidote.
Chief...
Don’t move.
Don’t touch it.
A woman.
She’s dead.
-What is this?
-A rocket.
A rocket?
What the hell...?
Chief, I’m receiving
a signal from Martos.
What? Cut in.
Cut in, Rosso.
Now we know where they are.
Watch out!
Get her off me!
Get her off!
The camera, get the camera!
I’ve got her, I’ve got her!
I know you.
Shut up! In the name of Christ,
where are you?
Record it all. That’s fundamental.
She knows you?
What the fuck’s going on?
They are her puppets.
She talks through them.
Who’s she?
The girl, Medeiros. The evil.
Where are you?
You never give up, father.
God protects me.
Help me, I can’t hold her back.
Here you are!
Get her!
In the name of God,
where are you hiding?
Search, priest, search!
She’s getting away, Rosso.
Help me!
No, wait, we need her.
For the last time, where are you?
Our God orders you: Tell me
where you are?
What should I do?
Rosso, fuck!
Hold her tight!
What have you done?
I could have made her talk.
We almost had it.
It was our last chance.
No, there’s still a chance.
-Martos.
-Shit!
What’s going on?
I don’t know.
The lenses are broken.
It’s shifted.
Use your lighter.
-I’m not sure.
-Where should we put it?
-Here, here.
-What the fuck am I doing here?
-It won’t fall?
-No, grab it over here.
I’ll give it some more,
just in case.
-How many now?
-Three.
Only?
-That’s what we said.
Will this last long?
Don’t you worry. Just record.
But, will it fly with three?
Well, it cost me 20 Euros which,
by the way,
we were to split between three.
Yeah!
Did we say that, or didn’t we?
Bull shit!
-Shit, didn’t we?
-Sure, man.
She’s an asshole!
come on, she’s your sister.
-Sure, you like her.
-What, asshole?
-What a pain.
-Where do we put it?
-Here.
-I don’t know why the fuck I’m here.
-You sure it won’t fall?
-Yeah, grab this.
Mire, come over here.
It’s going to fly and
you must follow it.
Sure, we’ll see.
Fuckin’ shit!
You record, I don’t trust her.
Yeah, you record and don’t get...
come on, come on...
One, two, three.
come on, guys!
come on!
Up and away!
Come on, cutie, let’s fly!
What shit!
You were taken for 20 Euros.
-Oh, shit.
-What the fuck is this?
What a couple of assholes, guys!
Shit, what is this?
Fuck.
What the fuck are you doing here?
Nothing!
We are evacuating the building.
-Why?
-Move it, now!
What is this?
Incredible, man!
It’s covered with plastic.
Let me see.
Fuck, and those?
-I don’t know but they’re like SWAT.
-SWAT?
What are they going to do?
I don’t know, but something
big is going down there.
If not, why...?
Uri, Uri. Look at that guy.
You’re recording, right?
He’s out of it, man.
What?
-Follow him.
-Shut the fuck up!
-come on Uri, follow them.
-Hey, you can’t be here, guys.
Uri, come on, fast.
-I’m coming, fuckin’ hell!
-What?
-He’s there, man, over there.
What’s he doing?
Look, he’s with a fireman.
They’re up to something.
Tito!
We’ve got coverage.
I spoke with mama.
She said to go to auntie’s place.
-You’ll go to auntie’s place.
-Idiot!
-Look! What are you doing?
-They’re coming, man.
I told you!
I’m sure they’re coming in.
Let’s go!
-Fuck, let’s go!
-Go, go, go...
-Tito, you’ll get into a mess.
-come on, man!
Wait, Mire!
Fuckin’ wait.
-Run, run, run!
-Holy shit!
You’ll get into a mess, Tito.
-It’s here!
-You sure?
If not, why would it be open?
-What do we do?
-Fuck, go in, right?
-Don’t fuck around, man.
-Well, okay...
-come on, help me.
-Mire, hold it, please.
No, I’m not going in.
-Sure you are!
-No, I’m not going in.
Fuck, Mire, please...
This is our chance.
We go in, and that’s it.
Sure...
maybe we’ll make some money.
You’re out of it!
Can’t you see what’s going on?
-You’re like kids.
-Then why the fuck did we come here?
You guys came.
Don’t involve me.
I’m sick of your stupidities.
First with the doll,
and now this.
-Okay, don’t blow my mind!
-Fuckin’ relax, guys!
She’s always fuckin’ us.
For once we can do something cool...
You know what?
The camera is mine
and I’m out of here.
Fuck, Tito! Fuck, Tito!
Fuck, man!
She’s so dumb.
Then let her go.
What’s this all about?
You always mess things up.
-Don’t mess up, Mire.
-Fuck, Mire.
Mire...!
-Do it for me.
-This girl is dumb.
Go to hell, you nerd!
-Mire, please!
-I said no...!
-Fuck!
-What’s up?
I don’t know,
I can’t see a shit.
How weird because this is full of it.
We’ll get sick here.
Fuck, I thought it would be worse.
Worse? I’m about to throw up.
This is your street, isn’t it?
-Some of your shit must be here.
-You’re such a pig!
You don’t shit, or what?
Sure I do,
but this isn’t my street!
-Dogs?
-Uri, hold the camera.
Okay, okay.
-Got it?
-Tito, this isn’t cool, let’s go.
-What the fuck is this?
-The cops!
-Fuck!
Run, run, run...
Shut up!
They’ll hear you.
We’re fucking this up!
They are coming!
What are you doing?
-This way.
-come on!
Make it fuckin’ fast.
This way!
We’re gonna flow it, man.
Shut up!
-They got in this way.
-You’re crazy!
We’re overdoing it.
Mire, we can’t go back.
They’ve seen us.
Go on, move.
Where are we?
Shit!
Okay, we’re in, now let’s get out.
Fuckin’ wait.
You’re a pain in the ass!
Hell, Tito.
Have a look, man.
-Uri, drop that!
-Shit!
Cool. Is it real?
-It weighs a lot.
-Tito, please, drop that.
Fuck...
I told you, we’re gonna get caught.
You see, it’s them.
The fireman and the freak.
See anything?
-Holy shit!
-It just went off.
Shit!
-We’ve done nothing!
-How’d you get in?
That way, just like you.
What’s going on here?
This is dangerous,
you can’t stay here.
What about you?
come on, let’s go.
Fuck, wait, wait!
What are you doing with the camera?
-Holy shit!
-I’m sorry!
Where the fuck did you get that?
It was there, on the floor.
It looks official,
police issue.
Must be from the first who came in.
Get out of here, fast!
Why is that?
There’s an infection in the air!
And so you don’t wear masks.
You think we’re dumb?
-They are of no use.
-Shut the fuck up!
But it’s true.
Just shut the fuck up.
And you guys, out.
-Tito, let’s go.
-No, Mire, no.
-Fuck, I’m out of here.
-come on, Tito!
Didn’t you hear?
If not, will you shoot me?
Tito, Tito!
Uri, hold it, please.
-Tito, please.
-Leave me alone.
come on, Tito.
Tito!
Son of a bitch!
This is locked.
Get the fuck back.
It’s fuckin’ hot!
-It’s burning...
-Shit!
They’ve welded it,
we can’t get out now.
-Fuckin great!
-But why?
Because they followed you,
assholes. Shit!
There must be another exit.
What exit? They have orders to shoot.
I hear them over the radio.
And now what?
Now you’ll do what I say,
understood?
Understood?
I told you to turn
that fuckin’ camera off.
You wanted to record, right?
Well, record this, let everyone see!
-They’re fooling you...
-What is this?
Ask them outside!
No, we’ve got to go now.
My daughter, upstairs...
Calm down, you’re putting
all of us in danger.
I too want to find my companions.
But all together.
Shut up! Where is it?
-Second floor.
-Okay, come on, then!
Let’s go, let’s go, fast!
come on, come on!
-I don’t want to go up.
-Mire, please!
No, please! I don’t want
to go up there!
Please, I want to go home!
You should have thought
that before!
Mire, relax...
Fuck, come on.
It’s here.
come on, fast...
Don’t lag behind. Move it fast!
Go on, go on, go on... go on!
Shit! Sure it’s here?
-Which one?
-This one.
Shit, shit, shit.
Move it fast, don’t lag behind!
In, fast!
Tito, please, let’s go.
Be quiet.
Relax.
Jennifer? Mari Carmen?
Jenni...
Mari Carmen!
Where is Jenni?
Mari Carmen, where is the girl?
Take it easy, lady, take it easy!
Shit!
What’s on her face?
Hold the camera.
Hold it!
-Where’s the lighter!
-What now, Tito?
Tito, what are you doing?
Mari Carmen!
We’ll all die,
thanks to your fuckin’ video.
Listen, no one is going to die here...
no one.
And what are you doing?
She’s bitten me.
I must stop the infection.
Water... water... water.
-You have to help us, please!
-You have to do something, please!
You can get us out.
Outside is full
of policemen, please!
Take it easy, relax.
Okay.
Everyone relax.
Don’t go near the windows
for your own safety.
I repeat, keep away
from the windows.
Tell them we’re kids
and have done nothing.
Snipers, code 3.
What happened?
Down! Get down!
What’s going on...?
I don’t know.
They’re shooting.
come on, come on!
Hey, wait! Fuck! Hold it.
Jennifer!
Hold it.
Get back, Larra!
Who the fuck are you?
SWAT.
What should we do?
They’re cops, they have to help us.
Fast... don’t let them get away!
Be quiet! Be quiet!
Where the fuck are they?
Be quiet.
What do we do now?
I want to get out of here,
to get out, please!
Well, fuck you!
We’ll never get out of here.
We’ll all die for your fault!
Shut the fuck up! Shit, shut up!
What’s going on?
What is this?
Uri, there’s something here.
A helmet.
-What could have happened?
-Give me that.
Daddy...
Is that you, Daddy?
Who’s that?
The child.
I’m here.
Jennifer?
Daddy, I’m afraid.
It’s over there.
What should we do?
We must get her out of there.
-What is this?
-Daddy, open up.
Open up, please.
-We have to help her, please!
-No!
The girl... where is the girl?
We’ve done nothing.
We just want to help her.
-Go away, go...!
-No!
The pistol, the pistol.
Shoot him!
Shoot!
-The pistol!
-Shoot him!
Shoot!
Kill him, please!
Shoot, Mire!
Mire! Fuck, Mire!
Shoot!
Hold it!
Don’t move. Hold it!
-Please help us!
-Don’t move... freeze!
We haven’t done anything, please.
Relax, relax.
Where is he? Where is he?
-He attacked us.
-But where is he?
I killed him.
Okay, it’s okay.
Just give me the gun, slowly.
Why’d you open the door?
You shouldn’t have done that!
He talked like a little girl,
and we thought...
What the fuck were you thinking?
What the fuck are you doing here?
I don’t know, I don’t know.
What do we do now?
You tell me.
That was our last chance.
We’re back where we started.
What’s wrong with you?
It hurts a lot.
I think he bit me.
-Stay back!
-No, no, what are you doing?
Grab him, we need him.
Relax, kid, just relax.
Everything’s okay.
-No, no, no!
-What are you doing?
That door, we must lock them in!
come on, come on, put her inside.
Quick, close it.
We have to block it.
Get that piece!
come on, quick, move it.
Shit! He got away.
-Don’t run, kid.
-Don’t let him get away.
come on, bring him here.
Help me!
Rosso, get the camera,
we need it.
We must record everything,
document it.
-Shit!
-What’s wrong?
The battery is about to die.
So what?
Let’s get this over.
No, we need proof. I told you,
those are the orders!
Okay, the sound
seems to be coming in.
-Does it work?
-I’m working on it.
come on, Rosso.
Okay!
Recording!
Now I am going to ask you
once again.
Who are you and
what are you doing here?
We came to make a TV show,
and that’s it.
A TV show...
...I hid because...
She must be the TV anchor
who came in with the firemen.
-Stay back, we can’t be sure.
-Careful.
Make sure.
come here, come here.
Turn around!
-What is this?
-None of your business. Relax.
Careful.
Relax.
Look at me, look at me....!
-She seems to be okay.
-She started it all.
-What?
-I saw her.
-Who?
-I don’t know, it was dark.
The girl Medeiros?
It must be her!
-I don’t know.
-Where?
In the penthouse.
There’s no one there.
Wherever she is,
it’s time to find out.
Let’s go.
You shouldn’t insist so much,
I warned you last time.
Last time you were lucky.
But not this one...
Now tell me where you are.
Tell me.
In the name of God Almighty,
who orders you,...
tell me where you are.
Everywhere.
No, the original body,
the girl,
that’s where you hide.
Don’t be so smart.
If you were you’d be running.
Under the protection of God.
He gives me the power to
walk over snakes, and
win over all my enemies.
Where are you?
In your mother’s cunt!
Look there,
you will enjoy it.
Your tricks work no longer.
Tell me where you are.
I will not fear the night terrors,
nor the arrow that flies by day,
nor the plague that
stalks the darkness,
in the name of the Father,
the Son and the Holy Spirit,
tell me where you are.
High above.
Your blasphemy
doesn’t scare me.
Where are you?
I told you, high above.
Perhaps you’re afraid, priest?
In the penthouse.
She’s not there,
there’s nothing there.
The light blinds you.
In God’s name, where?
The light doesn’t let
you see the path.
What a shame, don’t you think?
What fuckin’ light?
You said it was dark.
How’d you see her?
What?
How’d you see her if it was dark?
The camera...
It has night vision.
-I should have imagined.
-What?
...And the angels who
lost their dignity,
but abandoned their own dwellings,
The Lord kept them in eternal
prisons of darkness,
until the final judgment day.
What the fuck are you saying?
Prisons of darkness,
where she is, light is not reflected.
Hot, priest, hot,
but don’t get excited.
In the penthouse!
Let’s go!
Rosso, did you fix the spotlight?
Yes.
Where are they?
Why don’t they attack us?
I don’t know, but I don’t like it.
Rosso, from now on be on alert.
The night vision will
reveal hidden things,
things we didn’t see.
Where do we start?
I think I know.
come on, quick!
Please, please, no!
-come on, come on!
-Let’s go!
-Rosso!
-I’m... I’m coming.
In you go!
Now what? Fuck, we were here
before, and there’s nothing.
What are we looking for?
Okay, turn the light off.
Turn it all off.
Night vision, turn it on.
What? No, that’s impossible...
-What?
-What the fuck is this?
-What do you see?
-A door...in the back.
A door?
What the fuck are you saying?
-I assure you there was a door.
-Of course... A door...
Okay, turn it off.
-Shit!
-Guide me.
Go to the back.
In front of you.
You’re almost there, 3 steps.
You’re touching it.
Get back!
Calm down, okay?
Do you want to get out
of here or not?
Let’s go!
Watch it!
Grab on to me, grab on to me.
Be careful.
Rosso, light!
Watch it, chief.
There’s nothing here.
The light doesn’t
let us see. Turn it off!
Go on, search.
Something must be different.
What do you see?
Do you see anything?
Shit!
-Here.
-What?
There was something there.
-Where?
-Up front...
Okay.
Turn it off.
There it is.
Watch it!
Guide us!
Chief, not that way. To your left.
Right in front.
-Watch it!
-There, there!
There’s water.
It’s... it’s like a well.
-Be careful, chief.
-There’s something here.
Watch it!
Chief, chief!
Shit!
Rosso, where is he?
I don’t know.
He was over there.
Turn it off, off!
Rosso, where is he?
I don’t know. Something
took him away.
Guide me, Rosso!
Holy shit!
Rosso, Rosso, where are you?
What happened, what was that?
Something hit me.
-It’s her.
-Shit, shit!
Is that her? Is it her?
Tell me.
I don’t know!
We have to get out of here now!
I lost the camera!
Find it, we need it!
Find it, Rosso, for God’s sake!
I don’t know where it is.
I can see nothing.
-Well, look for it, Rosso!
-I’m working on it!
I can’t find it, I can’t!
I’ve got it, I’ve got it!
I’m over here.
It’s me, relax.
-We have to get out of here.
-She’s going to kill us.
No, we’re getting out.
No, I need that blood!
Rosso, where is she?
Can you see her?
-I see nothing.
-Look for her!
-I can’t see her.
-I need that blood, Rosso.
She can’t see us.
Don’t move.
If she doesn’t hear us
she can’t find us.
Doctor. Respond.
Voice recognition requested.
Doctor, respond.
Please, I repeat, respond.
Voice recognition requested.
Doctor, respond.
What the fuck are you doing?
Stop it!
You bitch!
Let’s go, let’s go!
What have you done?
I needed her.
-I don’t care.
-I needed that blood.
I don’t care.
We’re out of here.
Wait, wait...
we can’t leave until
he gives the order.
What is that?
Helicopters.
Give the order!
Not until my mission is finished.
I said: Give the order!
And I said I have
to finish the mission.
Nothing more can be done.
Get us out of here!
Give the fucking order!
What the fuck are you doing?
-Give the order.
-I can’t.
-Stop.
-I want out!
What are you doing?
-I can’t.
-Yes you can.
-Stop it.
-Of course you can!
Listen to me.
Get away!
Give it!
Calm down.
I must finish... the mission.
You’re mission is over.
Hold it, stop!
You’re out of your fuckin’ mind!
What are you doing?
Listen well.
You can’t short him.
We need him to get out.
Don’t you get it?
Calm down.
Don’t make it any more difficult.
Give the order.
How did you do it?
You can’t force me!
God protects me.
I’d have loved you getting
me out of here.
It would have been perfect.
But, you know what?
I don’t need you.
You know that, right?
Voice recognition requested.
Owen.
Voice recognition confirmed.
The mission is over,
I request evacuation.
Any survivors?
Just one, a woman.
I’m staying, I’m infected.
Follow the plan and
burn it all.
A woman? Who?
How could she have survived?
It’s here.
We must search it all.
Watch it, battering ram!
-Knock the door down, Martos.
-All clear.
Larra, light!