Subtitles by explosiveskull
Hello.
What are you doing
in my house?
We're gonna be late.
I got it.
There you are.
Who knew you had so much stuff?
Your dad is the Tetris king.
- She doesn't have to like it. Not why we're doing this.
- Where's Luke at?
He's at the ball park with his friends.
We're gonna pick him up...
- Jesus, we are late.
- You expect something else from this family?
No, I do not.
Ain't no way we're gonna
get there before dinner.
Uncle Marv said
he could leave a key.
Okay.
Huh?
Oh, boom!
Let's go!
Seat belt, missy.
Luke!
We just started a new game.
Sorry, kiddo.
We're already late.
Hey, let me know how it goes.
Okay.
Why can't I just
stay here for the weekend?
- By yourself? No, sir.
- All my friends do it.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Exactly.
Besides, it might be nice
for you to help your sister
move into her
new school tomorrow.
Hold on.
I'm gonna leave a message.
You smell horrible.
Hi, Uncle Marv.
It's Cindy.
We got a late start,
so we're not going to be
to Gatlin Lake until, um,
around 9:00 or 10:00.
Hey, guys, cut it out.
We'll just stop for a bite.
Do you guys remember
Uncle Marv and Aunt Sheryl?
I remember Uncle Marv
smelled like wet dog and beer.
You know Mom and Dad are going broke over
sending you to boarding school, right?
Hey, we never said that.
Why else would you guys
have canceled the cable?
See? I was right.
- You think I wanted this?
- I think you like the attention.
- You're a dick.
- You're a queef.
Whoa!
What-what's queef?
Seriously, what's a queef?
- You want me to go get her?
- She's punishing us.
Folks need another couple
of minutes with the menus or...
Yeah, we're gonna... we're gonna
need a few, thank you.
I'll go.
Not even gonna
pretend, huh?
What difference
does it make?
does it make, right?
Just ditch those before
you get to your new school.
God forbid they kick me out.
Oh, they're not gonna
give up that easy.
No, no. Not like
you and Dad, huh?
I wish someone
had done this for me.
You turned out fine.
You didn't
know me back then.
I made mistakes.
A lot of them.
Teenagers do stupid shit, Mom.
I am a teenager.
This is more than
stupid shit, Kins.
This past year?
Sabrina, Laurie, none of them.
None of their parents
are sending them off.
Well, I'm not their mother.
I'm yours.
They're lucky.
And I am worried about you.
And now you won't
have to worry.
Be just the three of you again like
it always should have been, right?
You believe that?
There even anybody here?
I think everybody leaves
after Labor Day.
The office is
a little further down.
They left a note, said they'd
see us in the morning.
We're staying in number 47.
This is nice, right?
Mm. Cozy.
Okay, so, who's staying
in this trailer?
All of us.
Of course.
Hmm.
Is there someone else
staying here?
That's weird.
Hmm. Should I toss it?
What, are you
gonna eat it?
- Throw it out.
- It smells fine. It's beef and broccoli.
- Please do not eat that.
- I love it.
- There are no glasses.
- Just chug, woman.
Remember when we went
camping in the Rockies?
- That's exactly what I was referring to.
- Mm-hmm.
Is that Uncle Marv?
- Probably.
- He probably smelled the wine.
Mom, there's someone knocking.
No, don't get up.
I've got it.
It's a girl.
Girl?
Can I help you?
Is Tamara home?
I think you have
the wrong trailer.
Okay.
I didn't think anyone else
was staying here.
She must be lost.
All right, guys. You wanna
play some cards or something?
- Well, you and me.
- It's you and me.
You guys sure
you don't wanna join us?
Oh, come on.
Can we just have one last evening
where you're not on your phones?
Okay.
Thank you.
What do you wanna play?
Five hundred.
We'll keep you here all night.
Oh.
Come on, why don't
you just put that down,
just for a while,
and join us?
Sweetheart, this, um...
this parent gig,
you know, it's, uh...
it's tough.
The bad grades.
Cutting class.
We're just scared,
you know?
Thank you.
- Hey. Hey, baby doll.
- Where are you going?
I need some air.
Should I go after her?
No. It'll only
make it worse.
Either one of us.
Luke, you go talk to her.
What? Why?
Because you're her brother.
Can you please do
what your mother asks you?
Okay.
I don't know what you guys
want me to say to her.
No one said
it would be easy.
Kinsey!
Hey, Kins!
What are you doing?
I don't know. Mom told me
to come hang with you.
- Such a bitch.
- Just being dramatic.
- Yeah, ya think?
- I meant you.
Fuck off.
You know you're supposed
to inhale those? Cigarettes.
You're supposed to like, um,
actually inhale them.
Come on.
Ah, Sis,
just get over it.
They wanna send you away.
I mean, boo-fuckin'-hoo.
Yeah, you're
out of here next year.
You get to start
your own life.
Maybe it's like that
for you too.
You know, this place
could be a fresh start.
You could be
whoever you want to be.
Don't.
You really think
we're doing the right thing?
I know we are.
It's not like
we haven't tried everything.
Yeah.
It'll be nice to have the house
back to ourselves again, I guess,
once Luke goes off to college.
We can do it on the couch
like we used to.
I look so tired.
You look beautiful.
I love you.
You lock 'em out?
Mm-mmm.
Guys, the door's not even locked.
Is Tamara home?
You lost or something?
You want me to call someone?
Are you okay?
Same girl?
Yeah.
Where are the kids?
- What?
- Did they wander off?
Luke!
Kinsey!
I'm gonna get my shoes.
I'm sure they're okay.
I mean...
- That girl weirded me out, hon.
- Yeah. Yeah, that was...
a little...
Remember when I was
in Little League?
You used to follow me
to the park.
Yeah, I always wanted to play.
You never let me.
Well, 'cause you were little, Sis.
That's just how it goes.
You could barely lift up the
bat, let alone hit anything.
Here.
Wind up for the pitch.
Mmm, what about
the mailbox?
Oh, nice.
- Should have let me play.
- Hmm.
What do you think Uncle Marv and Aunt
Sheryl do here all alone in the winter?
Oh, I don't know.
Probably have tons
of filthy, porno sex.
Ew.
Weird.
Yeah.
- Are you scared?
- No.
Hello.
Oh, geez!
I'm gonna kill you.
That's not funny.
Oh, God.
Mmm. Bingo.
Okay, yes. One shot.
- Three.
- Two.
All right.
- What was that?
- I don't know.
- Come on, we should get out of here.
- Wait. Wait.
Is somebody there?
- Luke, seriously, let's go.
- No, let's just...
Hello.
Is somebody there?
Oh, geez.
It scared me
half to death.
What the hell is that?
Nothing.
What the hell?
What the fuck?
- Luke.
- What?
Oh, my God.
Come on.
- Okay. Okay.
- Come on. Come on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
- Where are we?
- I don't know.
- Did we come from that way? No, no...
- I don't... I don't know.
It all looks the same.
Here. Okay.
- Jesus!
- You guys, what the hell is going on?
Uncle Marv and Aunt Sheryl are all cut
up and there's blood everywhere...
- Luke.
- If this is a joke...
It's not a joke. I swear I
would not joke about this.
Where was this?
Where did you see this?
In one of the trailers. One of the
trailers was open and we went inside.
I'm... I'm not...
I'm not messing with you.
I swear.
He's not. He's not.
I... We both swear.
They're all cut up.
Okay, get Kinsey
back in the trailer.
What?
- Take Kinsey back to the trailer.
- Okay.
Call the police
and lock the door, okay?
Okay.
- Do you know how to get back there?
- Yeah.
- Can you show me?
- Yeah, I think so.
We came from there.
I'm scared, Dad.
Who would do
something like that?
Okay.
- You're okay.
- No, I'm not.
- No, I'm not. No, I'm not.
They weren't okay. They weren't okay.
They weren't okay.
You are going to be okay.
It's okay.
Mom.
Mom, the phones.
The phones.
Mommy.
Oh, my God.
Hello.
9-1-1 emergency.
Hello, can you hear me?
Hello. Can you hear me?
- Mom.
- Hello?
Hello? Hell...
Mom. Mom.
Mom?
Mom.
What do you want? Hello?
- Hello!
- Mom!
Can you hear me?
I need to report a murder.
Hello. Can anyone hear...
No.
Get in the bedroom!
Shut it!
In the bathroom!
Shut the door!
God. Please, God.
Leave us alone!
Mommy.
Who is she?
- Okay.
- I got it. I got it.
- I'm gonna lift you up.
- Okay.
Pull yourself up!
Come on!
Go! You go! Run!
Oh, my God!
Run. You have to run!
No. Oh, my God.
Baby, go.
Mommy!
Let go of her!
This is it, right?
Yeah, it's this one.
- Okay, just wait here.
- What?
Just let me look.
I've already been there.
I've already seen it.
They don't work.
Back room.
We gotta call the cops.
- You got a phone on you?
- No, I... I think I left it back at the trailer.
Okay.
What the fuck?
Right there.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Hi, Uncle Marv. It's Cindy.
We got a late start,
so we're not going to be to Gatlin
Lake until, um, around 9:00 or 10:00
Shit.
What was that?
- Dad?
- Shh.
Fuck! Get down!
Who is that?
Okay, we're gonna
get back to Mom and Kinsey.
Okay, we're gonna make
a run for it, okay?
- Mm-hmm.
- You're gonna run like hell.
- I'm gonna be right behind you.
- Okay.
And you don't stop until
we get right back to them.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Go!
Dad.
Shit.
- What are you doing?
- There was a gun.
I remember they used
to have a gun in here.
Hang on.
Do you know how to use that?
Are you... Are you
really gonna shoot them?
Okay, you have five seconds!
Five seconds to leave
and then I start shooting!
Five!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
Go check back there.
They're gone.
Okay, we'll go back.
Come on,
you stay with me. Okay?
Come on!
Oh, my God.
No!
Okay.
Help!
Please!
Fuck! Kinsey! Cindy!
That's my phone.
Oh.
Dad, what is it?
No, no, no!
We have
to go find your sister.
Listen to me! We're
gonna go find your sister, okay?
- I need you to be with me.
- Okay.
What do we have to do?
I'm gonna get the car
and we're gonna go find her.
All right? Okay?
Kinsey!
Kin!
Where is she?
Come on, Kins!
Kinsey!
Oh, shit!
This isn't happening.
Hello?
Leave us alone!
But we've just started.
Aah!
Oh, God. Dad?
No. Dad. Dad. Dad, wake up.
Wake up. Come on.
Fuck. Luke, Dad.
Fuck.
- You okay?
- Fuck.
Oh, my God.
Aah! I can't...
I can't.
Okay, I'm-I'm-I'm-I'm gonna, uh,
try and, uh, pull-pull it out.
Okay, I'm-I'm gonna...
I'm gonna...
Aah! Shit.
Fucking...
Tell me what to do.
What do you want me to do?
Okay, you...
you gotta get out of here.
I'm not gonna leave you.
- Get the fuck out of here.
- I'm not gonna leave you.
- You gotta find your sister.
She needs you.
The gun.
Okay, find the gun.
Um... Here.
- You know how to use that thing?
- No.
You just...
It's loaded, okay?
Pull back on the hammer and
then you squeeze the trigger.
Okay. You're gonna be okay.
You're gonna be okay.
Oh, fuck.
Okay. Okay.
I'm gonna go find her, okay?
We're gonna get the cops. We're
gonna get the ambulance, okay?
I'm gonna be right back.
I'm proud of you.
I know.
Aah!
Fuck! Aah!
Please.
Why are you
doing this?
Fuck!
Please. Hey, whatever it is
you're doing, just stop.
Okay, you leave
my family alone.
Let my family go.
Please.
Okay. Okay, can we just
talk about this, okay?
Aah!
Fuck!
You mother... Fuck you!
Aah! Aah!
Oh, my God.
Kinsey!
Hello.
Whee!
No, no, no.
Stop!
Let her go.
Luke.
Luke. Luke.
Put the fucking knife down.
Put the knife down!
Are you gonna shoot me?
Give me the gun.
Give me the gun, Luke.
- Run! Run!
- I will fucking shoot her! I will fucking shoot her!
Go, go, go.
Hey, Luke, the window.
- Do you think you can reach it?
- Yeah, I could give it a try.
Yeah, I'll boost you.
Oh, shit, it hurts.
- You ready?
- Okay.
Okay.
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
Oh, my God.
Okay. Hey, you're okay.
Hey, hey.
There's so much blood.
- Grab that shirt off, okay?
- What?
Take that flannel off.
Okay.
It's okay.
Mom.
I know.
Hey, we're gonna
get out of this.
- I tried to get her... I tried to get her hand.
- We're gonna get out of this.
Stop.
I had her hand.
I couldn't get her.
I was so mean.
- I was so...
- Hey.
Do you remember that...
Hey, do you remember that...
that time that I fell out
of that tree at Marshpoint.
Do you remember that?
- You remember that.
- Yeah.
Right.
You...
- You rode your bike home even though it was broken.
- Yeah.
You were an idiot.
Total idiot.
Mom found me on the couch.
I was eating pizza, trying to
pretend like nothing happened.
My leg was
all swollen and blue,
and she was like, "Luke,
what the fuck did you do?"
- Aah!
- It's okay.
It's okay.
- She probably said it just like that too.
- It was exactly like that.
"Luke, what the fuck
did you do?"
And she tells us
to watch our mouths.
Here, give me your arm.
It's my fault
that she's dead.
Kins, stop.
No, you wouldn't
have been here, Luke.
- You wouldn't have been here if I wasn't such a fuck-up.
- Stop. Just shut up.
- No.
- Shut up.
You know that's not true.
- I'm sorry.
- You know that.
I'm sorry.
Why are they
doing this to us?
Why?
Okay, we got to find
a way out of this.
Okay, we got to get
to a landline.
Call 911.
- Luke. Luke, help.
- Come on.
I... I can't.
Okay, get in there.
- Here.
- Okay.
Give me your hand.
- I'm gonna try and find a way the office.
- What?
You have to stay here.
Trust me. Do not move.
I'm gonna call 911.
Ambulance will come.
- The police will light this whole fucking place...
- I'm coming with you.
No. Stop, stop, stop. Stop.
Listen to me.
I'm gonna be moving much faster and
you're gonna be a lot safer here, okay?
You understand?
- You understand?
- Okay.
I love you, Sis.
- Yeah, I love you too.
- We're gonna be okay.
We're gonna be okay.
We'll be okay.
911.
What's the emergency?
Hi. Um, yeah, we need help. There's
these crazy people trying to kill us.
Okay. Calm down.
What's your address?
Um, I don't know.
I'm not sure.
I wasn't... I wasn't paying attention.
It's some trailer park.
I don't know.
I don't know where we are.
Um... Uh... Uh... Uh, Gatlin Lake.
It's Gatlin Lake.
Hello?
Just leave us alone.
Just leave us alone!
I killed one of yours.
How's that feel, huh?
How's that fucking feel?
Luke! Luke!
Luke!
Come on.
I need you to help me. Ready?
Come here. I got you.
Right here. Right here.
Okay.
Okay. We need
to get you help.
Look at me. I need
to get to the main road.
Okay?
Okay. Okay.
Oh, my God, please. No.
Please.
Are you okay?
Whoa.
Okay. Come here.
Come on. It's okay.
It's okay. Come here.
Okay, calm down. Okay.
Calm down. Okay.
It's okay.
- Tell me what happened.
- Okay, I need... I need... I need you to help my brother.
He's at the clubhouse. I told him
to meet me at the clubhouse.
That's where
he might be.
And there are these crazy people,
and they're trying to kill us.
Where are the keys?
Come on, come on, come on.
Get off! Get off! Get off!
Why are you doing this?
Why not?
Come on!
Come on, please.
Please, I need you to go!
Stop! Stop! Help!
Wait! Stop the car!
Stop the car! Stop the car!
Oh, thank God.
Hi. Hi.
Help me, please.
- Are you okay?
- Please.
Please. Wait.
Wait.
Drive!
Hello.
Subtitles by explosiveskull