There we go.
Hands up.
Great. There we go.
Beautiful.
You remember what we did.
Higher, Mark.
Lovely. Ah.
To the side. Beautiful.
- Yay.
- Oh.
Aw, thank you.
- Sorry. I just gave away your piece.
- Who's next?
- Mom, take it easy.
- Oh, come on.
Kids keep us young.
Okay.
Are you okay?
Grandma.
- Are you okay, Grandma?
- Mom?
Somebody call an ambulance!
You don't
have to do this, Grandma.
Oh, I do. My health.
This'll be better for everyone,
believe me.
Hello. Welcome.
- You got it?
- Yeah.
This way, please.
It's a lovely second-floor room.
- You okay?
- Mm.
Here we are.
Oh. Hello there.
- Hi. Hi.
- I'm Liesel.
Uh, Judith.
Oh.
You didn't have to
unpack for me.
I could have done it myself.
Those are beautiful.
You were a professional dancer?
Mm, I dabbled.
Wow. I just...
Before I forget,
your medication...
For Parkinson's
and for your stroke...
Just leave it with me.
The nurses will
make sure you get
the right pills
for each meal or at bedtime.
Oh, I've always
managed myself, thank you.
Well, you'll no longer need
to worry about it now.
Isn't that a relief?
Perfect timing.
I need a new prescription,
actually.
At least it's quiet here.
That's good.
I'm a light sleeper.
Well, I'll leave you to it,
and let me know if there's
anything that you need.
Ms. Benson,
may I speak with you?
You don't belong here.
Oh, I'm 70, Josh.
Age is just a number.
It doesn't mean anything.
No, my darling.
That's just something old people
tell themselves to feel better.
Doesn't sound like you.
Age is what stops me
from dancing or teaching or...
keeping up pace with everybody.
You look younger than everyone here.
But you know what?
Every single one of these people
thinks the same.
We all still think we're 20.
I don't, I don't know how...
I don't know how
I'm gonna deal with this.
Well, can you deal...
Oh, what's that?
What? Oh! Stop!
Okay. Mom.
- We'll let you settle.
- Right.
Um... uh,
wh-why don't you go along?
I-I'll catch up later. It's...
You know, I'll just stay here
- for a little bit.
- Josh, you need to come with me.
Grandma needs to rest.
Call me if you need anything.
Sure.
Okay.
Don't worry. I'll be okay.
Bye, Grandma.
Tree.
Sorry. I didn't introduce myself.
Judith.
I guess we're roomies
like we're back in college.
Looks like I caught you
at a bad time.
Tree.
I'm watching.
I'm watching, watching.
Looking for this?
Thanks.
I was just about to panic.
Of course, you know about
our no-cell-phone policy.
I-I'm sorry. What?
For the peace and quiet
of the house,
we don't allow any phones
anywhere in the building.
You're pulling my leg.
It was in the contract
that you signed.
So much for all the exciting
Insta updates
I could have posted from here.
I'm watching.
I'm watching. I'm watching.
She still hasn't texted back.
- I'm sure she's fine.
- She's fine?
Did you see her roommate and
the people she's staying with?
It's tough, but we have to
remember this was her choice.
You could've at least tried
to talk her out of it.
No one has ever
talked your grandma
out of anything
she's decided to do.
That's bullshit. You didn't
want to look after her.
She moved here
to take care of us
when we needed her the most.
- But now she needs help, she's out?
- That's not fair.
I'm gonna go watch a movie.
This is weird.
This may make you
a little tense.
It made someone
a little past tense.
Here's looking at you, kid.
No! Oh!
- Let go!
- That is enough.
- Imogen.
- Let go!
- It is time to go to bed. Come with me.
- I don't want to sleep!
Go away!
- Go away!
- No, this... Come with me right now!
- Please go back to bed.
No! Oh!
I want to go home!
You are home.
I want home. Please.
How are you today?
Would you like to visit
the grounds later?
I could make time for
a little stroll if you like.
- Oh, I'd love that.
- Okay, great.
I wasn't ready for this change.
I miss dancing,
and I miss it
more than anything else.
But my prognosis isn't good.
My symptoms are under control
for now, but...
who knows how long that'll last?
Whatever's coming next...
Whenever or however
I end up diminished...
I don't want my family
to see me like that.
Well, you look in great shape.
You want to see something fun?
Come on.
You okay?
Where the hell
are you taking me?
Been a while
since my last safari.
Well, this is it.
Wow.
Oh, it's beautiful.
Right?
You just wish you could sit here
with a good book.
Or-or curl up and nap
and dream of fairies.
What's this?
Damn kids.
They have these drunken
sleepovers on the grounds.
We've added a fence,
but now they cut their way
through with pliers.
Takes me back.
My friends and I had these
wild parties in the woods.
We'd smoke grass
and play guitar,
- dance around the fire.
- Mm.
It's where I met
my husband George.
Aw.
Life was easy then. Carefree.
An adventure.
What'd you find there?
Anyone you know?
No. I...
Probably not.
Come on.
We should probably head back
before they call a search party.
Hmm.
You should
find yourself a hobby here.
- Gardening?
- Oh.
There's lots of things to do.
Uh, watercolors, crafts,
even ballet.
Maybe something you'd enjoy.
Nope.
Who wants to see an old bat
fluttering about
in a leotard, anyway?
And here's our vegetable patch.
Liesel, hi.
Hi.
Oh, hello.
Ladies, this is Judith.
She just moved in last night.
- New blood.
- Yes, you don't say.
- Hi. I'm Ruth.
- Hi.
Oh, nice to meet you.
- Trish. Welcome.
- Thank you.
- A wormwood.
- Yeah.
Do you make absinthe?
Do you know much about plants?
No, but I, uh,
know a little about absinthe.
Ah.
Watch your step, young lady.
- Yeah.
- I didn't see you there.
I'm sorry, uh,
if I frightened you.
I'm Roland.
Oh. Uh, Judith.
I-I was just looking
at the, uh...
Well, yeah, don't mention it.
It's lovely to meet you.
I was planning
to come to you
later today to, uh...
Well, we have
a card group going,
and, uh, we're missing
a player for bridge.
Do you, by any chance, uh...
- Uh, bridge?
- What a cliché.
Uh, it's not as boring
as it sounds,
I promise you.
- Hmm?
- Uh...
Th-That... Yeah, sure.
- Oh?
- Sure, that'd be nice.
Lovely.
Nice to meet you all.
Yes.
- Bye-bye.
Bye.
Attention, residents.
And plié.
Hmm.
Judith!
- Hi.
- So glad you could join us.
Yes, well, with this wealth
of exciting activity,
I wasn't sure I'd find time
in my schedule.
I, um, brought
a little something
- to get the party started.
- Oh.
Bring it on, sister.
Well, your spirit is
so visceral.
Wonderful.
Thank you, Judith.
So, first things first.
Any family?
Uh, my daughter and, um,
my grandson Josh.
He's 17.
Enjoy the visits,
if they do come.
I got to warn you,
they thin out quickly.
I hear you.
My friends deserted me
when I stopped being able
to teach their kids
how to dance.
- Uh-huh.
- But Josh will keep visiting.
He's the light of my life.
Keeps me young.
Does he? Really?
Well, his father died
when he was little,
and we were all affected,
of course,
but Josh, in particular,
just didn't know how to cope.
- Hmm.
- After a while, it was important
that he go back
to a normal life.
- You know, kids, fun.
- Mm, mm-hmm.
But his mother wasn't able
to provide that, so I...
Well, he and I grew very close.
A fact which his mother still
resents, I'm afraid, but...
Do you have family?
Oh, they're long gone.
Once you're here, you become,
uh, irrelevant to society.
You'd think we were in prison.
Well, we are on death row.
You married?
Oh, widowed.
- Oh.
- He was a good man
- and a great musician, and I do miss him.
- Mm-hmm.
You?
Same. I-I miss my wife.
Uh, it's good to have a
significant other in your life.
I sometimes think that the
toughest part of getting older
is that I might not get to see
the man Josh will become.
Geez, enough of
this depressing talk.
How do you like your new home?
- Uh, it takes time to adjust, right?
- Yeah. -Mm-hmm.
You've got to accept the change
and just move on.
- Right.
- People who don't,
they end up looking like, uh...
I-I can't cast the first stone.
I-I was a dancer, you know?
My-my work depended
on my youth...
Or the appearance of it, anyway.
I-I understand people's choices.
Well, I've had three face-lifts.
I've tried every fad diet.
Tried filler,
every Botox.
If I'd been told that "bathing
in the blood of virgins" stuff
actually worked, I'd have gone
the way of Elizabeth Báthory.
Oh.
Well, in the end,
there's only so long
you can hold the fort, right?
Fighting nature
always comes at a cost.
Wish you could recapture
the beauty of your youth?
Hebora, nighttime formula...
- No! No!
- In right here. Go.
No!
No, no.
Let me go!
- I don't want to go to sleep!
- Get her in the bed. Get her...
- No!
- You cannot sleep in the living room!
- No! No!
- Just relax.
Just relax.
No, no.
You're acting like a child!
Can I help you?
No, no. It's okay.
Don't you see him?
Pardon me?
He's watching us sleep.
Don't you see?
Are you talking about...
No.
It's okay. It's just Ozzie.
It doesn't mean anything, okay?
Look, see?
He's gone already.
Here.
My grandfather,
he had Alzheimer's
the last years of his life.
It was like little pieces
of his mind just...
falling apart one by one.
I'm sorry.
That's why I became a nurse.
I just wanted to help
make a difference.
My grandparents gave me this
when I was little.
Oh, nice.
I like to think that
they're watching over me.
Um, time for bed.
Uh...
What's that?
Oh, it's just something
to help you sleep.
We want to make sure
everyone has a good night.
You're drugging everyone.
Drugging?
That is awfully dramatic.
I know dealing with
screaming patients is hard,
but don't you think
your teammates are a bit rough?
We're all trained professionals,
and no one is sedated
against their will.
Look, don't worry,
it-it takes a bit of time,
but you'll fit right in.
No!
There! What is it?
Is she okay?
Where is he?
Are you having
a bad dream, Ms. Albright?
Fuck no.
He was standing right there.
Is that language
absolutely necessary?
- I'm not a child.
- Clearly not.
Good night, then.
Oh, Nurse, I...
Oh, it's you.
Do you need something?
Was anyone in my room
this morning?
My hairbrush is gone.
I wouldn't think so.
- Let me help you find it.
- I'm telling you,
someone took it.
It's gone.
Is this it?
Yes.
You were probably
just distracted.
New habits.
People misplace objects here
all the time.
Whose turn was it?
Ah.
Easy one.
"At what job
do Wilbur and Chick work
in Abbott and Costello
Meet Frankenstein?"
Uh, baggage clerks.
Boom.
What's the deal with him?
Oh, he's here every day.
He keeps thinking his wife's
picking him up to go home.
Keeps forgetting
his wife's dead and buried.
Can you imagine?
He could've been a mob boss.
He could've trained dolphins
to become assassins
or... who knows?
But now... his mind's gone.
He's gone.
Geez, make me cry,
why don't you?
No, no. I'm-I'm serious.
I... It's the worst, I think.
Oh.
Worse than having to pull a
tapeworm out through your mouth?
Worse than your house keys
falling into dog shit?
Oh, way worse. Way worse.
Or getting tiny paper cuts
between each of your toes?
Oh, wait. Wait, wait.
Between your teeth.
Okay, okay, no, no, no.
Oh, God. Oh, what?
Oh, that...
No. You-you win. You win.
It's gonna get easier, right?
Boom.
Anyone there?
What are you doing
in the hallway?
You're supposed to be
in your room.
There was something
right there, on my bed.
Where the hell were you?
I called you.
You're not my only patient.
If you insist
on wandering about,
I'll have to lock your door.
Look.
It was right there.
What the hell? Let me go.
Calm down.
You're gonna hurt yourself.
I can put myself to bed,
thank you very much.
Do you want me to call Gary
to come in here and assist me?
- He's right there in the hallway.
- He's there.
I knew it. He's the one.
Yeah, I knew it.
Gary has better things to do
than to lurk around your room.
It's just another nightmare.
Come on. Let's get you
back to sleep now, okay?
Annette.
Who is it?
You've seen him before.
Where's your crucifix?
Judith.
There you are.
- Hi. Thanks.
- Sit.
You look tired.
Speak for yourself.
If I didn't know better,
I'd say you were hungover.
Where was the party?
Feeling better
from last night, I hope.
Quite the nightmare you had.
"Quite the nightmare you had."
- They all treat us like children.
- Right?
I wasn't having
a nightmare last night.
I was awake.
I saw something.
What was it?
Someone standing at the end
of my bed, watching me sleep.
And I know what you're thinking,
but the same thing happened
the night before.
Well, how clearly could you see?
Well, it was dark, but...
- Ms. Albright, how are you this morning?
- You.
Were you in my room last night?
- In your room? What are you...
- Around 1:00 a.m.
- What kind of creep watches women when they sleep?
- Uh...
And Annette's crucifix
is missing.
Is that what you do?
Steal from the elderly?
Uh, Judith,
the-the tea's getting cold.
This isn't achieving anything.
- All right.
Okay.
I-I don't know what to do.
I mean, should I call
the police?
No, no, no.
Don't call the police.
Don't do anything dramatic.
Now, uh, you may be right,
and I-I don't like him, either,
but, Judith, everyone else,
not being able to distinguish
between what's real
and what's a dream,
that's a sign of dementia.
And they will have you diagnosed
and medicated in no time.
He's right. In their eyes,
none of us have both oars
in the water anyway.
Yeah, trust me.
The moment they see
any signs of illness,
they treat you like an invalid.
Look around you.
None of these people
are getting out of here.
Not for Thanksgiving,
not for Christmas,
not for their
grandkids' graduation.
Now, once they see weakness,
the only way you're getting
out of here is in a box.
Ms. Albright.
Is everything all right?
Oh, yes.
I'd just like to get some air.
Outside walks
must be accompanied.
What do you mean?
We're locked inside?
We need to know where
our residents are at all times.
Uh, some wouldn't be able
to make it back on their own.
Come with me.
We have a children's choir
recital in the living room.
I'd rather poke myself
in the eye.
Have a nice day, Ms. Albright.
George?
- How did you...
- It doesn't matter.
Come away with me.
This is no place for you.
Sorry.
I, um...
Um...
What was I...
Do... do I bid?
Bids are in.
Spades are up.
Are you okay?
Sure. Sure.
I think...
I must have been...
you know, I was dreaming.
- Uh-huh.
- For a minute there, I think.
Well, you'll adjust.
You'll find a... a new reason
to get up every morning.
Just give it time.
Look, we're all
in this together.
You know,
if ever you get the blues,
you just come see me and Ruth.
We're in the room
right next door.
Whoa. Oh.
What are you doing here?
Well, I thought that
we could prove to ourselves
we're not as old as we think.
- Roland.
- Oh, I was in my room,
and I thought about
that gorgeous woman
just across the hallway...
...and the connections
that we share.
And I thought that maybe...
No. No, no, no.
I-I mean, I really appreciate...
I mean, I'm flattered
by the attention,
but, um, I'm not ready for that.
Oh.
Ah, geez,
I got my signals crossed.
Listen, I-I... Sheesh.
I thought you'd be game.
- My apologies.
- Well, no harm done.
You move fast, Roland.
Let's not mention this,
all right?
All right.
Oh, cheese and crackers.
What a madhouse.
Who's there?
Roland?
Take a breath.
Another.
Uh, chick.
Uh, lemon.
Left hand.
The other hand.
I believe we are talking about
Parkinson's disease dementia.
I'm sorry, what?
It's not uncommon.
Hang on.
You can see dementia on the MRI?
I'm afraid so.
How can this be happening?
Would you mind waiting outside
for a moment, Ms. Albright?
I just have a detail or two
to settle with your daughter.
You're going to discuss
my treatment without me?
I'm not a child. I...
Ms. Albright, I-I understand
that this is a lot to take in,
but it would be easier
if you gave us a moment.
What can we do?
Your mother has complained
about vivid dreams
which she couldn't
differentiate from reality.
It's caused her to fall.
She needs
our constant supervision.
She'll be safer
here at the manor.
What's important
is that neither you
nor any member of your family
encourage her delusions.
She needs to understand
that her nightmares
are all in her head.
- Oh, God.
- Don't worry.
I've worked here
for over 20 years.
She's perfectly safe.
Listen to me. Listen to me.
Whatever I've seen at night,
it's real.
At first, I thought it was
a member of the staff,
but now I think...
Let me come home.
I mean, this clearly
is not working out for me.
Mom, I can't do that.
I can't go against
the doctor's advice.
Why won't you believe me?
Mom.
We all want you to feel better.
But, you know, you've always had
a vivid imagination.
We're all trying
to look after you.
I promise.
We'll see you soon, okay?
- Help me.
- What?
Help me get out.
- Imogen, come on.
- Let's go inside. Okay?
- Oh.
Come on.
- There you are.
- Sweetheart.
What's on your mind?
I don't want to worry you.
Then it's bad.
This place...
Being surrounded
by all these sick old people...
Makes me feel like I'm...
So, this must be the grandson.
Hi. I'm Roland. I'm a friend
of your grandmother's.
- Hi.
- I hope.
Anyway,
I heard a lot about you.
Hey.
I'll let you two catch up.
Hey, he seems cool.
Yeah, he is cool.
But we play cards
with his friends, and...
Don't judge.
Mm.
I better go.
You know, I'd-I'd really like
to get out this weekend.
Could you two pick me up?
Let's go for a, you know,
Sunday lunch or movie or...
Uh, no, I-I don't think...
I don't think
that's such a good idea.
Why?
They say you'll settle faster
if you don't go home right now,
so, you know,
maybe hang with
your-your new friend.
Roland, right? Yeah.
"They say"?
You listen to them now?
Do you know they won't even
give me the code to go out?
Oh, God, I'm so sorry.
I'm such a wet blanket
right now.
Come back later, okay?
Your ticket out.
Good boy.
I'll be back tomorrow.
Are you guys...
Hang on.
Are you smoking grass?
Uh, no.
- No.
- Oh, my God, you...
you are smoking grass.
It's-it's purely medicinal.
- And that's the end of it. Sorry.
- Yeah.
Did you grow it?
- Is that why you have to...
- Uh, well...
Whoa.
How long have you two
lived here?
I mean, you've almost made it
into a home.
Oh, it's a mess.
We've been going through
some old clothes.
- Yes.
- Oh, really? May I?
Sure. Have a look.
See if there's
anything you like.
Really?
Were you 20 when you moved in?
- Oh, no.
- Sure feels like it.
Oh.
- This had to be you.
- Oh, yeah.
Oh, you can have that.
Your roommate is not
looking too good.
Mm-hmm, she had a turn
for the worse last night.
What's going on?
No. Off, kitty.
- Off you go.
- Shoo. You're scaring everyone.
I don't understand.
What's the deal with the cat?
I've seen Annette freak out
about it before.
Ozzie, the poor kitty.
He can sense who's about to die.
Cats are smart that way.
I mean, we may have
one foot in the grave,
but nobody wants to be
the next to go.
Annette.
Are you okay?
The doctor insists you take this
to help you relax tonight.
Insists? Why?
Residents get a little agitated
when Ozzie, um, misbehaves.
I don't need to be sedated,
thank you very much.
It might help with those dreams
you've been having.
Hey.
Did Annette ever say
what she saw in her nightmares?
Please take the pill, Judith.
You'll sleep better.
We've been marked.
You won't be saved.
Find it.
Annette! Annette!
Help us! Somebody!
Annette.
Holy shit, Annette.
Oh.
Annette.
Annette. Annette.
Gary, get the doctor quick.
Come on. Come on, Annette.
Are you okay?
Oh, God.
Annette? Hon?
I'm so sorry
you had to see this.
Will you be all right in here
for the night?
Okay.
"Find it"?
Find what?
Oh, fuck this.
Oh, thank Christ.
Shit.
Oh, you're squeezing
my arm too tight.
What are you doing there?
- Whoa, no.
- Oh, careful. You're...
- I don't think that I'm...
- Wait a minute.
I heard something.
Did you hear that?
Come on.
I'm freezing my ass off.
- Let's go.
- Oh, all right.
- You're so cranky.
- Oh. If you were a real gentleman,
- you'd give me your jacket.
- Really?
You eat your eggs with a fork?
I don't have a fork.
Have you seen Judith today?
Uh, no.
Can't say that I have.
Hmm.
Judith?
Ms. Albright?
Ms. Albright is MIA.
Shit. There she is.
Oh, am I glad to see you.
Yes, we found her, thank God.
How could this happen?
What do you mean, no harm done?
For Christ's sake,
she's not even dressed.
Josh.
I have to tell you something,
but you have to promise
you'll keep an open mind, okay?
Sure. Sure.
I think there's something out
there in that house killing us.
Wait. Wh-What?
Look at these names.
Annette, my roommate,
she died last night.
All the others above her name
have died, too.
I don't know who
or what it is, but...
Imogen's next, and then me.
Help me.
I need to get out of that place.
All this proves is that
whoever wrote this
was really paranoid.
God, why does everyone
treat me like I'm crazy?
Even you.
Remember when you were little
and I used to chase the monsters
out from under your bed,
and I'd listen to your stories,
and I'd listen
to your fears and your excuses
when you came home late?
I have faith in you.
Can't you have
the same faith in me?
Mom, you... you can't
do this again, ever.
If Ms. Benson hadn't called us,
if-if we hadn't found you...
I'm not a prisoner.
I shouldn't be locked up.
It's the rules.
You agreed when you signed them.
I didn't agree to have
my freedom taken away from me.
I'm not gonna
take you home, Mom.
You wanted a Sunday lunch,
fine, but the doctor...
That doctor's a charlatan.
I won't go back.
"The doctor's a charlatan."
All right, that's enough.
I'm your mother, not your child.
I'll be right back.
End of discussion.
She's clearly not happy there.
I think we should take her home.
They warned me about this.
I don't want to make things
worse than they already are.
Worse?
How can things be worse?
Open your eyes. Can't you see
the state she's in?
Honey, I know Grandma's scared.
I know she's worried.
We all are.
This is a difficult time
for everybody.
Dad would know what to do.
Josh, you should know, um...
She's not doing so well.
What do you mean?
Oh, shit.
Mom, they've come
to pick you up.
No. No. No.
- This way.
- No, Barbara, look.
- Look-look at this picture.
- Come on.
Leave me alone. I-I'm not crazy!
- Just look at the damn picture!
- Keep walking this way.
- Come on. -Yeah, okay.
- I don't want to go back!
How can you do this to me?
I'm your mother!
- Calm down.
- How can you do this?
Hey.
Roland Benson.
Ms. Benson.
Trish Price and Gary Price.
What the fuck?
Ruth Cooper and Elizabeth.
Annette.
Imogen.
What the hell?
This is Josh.
You know what to do.
Josh. Come here
as soon as you get this.
It's-it's very important.
Please.
...you as well.
I'm heading into my office.
Let me take a look
at the calendar.
We don't have any rooms
available right now, I'm afraid,
but I should have an opening...
in about a week.
I'll send the application
right away.
Okay.
Of course.
Thank you. Bye.
I was... I was just...
I know. I was...
Liesel, come in, please.
I need you to check
the medication for 312.
Okay, perfect. Yeah.
I actually did check...
Oh, God.
Oh, Josh.
- You okay?
- Oh, thank God you're here.
I have to get out.
No, again?
I know who's killing people.
It's Roland.
- Wait, the-the old guy you play cards with?
- Yeah, I...
I thought you liked him.
I'm in danger.
I haven't seen Imogen
since yesterday.
I'm next on the list.
Okay, okay, why don't you speak
to the director, then?
- She can help.
- No, she's his daughter.
Or his granddaughter.
- I mean, she's in on it.
- In on what?
These so-called nightmares
I've been having,
this man's behind them.
And his friends, too.
And they're all related
to members of the staff.
Isn't that weird?
Yeah, that's super weird.
- Yeah.
- Wait.
I-I thought you said
what you saw wasn't human.
Oh.
No, no, it's not them.
Or it could be.
It-it could be they-they turn...
turning at night
into something... else.
I don't... I'm confused.
I don't know...
What are you talking about?
I saw Roland in a photograph
at the diner in the hallway.
He looked exactly the same
40 years ago.
Oh, I know it sounds insane,
but it's the truth.
Um...
The doctors said...
...you might try to convince us
that you're seeing stuff.
Is that what you believe?
That I'm crazy?
He says you-you have...
Dementia?
That doctor's a crook.
And he's part of the conspiracy,
and I can prove it.
Where the hell...
What are you looking for?
The file.
What file?
It's gone.
It was... it was right there.
Somebody took it.
- What was it?
- My brain scan.
And-and those of others here
diagnosed with the same disease.
All exactly identical.
They're fake, Josh.
Brain scans?
How-how do you even know...
that they're brain scans and
if they're slightly different
and-and someone...
someone took them?
I hate to say this,
but it sounds bonkers.
You're right.
I should be going.
I should get back.
You only just arrived.
Yeah, I got to be home
for dinner.
Will you be coming back
tomorrow?
Tomorrow? I-I don't think so.
I, um...
I'm s-swamped this week, so I...
Next week, for sure.
Next week.
Yeah.
Good night, Grandma.
Time for bed.
Oh, not yet.
It's very late.
Wait, what's that?
Well, I've been asked
to restrain you.
Whoa, no. No, no.
Look, Judith,
it's for your own good.
So you won't fall out of the bed
- if you have nightmares.
- I said no. No.
Let go. Stop it.
No.
No, you don't touch me.
- Not you.
- Judith, Judith, calm down.
- No! No! Stop!
- Judith, get your feet together.
- Please just...
- Stop it!
- Please just hold her down. Please...
- Get off me!
- Get the fuck off me!
- Please, Judith.
- Get off me!
- Calm down!
- Judith, you need to calm down.
- No, I don't want this!
- Calm down right now. Calm down.
- Stop! -Judith. Wait.
No!
Good.
You said you wanted
to help people.
Your grandfather's real proud
of you, don't you think?
I once heard
Dr. Geoghegan say that
when you've experienced
something disorienting,
you should close your eyes
and count to five.
When you open them again,
whatever you saw or heard
will be gone.
Seriously?
Count to five?
What the fuck
kind of advice is that?
- I believe you.
- What?
But you're gonna
have to stay like this
and play along tonight.
I'm being watched.
But I know what's going on.
I'll check in on you,
and we'll talk in the morning.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
Okay.
Oh, my God!
Help! Help me!
Somebody help!
Help me!
Oh, my God, they're right.
I'm going crazy.
Oh, my God!
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Good morning, Judith.
Oh.
Oh, where's Liesel?
Oh, she won't
be back for a while.
She said she'd be here.
She's on sick leave.
What?
- I'm sorry.
- No.
I know you two get along.
Hopefully, you and I
can be friends, huh?
Imogen.
Help me get out.
Imogen, let's go.
Imogen.
Out and up to fifth position
and around.
Beautiful, class.
Oh, no.
No.
- -I've seen it...
- The photos on the wall
and these-these
friends of yours.
Look. Look.
Thought it might mean something,
so I looked it up on-online.
It-it's a Celtic sigil,
representing an oak tree.
A symbol of-of longevity
and regeneration.
Like-like a tree of life.
Do you understand?
- Celtic?
- Yeah.
- So?
- So... you were right.
You're not going crazy.
You're right.
There is something
going on here.
I-I don't know what it is,
but it's some Wicker Man magic.
But I-I don't think you should
stick around and find out.
Well, I can't...
I can't just leave.
I... We have to do something.
Go to the police.
No, we-we need evidence.
Trust me, they won't
believe us without it.
I'm s... I'm sorry
I didn't believe you.
Oh.
Come on.
Let's go before the nurse
starts her rounds.
Let's start with Roland.
Roland?
- You watch the door.
- Okay.
What are we looking for?
Anything incriminating.
Like what?
I don't know.
Cauldron, broomstick.
Just let me know
if anyone shows up.
Oh, my God. The scans.
Yeah.
I knew it.
I knew I didn't lose
my hairbrush.
What is that?
Oh, gross. Is that his?
Quite sure it's mine.
Oh, my God, what a perv.
Wait a minute.
Shit, shit, shit.
Someone's coming. Come on,
come on, come on. Under the bed.
Hurry.
Hurry up.
Come on. Hurry up.
No! What are you doing?
Fuck.
Roland?
Where the...
Where the fuck did he go?
Oy, language.
Hey, "language" yourself.
You cuss plenty.
Yeah, well, I fucking earned it.
You're 17.
Oh, my God.
Holy shit.
What the hell was that?
- It'll be all right.
- What-what was that?
We have to follow them.
I think I know where he's going.
Do you know the new code?
- I-I-I do, but, um...
- Yeah.
Let's not waste time.
We got to get moving.
- Now.
- What the f...?
This way.
Pass me your cell phone.
My grandparents gave me this.
I'm being watched,
but I know what's going on.
She's on sick leave.
Oh, Liesel.
Turn off your light.
Before we go any further,
if anything goes wrong...
Anything...
I want you to run away
as fast as you can.
I can't run, but I don't have
as much to lose.
- No, no, no. I am not...
- You...
I'm not going anywhere
without you.
I'm the Wilbur to your Chick.
Fine.
All right, let's do this.
They're witches.
They're fucking witches.
Holy shit.
So they are.
Lord of the forest,
we welcome you unto us.
Into this circle we are bound.
We refuse the degradation
of our bodies.
Allow us to once again feed
upon the weak,
through your minion,
to absorb their energies
and replenish ours,
to thrive
through their ill health
and live beyond their death.
Oh, tree of life,
send your minion to feed for us
and extract
the last remaining energy
of Judith Albright.
No!
Josh, no!
No! Let him go!
Judith, I knew
from the beginning
you were a vivacious one.
Help!
There's no one here to help.
- Why are you doing this?
- Isn't it obvious?
I watched my wife
lose her mind bit by bit
until she couldn't recognize
our grandchild.
I'm not gonna
go through that ever.
What about the people you kill?
Their sacrificed souls
keep us going.
They already had
one foot in the grave.
If you're going to cheat death,
you got to pay the price.
But from midnight until dawn,
the witching hour,
I get to be young again
every night.
Those kids I saw in the woods...
They were you.
Incredible.
This is nothing personal.
Judith, you'll excuse the...
the cliché.
I really like you, but...
- you can't make an omelet without...
- No.
...breaking a few eggs.
No!
No. I don't understand.
It's your fucking hair, Roland.
Oh.
Let him go,
or I swear I'll trim this fucker
into kindling.
No!
Judith, wait!
It doesn't have to end this way.
There's another way.
We welcome you among us.
Both of you.
You can destroy that tree,
and then sit
and wait to slowly die alone
with all the other people
in that house.
And you, young man,
you can watch her fall apart,
lose her mind,
no longer recognize you.
Or you can join us
and be young again.
Healthy, vibrant forever.
Think of the happiest time
in your life,
when everything was exciting,
you had a purpose,
you were loved.
Think of all that you've lost.
Remember that feeling,
those happy times.
How easy it all was,
how carefree.
We can give that all
back to you.
And you have a young person...
Like my Elizabeth
or Trish's Gary...
Who can help you
and keep your secret.
It's a perfect partnership.
All those poor people.
Imogen, Annette,
God knows how many others.
The lives you sacrificed.
Are they really living?
They merely exist.
They're awaiting death.
They're ghosts.
That's your future, Judith.
Can't you see?
We're just cutting short
their suffering.
It's a mercy.
The price to pay
is very small, really.
And what other choice
do you have?
A useless existence
in a broken body.
Think about it, Judith.
No more limping.
No more pain, no more disease.
We dance, Judith.
We dance every night.
Just think of it.
And you, young man,
will never have to know
the anguish
of watching your loved one
slip away.
Or die, like your father.
Remember how hard that was?
And how your grandmother
was there for you?
Who will be there
for you, Josh, when she dies?
Judith, do it for Josh.
Grandma, please.
Don't leave me alone.
Oh, Barbara.
- Come here, sweetie.
- Happy birthday.
Aw.
Josh, sweetheart.
Mm.
Isn't it the wrong birthday?
Oh.
We thought they'd remind you
of the past.
Oh, that's wonderful.
Oh.
My grandson, everyone.
He's joining the staff here.
Isn't that great?
He keeps me young.
Oh, anybody want cake?
Let's all have some.