You spoiled brat!
You brat, where are you?
You think you can
escape from me?
It's ok, my child.
Don't cry.
Look at your brothers and sisters,
they are such good kids.
Pom, are you sure Chaba was
the one who abducted the kids?
You're sure about that?
She looks so frail.
She can barely walk.
I heard Pang's voice
coming from in here.
Be still my child. So you won't
be afraid to look at me anymore.
Don't worry, it won't hurt.
I'll be quick.
Get out!
- Jesus! It's me, Mom.
- Mom, help me please!
You bitch, don't you
dare touch my kid.
No!
Stop!
My child...
Stop! Don't touch my kids.
Crazy bitch, your kids
were burnt to death.
How could you do this to my kids?
Kill her!
Kill her! Kill her right now!
Hey Toh, why are you sitting here?
You don't want to go
back in to see your work?
Last night I already watched it once.
So how was it?
You weren't happy?
Um... I think...
I'm going to edit the
scene where Chaba was hung.
Hello, what's up?
Pang...
- Pang... what's wrong? Pang are you alright?
- Leave me alone!
She is here.
Chaba is here.
Pang, don't be afraid.
Pang, you are having a bad dream.
Who's that?
Toh is that you?
Toh?
Shit!
Shane, the reel is running out.
Hey, this is the ghost movie
showing in theatres next week.
Where did you get these reels?
The production team
had a private screening.
Is it scary?
I really want to see this movie.
No, I don't even like scary movies
so I won't see it.
Gosh, you think you're
just too cool, huh?
So you're so chicken,
you don't even dare to watch it?
It's not like that.
I just don't like to watch stupid movies.
Is it ready yet?
No, not yet. I just got around to it.
So just swap these reels in for now.
They're outside, waiting for the film.
Yod,
are you sure we won't
get in trouble for this?
You pussy.
It's too late to back out now.
If you want your money now, just say so.
This is your share.
Here's half now.
As for the rest,
I'll get it to you later.
Hello, is this Joe?
Tonight, I want to bet on three matches.
On Calcio.
OK, yes Cagiari, Milan, and Palermo.
Palermo!
You idiot, not Palamo Picasso.
Yeah, 1,000 baht.
Yes, 1,000 on all 3 matches.
So are you leaving now?
Hello?
Thank you.
I didn't think you would
remember my birthday.
Som,
happy birthday.
Hey, am I interrupting something?
Yod!
What the hell is wrong with you, Shane?
Shane!
Yod!
- Yod, are you ok?
- That freaking hurts man!
Oh my gosh!
I'm sorry.
Som, did you really have to hit me?
I didn't know it was you.
Everyone already ate everything.
I wanted to taste your cake.
I really didn't think you
were going to remember my birthday.
I don't remember,
but your boyfriend did.
Cheers! Cheers man!
Pepsi? Whatever!
Bro, try not to drink too much.
Tomorrow you have to go to work.
Som, you're my sister, not my mother.
It's just a little, I will be fine.
I got to go now.
Why, what's the hurry?
I won't be able to wake up.
Ok, it's up to you.
You know, a petite girl like you
going home alone late
like this is not safe.
I told you to move in with me.
Bro, your place is way too dirty
for anyone to live.
Even the rats have to leave.
You're so dramatic.
I'm going now, bye.
Go...
Isn't the weather nice tonight?
- Um, Som about the watch I took...
- Forget about it.
Hey Shane, you have the worst luck man.
I really think Som hates your guts.
Uh... Yod?
Yod, are you sure
security is not going to walk in?
Shit man, you know I got your back.
Don't you need the
money to get Som's watch?
Just hurry and get it done.
"Taweesup Pawnshop"
"Pawing: 1 Lady watch"
Shane! What are you doing?
Why are you taking my watch?
I just need to borrow it, Som.
You're gonna trade it for drugs, right?
- C'mon Som I will give it back later.
- No! You can't have it! Give it to me!
Let go!
Som...
Oh shit!
Damn it!
Who is that?
What are you doing here?
Uh, I am looking for my stuff.
Yesterday, while I was watching a movie,
I must've dropped it.
Ok, have you seen Yod?
Um, no. I just got here.
Where the heck is he?
Why, do you have something urgent for him?
If I run into Yod, I will let him know.
Yesterday Yod returned the wrong print.
Now everyone is scrambling to find it.
They are worried the
film will be pirated.
Som where are you?
Please go get the posters
at the entrance for me.
Yes, I am on the way.
Dude, why is the door locked,
are you wacking off in there?
Oh, I accidentally locked it.
Dude, do you know the result of
last night's games?
You won all your bets!
- Today your shift ends in the afternoon right?
- Yes.
Can you do me a favor?
Go collect my winnings for me.
Then take my share of the winnings and
this money and go redeem my stuff for me.
- I got to go now.
- Ok.
Don't forget.
Yod...
Yod.
Shit! Damn it!
Hey Shane.
Where is your supervisor?
When I call, no one picks up.
I really don't know.
So the both of you think
you can screw me over, huh?
So, where's that movie
that I asked you to copy?
Right now all the theatre staff
is on the lookout.
About the money,
I'll find a way to pay you back.
I don't want your money.
You got to find a way to copy that film.
I want to deliver the copy
before its release date.
Hey Pom, are you sure
it's Chaba who abducted the kids?
Seriously,
I've heard Pang's voice from the inside.
Pang! Pang!
"Calling... Yod"
Phong!
What is it, Pom?
Hurry, take the girl with you and run!
Chaba's ghost is back to take revenge.
Everyone else is dead.
Hurry! Grab your sister.
Go Phong! Get out of here.
Yod?
Who is that?
"Calling... Som"
- Yesterday were you at work?
- Yes.
When you were on your way out,
did you see Yod?
No, I didn't see him.
Did you see the film?
- Which film are you talking about?
- The Film
No, I didn't see it.
And do you know where the
print could be sent to?
Shane,
are you free?
Please come and help us
assemble this Standee.
Som, ever since the both of you broke up,
you haven't given any thought
of ever talking to him?
If I have nothing to talk about
why should I talk to him?
You knew that Shane was high on drugs.
He didn't mean to hurt you.
Who knows... One day, he might not be there,
and you're going to regret it.
"Base on the most horrifying true story."
Why are you doing this?
You want to go to jail?
Don't tell me that you
need the money for drugs.
Is Yod part of this too?
Where is he?
Yod...
Yod is dead, Som.
Shane, what are you talking about?
This might sound ridiculous,
but there is something
more to this movie.
The ghost in the movie,
I think she is for real.
Shane, are you high?
No, Som.
Som, take a look at this.
Last night,
I was screening the movie again.
I...
I noticed Yod's corpse in the movie.
In the movie?
Ever since I watched this movie,
I've seen her haunting me.
Don't watch the movie,
Som or else you will end up like me!
Why? If I want to watch,
what are you going to do? Hit me?
"Calling... Yod"
Sorry, the number you've dialed...
Shane, why the hell are
you sitting here for?
I thought you went home already.
Here is the stuff you
asked me to get for you.
Luckily, I redeemed it in time.
Or else it might have been sold.
Open the door!
Let me out! Help!
Open it!
Shane!
Shane, what's wrong?
Please help him.
Shane, what happened?
What the hell is going on?
I have no clue
what's scaring the shit out of him!
But this time he is really in bad shape.
What else could be causing this...
except for him getting
high and overdosing again?
Som, you know what? Ever since you broke up.
He stopped using drugs.
- See you tomorrow.
- Ok.
"Production crew of
felt the curse."
"Electricity went out during the shoot,
staff prayed for forgiveness."
"Chaba"
"Chaba / Wikipedia"
"Hanging"
"Eye-gouging"
"An insane woman captures the children
and gouged their eyes out."
"Do you still remember this house?!?"
"Here, an insane woman
captured children and"
"gouged their eyes,
believing they were her own."
"Do you still remember this house?!?"
"30 years ago, Mrs Chaba Ngamsri,"
"an insane lady who captured"
"kids and gouged their eyes out,
thought they were her own."
"The villagers found out,"
"broke in and swarmed Chaba,
and hung her."
Thank you for taking care of me, Som.
Shane,
you know that story you told me
about Yod
and the ghost in the movie?
I just don't know,
it's so hard for me to believe.
But...
I came across the story you told me
from the internet and
it's exactly as you told me.
Shane, if everything that is happening
to you takes place exactly like the movie,
then how does the movie end?
In the end,
the hero dies.
He breaks into an abandoned house
to find Chaba's body to cremate.
But he doesn't make it.
What if?
We can make it?
Chaba's body might
still be in this house.
"Until now,
Chaba's body still has not been found."
Shane,
look!
This can't be?
There should be another room here?
Shane, everything might not be exactly
like the movie.
Som.
Shane...
Shane, are you ok?
Shane, can you hear me?
Shane...
Shane, I will be right back.
Shane, are you ok?
Are you hurt anywhere?
I'm fine.
Let's get out of here.
Shane...
Shane climb up here quickly.
Shane, what's wrong?
Shane, come with me.
Just come with me.
Shane, I told you to come this way.
Shane...
Shane, hurry this way.
Come with me.
Go away!
Shane...
Shane,
it's me Som.
Shane, it's ok now.
It's me Som.
I am going to die like Yod.
I got your watch back to return to you...
but I accidentally broke it again.
I don't think I will be around
to get it fixed this time.
Shane, don't talk like that.
You are going to be alright.
Mr. Rashane, please go
to the examination room.
From what I can see,
you have a fracture in your left arm.
I will give you some medicine for pain.
Take some and you can go home.
So, what were the two of
you doing in that house?
We were looking for more information
to do a news story about Chaba's death.
What are you talking about?
Chaba is not dead.
Doctor, what do you mean?
Right after Chaba
was taken by the villagers to be hanged,
the police arrived just in time to send
her to the hospital and saved her life.
However, all the villagers believed she died.
So the story was forgotten.
There... there she is - Chaba.
Are you sure that old
lady is really Chaba?
Yes, I'm sure.
So if Chaba is not dead
then who was that woman you saw?
Who is she?
Is it possible that everything is
just your imagination?
Shane...
Shane?
Som,
the person that I keep seeing is her.
Shane, you mean this actress?
", starring Ingchan"
Thank you.
Are you looking for somebody?
Nobody has come to work
at this company for over a week.
"Cast and Crew"
"Crew List: "
"Behind the scene:
villagers search for missing kids."
"Behind the scene: Chaba was hung."
Sorry, the number you've dialed...
Ok, ready?
Action!
Kill her! Kill her!
Cut.
Action.
Yeah! Kill her! Kill her!
- Action!
- Help! Somebody help!
- Cut!
- Take 25
Action!
Help! Help me!
Cut! Damn it!
Get you act together!
Jeab,
you call this acting?
Hey, your foot position is wrong.
You know what I mean?
What are you afraid of?
Your tensing all the wrong body parts.
You look like you're dancing, not dying.
Try to focus this time!
Action!
Cut!
You don't even have any lines.
All you have to do is act like you're dying.
You can't even do that!
Action!
Kill her! Kill her!
Cut!
Damn, why is it so difficult?
Can we try it again, one more time?
If she can't get it this time, then Jeab,
you go change and take her place instead.
What are you scared of? I don't get it!
What's not safe about this?
See? It's safe. Ok?
How many times are you
going to repeat the same mistake?
Everybody is waiting on you.
Can we film already, damn it!
Ok, ready everyone?
Just one more time ok?
Get out of my way!
Help! Help!
Hey, Jeab. Jeab. Come here.
- What?
- Look at this, the sling is broken.
Oh damn! Stop!
Everybody stop!
The sling broke.
Toh, the sling is broken.
Hey, get her down from there.
Get her down. Cut! Cut!
Get her down.
Come on help her down.
I'm sorry...
Shane.
Where are you going?
Som,
if I don't make it back tomorrow,
don't go to the theatre.
Don't watch the movie.
Why?
The scene where Chaba
died in the movie is for real.
Ingchan... she really died.
Whoever watches that scene
will die too.
And what are you going to do, Shane?
Shane, where are you going?
Shane.
Som, I am sorry.
Shane...
Shane.
Hey Shane, keeping to yourself lately?
Where are you going in such a hurry?
I've been waiting for
you for many days now.
Don't tell me that you're going to
try to skip out on me again.
The exit is to your right.
Yeah, the movie just ended.
I'm leaving now.
Hey wait up! What's the hurry?
Hey Shane, keeping to yourself lately?
Where are you going in such a hurry?
I've been waiting for you for many days.
Don't tell me that you're going to
try to skip out on me again.
The exit is to your right.
Yeah, the movie just ended.
I'm leaving now.
Hey wait up!
What's the hurry?
Hey!
Shane, keeping to yourself lately?
Where are you going in such a hurry?
I've been waiting for
you for many days now.
Don't tell me that you're going to
try to skip out on me again.
Piece of shit!
Som.
Shane.
Som!
You really want to see me die?
You really want to see?!
Here look!
Look at me!
You really want to see me die?
You really want to see?!
Shane?
Yod!
Shane!
at 14:15
is now ready for showing.
"A Film by Sophon Sakdaphisit"
You really want to see me die?
Subtitles by LeapinLar