To everything
there is a season.
A time to be born,
and a time to die.
Time to love,
and a time to hate.
A time to keep silence,
and a time to speak.
A time to cast away stones,
and a time
to gather stones together.
A time to kill,
and a time to heal.
A time to break down,
and a time to build up.
A time to weep,
and a time to laugh.
A time to mourn.
(Screaming off screen)
I know.
I know, girl,
that's what I'm talking about.
I mean, he would have
straightened up his act by now,
and he just didn't.
I just don't have time
for these games, Charmaine.
No.
No, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
I mean, once he sees what's
really out there, he'll know.
No, I think I'm just gonna go
back home.
I think I might take
the semester off
and hang around the house.
(Police siren)
Oh, shit.
Shit, I gotta go, Charmaine.
I think I'm getting pulled over.
Oh, man!
Damn it!
God.
Oh, God.
What did I do?
Well, ma'am,
it looks like you can't seem
to drive in a straight line.
Listen, I was just getting
a little tired.
It won't happen again.
Promise.
Well, pumpkin,
I don't think that promise
is gonna keep the rest of the
motorists on this road safe.
I think they'll be okay.
(Laughing)
Look, I only have 100 more miles
to my mom's house in Ascension.
Can you just please let me go?
Yeah, well...
Now what do we got here?
Looks like you started the party
a little early, huh?
(Laughing)
I was just trying to stay awake.
Sorry.
I'm gonna have to ask you
to step out of the car, ma'am.
I'm really sorry.
I mean, it won't happen--
Step out of the goddamn car!
Please,
I've just never been--
Get out of this goddamn car.
(Screaming)
Get and turn around,
and hug that!
Spread your legs!
Spread it and shut up!
(Crying)
Turn around.
I said turn around!
(Laughing)
You know,
I got a daughter your age,
and I'd hate like hell
to see you spend the night
in a dirty, stinking
holding cell,
'cause I know you wouldn't
want to have to squat
that pretty little ass of yours
on some dirty toilet seat.
No.
What are you saying?
I can't let you back on my road.
I'm gonna have
to take your car keys.
What am I supposed to do?
Easy.
Well, I tell you what.
I could just give you a ride
down the road to a motel.
You could spend the night
on me.
I'll pay.
And then in the morning when
you're all sobered up,
I'll give you your keys back,
and you can just be on your way.
But I need to get home.
I just need to get home.
Is your mama expecting you?
No, she was already asleep.
Well, now you got two choices.
Go to the motel or go to jail.
I'll take the motel.
That's right.
Right this way, señorita.
Come on.
Carter, glad to see
you could make it.
I've only been waiting an hour.
Yeah, well, time's getting
scarce nowadays.
I guess it is,
all that money you making.
You keep your goddamn eyes
off my pockets, Freddie.
Are we gonna do some business,
or just stand here and shoot
the breeze all fucking day?
Got some new clients for you.
Some real high-rollers.
I need names and addresses
and social security numbers,
and all that kind of thing.
Carter.
I got a truckload of Mexicans.
Snagged them when
they were trying
to make it across the border
in a U-Haul.
You snagged them yourself, huh?
Yeah.
15 of them amigos.
Got them in a safe house
down in Waco.
I figured that you can put on
a pretty show
with those Speedy Gonzales
mother-fuckers.
You know,
running for their life.
How much?
$500 a piece,
for the whole motherlode.
Even got a couple of teenagers.
(Crashing)
What the hell's the matter
with you?
No kids!
Goddamn it, you hear me?
Ugh!
I'll give you $250.
You let them damn kids go.
I want everybody else here
in less than 12 hours.
You can stop at Sonic
on the way back.
Get me a cherry limeade.
God, my eyes
are like 1,000 pounds.
I told you you wouldn't be able
to get any work done in the car.
Why don't you just shut the
computer and put it away?
Way to support
your wife there, Don.
God, I told you
I had a deadline.
Can you just give
a damn once, please?
It's not that I don't give
a damn, Nancy.
It's that we're on vacation.
And when you're on vacation,
you don't work.
That's, uh, why they call it
a vacation.
You know, it never ceases
to amaze me
that you always deem it
necessary
to tell people what to do.
May I remind you that making
a stupid website 10 years ago
does not make you the dictator
of everyone.
Why don't we pull over
at the next place?
Grab some coffee and a couple
of those beignets you like?
I hate those beignets.
I do not want to pull over.
I just want to get there,
please.
We're always rushing
everywhere, Nancy.
Let's just mosey around
a bit
and take in some
of the local flavor.
Mosey?
Stupid website, huh?
Well, next time you want to add
to that shoe collection
of yours,
or flash the American Express
Platinum card
around the way you like to,
we'll see how stupid you think
the website is.
May I remind you
that I have been there
from the very beginning?
Who, who stayed up all night
doing research for you?
Who watched every dime for you?
Who told you to sell
those tech stocks
before they took a nose dive?
I have been cleaning
your shit-stained underwear
for years, Don!
I deserve every pair of shoes
in my collection,
so don't make me feel bad
about it.
If anything,
you should be supporting me
in my career, you idiot!
Just try not to act normal,
Nancy!
Fucking arrogant bastard.
Supposed to be a vacation.
I'm--
I'm sorry that I called
your website stupid.
Whatever.
Don't worry about it.
Hey, hey!
When did you stop listening?
Okay, when did we stop listening
to each other?
You haven't listened to a word
I've said in years.
Stop.
You know what?
Fuck you.
Yeah.
Exactly.
I thought we were talking about
listening, anyway.
Listen to this, fuck you.
Fuck you!
No, fuck you.
Fuck you.
Stop it! Stop it!
What are you, nuts?
Get a hold of yourself.
Jesus Christ.
Hey!
Yes, we're in the middle
of fucking nowhere!
Can you just--
Can you just send somebody,
please?
Trace the call!
Unbelievable,
it's been over an hour.
Yeah, well, they probably had
to finish milking the cows
before they headed out.
Always on time
with the jokes there, Don.
Well, you know,
there's nothing like playing
to a friendly audience.
I wish they'd get here soon.
I would hate to see what would
come out of those woods.
Thank you very much
for coming.
We got hit.
Some guy hit us twice
and drove off.
Can you start her up?
Well, it wouldn't start
earlier.
But look,
I'll try it again.
(Engine stalling)
Pretty good-looking gal
you got there.
Thanks.
Y'all going on a road trip?
Hey, did you call
a tow truck?
Where you all going?
The casino in Marksville.
Hell, that's 100 miles back down
the road from where you came.
No, it's not.
Oh, yes, it is.
Oh, come on.
You told me
you'd been there before.
GPS says it's this way.
This ain't none of my business,
but pretty gal like that?
You ought to be taking her to
a nicer place than Marksville.
No disrespect.
None taken.
Can't afford to have pride on
a night like this, right?
That's right.
So, did you call
a tow truck?
Oh, hell, you ain't gonna get
a tow truck
this time of night
within a hundred miles.
You'll have to wait until about
8 a.m. in the morning.
8 a.m.?
8 a.m.
You're sure?
I'm sure.
Well, hell,
I'll tell you what.
If you'd like, I can give you
and the pretty lady here
a ride down to a little motel
about 15 minutes down the road.
Get yourself a room,
get a good night's sleep
and I'll make sure
you get a tow truck
first thing in the morning.
What about
a rental car company?
Come on now, do I look like
I work for Enterprise?
Hell, this time of night, I
should be sleeping in my car
somewhere on the side
of the road.
Now, if you wanna get your gear
and come with me,
I'll take you down to that motel
if you'd like.
Well, make up your mind, 'cause
I'm leaving in two minutes.
Gotta protect and serve!
We just need a minute
to gather our stuff.
We're lucky he came.
This is ridiculous,
absolutely--
No, no, no!
Do not take that thing.
I hate that thing,
put it back.
Put it down.
You'll probably get arrested
or something.
¶ Tell my mother
that I love her ¶
¶ Tell my lover
there ain't no other ¶
¶ Tell my brother I'll see him
down the road sometime ¶
¶ Oh my ¶
¶ My my my my ¶
¶ My my my ¶
Whoo!
All right,
here we go folks.
Welcome to the finest digs
in Parish.
Oh, come on!
Are you serious?
Hey, it's not so bad.
I'm sure you got yourself
one of those platinum cards
you can just swipe,
swipe, swipe.
Unbelievable
I would rather stay in that car
than sleep in this shit hole.
Well, you're gonna have yourself
a long walk,
'cause as of now,
my shift is officially over.
Who you calling now?
911, this is a fucking
emergency!
You're wasting your time, ma'am.
As I said, I am the law,
and I'm the only law in town.
Great, now I don't even have
a signal.
Don, give me your phone.
Look, if you don't have a
signal, I'm not gonna have one.
Great, this is just great.
I'm stuck in the middle
of nowhere
and I'm gonna catch crabs
tonight.
Hey, this here's a fine
establishment.
Matter of fact--
I had my wedding
reception here.
Now if you don't mind,
I've got business to tend to.
On the side of the road,
right?
Little something for my time?
Go fuck yourself.
Here.
Unbelievable.
We don't want any more trouble.
Well, you don't start none,
there won't be none.
Now you all sleep tight.
Don't let the bed bugs bite.
I'll get that car of yours
towed in the morning.
In the meantime, I suggest you
wash this lady's mouth out.
Now y'all get the hell
out of my car.
Nice, Motel Royal Vista.
This is really romantic, Don.
They're probably sleeping.
Like we should be.
This is romantic,
thank you!
These are the kind of moments
that bring people closer.
Hello!
Hello?
Hello.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God,
this place is disgusting!
I am so sorry!
Wasn't expecting anybody in
this late.
This is our slow season.
Yeah, I'll bet.
Um, we had an accident
down the road.
Sheriff brought us here,
said you could get us a room.
The sheriff brought you here?
Yeah, that creepy sheriff.
He kicked us out of his car.
Yeah, that old Cleveland can be
a real son of a bitch sometimes.
You know, I sang in the choir,
third grade, with him.
Couldn't carry a tune
to save his life.
Yep, we heard.
Uh, look, I don't want
to be rude,
but we're pretty tired
and we gotta get an early start
in the morning.
So, uh, do you have a vacancy?
Oh, sure, sure, sure!
I forgot you big-city types
don't always like
this small town chit-chat.
Let me get you all fixed up.
Can we get the cleanest room,
please?
Around here,
we believe that cleanliness
is next to godliness.
Well, what do you need?
King room would be ideal.
King suite?
$129.99.
What?
Oh, come on,
that's unbelievable!
It is!
We cater mostly
to the corporate type.
A1 Trucking out of Appaloosas.
It's our biggest customer,
and they usually have us
full up.
I'm sure.
Take American Express?
Oh, we gladly accept
all major credit cards.
Great.
Well, if you excuse me
for a minute,
our credit card machine
is there in the back.
I'll give it
a little swiping,
be right back here.
Don't you go anywhere.
Uh, I'm really sorry,
but there seems to be
some problem with your card.
What?
Problem?
Can I use your phone?
Let me call them.
Not to worry!
It's kind of slow
around here tonight.
You've already told me how you
two have had a tough evening.
So your room tonight will be
complimentary, on us.
Just a little old southern
hospitality!
I can even turn on
those dirty movie channels
if you want to blow off
a little steam.
How thoughtful.
We'll be okay.
We just want to get some sleep.
We're gonna need the key.
Oh no, it's all friendly
around here.
Nothing's locked up.
You just take, uh, room 4.
Just down the way there.
Feel free to buzz me up front
if you need anything at all.
Dial 0, I'll be
at your beck and call.
Thank you, good night.
Sleep tight now!
Dispatch, I'm in the area
and there's no car in sight.
Are you sure
this is the right location?
RADIO:
10-4, 313, mile marker 21.
Looks like they must have got it
up and running.
I'm heading back to my post.
10-4.
Oh, my God!
Ugh, I'm definitely catching
a disease tonight.
Well, I tell you after 8 years
in the marine corps,
it'd take a lot worse than this
to scare me.
Aren't you the macho man?
Maybe I can sleep standing up
like a giraffe.
Well, you already sleepwalk,
so it would be
the next natural step.
Maybe I could break
the world's record
with saying "Fuck you"
enough times in one night.
No, I think you've already
achieved that goal, Nancy.
You may want to set the bar
a little higher.
TV's broken.
Oh my God, what is that?
Don, there's blood on the wall!
You sure?
There's blood on the wall!
Yeah, it's still wet.
Ugh!
Those A1 truckers
must like it rough.
I am not staying here.
Huh.
We are leaving at 7:45 a.m.
No later!
That was the plan.
He didn't turn the porn on.
Well, let's get some sleep.
Oh, bed's comfortable.
You're taking way
too much time, Jonas.
God, Cleveland!
Will you just let me log in?
Why you always move so slow?
I'm going as fast as I can.
Well, better hurry up
because we got a lot to do.
We ain't got much time.
I'm hurrying, all right?
I almost got the list
sent out to everybody.
The whole list, all right?
There, it's gone.
It's about time.
You idiot.
Yes, sir, we can get a private
room for the congressman.
That's right.
From now on,
he's gonna be known
as, uh, R15.
Yeah, that's right.
Don, put that down.
That's disgusting.
It's right
on the bar of soap.
It's gross,
put that down!
How did it get there?
That's an article
you could write.
Thrilling.
You can almost see yourself
in this mirror.
Huh.
Well, been an interesting
evening.
Morning cannot come
soon enough.
You know what this
reminds me of?
Summer vacation bible school.
What?
Remember?
The boys and girls had to sleep
in separate cabins,
and for good reason.
And you snuck into mine.
We were so scared all we did
was hold each other
and talk all night.
We didn't even kiss.
That's because
you were too scared.
Oh, you were scared too.
But when you finally did,
a week later...
your lips were trembling.
Where did we go wrong?
Do you think I wanted it
to be like this?
Every girl wants the perfect
marriage and the perfect family.
Nancy, I said I was sorry.
I made a mistake.
I'm sorry.
Counselor said we just need
to relearn to communicate.
That's why we went
on this trip, Nancy.
But all you've done so far
is yell at me.
What am I supposed to do
with all the anger?
I made a mistake.
A big one.
That is the truest thing
that you have said all night.
You know, I'm the one
popping Paxil.
I'm the one popping
fertility drugs.
I'm the one doing everything
that I can.
I can't just stop feelings.
I want to make it work.
Baby, I'm gonna make it up
to you.
Just give me another chance.
I am just so angry.
I'm angry at everybody
and everything,
and I am not an angry person.
I do not want to be
an angry person.
And you're the one who made me
I guess somebody checked in
next door.
Yeah, checked in with a bang.
God!
What the hell?
Hey, mind your own business.
I want what they're drinking.
Hey, I got an idea for you.
You should write an article.
Great sex in nasty hotels.
I could probably win
the Pulitzer with that one.
Holy shit.
That's enough.
Go talk to them.
You want me to go over there?
Yes!
We're not gonna put up
with that all night.
Go talk to them.
All right.
Sir, may I help you?
Yeah, look, I'm, uh, sorry
to disturb you,
but, um, I'm in the next room
and my wife and I have just been
to hell and back
and well, we've been through
a rough night.
Just appreciate it if you could
keep the noise down.
Yeah, sure.
Sorry to disturb you.
Thanks.
Hey!
I'll give you $1,000
if you drive us into town?
No, no, no thank you.
What'd they say?
They said they'd tone it down.
Thank you.
Yep.
Maybe we can get a little
shut-eye before morning.
Yeah.
I got you covered.
Yeah, no problem.
Same place as before, right?
Same place.
You back again, huh?
I wouldn't miss this
for the world.
Have fun, boys.
I got you something better
than those ponchos.
Yeah, besides they sell for more
as sex slaves.
Yeah.
Got you this one.
Ah, how about this?
Oh!
Fresh shipment of young hookers
from the Ukraine,
or former Yugoslavia.
Who cares, huh?
You can't beat this
with a bat, man.
How much?
A thousand a piece.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
We said 250.
But these here are, um,
multipurpose, man.
Come on, look,
look what you got here.
Okay, hey, hey,
I'm a businessman, you know?
What, uh--
You tell Carter Fairbanks
it's a pleasure.
And maybe, uh,
maybe next year,
I'll find out the location
and I can be there
the night of the big show.
The shit we get ourselves
into, huh?
My grandmother told me to,
um, join the air force,
stay single,
and be done with it.
But no, I wanted to be
a journalist, look for love.
Well, your grandmother
was a mean, lonely woman.
She was a 4-star general.
Oh, for crying out loud.
Forget it, I'm not--
No, no, no, no, no,
go please!
All right.
Thank you.
What's going on?
Shit!
You gotta stay calm, okay?
Don't ask any questions.
Just do what I tell you to do,
okay?
Tell me what's going on!
Don, what is going on?
You gotta tell me
what's going on!
They killed a girl.
What?
Right next door,
they killed somebody!
I saw them through the window.
That's crazy!
Get in the closet!
We got a good one.
Go!
Nancy!
I think they're gone.
Are you sure?
Yeah, come here.
You see that Buick?
Yeah.
That's our escape right there.
I can hotwire it.
Okay.
All right.
Let's get the fuck out of here,
all right?
Ready?
Look, that car.
Maybe the keys are under
the visor or something.
Looks good there,
let's go.
This way!
Oh, my God!
Come on!
Ahh!
Holy fuck!
Oh, my God,
what are we going to do?
Fuck!
Well, hello there,
big-city boy!
Looks like you found yourself
in the wrong place
at the wrong time.
What do you want?
You want money?
I can get you money!
I can get you $1000 cash.
Take me to an ATM right now!
Now what makes you think
I want your money?
Why are you doing this, huh?
What kind of sick shit is this?
What are you doing this for?
Hey now, who you calling sick?
You're the one who
almost killed somebody.
So you want to play rough,
city boy, huh?
Tell him that my dad's
a U.S. Senator.
Tell him!
Hey, little lady there!
Even the President
of the United States of America
ain't gonna get you
out of this fix.
What the fuck did
we ever do to you?
You sound like a gambling man,
since you was going
to the casino and all.
So how about we-- how about we
make ourselves a little bet?
How about that?
What?
Did you see that white Buick
out in the parking lot?
I know you saw it
when we was coming in.
We call her old Betsy.
She got about a, oh,
a half tank of gas in there.
That ought to get you
to Lafayette,
where your wife can take
a nice, hot shower.
They even sell beer
after midnight.
Key's under the visor.
What do you say?
What's the bet?
Well, the bet is if you make it
to the car,
you can drive out of here.
And if you don't?
Well, you don't!
How do we know the car runs?
'Cause I'm a man of my word,
goddamn it!
I'm the law!
I took an oath!
Jesus, you scared the shit
out of me, Cleveland.
What?
What is it?
He said there's a car out here.
A car?
Come on.
All right.
I saw him going
around the corner.
Let's go.
Over there?
Oh, my God!
Can you see it?
It's right there,
all right?
Okay.
Let's go.
No, wait!
What?
It's too easy.
Well, what other choice
do we have?
Okay.
Don, Don!
Oh, my God!
Come on!
Ahh!
Go, go!
Argh!
Check the window.
Oh, my God,
they're gone.
I love you.
I love you too.
I see, compadre,
you got some cojones.
Hell, this is gonna be
more fun than I thought.
You told me if we made it
to the car, we could go.
I'm gonna have to delegate
that answer to my associate.
Sorry, brother.
I decided to change my mind.
Hey, you listen to me,
you sick fuck!
You think this is a game?
We're gonna change the rules
a little.
We're gonna let my wife go,
and then I'm gonna give up.
I'm gonna make it easy on you.
Young man, I make the rules
around here.
You live when I say you live,
and you die
when I say you die--
We are gonna die in here.
Listen to me,
listen to me.
We are not gonna die.
We just need a plan.
So, look around,
check in the drawers.
Look for something,
anything, all right?
Wait a minute.
If he called us,
maybe we can call out.
Dial tone.
It's ringing.
Hello!
Hello, listen, somebody
is trying to kill us!
We're at the Motel Royal Vista!
Route 16, Garcia Parish.
Didn't your mama ever tell you
that it wasn't nice
to be a tattle tale?
Hmm?
Well, it's not.
Now you're gonna have to get
a little spanking.
Go on over there
and look out that window.
Yeah, that's just in case
the state troopers
come snooping around,
or maybe some detective
wondering what happened to you.
Look, I'll tell you
what I'm gonna do.
If you call this thing off,
first thing in the morning,
we can call my banker.
I'll have a quarter of a million
dollars wired into your account
Anywhere, anywhere you want!
No questions asked.
Hey, big-city boy,
didn't your mama ever tell you
all the finer things in life
are free?
Listen to me,
you are gonna burn in hell!
You are gonna burn in fucking
hell, you mother-fucker!
Yeah.
We're out of time.
We got to do something.
We got to do it now.
Come in.
Got your cut, boss.
It's about time.
Well, you know,
I just love the smell of--
Mmm, blood money.
Yes, sir.
Comes fast, spends fast.
Almost like the days
of Ancient Rome
when gladiators used to fight
to the death.
Why, yes, sir.
Yes, sir, just like them
gladiators.
Entertained the crowds.
Any way you slice it,
people will always pay money
to see blood hit the floor.
Pays better than pussy.
Better than poon tang?
Shh, I don't know
about all that.
Trust me.
You're right.
You take care
of them VIP customers?
I did, I did.
Took care of them very well.
All right.
Well, I am proud
to be an American.
And I hope that you are too.
I am.
Well, take this from me,
it's a gift,
and listen to it
every single day.
And behave yourself.
Okay, it's $10,000.
It's your half.
Supposed to be $12,000
No, it's 10.
You said you were gonna find me
some redheads this time.
You know they like redheads.
It's 12.
Why don't you go to hell?
I want two things, Jonas.
$12,000 and respect.
Because I am the law.
Now, you better start figuring
out how you're gonna count
another $2,000 off that stack,
or I'm gonna have to figure out
how I'm gonna wipe your brains
off that wall
before we open in the morning.
Now, hold on, Cleveland.
Uh, I was just pulling
your chain, man.
There.
That's more than your share.
It's all good.
You ever tell me
to go to hell again,
I swear to God
I will kill you on the spot.
Never happen again.
Goddamn, I'm--
I'm getting thirsty.
Couple beers?
That's a good idea.
Yeah, sounds good.
Don, come here!
Someone must have called
the fire department.
Wait, wait!
We don't know who's who.
It's the fire department.
They're here to help us!
Come on,
this is our only shot.
We gotta make sure
they're legit.
Jonas.
Yeah, everything's all set,
just like you want, Carter.
Yeah, we're right here.
Don't you worry
about a thing, boss.
We got it covered.
Well, looks like he's here
to put the fire out.
I don't see anybody.
Okay, come on right, okay.
Look.
When I open the door, we run
as fast as we can right to him.
Okay, we don't stop.
Straight there, all right?
Yes.
We use his radio
to call for help.
Go, go!
Hey, hey, hey!
Oh, my God, thank you so much
for coming here!
They're trying to kill us!
One second, one second!
Listen to me.
What's going on?
There are four men.
Yes, sir.
They've killed a girl.
They're playing some kind
of sick game.
You need to contact the state
police now.
Yes, sir.
I need a weapon!
All right, right around the back
there's an axe.
You go grab it.
I'm gonna go call it in
on the radio.
You go.
Honey, hurry up.
Where is it?
Don!
Oh, my God!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Let's take this truck.
Okay.
Careful!
Don, hurry.
Oh, my God!
Run!
This way!
Fuckers!
Oh my-- oh, my God!
Don!
There's a window!
Get out the window.
There's--
Listen to me.
If you make it to the car,
try to get the gun.
Okay?
I'll be right behind you.
I will hold them off.
Go!
I can't go
without you, Don!
Listen to me,
we're gonna make it.
When you see someone,
you start firing
and you don't stop.
Go.
All right, you mother-fucker!
Goddamn it!
We got to go in there and kill
that son of a bitch right now.
He's gonna be a problem.
Not yet.
What do you mean,
not yet?
He killed my cousin Cody,
you son of a bitch.
I said not yet.
Now, Carter,
you put that pistol away.
Otherwise, one of us is gonna
die today.
But which one?
Now, why don't you give me
a chance?
I bet you I could outdraw you.
Don't get all tough
on me now.
I like it when you do
the gladiator thing.
Why don't we just get the show
back on the road?
All right?
All right.
Fuck!
Find the gun, find the gun!
There was a fucking gun.
Ahh!
Oh!
Shit!
Argh!
You listen to me!
Take me to my wife,
or I will fucking kill you!
Easy now!
You are one tough
son of a bitch.
But I know you.
You are not a real killer.
I just work here.
Where's my wife?
You kill me and you ain't never
gonna find her!
Just listen.
Let's make a deal.
I will help you and your wife
get out of here alive,
but I need you to do
two things for me.
One, let me walk out of here.
And two?
You go kill that son
of a bitch Cleveland first.
You shoot him right between
the fucking eyes.
Agreed?
I'm listening.
Okay.
Right behind you,
under that table,
you're gonna find a pistol.
It's fully loaded,
taped in place.
I'm ain't going nowhere.
There.
It's all good.
We got a deal, right?
I decided to change my mind.
Stand up.
Stop that whimpering.
We're gonna walk out to my car
and if you run away,
I shoot you down like a dog.
Argh!
Go, go, go, go!
Whoo, we got ourselves
a gun fight!
Hey, ya!
Yee-ha!
Run little doggie, run!
Come on, you son of a bitch!
I hope you run better
than you shoot!
Ugh!
Oh!
My favorite part.
Ah, you son of a bitch!
Put that goddamn thing down,
you son of a bitch.
Ugh!
Carter!
Carter.
What's a matter, Cleveland?
Don't want to play anymore?
Help me.
You know, I feel kind of
like an emperor.
Should I give you the thumbs up,
or thumbs down?
Goddamn, this ain't funny.
Help me out.
Come on.
Goddamn it!
And all I asked of you
is one goddamn thing,
just stay organized.
You just couldn't do it,
could you?
These things cost.
You're right about one thing.
Somebody is gonna die tonight.
To everything there is a season,
and a time to every purpose
under the heavens.
A time to be born,
and a time to die.
A time to plant,
and a time to pluck up
that which is planted.
A time to kill,
and a time to heal.
A time to break down,
and a time to build up.
A time to weep,
and a time to laugh.
A time to mourn
as we say goodbye
to our dear friend, Sydney.
We lament her loss yet we
rejoice in gaining the knowledge
that she still continues
to look down upon us.
Let's make Sydney proud.
Go in peace.
This funeral has ended.
I'm so sorry for your loss.
Thank you.
Sydney was a friend of mine.
Is there anything I can do?
No, thank you.
I can't think of anything.
I have a place for you
to stay tonight
if you don't want to take
the long drive home.
Thank you, sir.
We do have a code, you know.
Code of silence.
Yeah, I heard a rumor
from a little birdie
that you've been running
your mouth
about our organization.
Well, I didn't figure you
were gonna level with me.
Can't live by the code,
then you're gonna die by it.
All right,
you take it easy there.