Welcome to Zombieland.
Back for seconds?
After all this time?
Well, what can I say,
but thank you.
You have a lot of choices when it comes to zombie
entertainment, and we appreciate you picking us.
So you know how Eskimos have
a bunch of words for snow?
The only reason we've survived
the last several years
is that we've gotten to know our bloodthirsty
enemies better than we know ourselves.
In the time since we last saw you,
zombies have evolved,
so we've given them
different names.
This lady here is getting chased by the dumbest
Z there is, what we call a Homer.
In a world without YouTube,
who isn't entertained by a Homer?
Unfortunately, for every Homer,
there's a Hawking,
as in Stephen.
Or maybe his slightly less accomplished sister, Beatrix,
who's still got some brains left to figure shit out.
Open, open!
Clever girl.
Okay. Last one.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
what was that?
Okay, all right. Well, this time,
let's play Name That Zombie.
Hello?
The Ninja.
Silent, deadly.
The first thing you hear is
your own scream.
You can imagine how thrilled we were
to crack the zombie code.
But life is about more than
just survival.
Ever since we were evicted from our normal lives,
I'd been searching for a place to put down roots.
My old pal Tallahassee has this saying,
"Go big or go home."
It's not his signature phrase,
but it did give me an idea.
Why not go big...
and go home?
♪ End of passion play,
crumbling away ♪
♪ I'm your source
of self-destruction ♪
♪ Veins that pump with fear
Sucking darkest clear ♪
♪ Leading on your death's
construction ♪
♪ Taste me you will see ♪
♪ More is all you need ♪
♪ Dedicated to how I'm killing you ♪
♪ Come crawling faster ♪
♪ Obey your master ♪
♪ Your life burns faster ♪
♪ Obey your master, master! ♪
♪ Master of puppets,
I'm pulling your strings ♪
♪ Twisting your mind
and smashing your dreams ♪
♪ Blinded by me,
you can't see a thing ♪
♪ Just call my name
'cause I'll hear you scream ♪
♪ Master, master! ♪
♪ Master of puppets,
I'm pulling your strings ♪
♪ Twisting your mind
and smashing your... ♪♪
Hail to the motherfucking chief.
There are worse places
to hang your hat.
Wait, why does he get to be president?
I would have made a damn fine president.
Kissed a few hands, shook a few babies.
- You would have brought a real dignity to the office.
- Thank you.
You don't have what it takes. I'll be president.
And I nominate Little Rock as my VP.
So that means I get to be president
if you get killed by zombies.
That wasn't what I was thinking
when I offered the position, but yes.
I have this rule:
Enjoy the little things.
Which is what we spent a lot of time doing
in those early days at the White House.
And it was a really special time,
making a house our home.
♪ Happy birthday to ♪
Shooting up, not to.
All right. Nice!
Wichita and I fell into
our own version of domestic bliss.
Well, not quite bliss,
but domesticity to be sure.
- Did Abe's blindfold fall off again?
- No, it did not fall off. I took it off.
It's so creepy.
He just stares at us all night.
That stare emancipated the slaves, okay?
And it ended the Civil War.
We should be grateful
he's gawking at us.
Remember what happened
the last time you took the blindfold off?
- You made me sleep on the Lincoln couch?
- Mm-hm.
- Is that better?
- Much better.
Good.
- I love you so much, baby.
- Sorry.
You are so gorgeous.
We really need to find you someone.
That's where you're wrong.
Any romance left in me belongs to the Beast here.
Okay. Well, then we need
to find someone for me.
Shouldn't be a problem,
long as you're open to dating zombies.
So you're saying what?
I'm never gonna find a boyfriend,
or get married, have a family?
We're your family,
so one out of three ain't bad.
Little Rock had a strong desire
to leave the nest.
And let's just say Tallahassee wasn't
the most understanding father figure.
Little Rock!
But for better or worse,
we were a family.
And for the first time since the virus,
we were living somewhere truly safe,
making every day feel like...
Well, like Christmas morning.
Hello? Ho-ho-ho!
Merry Christmas!
- Hey, Tal.
- Santa.
What would you like for Christmas,
little girl? A pony?
I'd like you to stop calling me
"little girl."
Well, technically, you are little
and you're a girl.
Well, I am not a little girl,
but do you know what I would like?
I don't give a fuck what you'd like.
Not to sound too sentimental,
but those days at 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue
may have been the best days of my life,
and that's counting pre-Z.
Wait a second.
Oh, my God. No.
A first-edition Tolkien,
and you wrote in it.
There's my name right there,
marring this perfectly preserved paper.
Thank you. And yours too.
You didn't stop. Thank you so much.
It's a bit touching.
Hey, I couldn't find any wrapping paper,
but don't worry about it.
Just tear it open. It doesn't matter.
It's only Taft.
He was our fattest president,
so there's a lot left over
if you need some wrapping paper.
Columbus, I didn't get anything
from you.
Just what I wanted. Another gun.
Oh, hey, well, not just any gun.
A Colt 45.
And not just any Colt 45.
The King's.
- England? Denmark? Lichtenstein?
- There's only one king.
Elvis Aaron fucking Presley,
the greatest who ever lived.
The king of kings.
He gave this gun to Nixon
when he visited the White House,
and I give it to you,
locked and loaded.
Yeah, he used to shoot
that Colt in his backyard.
King's palace, Memphis, Tennessee.
I tell you about Graceland?
- Only a hundred times.
- We're gonna go there together someday.
Actually, I'm gonna go
shoot this right now.
I think I saw some Zs down
by the reflecting pool.
- Well, I'll go with.
- I'll go by myself.
- It's Christmas.
- It's not fucking Christmas. It's November 17th.
Little Rock was on the hunt, all right,
for people her own age.
And the thing is, they were out there.
We just made it a point to keep our distance.
Which would kind of suck
if you were the one stuck in the nest.
God, this is really terrifying,
but totally unrealistic.
Hey, she'll be fine.
Wish she didn't remind me
so much of me.
Hey, come on.
What's wrong with you?
Nothing.
All right. I wasn't gonna do this now.
Okay. Look, you always say that,
like, I play it too safe,
and I know we've been in, like,
a bit of a rut lately.
So I thought, what better way
to spice things up than to...
Get married?
- Yeah, well, I was gonna say, "Get married!" Yay.
- Is that the Hope diamond?
I certainly hope it is. I want you to be Miss Ohio.
Or I guess Mrs. Ohio.
This is so unfair.
You know how I feel about this.
- What?
- We've talked about this.
In my limited, but absurdly painful experience,
married people only do one thing.
- What, fight? We already do that.
- Get divorced.
I don't see us going that route.
I mean, where would we find the lawyers?
- I don't know what to say.
- Well, don't say anything. Yet.
Okay? This was my fault.
I put you on the spot.
Just think about it,
and let me know whenever you're ready.
Everything will work out
exactly as it's supposed to.
Hey, Buttercup. What's wrong?
Get a little too much eggnog last night?
- Bad news.
- Bad news?
Well, you know what cancels out bad news?
Good news.
- Today is the day that Wichita says...
- Adios.
Hm?
"Dear C and T,
we feel like total shit about leaving.
Sorry, not good at notes.
W and LR."
Well, yeah. "Not good at notes" is
a pretty huge understatement.
You know he's gonna
take this Beast thing pretty hard.
Well, he should learn
to not get so attached.
Never get attached. Remember?
That was the problem with Columbus, he got too attached.
- Well, with Tallahassee, it's like he thinks he's my dad.
- Sure, but you are so lucky you don't have a boyfriend.
Have you seen him use Q-tips?
His bedtime routine took an hour.
- Stop.
- What? God, sorry.
- No, stop! Stop!
- Oh!
Namaste.
Hi.
Wichita leaving hit me
like a shotgun blast.
So after weeks of feeling sorry
for myself,
I thought a little retail therapy might help
get her off my mind.
It's not like I immediately wanted to start,
like, wedding planning or anything.
I'm not crazy.
And who wants to get married in the winter?
Spring, sure.
- Although my hair and the humidity...
- Oh, my God! Man, I cannot listen to this shit anymore.
- My God, it's been over a month.
- Yeah, I'm bereft.
Okay, I'm giving you one more day
to mope around,
and then you gotta snap the fuck out of it.
This whole "finding a home" idea of yours
has made us soft.
And by us, I mean you.
It's high time that we nut up and hit
the road again. And by we, I mean me.
That's where I belong.
On my own. Lone wolf.
You're welcome to tag along.
- Yeah, but when they come back, we won't be here.
- They are never coming back.
- I got it.
- No, no, no.
Okay.
Yeah, it was good.
You shot your alcohol with your gun.
Not bad, huh?
No. Not bad,
but definitely no ZKOTY.
ZKOTY,
that is "Zombie Kill of the Year."
Like a junkie in search
of a higher high,
Tallahassee is no longer happy
with Zombie Kill of the Week.
Which, if you're keeping score,
just went to Dave Sanderman of Riverside, Iowa.
You may wanna set down
the Milk Duds for this one.
You dead, zombie!
Whoo-whee, pig!
Congratulations, Dave.
Listen, I never told you this before.
In fact, I never told anybody.
But I have Native American blood
coursing through my veins.
- Like, right now?
- Yeah. Right now.
Blackfoot Indian to be exact.
The freest men in history.
Mid-1800s, roamed the plains,
no houses, no laws, no possessions,
no chiefs to report to,
no wives to listen to.
They listened...
to the call of the buffalo.
And they hunted those buffalo
by herding them off the cliff
to their deaths.
The great buffalo jump.
Oh.
I don't know why I never told anyone
about my Blackfoot blood.
I guess it's a sacred little secret.
Honestly, you're the first paleface
I have genuinely trusted
because you've always been there for me.
You care and you really listen.
Unless you're in a 4D theatre,
there is no way I can communicate
how bad Z-land smells,
which is why I like candles so much.
Today, maybe a frosty gingerbread
or a Bahama breeze.
Mmm.
- Whoa!
- Ah!
Oh, my God! Please forgive me.
It's fake fur!
Oh, my God. I'm so sorry.
I thought you were a...
- You thought I was a zombie?
- Yeah.
Oh, my God, no. I don't even eat meat.
I'm a vegetarian. Vegan, actually.
- Sorry. Hi, I'm Columbus.
- Madison.
- Hi. Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you. Oh.
All right. We're hugging. So soon.
Nice to meet you.
It's nice to touch a human.
- Don't mind me.
- Oh, hello. If I can have my body?
Hi, sorry. This is Tallahassee.
This is Madison. Madison, Tallahassee.
Is this your dad?
For shit's sake, slightly older,
better-looking friend.
- Cute.
- You live here?
No, Paul Blart. I live in the freezer
in Pinkberry.
It keeps the zombies out,
though it is awfully chilly.
Do you ever consider turning it off?
Couldn't find the switch, like, anywhere.
Just hoping the electricity would run out.
I know, it's amazing.
As long as it rains, the dams give us power.
Apparently not brain power.
I feel like you're being super judgy.
Like, I'm getting a real anti-me vibe off of you.
- Are you?
- Oh, my God. There it was again.
- Yeah, I saw it.
- And that's hurtful, okay?
I'm, like,
really good at surviving.
I carry a can of mace with me everywhere I go.
And I can run really, really fast.
Probably because I used to do
a lot of hot yoga and SoulCycle.
Cardio! Sorry,
I do a lot of cardio too.
It's actually my number one rule, which is so dorky.
But I have rules for surviving Zombieland.
- Really?
- Yeah.
So do I!
You have rules
for surviving Zombieland?
Actually, mine is just mostly stay
in the freezer.
- Oh.
- Ha, ha.
You know, we actually set up camp, like,
down the road, like, at the White House.
Ah-ah.
- The White House? Oh, my God.
- Would you wanna come and, like, hang out?
- I would love that.
- Cool.
Okay.
How many rules do you have?
- You wanna know about my rules?
- I wanna hear all of them.
- Well, number two is double tap.
- Double tap.
- Double tap, yes.
- Double tap you.
You got me.
I'm murdered.
Okay, yeah, I know what you're thinking.
She's absolutely not my type.
But after Wichita
broke my heart,
I was just excited to talk to somebody who smelled
like a candle, and not whisky and gunpowder.
So Wichita and Little Rock left. It leaves
just us guys again. You know, bachelors.
This guy. You know, making a mess.
Which actually brings me
to rule number 53, Wet-Naps.
- Whoa.
- Yeah.
- I can't believe that you keep all this stuff in your head.
- Thank you.
- It's amazing.
- You know, you're really lucky.
- What?
That you found someone so smart
to take care of you.
Most people your age,
they get left all by themselves,
and that can be so sad.
Yeah. I am so lucky.
- Hey, can we have a little summit in the Oval Office?
- Yeah.
You guys, I can't believe we're
in the White House. This is soy random.
You got to broom this girl.
You know why she's still alive?
Because zombies eat brains,
and she ain't got any!
All right? It doesn't matter
because I'm hitting the road come sunup.
- Columbus?
- Yes?
Could you maybe give me a tour?
Whoa, this is the Oval Office.
Why do they call it that?
- You ready?
- I'm ready too.
- I'm ready.
- Great.
- Too.
- Let's go.
- He's kind of funny.
- Yeah, he's great. Try not to speak to him.
- Okay.
The main attraction. Ta-da.
The Lincoln bedroom. And believe it or not,
Lincoln never even slept here.
- I didn't actually want a tour, silly.
- What?
- Hi.
Mm-mm. Mm-mm.
- What's the matter?
- I don't know.
- Don't you think that I'm pretty?
- Yes, you're very pretty.
You're like
"the girl in Apartment 406" pretty.
I just...
I feel kind of guilty.
Because of Jesus?
I know ways around that.
- No, no. I... Please. I can't.
- Okay, look, I've been alone in a freezer for years.
So either we're doing this right now,
or I am biting the bullet, and I am doing the old guy.
Okay.
- God! You're so hot! Oh my God!
- It's the humidity.
Oh, yeah!
Holy...
Nutting up,
definitely not shutting up.
Yeah!
Shit.
Sorry,
it's Washington's old flintlock.
It's a gift to Dwight D. Eisenhower
from the emperor of Japan.
Oh, touché.
- I heard a strange noise.
- Yeah, I've been hearing some strange noises too.
Oh, yeah.
That was us having sex.
Rule number one.
Yeah,
maybe rule number 32 for her.
What? Hey.
Okay. Ready?
- Go!
- Okay, let's go. Come on.
Oh, fuck.
Shit.
Honey, I'm home.
Oh, my God, you're back. I mean,
you're back or whatever. That's cool.
I'm not staying.
I just came to get weapons.
- At 1:00 in the morning?
- Yeah, after a month missing.
Little Rock's gone.
It was great. It felt so good
to be on the move again.
Yeah, we've been having, like,
a really good time here too, right? Together.
We picked up someone new.
Just a boy.
He's a couple years older than Little Rock,
and he's from Berkeley.
- Berkeley?
- Mm-hm.
♪ Don't worry ♪
- You said Berkeley?
- Yes.
Berke-fucking-ley?
He plays the guitar.
Shut the fuck up right now!
I know what you're about to tell me.
She's dating a musician!
Hey, come on, dude. Don't you think you're,
like, overreacting maybe, like, a little bit?
Yeah. Yeah. No, I could be overreacting.
I'm sorry. You're right.
You go ahead.
And he's a pacifist.
He has survived on a strict policy
of conflict avoidance, like Gandhi.
No!
Birkenstock sandals,
wheatgrass!
Fucking basketballs!
No, I really...
I have nothing against pacifists.
I just wanna beat
the shit out of them.
♪ This is my message to you ♪♪
Wow, I mean...
You have a beautiful voice.
- Thank you very much. Thank you.
- Yeah.
Hey, have you ever heard
of this place, Graceland?
Elvis was a fraud.
He ripped off the black man.
Oh. I don't know.
I've just always wanted to go there.
Yeah, me too.
Yeah.
- Graceland would be cool.
- Yeah. Yeah, it would be.
I was adamant it was a dumb idea,
so I did what I never do with her.
I told her no. And you can
probably guess what happened next.
She left a note,
and then she hit the road.
Does anyone else get
the irony in that?
Huh?
I'm so worried,
you guys.
They're travelling all that way,
and all they have is a fucking guitar.
Yeah, with no intention of ever swinging
it at anything. You know, because he's a hippie.
- She's supposed be killing the dead, not following them.
- Oh, God.
- There's something going on out there.
- What?
Berkeley told us about this new kind
of zombie that's stronger, and faster,
and deadlier and better adapted
to the hunt.
What? I'm sorry, but that sounds totally made up.
I mean, if you want us to come with you, just, like, ask us.
- Honestly, I just came back for guns and ammunition.
- Sure. Come on. Stop begging. We'll do it.
- You know, this is all your fault.
- Me?
- If you hadn't pushed her away...
- Well, not exactly.
No, I didn't just run from him.
She ran from you too.
What?
You... You mean well,
but you're kind of overbearing.
- Oh, right. I'm overbearing?
- She's not a kid anymore.
Yeah, she's not a kid, but I don't know,
it sounds like she needs us.
Whatever.
We're gonna go get her.
We ride at dawn.
Once she's safe,
I'm going my own way.
So no goodbye, just like...
- Yeah, I'm terrible at notes.
- A lame note.
Yeah, I know.
You mentioned that in the note.
I...
I might have overreacted
a little bit.
I mean, the proposal kind
of spooked me.
You know what I'm trying to say.
Oh, God. I'm sorry.
You know how hard it is
for me to say that
because I hate women who are always apologising
for things they have no reason to apologise for.
But in this particular instance,
I actually am really sorry.
Well, thank you.
That actually does mean a lot.
I don't know.
Maybe this could be like a...
Like a turning point for us.
Yeah, maybe.
Columbus, you coming back to bed?
Wow.
Oh, boy.
I mean, wow!
Glad we had this little talk.
Real turning point.
Hi.
- Is that your sister?
- Oh, fuck.
- You definitely don't need any help. Cool.
- No, I've got it.
The Beast is back.
I cannot wait
to get my hands behind the...
What the fuck?
No, no, no.
No way is that GD minivan
even sniffing at Graceland,
home to perhaps America's finest automobile,
Elvis' 1955 Fleetwood Series 60.
No. You know, it takes a real man
to drive a pink Cadillac.
Might make that a rule of my own.
On second thought, fuck that,
rules are for pussies.
- Nothing personal.
- How could it not be personal? That's my whole thing.
- Yeah, you're right. It was personal.
- Yeah. Come on. It's gonna be okay.
Even Tallahassee knows
beggars can't be choosers.
Vehicles with working batteries
and parts are way scarcer nowadays,
thanks to years of neglect
and decline.
Breakaway mirror.
We can't be so picky anymore.
- Clear.
- What? Oh, okay.
Boo-ya!
Okay.
This never happened.
- I'll get the door.
- I got it. I'm gonna lay in the back.
- Oh, catch.
- Oh!
Shoot. Ha, ha. I got it!
What in the butt?
- Ah, shit.
- What?
- Hi!
- Hi.
Are we dropping her off
at a no-kill animal shelter or something?
Come on, she's a human being.
We're not gonna, like, leave her here alone.
- Yeah, we can't just leave Columbus' girlfriend.
- Okay.
A minivan. Nice.
I won't feel guilty.
You left me in the harshest way possible.
- You recovered pretty quickly.
- Well, thank you.
Can you help me?
- I got it.
- Okay.
- It's just, like, heavy. Thank you.
- No problem.
- Go ahead, get in.
- Okay. You are so nice.
Makkapitew, Askuwheteau,
Sunukkuhkau...
Is he having a seizure?
I'm trying out Blackfoot names, so full shushy
or you go back in your mall fridge.
- Okay.
- Oh.
I didn't tell you.
We met at the mall.
Yeah.
I was living there.
Like Dawn of the Dead.
Last I checked,
it's the post-acropolis.
- It was so sad when the acropolis struck.
- Yeah, I know.
Hey, Madison, can you remind me, when we first met,
did you point a gun at me and steal my car?
No. When we first met,
I told you you were really smart.
- Oh, yeah.
- And then I slept with you.
That's right. You did.
Road trip! Here we go!
This is gonna be a long drive.
I love the smell of gunpowder
in the morning.
I'm more of a patchouli oil guy myself.
You don't...
You don't have weed, do you?
I've always wanted to smoke
way too much weed.
Do I look like the type of person
that would have weed on me?
- Oh, no. I w... That... I'm sorry, that was...
- Boom, yeah.
- Of course I do. Oh, I love weed.
- You got me there.
- Look. I mean, look at me.
- Yeah.
I just wanted to say it's really nice
to have another woman around.
Yeah.
Like,
to talk about relationships.
- Recipes.
- Rings.
Oh, my God.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, shit.
I know.
I found it in the bedside drawer.
I think it belonged to the first lady or...
You know what? I think you're right.
It did belong to the first lady.
Well, I think it was given to the first lady,
but she heartlessly rejected it.
What kind of idiot would turn down
a ring like this?
Maybe an idiot who didn't
wanna be weighed down.
- Anchored. Chained to something immobile.
- Hm.
- Oh, shit. Are you okay?
- Oh, shoot!
Forgot the seatbelt rule.
So she knows the rules?
I mean,
I told her just a few of them.
- Seventy-three. Are there more?
- Nope, that's it.
- I gotta check this out.
- You guys have spent a lot of time together, huh?
That's sweet.
You're cute together.
I like it.
Aww.
This looks promising.
He's so flexible.
That's what's so great about him.
He's very bendy.
- Ohio, whenever you're done with that...
- What? Yeah.
Ah!
What? No.
No, no, no. No way. Nonstarter.
You know how I feel
about clowns.
- No, not that.
- What?
- That.
- Oh.
Looks good.
- Can I see?
- Hm?
Can I see?
Yeah. Here you go.
Yeah.
The old man is so tiny.
- Can you see that?
- Ha, ha, ha.
What's-his-name, you're so tiny.
Now you're not. Now you are.
Now you're not.
Tiny. Big. Tiny!
- She is adorable.
- She is. I'm lucky.
Tiny. Big. Tiny.
Look, you're overreacting, okay?
Madison's not, like, a real thing.
It was just circumstance.
It was, like, a lack of options.
- You could say the same thing about us.
- What?
- Circumstance, lack of options.
- Really? You really think that?
Whereas you two seem like soul mates.
Destined to share deep, intellectual thoughts.
Maybe you're right, maybe we are soul mates,
okay? Because she's nice, all right?
And I'm nice. And you're not.
You're mean.
- Whatever. I'm not mean.
- Yeah, you're kind of mean.
Well, my sister is missing.
She could be dead, and you're screwing
some Forever 21-year-old.
- So if I wanna be mean, I'll be mean.
- I don't have the right shoes for this.
- Oh, you could borrow a pair of my strappy sandals.
- Really?
Mm-hm.
Kidding. You... She was ki...
You guys are all very sarcastic.
Yeah, they're not nice people.
Sorry about that. Just try to ignore them.
Yeah. Yeah.
- Ignore us.
- Please, God, ignore us.
See? Mean.
All right!
This is what I'm talking about.
We're finally gonna be riding in style.
You guys, I partied with 3 Doors Down
in one of these. It was so...
Oh, shit.
What?
- Man, we're getting good at this.
- Columbus.
Tallahassee.
- The hood is 12 o'clock, trunk is 6. You're our eyes.
- Yes.
Hey, don't worry, you guys.
They are much more afraid of us
than we are of them.
God, that is not even
remotely true.
Well, what do I do?
- You know how cheerleaders form a pyramid?
- Yeah.
- You know how the three on the bottom anchor the pyramid?
- Oh, yeah.
I don't give a shit what you do,
just stay out of my way.
Okay, 8 o'clock.
Eight o'clock.
Did you say the front was 12?
Oh, fuck me. Sorry. Two o'clock.
Eleven! Eleven! Seven-thirty!
Six o'clock. Six!
I'll get 6.
Shit. One-fifteen.
One-thirteen, 1:20. I don't know.
It's moving that way.
- Why is everyone shouting numbers?
- Eleven!
- Twelve!
- Six!
Two o'clock!
Eight.
- Six o'clock.
- Shit.
One o'clock. Six-thirty.
Ten! Eight!
- Eight o'clock! Eight!
- Shit.
Shit!
- Narsty!
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
One o'clock!
Two-thirty! Three! One!
Okay. I'll get 3.
Right on time, Columbus.
One o'clock!
Ten-thirty!
Eleven! Eleven!
Actually, you know what,
it's a Homer.
- Abort! Abort 11. Don't waste a bullet.
- Hawking!
- What? Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
Ha-ha-ha! Yay!
- Ah! He's trying to bite me!
- Ninja! Ninja!
Oh, my God!
You saved me.
All right. Settle down.
- Hey, Tal, 1 o'clock.
- Pardon me, Pop-Tart.
Not quite done yet.
What the fuck?
Try to dodge me, motherfucker.
This was our first T-800,
named for the Terminator it-fucking-self.
- Tal?
- Yup?
T-800s were a mutated strain
of zombie,
stronger, deadlier
and harder to kill.
One plus one is still two,
right?
They were the apex predator,
top of the food chain.
Single-minded and relentless
like their namesake,
once they locked on to a target, T-800s stopped
at nothing to devour their prey.
What the ever-loving fuck?
Ew.
Seeing that T-800 firsthand
was all the more worrisome
knowing that Little Rock was out there
with nothing but a hippie and a guitar.
♪ Like a rolling stone ♪♪
Okay. That song is amazing.
Did you write that?
Wa... Was that a dumb question?
- Sorry, I was like 11 when the zombies took over.
- Not a dumb question.
I was laughing because you think
I'd play you some stupid cover song.
No, of course I wrote it.
If you love that, then you're
really gonna love this.
But it's a work in progress,
so be gentle.
♪ If I leave here tomorrow ♪
♪ Would you still remember me? ♪♪
♪ Well, I must be travelling
on now ♪
A poem by Tallahassee.
Travelling to Graceland
in comfort and class
That Pontiac Trans Sport can
kiss my ass
Whoo-hoo!
Here we go, baby!
Let's go see the King
and let's go get Little Rock!
♪ 'Cause I'm as free... ♪♪
- Did... Did we just get...
- Shorter?
I say we take the clown car.
No, no, no. No! That is a deal-breaker.
No fucking clowns!
In moments of great dishonour such as this,
ancient samurai warriors
were required to commit seppuku,
or ritual suicide by disembowelment.
My mom had this car.
- So did mine.
Fucking minivan.
Back on the road. Yay.
I've always wanted
to start a business
where strangers drive strangers
around in their car for money.
Let's say you were really drunk
and you needed a ride home.
You'd just get online
and hop right in with a stranger.
And they'd take you
anywhere you wanna go.
Oh, yeah.
Who then kills you.
- Yeah.
- They'd have gum or, like, lollipops.
That was what my parents taught me.
They were like, "If a stranger offers you
candy or gum, get in their car." Great idea.
If they try to murder you, you can have
a point system, so you can rate them.
If they try to murder you, like,
"You get zero points."
- But if they don't try to murder you, "You get five points."
- Okay.
Madison, I think
it is a very good idea.
- That's... No, I cannot see that going wrong.
- All I'm saying is the taxi industry was very flawed.
- Uh.
- Are you okay?
- I think I'm, like, hot. I'm hot.
- Yeah?
Mm-hm. I'm so used to being in the freezer
all the time. Get this off.
Oh, yeah, yeah. Sure.
Yeah, that makes sense.
I feel funny.
My tongue...
- Hey, boss? You're gonna wanna pull over.
- Yeah?
- No.
- Pull over.
- No, we're making good progress here.
- Pull over!
- Yeah, yeah.
- Okay. Okay. Okay.
- Oh.
Chunkage.
I don't know,
maybe she'll pull through.
What do you mean? You are the one
who always says "don't take chances."
So who wants
to do the honours?
I mean, personally, I wouldn't mind,
but I don't want you guys calling me selfish.
Hey, come on. She is a living, thinking being.
Okay? She's a living being.
Look, I know you guys are
in love or whatever,
but in two minutes,
she's gonna become a:
A zombie, not a velociraptor.
And it's the right thing to do.
If you love something, you shoot it in the face
so it doesn't become a flesh-eating monster.
- I know.
- She's making a good point.
Maybe it's time for you
to be the Brave Little Toaster.
They say when something bad happens,
you have three choices:
Let it define you, destroy you
or strengthen you.
Time to teach Lennie
about the rabbits.
- No! Don't come with me! Don't come with me!
- Madison, Madison, please.
- Madison, please. Please, please.
- Don't hurt me!
- No, no, no!
- Wait. Listen to me!
- Please. Wait.
- No, no, no!
- Madison, just wait.
- I'm a monster.
- Please, please, please.
Listen. I realise that we don't
know each other that well.
I mean, well, we do in the biblical sense, yes.
But I think you're a really great person.
Well, not now.
I'm sorry.
Thanks.
Can we just...
- I'm so sorry.
- All right. Just... Come on, come on, let's go.
I'm not gonna lie and say
that I'm broken up about it, but...
I am sorry.
- She didn't deserve that.
- Thanks, man.
- Thanks.
- He's right.
That's a terrible way to go,
even for...
- Oh, come on. It's Madison. You know that.
- Madison. Madison.
Yes, you know that, okay? Her name is Madison.
Or her name was Madison.
You know, and she was
a real person, okay?
She had, you know, complex feelings
and emotions and interests.
You know, she liked dolphins and rainbows,
you know? And double rainbows.
I'm agreeing.
It's sad.
- Okay.
- That is obviously not what I wanted.
- What is it that you do want?
- I wanna find my sister.
Me too.
- Good.
- Good. Great. Awesome.
- Great, in fact. Great.
This is gonna be a long drive.
This is it.
Hey, little buddy, don't be cruel to me
for waking you up, but we're here.
Oh! Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
Every choice I've ever made in my life
has been leading me to this moment right here,
right now,
3764 Elvis Presley Boulevard.
I feel like a 1954 teenybopper.
And here comes...
No.
No, no, no!
Hey, dude, if you need
a moment or...
Oh, my God.
No Graceland.
No Beast.
- No Little Rock.
- No Little Rock?
Am I not allowed one cock-sucking
duck-fucking little break in this world?
You're not the only one
that's upset.
Just... Just drive.
Drive, drive. Drive now!
Get away from here. Go!
Graceland was
a pile of rubble,
Little Rock was still missing,
and we were unsure of our next move.
But sometimes, you just have
to follow the signs.
Hm.
When Z-land serves you lemons...
Hey, Florida, 11 o'clock.
What?
Hound Dog Hotel.
Oh, what a bunch of bull.
- Whoa! The Beast!
- Little Rock!
Damn. Wow,
for a place that ain't Graceland, it sure
looks a hell of a lot like Graceland.
- Yeah, it does.
- Here's the idea. We'll split up. I'll go this way.
No, no, no.
I should talk to her.
- I'm her sister. I'll talk to her first. You guys stay here.
- Sound.
Bop, bop, bop!
- Little respect.
- Why? He's dead probably.
Oh. Oh, for you.
Okay.
- This is so degrading.
- It's not for me.
Yeah, I know.
Okay.
- Oh, yeah. That's not... Push it.
- Smells like a wet dog died.
- I am. Okay.
- Square peg, round hole. Stop.
Sorry.
Oh, my God.
It's uncanny.
This is incredible.
It's a perfect fit. I feel like
Cinderella at the ball.
What, are you jealous that I have
the exact same size shoe as Elvis Presley?
No. It's not like those are
Elvis' actual shoes.
Sorry.
♪ Well, I never been to Spain ♪
Little Rock?
♪...ladies are insane there ♪
♪ And they sure know
how to use it ♪
♪ Well,
I've never been to heaven ♪♪
- Start talking.
- You first.
- Hi, my name's Tallahassee.
- Nevada.
- Which part?
- Nevada's as close as you get.
Now, what are you doing
in the Hound Dog?
I got a thing for the King.
No, no, no,
don't shoot my friends.
- Anybody else in here with you?
- No, no. Just us.
We're all civilised people.
Let's just put the guns down.
Why the hell are you wearing
Elvis' actual shoes?
Comfort.
- You live here?
- Yeah.
So that car out front, the girl
who was driving it, is she...
Gone. She and that poser
peace lover of hers...
- Berkeley.
...took off a few days ago.
And trust me, they shouldn't have.
It's not safe out there.
- Damn it.
- Why didn't they take the Beast?
- He said it was too "establishment."
- Oh, I will kill that little fart snack myself.
You're lucky I didn't do the same to you. Seriously.
You know how close I came to Murraying you?
To what-ing him?
Murraying him.
You know, when you shoot someone
because you think they're a zombie.
Apparently,
that's how Bill Murray died.
Wow. God, who's Bill Murray?
I never... I don't even know what that is.
Oh, the actor. That's so sad.
I don't read, like, Variety or anything.
So sad. Sorry if you knew him.
If you didn't, I'm still sorry.
It's sad when anybody dies.
Sounds like an urban legend though.
- It happened.
- I doubt it. It's weird. What?
I'll say this about Murray, if I ever
find out who did him, I'm gonna do him.
Me too. I'll be...
You first, but me second.
Don't listen to this guy.
He's killed more celebrities than cocaine.
The girl that was here before,
did she say where she was going?
No, but that idiot Berkeley
wouldn't shut up about it.
Babylon is a commune, safe haven,
protected on all sides.
Completely pacifist.
No guns or violence of any kind.
A lot of young people too, you know.
Generation Z living in peace and harmony.
Yeah, it sounds cool.
I know you had your heart set on this Graceland,
but this is mucho, mucho better.
This is a very good replica of the King's Jungle Room,
where he recorded his last two albums.
From Elvis Presley Boulevard,
Memphis, Tennessee and...
And Moody Blue.
You know your Elvis.
Every lover of
the King has a story.
What's yours?
My mama took me to see Elvis
when I was a kid. Something about him.
- Attitude, the music...
- The hips, the ass.
Well, I was 10, but, you know, with Elvis,
there is something for everyone.
Cut to later, I'm in high school.
And my buddy Frankie Hammond says:
"Do your Elvis."
I said, "We're in a library.
It's gonna be loud."
He convinces me. He starts
tapping his pencil, and I get up.
♪ You ain't nothing but a hound dog
Crying all the time ♪
Everybody starts gathering around
and clapping, and I jumped on a table.
I finish off with a flourish.
♪ You ain't never caught a rabbit
You ain't no friend of mine ♪♪
Yeah! And the whole place,
thunderous applause.
And up comes the cutest girl
in the school,
Robin Rogers, who never gave me
the time of day before.
She plants a kiss on my cheek.
And for a moment, just one,
I felt like the King.
I suddenly feel a little jealous
of Robin Rogers.
Ahem.
You don't say.
I don't know about you...
but I feel my temperature rising.
This is Babylon.
Oh, like those ancient hanging gardens.
- Huh?
- Of Babylon.
No, no. It's named
for that cool David Gray song.
Man, I wish I'd written that one.
No guns allowed is our one rule.
- That, and no group sex.
- All right. Hand them over.
Here you go.
No guns. No guns.
Just hugs.
Then welcome.
Come on, señorita. You're gonna love this place.
It's completely safe and entirely organic.
- This is so cool.
- All right.
We're gonna melt your guns over here
and then give you a pendant.
- They melt it?
- Yeah, they melt it.
It's a symbolic thing.
Goodbye, violence.
Hello, peace.
Once we're done here, we'll take you up
to the rooftop. I hope you like stairs.
That's good.
- Thanks.
- Welcome to Babylon.
Let me show you the way.
Right on.
Hey, brother. What's up?
- Hi.
- Yeah.
Wake up, my little blue suede baby.
It's now or never.
Hoo!
My friends say you're
sleeping like a tired pup.
What the fuck?
Shit.
Oh, no, no, no!
This is not happening!
This is not fucking happening!
Hey, motherfucker,
that's my ride!
Oh, my apologies, tiny Elvis. Just didn't
expect anything to be parked in my driveway.
Your driveway?
That's right.
My driveway.
Well, that's funny. When I parked
in it, no one told me to pull out.
Well, actually,
it's my driveway.
Hey, Nevada.
But see, when I'm in town,
I use it.
Well, I'm in town now,
and I'm using it.
Keep talking like this, and I can arrange
so neither of you ever uses my driveway again.
- I don't think they're talking about the driveway.
- No, I don't think so.
- You happy now? Great. Good move.
- Satisfied? Good job.
- Is it me, or does he kind of remind you of...?
- Yeah, it's weird.
- I don't like you at all.
It's not weird,
it's creepy.
- It's like an un-funhouse mirror.
- I think you double-parked or more perpendicular-parked.
- Hope we don't get a ticket.
- Whoa.
- Calm down. It's okay.
- I'm just ragging you.
- What is going on here?
- What?
- What do you mean, "what"?
- Does he not remind you of...?
- Hello everyone.
Of...
Of what?
- This is Albuquerque. I'm Flagstaff.
- Howdy.
Hey.
I'm Columbus.
Oh, great.
This is Tallahassee, Wichita,
and I guess you know Nevada.
- Yes, I do.
- Easy, cowboy.
So sorry about your ex-car. I guess,
as I like to say, expect the unexpected.
- It's one of my commandments.
- Oh.
- Commandments?
- Yeah.
Just sort of guidelines for staying alive.
I've got loads of them.
- Interesting.
- Yeah, number one is teamwork.
- Teamwork. That's so great.
- Thanks. I actually spent a long time thinking about it.
- I have rules, you know, which is, like, less biblical.
- Love rules.
Without rules,
everything's chaos.
- Thank you.
- Columbus has quite a few rules.
- I do.
- Awesome.
Like what?
- I don't wanna toot my own horn.
- Go on, toot, toot.
- Let me toot for him.
- Thank you.
- Number one, cardio.
- That's right.
Cardio.
Okay.
- What?
- I don't mean to laugh.
It's just that cardiovascular fitness
is his number 29,
meaning he has 28 other commandments
that he finds more important,
like, say,
what's one of your great ones?
Number 12.
The world is your bathroom, meaning you can
just whip it out wherever you want,
and just have at it.
Oh, just whip it out wherever you want!
That sounds a little uncouth.
The "whip it out" part's for guys, obviously.
If you're a woman, you can reveal it.
- Whichever.
- I have beware of bathrooms.
Yeah, I'm just generally careful
around them.
- We don't have to compare. It's not a competition.
- Doesn't have to be.
But number 18 is limber up.
- But that's...
- That's fine. I have warm up.
Again, not a competition,
but commandment number 45 for me is,
well, mind your manners.
Just because it's the apocalypse
doesn't mean you have to be rude.
Yeah, keep your hands to yourself, number 42.
Do you have sunscreen?
- Just shade.
- Shade. Of course.
It's free. It's everywhere.
Yeah. Number two, double tap.
- I have number five, confirm your kill.
- Confirm your kill.
- Avoid perishables. Do you have that?
- Sorry. Ziploc bags.
- Same thing, different word. Yeah.
- Yeah. Exactly.
I probably would shy away
from the word "Ziploc"
because I try
to avoid name brands.
Okay, great. So, what brought
you guys back so soon?
We was headed for the Rockies,
but the goddamn Bolts...
Bolts?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, the zombies out on the plains.
They're a lot tougher than
what we're used to.
I guess because of all the running and hunting.
So we call them Bolts, as in Usain.
- As in pretty fucking athletic.
- Oh, yeah. No, that makes total sense.
- We actually call them T-800s.
- Terminator. Yes! I love it.
- Really?
- Yes. Literally my favourite movie. Well, T2.
- Yeah, T2 is my second favourite movie.
- What's number one?
It's Fantasia.
Well, anyhow, the Bolts' food sources are running low,
so they're pushing east, which is no bueno.
You know what else is
no bueno?
You murdered the Beast.
Yeah, well, let me call AAA
for you. I'm sure they'll be right over.
So you have
to play your cards as...
That onesie was starting
to cut off my circulation.
To your vagina?
Your vagina.
- What'll you have, Florida?
- He strikes me as the lemon drop type.
You know, something with an umbrella
or something like that.
- I heard "something with an umbrella." Make it two.
- Three please. Three.
So that's your sidekick.
That there's my partner.
You might look at Flagstaff and think,
"Oh, he's a little slight, diminutive."
Effeminate even, but he's a real beast
in battle. Yeah.
Come on now. You're being sweet.
You sweet, sweet man.
- Thank you.
- Well, I love you.
Love you too.
Yeah, you know, Tubbs to my Crockett over here.
He may look a little bookish, but he's an animal too.
He eats zombies for breakfast,
shits them out by lunch.
Cheers.
He shits out everything
by lunch.
What the hell was that?
They must have
fucking followed you.
Oh, God, those are T-800s.
Or at the very least T-700s.
- There actually was no T-700.
- Yeah, T-800's the first model.
- This is great, having two of you.
- Okay.
Time to nut up or shut up.
That saying's very 2009.
Okay.
We got this.
Ho!
You don't send
a boy to do a man's job.
We brought them here.
We'll take care of it.
Yeah, you know what?
Have at them.
- Yeah, you have a safe word in case things go bad?
- Ha. That's good.
- Come on, Flag, let's show these fuckers how it's done.
- Sure. You got it, boss.
Hasta la vista, baby.
Terminator 2.
Remember?
Whoo! Ready, buddy?
He's so cool.
- Whoo! Hell!
- Suck these bullets!
Come on! Get you some!
- Anybody else find those two uniquely annoying?
- Get it!
Uniquely?
No.
Well,
I don't love their chances.
And they ignored rule 52,
don't be afraid to ask for help.
Get fucked in the face,
bitch! Whoo!
- Flagstaff?
- Yeah, boss?
You made the all-star team today.
I mean, no kidding.
Unbelievable job.
And is it me, or are those Bolts
just getting meaner by the day?
They're full-blown dickheads.
I got an action shot of you
that's going right into the scrapbook.
This is gonna be a good one.
You just keep raising the bar, and that's why
we will continue to ride these highways together.
- I'm so proud of you.
- Well, I learned from the best.
Oh, come on now.
- Nice work, Querq.
- Thank you. Thank you.
- This is gonna be a hell of a shot.
- It's so cool he let you wear the hat.
- Querq?
- Yeah?
I think you got
a little something here.
Oh, what that?
Oh, yeah, that's just...
That's just a tattoo.
- Sorry, you got a tattoo of a zombie bite?
- No, it's just a tattoo I got one night in Bernalillo.
All right, everybody.
Just take it easy.
Everything's fine.
Nevada, why don't you whip up
some of your signature...
All right.
That was a little weird, huh?
- Yeah.
- All right. Just calm down.
We'll just kind of have a drink, you know.
So we can just kind of celeb...
Celeb...
Excuse me. It's okay. It's just nerves
from the fight. Just...
You guys, I think Albuquerque
might be infected.
Me? I'm infected?
You got bit twice.
Flagstaff!
No, no, no. That's a lie.
Trust me. Okay? Trust me.
- I don't get bit. I never get bit.
- I know. I don't get bit either. We're slippery.
- See?
- I know. Are you okay?
- I'm fine. I'm totally fine. I'm fine.
- You are?
- I'm fine.
- Okay. Okay, guys, he's fine. He's fine.
No, he's not fine.
No.
No. Flagstaff, you're starting to look
like a T-800. Terminator 2.
No. No, no, no!
No!
Move! Move!
Get out of the way.
No! No!
Flagstaff, you're breaking
like 10 commandments right now!
This is for what you did
to the Beast!
Sorry!
- How you doing?
- Bad!
- How are you?
Sorry, shoes. Sorry, Elvis.
Oh, shit.
- How you doing now?
- Still bad! You wanna switch?
Switch? How would that benefit me?
Shit!
Help!
- Shoot him! Shoot him!
- I don't wanna hit you!
Shit.
Gun, gun, gun! Shit!
Stop shooting!
I got this!
Great, because I'm reloading!
Don't swing! Don't swing!
Don't swing! Swing!
Shit.
No, no, no, not me!
Not me! Oh, fuck!
Hasta la vista, baby.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Those guys were dicks.
- Great job.
- Thank you.
- Can I wear the hat?
- Oh, negatory.
Cool.
Zombie Kill of the Year?
Sorry. Not with the performance just
turned in by Matteo Bianchi of Pisa, Italy.
Help! I'm a lost tourist
with two defenceless children.
Help!
Fucking sons of bitches!
Yeah, yeah. That Pisa.
You won't eat me.
Not today!
Go fuck yourselves!
Bravisimmo, Mateo.
- Ahh. Sunday, Sunday, Sunday!
- Jesus, Big Fat Death is right.
That thing is, like,
a huge rollover risk.
It is.
Hey, dude, I think you should
ask her to come with us.
- No, no, no.
- Come on. I think they make a nice match.
Look, what have I been telling you guys?
I'm trying to shed baggage, not pick it up.
- Yeah.
- Besides, she wouldn't do that. She's not the type.
Stay safe,
Sunshine State.
Excuse me.
Stay dangerous, Nevada.
Okay. Hey, no offence,
but my sister is still out there.
Wanna hit the old road.
If by some miracle you don't die...
there's always room
in my driveway.
I best stay alive.
Okay, you're back.
Good.
So do you know how to drive
one of these things?
I'm gonna just pop that puppy off of there
and then you guys can jump in.
Nice.
She's a big old stallion,
but I can tame her.
Whoo!
Oh, shit.
- I think he's got the hang of it.
- Shit!
- No. No, no.
- No, no, no.
Goddamn motherfucker!
Got it.
Fuck, fuck, fuck!
Fuck!
Maybe you should leave a note.
That's your department.
I...
I just can't do it.
Yeah.
I'll drive.
What was that?
Satisfying.
Teamwork. Always put the team first.
I can't believe I didn't have that. Stupid.
You know,
if Flagstaff was so great,
then where was the undeniably gorgeous
but emotionally inaccessible Kansas City?
I don't know. Maybe she split because
she thought they had a random relationship.
Or maybe she was just about to come back under
the thinly veiled cover of needing guns and ammo.
Wait, what are you getting at?
I think you're smart enough
to figure it out...
Oh, my God.
You gotta be kidding me.
- You gotta be kidding me!
- You gotta be fucking kidding me.
Why the hell is she still alive?
Oh, my God,
I literally missed you guys.
- Yay!
- Oh, my God.
Just...
No, just look ahead.
Hi, old guy!
Let's hang out.
It is so weird to see you.
The last time I saw you, you were like a...
- You were a zombie.
- I wish.
Stupid nut allergy.
- Nut allergy?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I think it was the trail mix
that Wichita gave me.
Yeah, who knew there were nuts
in trail mix.
Not me. I thought it was vegan.
I kept trying to tell you it was only an allergic reaction,
but you thought I was trying to bite you.
- Yeah, well...
- Not that you minded last time.
Thank you
for shooting over my head.
I was reallyjust trying
to scare you off.
You're not gonna get rid
of me that easy.
- Oh, no!
- Ha, ha, ha.
There I was hiding in the woods,
when I thought, "I used to live in a freezer,
so why not a freezer on wheels?"
Can't argue with that logic.
I really miss this.
- Was that sarcasm?
- Was it?
Mm-hm.
Why wouldn't we just move to an island?
- That's a really good idea.
- Because then there wouldn't be zombies.
- Of course.
- We should go to Temptation Island.
Hey, hey, hey.
- What?
- Hey, hey.
- Hey, hey. Hey, hey.
Just...
Just eyes on the road.
Do you want me to change
the CD or anything?
Is this a CD playing?
- Yeah. It's Port... It's Portishead.
- What is this?
- This is Portishead?
- Yeah. You know what's funny?
I used to think it was called "Portashed" until I went
to one of the concerts, and she explained.
Yeah, I would think "Portasheed."
- Right. Yeah, that's funny.
- Yeah.
It was obvious to me that Wichita
and I were meant to be together,
which is why Madison's return
could not have been worse timing.
Of course, I was glad she wasn't a zombie.
But couldn't she have just gone back to her mall fridge?
Hey. Hey, look, look, look.
Look.
We made it to Baby-lon.
If you hear more than the usual excitement
in my voice, it's for two reasons.
One, we may have caught up
to Little Rock, for real this time.
And two, we may have finally found our forever home,
which is what I've been looking for all along.
- Babylon.
- I love that song.
This place is soy cute.
- Jesus!
- What the fuck?
- Enjoy the little things.
- My bags were in there!
- No, they weren't.
- No guns allowed!
I like this place already.
You got a sense of humour.
No guns allowed.
I'm not giving up my guns
under any circumstances, period-o.
Well, then, there's no way
you're getting up to Babylon.
You know, you could always wait
in the car.
Do you wanna see
Little Rock or not?
- There she is.
- I wouldn't know. I'm on a 40-day bowel blast.
Little Rock.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- What are you guys doing here?
- I am so glad you're safe.
- Wow, okay.
- Oh, my God.
- Come here.
- Hi.
- No, seriously, what are you guys doing here?
- Hey, we don't leave each other.
I know, I know.
I'm really sorry.
- Make me a pact. No more notes. Ever.
- No more notes. Ever.
- Ever. Great.
- Okay.
Just so you guys know,
there's no group sex.
- Okay, fine, group sex.
- No!
Hey, Wichita. That means you're Columbus,
and that makes you Tallahassee.
- Berkeley?
- You're from Berkeley?
- You're Berkeley?
- No, come on.
What are the chances we're
both from Berkeley?
- Berkeley!
- Calm down, calm down. Okay?
Thank you guys for coming to check up on me, I guess.
But you have to understand these people are peaceful,
and they're friendly and nice. And honestly,
I don't think you're gonna fit in here.
- They melted our fucking weapons!
- This is exactly what I meant.
Guys, I think we should stay.
- You don't get a vote.
- I do get a vote.
Haven't you ever heard of women suffering?
Women suffrage?
- No, honey.
- Oh, boy.
- Who the hell is this?
- I'm Madison.
- Don't say it.
- You'll love this.
- That's Columbus' girlfriend.
- It's official.
- Wow.
You reallyjust didn't waste
any time, did you?
- Well, thank you for your vote.
- And you're welcome.
- Okay. I'm late for my drum circle, so I gotta go.
- Hey, Little Rock!
Sorry about that.
Seeing Little Rock safe
and surrounded by friends her own age,
Tallahassee realised
his nest was now empty.
And he began to hear
the call of the buffalo.
All right, I'm ready!
Come on, don't be so Gloria Glum.
I told you guys I was leaving.
So, what,
you're just gonna split?
It's time. Gotta set out
on my own adventures.
Little Rock's safe,
and a lone wolf's gotta hunt.
So where are you gonna go?
The direction's
the destination. West.
West is that way.
Yeah. Anyway, like the title of
a great Phil Collins song,
"If You Love Somebody,
Set Them Free."
- Pretty sure that wasn't him.
- Pretty sure it was.
- No, it was someone else.
- Pretty sure it was him.
Yeah. Peace.
I'm not much for goodbyes,
so...
- Yeah, just don't say the pig thing.
- Keep your tits dry.
- Oh, okay.
- Didn't see that coming, right?
I would've rather the pig thing.
Hey.
Hey, don't do nothing
I wouldn't not do.
- You get what I'm saying.
- Not really, no.
No? Okay.
Anyway, gonna miss you guys.
- I will never forget you, what's-his-name.
- See you, pals.
- It's Tallahassee. I told you that.
- Sally Tally!
♪ Give me a home
Where the buffalo roam ♪
♪ And the deer
and the antelope play ♪
♪ Where seldom is heard,
a discouraging word ♪
♪ And the skies are not... ♪
T-800s.
That decides it.
♪ Kumbaya ♪
♪ Kumbaya, Buddha ♪
Everybody.
♪ Kumbaya ♪♪
Coming to you.
There it is.
Let's start again.
Oh, it's all right.
I got it. Excuse me.
Yes. I got it.
- You're supposed to kick it back.
- Really?
- You never seen hacky sack?
- Oh, I thought it's like hopscotch.
- Salty Taffy's back!
- Holy shit!
Hey, T-800s, a whole swarm of them,
heading right this way.
Those goddamn fireworks
might as well be a dinner bell!
Stop the fireworks! Stop the music!
Everybody shut the fuck up!
Shut up.
Question:
Did you melt all the weapons?
Yeah, that's how we made these
cool peace thingies.
- Oh, Jesus.
- My guns!
Hey. Hello. I got something going.
I think I might have a plan.
What?
I got nothing.
I'm just a songwriter.
No. No, you're
a song transcriber.
- Listen, Berkeley?
- Yeah?
I don't think
this is gonna work out.
Even 12-year-olds know
who Bob Dylan is, you fucking poser.
Oh, my God. I'm not gonna lie,
I have truly enjoyed this moment,
but there are
zombies approaching.
Okay. Civil War general,
you must know how to fight?
Sure.
Poverty, sexism,
social injustice.
- We could try running.
- I'm done running.
I mean, what good is a home
if you can't stay in it?
- Columbus.
- Yes, Thor?
You're making me cry right now.
- No, please don't.
- Oh, my God.
Okay.
I moved through it.
Now from where I stand,
there's only one thing we can do.
Group sex. Right?
No.
We'll fight them.
You'll be the first to die,
but I like your enthusiasm.
- You might die.
- Thank you for your sacrifice.
All right,
everybody, listen up.
They outnumber us 100 times,
but they ain't got what we do.
Guns?
- We don't have guns.
- What?
What we do have is heart,
brains and biodiesel.
We're gonna light these zombies up
like it's the Fourth of July.
Then we hit the stragglers.
What we do is we form a gauntlet.
Ha!
One, two, three.
- Then we mop them up.
- Sick.
- This is gonna work, right?
- It has to.
Rolling.
- Keep screwing.
- Yeah, I am.
- I am.
No turning back now.
There we go.
Nice.
Yeah.
Oh, that's gonna work.
Oh, that's pretty.
- That means the zombies are coming!
- Okay, you guys, they're coming!
- Time to nut up or shut up.
- You need a new line.
Let's kick some dicks.
Just because it rhymes
doesn't make it a great catchphase.
- What's her problem?
- I don't know. I like it when it rhymes.
- Here we go.
- Okay.
The zombies are coming!
- Oh, dear.
- Look out, guys!
- Here they come. They're coming!
- Battle stations!
Light them up!
Let's go, let's go!
Get up to safety.
Here we go.
Okay now, blow!
Come on. Now would be
an ideal time to blow.
- It's not working.
- Damn.
God.
Holy shit.
It worked.
Oh, my God.
- Okay. Here, now we mop up the stragglers.
- Okay. Yeah.
Oh, shit. Would those be
considered the stragglers?
Oh, boy.
Here they come.
Get ready.
Kill those motherfuckers!
Well, guys,
I hate to say this.
I think this might be
the end of the road.
- Come here.
- I love you guys.
- I love you more.
- We had a hell of a run.
Oh, my God.
They're gonna die.
Hey!
Sunday, Sunday, Sunday!
Thank God for rednecks!
- Need a ride?
- Oh, yeah.
- Get in.
- Let's go!
- Are y'all strapped in yet?
- Yep. Strapping in now.
Rule four.
Got it.
- You too.
- I'm not a pussy like Columbus.
Nothing personal.
- Oh, God!
- Seatbelts are there for a reason.
Yep.
I think I'm feeling
a little nauseous.
- Can somebody crack a window maybe?
- Oh, no, you don't.
Little Rock,
roll down the window.
If you get sick,
we all get sick.
Okay, okay.
Oh, God.
Could you just pull over so I can get
eaten by zombies? It'll be more comfortable.
Whoo!
- Oh, shit. Watch out!
- Do it!
Yee-ha!
- Oh, my God, you are sexy.
Can you not say "sexy"?
I'm already nauseous.
Shit.
Shit, shit, shit.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Shit.
- Oh, shit.
- You guys okay?
- Thank you for flying Big Fat Death.
- Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
I told you these things
were a huge rollover risk.
- We gotta move!
- Come on!
Hurry! Hurry!
They're coming!
- Oh, no!
- Come on! Here they come!
- Go, go, go!
- Shit.
- Come on!
- Oh, shit!
Come on!
- Shit!
Thank you.
- Yes!
- Here they come!
- Go, get in. Go, go, go!
- Go, go, go!
Run!
- I'm out of bullets!
- Guys, go! I'm right behind you!
Get in position! Form the gauntlet!
I'll hold them off!
Donkey Kong,
motherfuckers!
You can't write
the history of Zombieland
without telling the story
of one momentous day.
The day one free man
made the ultimate sacrifice
and paid respect to the Blackfoot ancestors
he may or may not have had.
The day he led the first, the last,
the only great American zombie jump.
Zombie Kill of the Year?
Century.
Only one problem.
Well, okay, two.
Oh!
- Tallahassee!
- Hang on, we're coming.
Hold on.
- Help! I'm falling!
- Shit!
We can't help you.
Guys! Help me!
- Shit. What should we do?
- Throw something at them.
Oh, shit. Okay.
Shit. Sorry.
You hit me in the nuts
with a hacky sack.
- Sorry.
- What?
I'm losing my grip.
I'm gonna fall.
No! Oh, no!
Long live the King.
- Oh.
- Ugh.
Guys, I'm still here!
- Give me your hand!
- Hold my arm.
- Kick your foot out.
- Goddamn it, Columbus!
- Point your toe!
- Human chain, this is a terrible idea!
- I can't reach.
- Kick it, kick it. I got it.
Pull, pull.
Okay. I got you.
Okay.
Oh, man.
Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- That was amazing.
Thank you.
Hey.
You kept the gun?
How could I give up my favourite
Christmas present?
Why didn't you
pull it out sooner?
I forget about it but...
I smoked a lot of weed.
Chip off the old block.
Yes.
Yes?
Oh, yes, yes?
Yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes?
- Yes. Yes.
- Yes?
- Really?
- Mm.
What changed your mind?
Because Zombieland or not,
we're meant to be together.
So basically, that means
this belongs to her.
Oh. Huh.
Cool.
Thank you.
Okay.
- Okay. Are you ready?
- Yeah.
- Okay. I'm good.
- Okay.
- Yeah, do the damn thing. Yeah.
Great.
- Which hand do I...?
- This one.
- Okay.
- Okay, yes. Here we go.
Wow.
Come here.
- Ah.
- Nicely done.
I'm gonna walk that little
spitfuck down the aisle.
It's a good thing
you didn't die, then.
Washoe County.
- What?
- Washoe County, Nevada.
Reno.
Biggest little city
in the world.
- Just go for it.
- Thank you.
- Sweet.
- Oh, my God.
What? What?
- Oh, my gosh!
- Shit!
- Homer. It's a long way down.
- Our work here is done.
Let's party.
- Come on!
- Yeah!
Wait for me.
Elvis' 1955 Fleetwood Series 60.
Every hair on my body feels
like a little wang.
- Yikes.
- Where to?
How about home?
Home?
- Yeah.
- Yes, good idea.
Where's home?
I think we're already there.
Because if our adventures had taught us
about anything, it was home.
Wichita didn't need to be afraid of it.
I didn't need to keep looking for it.
Because home isn't a place,
it's the people you're with.
I guess that's why they're called your homies.
And my homies are pretty fucking awesome.
So till next time,
this is Columbus, Ohio,
on behalf of Wichita, Little Rock,
Reno and Tallahassee,
saying hasta la vista,
baby.
That one's for you,
Flagstaff.
♪ Lord Almighty
I feel my temperature rising ♪
♪ Higher, higher
It's burning through to my soul ♪
Oh, hey.
Yeah, sorry. One more thing.
I'm actually feeling a little guilty
about what Nevada said.
You know, about Murraying
a certain you-know-who?
Yeah, my bad. I blew a hole through
the finest comic actor of our generation.
But I would love to make it up
to you, to all of you.
And for that, we gotta
go back to 2009.
Welcome, everyone, to the
Garfield 3: Flabby Tabby junket.
You'll each have five minutes.
Please keep your questions focused
on the film and don't go off-topic.
The idea of a trilogy was something...
As an artist, you think the great ones:
Godfather and...
Lethal Weapon.
But the question is,
why in the world Garfield 3?
- Can this be just between us?
- Yes.
Drugs cost money.
And I have to say, as an actor, how many
of your nine lives do you think you have left?
Well, I've done three of these.
Three Garfields.
So that's six.
The essence of Garfield,
I think...
Right.
...is the hairball.
Didn't I say? I had a feeling
this would come up.
Can you give me a hairball?
Don't wanna do the hairball,
get it out of the way?
- No.
- Can you try now?
- Give me a little hairball now?
- Come on.
Come on.
You know, how about
if I did it with you?
- Okay. Come on. Come on.
- That was close.
We'll do a selfie together.
Great. Great.
You all right, man?
All over the mike.
Can we get a baby wipe for Al?
Maybe move him back to his room, please?
Huge fan, Mr. Roker.
All right, Tim, let's get out of here.
Somebody get my car. I'm ready to go.
- I've never seen Al Roker behave that way.
- That was crazy.
Sometimes it feels like
it's you against the world.
- Oh, my God.
- I think it is.
Oh, dear.
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo.
Excuse me?
♪ Do what you like ♪
Nice.
Help me!
Bill Murray! I love some of
your films. Please help me!
I ain't afraid of no ghost.
I hate Mondays.
♪ Lord Almighty
I feel my temperature rising ♪
♪ Higher, higher
It's burning through to my soul ♪
♪ Girl, girl, girl
You're gonna set me on fire ♪
♪ My brain is flaming
I don't know which way to go ♪
♪ And your kisses lift me higher
Like a sweet song of the choir ♪
♪ And you light my morning sky
With your burning love ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh
I feel my temperature rising ♪
Yeah
♪ Well, help me, I'm flaming
I must be a hundred and nine ♪
♪ Burning, burning, burning
And nothing can cool me ♪
♪ I just might turn to smoke
But I feel fine ♪
♪ Because your kisses lift me higher
Like a sweet song of a choir ♪
♪ And you light my morning sky
With your burning love ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Burning love ♪
♪ It's coming closer
The flames are now reaching my body ♪
♪ Please won't you help me
I feel like I'm slipping away ♪
♪ It's hard to breathe
And my chest is a-heaving ♪
♪ Lord, have mercy
I'm burning a hole where I lay ♪
♪ 'Cause your kisses lift me higher
Like a sweet song of a choir ♪
♪ And you light my morning sky
With your burning love ♪
♪ Yeah, your burning love ♪
♪ Your burning love ♪
♪ I'm just a hunk,
a hunk of burning love ♪
♪ Just a hunk,
♪ I'm just a hunk,
a hunk of burning love ♪
♪ Just a hunk,
♪ Burning love ♪
♪ Yeah
Burning love ♪♪
Oh, pardon.
En español, it's like:
P... P...
Pardon my accent.