An ordinary university student, Kurono Kei...
...and Katou Masaru, who is working
to support his younger brother.
The two people who were childhood friends
coincidentally encountered each other again.
And then...
...they died.
The two who were supposed to be dead
woke up in an apartment...
...in which a black mysterious sphere
called GANTZ is placed.
In that room which they can't get out of,
they received a command from GANTZ.
"If you want to go back, go crush this guy."
That was... to battle with the aliens
who would invade the Earth...
An inescapable command.
They were then sent to a parallel world...
...and without knowing what was going on,
they battled with the aliens.
They barely got their victory.
What awaited Kurono and the others
when they returned to the room was...
...were the remarks that GANTZ gave them
for battling.
and the total points they got
for defeating the aliens.
If they get 100 points,
they can be released from this world,
or revive a beloved person of theirs.
It was a frightening reality.
They have their life all thrown out of order...
...while being able to return to normal life
when day comes.
People who were supposed to die...
Kurono, who came to terms with reality
while battling...
...and Katou,
who continued to deny this battle.
The tough and painful battle goes on anyway.
...and their friends died one by one.
And, in the end,
while facing the huge Goddess of Mercy,
even Katou's life was taken away.
When Kurono was about to give in to sadness,
Kojima Tae helped him stand on his feet
again with her honest feelings.
He swore in his heart that he would earn
100 points in order to revive Katou.
In a battle that sees no end,
he's determined to continue fighting.
Let's go!
"Thank you for the hard work.
I'm Yoshioka."
"Tomorrow, the studio has delayed
the schedule to an hour later,"
"so I will come to fetch you
at 8 o'clock tomorrow morning."
"It's 8 o'clock, so the time's later
than the previous schedule by an hour."
"That's all for now.
Thank you very much."
"At 10:29 p.m."
The message is over.
[Thank you for your hard work last night.]
[You got the first key.]
[There are four keys leading to the room.]
[The next person is this.]
[Yamamoto]
[Special trait: Intelligence]
[Favorite thing: Good students]
[5 months ago]
You mustn't die!
Sorry.
I love you.
I love you, Kurono-kun.
[Postscript concerning file #1-378930-s]
[Unexplained destruction]
[Acts of terrorism?]
[A 23-year-old woman disappears
right in her own house]
Confirmed several consecutive new cases
where several people go missing.
[New developments from the incident involving the disappearance
of the victims' bodies in the subway the other day]
[Confirmed existence]
"GANTZ - Perfect Answer"
Translated by yuizaki_libra@livejournal
Timed by ianne_xxyl
Soon it will be five months since the day
the National Museum was collapsed,
and yet the cause of the incident
still remains unknown.
According to the police, there's a possibility
that it's an act of terrorism.
- Is the burger done?
- Yes, coming.
I'll take this.
Please.
- Please help me with the tomatoes.
- Thanks.
Excuse me.
Oh, Kei-chan.
- How's your homework?
- I'm done.
You're not.
But it's so interesting, Tae-chan.
Hey, Koruhi is written based
on Kei-chan, right?
I didn't mean that...
Are you embarrassed?
Yeah. This manga is interesting, right?
She can even get
the Rookie of the Year award.
I'm nowhere near good yet.
I have to improve my skills.
You're good already.
I'm no good yet.
There are a lot of better people.
I said you're gonna be fine.
Ah~ I want to show this to Nii-chan too.
He's not coming back yet?
Oh, maybe a little more.
It's really because of his job, right?
Of course.
Oi, don't take your time in there.
Where is he really?
Ayumu-kun's brother.
Sorry.
I heard from Ayumu-kun that the
same thing happened before.
That time, his brother was arrested
by the police.
Katou's not that kind of person.
This.
The pay for this month.
I don't need it, really.
Well you see, you don't have to pay
for the rents here, right?
However, I want you to come to
this house for a while more.
Of course I will.
If I'm not with him,
he won't do his homework.
Ayumu is good at cooking anyway.
Well, I can't deny that.
Also...
If I come here,
I can see Kurono-kun too.
Wa-wait. Please don't keep quiet.
It was what I'm gonna draw just now.
I was thinking of how to
put in this particular romantic scene.
Well, I have to get going.
Eh?
I thought you were gonna stay?
Ah, someone just called me suddenly.
Kojima-san, you can just stay over.
Hold on a second.
Huh?
"The train will be coming to the first line soon."
"Since it's dangerous, please stand
behind the yellow line."
You were chosen too, weren't you?
You will not get used to it at first,
so feel free to just watch what we do.
Kobayashi-san is the same as you.
[It's completely up to me how
I want to use you people's lives.]
I'm sorry for startling you.
There's something I want to ask you,
so will you give me some of your time?
Since you abruptly announced your break from activities,
there have been many speculations going around, haven't there?
Rumors have it that it could be due to
your illness, marriage, pregnancy, or your move to overseas.
But I've dug up everything.
You're from the media?
The motive is unknown but there is an incredible
sequence of events that've been happening.
People who are supposed to die from accidents
have their bodies suddenly vanish from the scene.
The day just goes on as if nothing happened.
And then, for some reason,
that night, there will definitely be...
...some destruction
occurring somewhere in Tokyo.
Don't you know about this?
No.
Well then,
how about that rumor?
The rumor about the black sphere...
...and the room that contains it...
You know it, don't you?
Then, four.
You can ask me four questions.
Your aim.
Why are you all gathering at this place?
We're searching for the black ball.
Black ball?
If we have it,
we can go where we want.
You mean the room that contains
the black sphere?
You know it, huh.
Where did you hear about it?
I came here today to ask about that.
Where is that room?
It's not in this reality.
What do you mean?
You can't to go to that room
if it's not necessary.
Who are you people?
That's the fifth question.
Why are you chasing
after the same incident as I do?
Sixth one.
What do you want exactly?
If you want to know,
investigate this one more person
and come back here.
Why don't you go somewhere together
once in a while?
You and Kei-chan.
Focus.
Why? You two are dating, right?
We are not.
How come? You confessed to him, right?
Until your brother comes back, Kurono-kun...
Seems that
he can't think of any other thing.
But I'm fine.
When things calm down,
I'll try asking him once.
Seriously?
Seriously.
Ok! Homework.
[Total 94 points. 6 points until it's over]
It's gonna be soon, huh?
Yes.
Let me go!
Where's the heck is this place?
- Where am I?
- Please calm down.
Speaking of which, who are you people?
Who cares about that.
I was an office worker.
For the last 20 years, I have worked
for the company every day.
Well, I was dismissed because of
a restructure though.
I'm a nurse.
That's during the day.
At night, she's a hostess.
You lie about you age, right?
This auntie's still popular at this age.
Can you believe it?
He's women's enemy even during the day.
I'm a freeter. Right now, I'm working
part-time at a curry shop.
It's a small shop, but the food is delicious.
I'm a system engineer
at this company named Orient.
Please contact me if need be.
And, how about you?
I'm a hairdresser.
Kurono-san is really
a normal university student?
Since... you're really strong and everything.
He is, indeed.
Why are you so strong?
Because there's someone I want to revive.
GANTZ.
He was one of us before.
He fought with us.
Kurono-kun wants to revive him.
But... not only him.
I want to revive everyone who's died here.
And then, let us all be released from here
and become free together.
[Nakamura]
[Special trait: Noisy]
[Favorite thing: Jogging]
[You got the third key]
[One more left, and you can go back]
[The last key is this person.]
[Kojima Tae]
[Special trait: Weak]
[Favorite thing: Kurono-kun]
Did you come on time the other day?
Hmm? For what?
Your part-time job?
Part-time...? Oh, yeah I did.
Tough, isn't it?
It is. There is this person named Suzuki,
and for some reason she didn't turn up.
That's why the shop didn't have enough
people, so they just called me out.
What's wrong?
Kurono-kun, did something good happen?
There's something, right?
You can tell?
What? What?
Well actually, I was gonna tell Ayumu.
Katou is gonna come home soon.
Eh?
He's been contacting you?
Hm?
Katou asked me...
...to keep it from other people.
I see.
More importantly, there's some information
I want to give Kojima-san...
Well, "information" isn't exactly the word...
Wanna go to amusement park?
Let's go?
Just the two of us, once in a while.
You mean... that time I confessed to you?
That was...
I told you it was
just at the surge of the moment.
Please forget about it.
How can I forget it?
Hey, let's go.
Impossible, impossible.
Absolutely impossible.
I have acrophobia.
I can't handle the ferris wheel
or roller coaster at all...
Look.
You even drew it in your sketchbook, right?
The scene at the amusement park?
Maybe if you go there, it can become
your source to draw manga.
Then...
There's one condition.
What is it?
Please start calling me
by my first name from now on.
Eh?
Call me now.
Please.
Well, that's a little...
Maybe now is not the right time.
The next time we meet,
I'll call you that, ok?
I'll definitely call you that when we
met at the amusement park.
Yes.
Definitely.
See you.
Welcome back, Kei-chan.
How are you alive?
GANTZ did something?
You don't remember?
How many people are there?
Eight people, including me.
Recently, we got three more people.
GANTZ...
I want to put an end to it.
How?
You don't know?
There's a ball this big.
No idea.
I'll come again.
If you know something, tell me.
GANTZ, show me people who've died.
What's the matter?
Katou was revived.
Eh? How come?
Well, I don't know about that.
But look, he's still in here.
What is going on?
[Katou]
Who...
Nii-chan?
What?
Um...
I'm Kojima, Kurono-kun's classmate
at the college.
Ayumu-kun, come see him.
Ayumu-kun?
What's so important that you
even neglect your younger brother?
It's because you have work to do, right?
I'm asking you, Nii-chan.
Because I have work.
Really?
Really.
Oh, yeah?
Should I go back?
There are things you can't talk
when I'm here, so...
I'm taking my leave.
I'm glad for you, Ayumu-kun.
[Welcome back, Nii-chan]
I memorized how to make it
when you weren't home.
Try it.
You're the first person I made it for.
This is Kojima.
Erm, Ayumu-kun's brother
came home earlier.
And also, there's something I want to ask...
About the amusement park, Ayumu-kun
and his brother are coming too...
That's why, it won't be a date.
I want to see you.
Can I go to your workplace right now?
[Kojima Tae]
Ayukawa Eriko's started to make her move.
At Kita, Senzoku.
"A new morning has come"
"It's a morning of hope"
This will repeat many times over.
I stopped this after my child was born.
I have to get released soon for
the sake of my family.
What's the matter?
[Your lives have been taken away.]
[If you want to go back, go crush this guy.]
[Alien dressed in black]
[Special trait: looking normal at first glance]
[Favorite thing: black ball]
Let's go.
[Please go.]
Where's this place?
A train?
Something is fishy.
Hey, you...
Have we ever met long before?
It moved.
It's the subway!
What?
The subway?
Everyone, don't space out.
"The train will be departing soon."
There are people here.
This has never happened before, right?
Take care of the front part of the train.
Ayukawa Eriko?
She's riding the train by herself?
Everyone, we are not
a suspicious group of people.
We are not doing anything to harm you either.
What? Is it like an event or something?
Kurono-san!
Don't shoot!
Don't drag others into this!
Can you hear people screaming?
It smells weird too.
What the? What's going on?
Isn't this dangerous?
Takahashi!
You guys are so amazing.
Damn it.
I remember...
I remember!
I remember.
I've done the same thing before.
What?
The two who were in the room before,
Nakamura-san and Kobayashi-san too.
Eh?
Stop! It's dangerous here!
Out of the way!
Come.
Kurono Kei.
Kurono-kun?
Run away from here.
Wait.
Sorry.
Stop it!
You're heavy. Move aside.
I'm covering for you.
She's tough.
Yeah.
This is revenge.
You people were the ones
who started this first.
You people have killed
so many of my friends.
I'll never forgive you-
Everyone's safe, right?
Auntie isn't here.
[Well then, let's see the points]
Hold on a second.
Oi!
[Well then, let's see the points]
[Takahashi]
[0 point. Total 88 points]
What the heck is this?
Oi.
I told you Auntie isn't here.
Auntie isn't here!
[Good work. You got the first key.]
[Kobayashi]
[The second key]
[Yamamoto]
[You got the second key.]
"You know it, don't you?"
"The black sphere...
and the room that contains it."
Black sphere?
Room?
GANTZ!
[It totally depends on me how to use your life]
[That's on theory.]
This is revenge.
You people killed my friends.
[Sakurai]
[0 point. Total 69 points]
Auntie's here, isn't she?
That's her, right?
Is this for real?
Isn't that Ayukawa?
Ayukawa... Eriko?
You finally came, huh?
Yes.
Seems so.
[Well then, let's continue with the points]
Everyone, please be careful.
This woman... was the one who killed me.
Long time no see, Kobayashi-san.
Huh?
Kobayashi-san,
don't you remember this room?
You don't remember me?
Huh? What?
[Kobayashi]
[0 point. Totally doesn't remember a thing]
Two years ago...
I fought while protecting you.
[Nakamura]
[0 point]
Yamamoto, Ayukawa, you, and I...
We defeated these aliens dressed in black...
...two years ago in Shibuya.
[Yamamoto]
[11 points]
And then, everyone could stop doing this.
We had our memory erased...
and were set free.
Ah...
Yes.
So if we get 100 points,
we can really be released, huh?
[Suzuki]
[17 points. Total 101 points]
100 points.
"Breaking news. There is
an emergency going on currently."
"An accident occurred at the subway,
causing 84 people to die and 260 people injured."
"A group of people bearing weapons
were seen on the train."
"The cause is also unknown this time."
[100 points menu]
[1. Erase all your memory and get released]
[2. Return the person you love to life]
That means you'll be released.
Suzuki-san, with this, you'll be a free man.
I'll choose the second option.
[2. Return the person you love to life]
I'm sorry.
First of all, let's revive Katou-kun.
No...
But, he...
I was... killed by him.
"This is revenge. You people killed my friends."
He said that and killed me.
That's the same thing
as what the girl said earlier.
Then... this Katou is?
Let's confirm it.
GANTZ.
Please revive Katou Masaru-kun.
Eh? That's it?
Kei-chan.
Where's the alien?
Katou.
Katou!
Oi GANTZ. Hurry up!
You mustn't die.
I'll wait for you.
I'll go first and wait for...
Kei-chan.
What about the alien?
What happened to it?
Was I... dead?
Was I alive?
I'm alive, and I can go back.
Suzuki-san used his points to revive you.
It's nothing. Well, it's been
my objective from the beginning...
...to get 100 points and revive Katou-kun.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much!
Ah, it's nothing.
Anyway, with this,
we've made it clear, right?
Yes.
The other guy is an alien.
We will avenge you.
I have obtained the key to that room.
[Kurono]
[21 points. Total 115 points]
More than 100 points.
GANTZ, I choose number 2.
[100 points menu]
[1. Erase all your memory and get released]
[2. Return the person you love to life]
The person I want to revive is...
Huh?
I have you revived.
I was dead?
Yeah.
That's so uncool!
Right now, you're important to us.
Now, explain to us.
Something strange is happening to GANTZ.
You guys...
Long time no see.
You're still doing this, huh?
Why are you here?
We were summoned by GANTZ.
A black ball was sent to my place.
Ex-members like us
were brought back here.
That's not the only thing.
There were people who were dragged into
the mission and got killed.
This has never happened before.
Say,
what's going on now?
How long have I been dead?
Five months.
It's gathering people because of this?
What is it?
Oi, spill it.
GANTZ runs using battery.
Huh?
This thing runs using battery?
From what I observe,
even though this is just a guess...
GANTZ moves by sucking his energy.
That's why, if this bald-headed guy
wakes up,
it's also the end of GANTZ.
If GANTZ dies, what will happen to us?
That is...
Right?
Extermination... perhaps.
We, who were revived by GANTZ...
...will also disappear together with it.
What the heck is that?
Maybe GANTZ is rushing too.
Before its lifetime ends, it wants
to defeat all the aliens.
That's why it summoned us
ex-members here.
I see what you mean.
So it's like homecoming, huh?
Perhaps...
...the archrival still remains.
The Last Boss, that is.
Don't tell me...
...that is...?
Today I met an alien who appeared
in the form of your body.
Eh?
The one who killed me is also...
...that guy.
He's an alien.
There it goes again.
"A new morning has come"
"It's a morning of hope"
"Open your heart with joy"
Today's mission just ended though.
"Look up to the blue sky"
"Listen to the radio"
"Take a deep breath"
"And take in the fragrance
of the wind"
"And then - one, two, three"
[Emergency mission]
[Go crush this person]
[Kojima Tae]
[Special trait: Weak]
[Favorite thing: Kurono-kun]
What the heck?
An ordinary girl?
Wait, look...
Her favorite thing is...
What the heck is this?
Why is she the target?
Shouldn't it be that fake Katou?
[People who crushed her will get 100 points.]
[The others will have their points taken away.]
This girl is...
Kojima Tae is not an alien.
That's why...
...please don't kill her.
Please.
She may look like that, but
she might actually be an alien.
That's not true!
The last person who appeared
on the black ball...
...was this girl.
So that means... she's also
an ex-member of the group?
No. I've never seen her.
Then... she's really an alien?
Hang on.
Where is that ball now?
The one who killed me...
So it's with that Katou alien, huh?
Isn't that bad?
Maybe he already killed
Kojima Tae before us.
The ones who hold the ball
can be transmitted around.
Seriously?
GANTZ wants to prevent that, right?
Anyway...
...if it's GANTZ's order, we just have to do it.
If I can get 100 points by killing
this one girl,
I'll kill Kojima Tae.
GANTZ.
Transmit me first.
Kei-chan.
I'll go to Kojima-san.
You go to Ayumu's place.
Sorry. I'll see you later.
Be careful.
Wait.
You intend to protect her?
I want to revive Auntie.
That's why...
...I have to gain more points.
Stop it!
Transmit me quickly.
GANTZ!
My house?
I will explain everything to you later.
Right now, let's run away together.
Um, what happened in the subway earlier...
It didn't make any sense at all.
But I believe...
I believe you, Kurono-kun.
This way!
Wasn't that Ayumu-kun's brother?
It wasn't him!
Urgent! Urgent! Calling headquarters.
Found one suspect just now.
The suspect is heading
towards the north direction.
The suspect is a man who possesses
a weapon and is chasing after someone else.
Quickly send more backups to the subway.
"Roger."
Found you.
Kurono-kun.
Let's stop this.
If GANTZ dies,
everyone will be exterminated.
Doing this to another human being
is just strange.
Though you can kill so many aliens?
Suzuki-san.
Since I'm thrown into this,
before GANTZ comes to an end,
I will get 100 points one more time.
Nice.
Kurono-san.
Run away.
If you move, we'll shoot.
No, you won't.
Suzuki-san too!
Me too?
They're shooting!
Please go first.
I will block them.
Sakurai-kun!
They won't get any points killing me.
Hurry up! I'll catch up with you later.
Thanks.
I'll aim at him for real.
Let's go.
[Katou]
Ayumu.
Ayumu!
Ayumu...
Calling headquarters.
Right now, the suspect is heading further
to the north direction.
I'm chasing after him.
It's me, Kei-chan.
By any chance...
...he is...?
Suzuki-san.
The two of you, please get as far away
from Tokyo as you can.
Hurry up!
I don't want to go!
I want to be with you, Kurono-kun.
Tae-chan.
I will definitely come pick you up later.
Let's go.
Let's make sure...
...we go to the amusement park.
This way!
Don't... get in my way.
You came to take revenge?
Why did you... have to kill Ayumu?
You also killed your father.
Give Ayumu back!
Someone who killed his father like you...
...can get angry when your brother is killed?
Because of those emotions...
you killed your father.
That was to save Ayumu.
It couldn't be helped!
It couldn't be helped?
That's forever your excuse.
You always make that excuse...
and run away from everything.
Katou!
Kei-chan.
Please tell me.
What's happening to Kurono-kun?
It's hard to explain, but...
He's fighting...
...to protect you.
For... my sake?
He might... even die.
I'm sorry.
My wife passed away.
I want to get her back.
I have to gain enough points before GANTZ is over.
Please run away.
If not, I will have to shoot you.
Kurono-kun will definitely come to pick you up.
It doesn't work on him at all.
This way!
You're in the way. Move aside!
I give up!
Let's stop.
Let's stop here.
Okay?
What are you shooting?
But...
...he-
[Kojima Tae]
someone saying something
the same someone saying something again
Oi.
Oi!
Oi!!
You want to know why I killed your brother?
This is revenge.
You people did the same thing to me.
We tasted the same hatred...
...and sorrow.
Like me, you people are...
...not fighting for anyone's sake,
Nor are you protecting anyone.
You're just...
...being controlled by that black sphere.
Katou.
Kurono-kun!
No way...
Kurono-kun.
I got you.
Tae-chan.
Let's go home.
You mustn't...
You mustn't die.
Kei-chan.
So you're saying that I should keep...
...fighting until forever?
That's why, you...
...made Tae-chan your target?
You can go to that room using it, right?
Hand the ball to me.
[Mission cleared.]
[Damn it Damn it Damn it]
[Someone, crush the alien in this room]
In here?
Not here.
The ones who were supposed
to have been killed by the alien earlier are...
We finally found you.
It is you who wished to start this fight.
[Start]
I understand now, GANTZ.
[Choose]
Kei-chan.
How about the aliens?
I don't think all of them have died.
That's great.
That's great?
Because we have to get more points.
What do humans fight for?
What do you people fight for?
For the sake of my loved ones.
When are you gonna keep fighting until?
Until... I can revive my wife.
Stop it.
I have to live.
I...
People in this world are longing to see me.
You're kidding, right?
GANTZ.
Stop it.
Shoot.
I can't stop this fight with you people.
Shoot!
Stop...
...already
Let's... stop this.
Why?
There's no way but to kill him.
Kei-chan.
[Well then, let's see the points]
[Kurono]
[Full points]
[Please choose from the "full points" menu.]
[Full points menu~]
[Forever...]
Oi! What's next?
What is it?
GANTZ is...
...over?
With this...
...no one will be revived.
Neither will us.
No.
There's still... a way out.
Kei-chan.
GANTZ...
...has decided already.
[Kurono-kun]
[Thank you]
Kei-chan?
What did you do?
Everything will end.
No one will be summoned here anymore.
You've gotta be kidding me!
What did you do?
Katou.
Thank you so much...
...for remembering our childhood together.
I...
...was really happy.
But...
...from now on, forget about me.
How can I forget?
How can I forget??
Katou.
Take good care of Ayumu.
We're going back together!
Together!
Kei-chan!
Thank you very much.
Wanna buy something?
- Yeah, buy me a map.
- Okay.
- I'll take them.
- Oh, thanks.
Map, huh?
Welcome.
"Ayukawa Eriko-san returned to
the entertainment industry"
It's confirmed that all of the members
present in your list are existent.
Please take some time off for yourself.
We will handle the investigation.
I saw them.
I saw those guys with my own eyes.
That room too.
I was just so close.
I'm made breakfast,
so you will do the cleaning.
Okay, hurry up.
Quickly put the mattress away.
Huh?
Well, just that... it feels as if
I haven't seen you for a long time.
You're so strange.
I have... always wanted to do this.
I...
...won't go anywhere anymore.
I know that already, so go to work.
Who... gave me this again?
"Draw the Ferris wheel here"
"To Tae-chan"
"I love you. Kurono Kei"
Kurono... Kei?
[Everyone, please be happy]