(WOMAN SCREAMING)
(CREATURE SCREECHES)
(EPIC MUSIC PLAYING)
MALE NARRATOR: The known universe,
with its heroes and marvels,
but what of the darkness?
In our modern world,
this is where monsters dwell,
alongside those who hunt
and slaughter them with pride.
None more prolific
than the Bloodstone family,
whose patriarch has long controlled
the powerful supernatural relic,
the Bloodstone, a weapon unlike any other.
But now, this weapon
is in want of a new master,
for Ulysses Bloodstone has died.
Tonight is his funeral.
Hunters have gathered
from around the globe,
strangers until this night,
for a ceremonial hunt which will decide
who next will wield the Bloodstone.
And woe to the monster
who finds itself among them.
(ENTHRALLING MUSIC PLAYING)
(OLDIES POP MUSIC
PLAYING ON RECORD)
Elsa's here.
JOSHUA: It's a beauty, innit?
Fifty-seven confirmed kills myself.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
Next year's my 30th season.
I can almost smell
the blood on your hands.
Thank you.
I like your whole look here
with the makeup.
It's a killer trademark.
Yeah. It's to honor my ancestors.
Yeah. Not much for honoring ancestors
and feelings and all that.
I just know it looks brilliant on you.
I mean, I understand the importance
of anonymity in our line of work,
but it gets lonely.
Just want to say I'm proud
to be honoring old Ulysses
with you here tonight.
Ulysses. Of course.
Hard to believe he's gone.
Aye, the mad bastard.
Quite a place
he built for himself here, eh?
So, any of these hacked beasties
your handiwork?
JACK: No.
No, but... But him.
Him, I fought a few times.
He's never looked so alive.
(CHUCKLES)
Elsa, after 20 years,
I hope you didn't feel obligated to come.
God knows the others won't like it.
How long can we expect you to stay?
Give me what's mine, I'll leave now.
What aspect of Bloodstone
are we after exactly?
The strength it lends, the protection?
Longevity...
Verussa, what I do with it
after I've earned it
will be none of your business.
To be honest, that might be the best part.
(CHUCKLES)
I wonder if you're up to it.
All these years without training...
Without his training.
Let's find out together.
Hmm...
You were so promising growing up.
We all believed
you would surpass your father.
Instead, you seem satisfied
to emulate your mother.
I did what I could with you.
Shame I didn't turn out.
Don't be too easy on yourself.
You were
the greatest disappointment of his life.
Over 200 kills, collectively.
Twenty-six for you.
Thirty-seven kills.
Forty-three.
An impressive 57.
And over 100 deaths, give or take.
Over 100?
Yeah.
So many death dealers in one room.
Oh, my dear heart!
(SCRAPING)
Thank you for gathering in ritual,
for shedding your masks tonight
in honor of Ulysses Bloodstone.
He was a leader,
a friend,
a lover without equal.
Knowing his spirit would not be
with us tonight
to state his wishes
for the ceremonial hunt,
he orchestrated his presence
in other ways.
(LAUGHS)
Incorrigible, really.
(MACHINERY CRANKING)
I do hope my attendance delights you.
Thank you, Verussa, for seeing it through
and for shaping our cause like no other.
Oh!
With my passing,
it is now time to choose a new leader
in the crusade against monsters.
This honor can only be bestowed upon
the strongest
and most committed to our mission.
Very soon, a monster
unlike anything you've faced
will be released
into these sacred grounds.
The hunter who slays this beast
will become our new leader,
taking possession of my Bloodstone.
Good luck.
I'll be rotting for you.
- (CHUCKLES)
- (VERUSSA LAUGHS)
Oh, forgive me. Graveyard humor.
There is only one Bloodstone,
and it can have only one keeper.
It was to be his daughter's,
but through decades of absence,
Elsa has long forsaken that birthright.
The only weapons permitted tonight
have been placed throughout the garden
for you to find.
Per my husband's wishes,
the stone will be affixed
to the monster's hide.
This will weaken it.
It will also make it angry.
Hang on.
The stone's finally up for grabs
and we all earned the right to hunt,
but she gets to crash this thing
like it's a backyard wedding?
He brings up a good point.
Where's the lovely lady's medallion?
Have you checked up your own arse?
Elsa is welcome to join.
And like the rest of you, she's fair game.
No special treatment.
Those who do not survive
will be honored appropriately.
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
For tonight,
it is every hunter for themselves.
Ya lucky bastard.
VERUSSA: You shall go first.
The others will follow.
MAN 1: Right there, come on.
- (MAN 1 YELLS)
- (MONSTER GROWLING)
(MAN 1 GROANING)
(MONSTER ROARS)
MAN 1: Put her out, put her out!
MAN 2: Let's move.
MAN 1: Close the gates.
(MONSTER ROARS)
I'd say the stone was in place.
Off you go.
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
And now, we pledge.
We spill all blood for the hunt.
ALL: For stone and creed,
for those who forged our blade.
To rid this land of its abominations.
ALL: There is no peace without blood,
and so it shall be.
And so it shall be.
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC PLAYING IN DISTANCE)
(MUSIC STOPS)
I suggest we just pass each other by.
What?
(JOSHUA GRUNTS)
(ELSA GRUNTS)
The stone is mine!
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(ELSA CHUCKLES)
Death is coming for you, lassie!
(MONSTER SNARLS)
(EXHALES)
(RUSTLING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
- (GRUNTS)
- (YELLING)
(GROANING)
- (GRUNTS)
(ELSA YELLS)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
(CHOKING)
(CHUCKLES)
(MONSTER ROARS)
(MONSTER SNARLS)
(GASPS AND LAUGHS)
Hey. Hey. What's up?
Well, of course I was gonna come find you.
Of course. Are you okay?
(MONSTER SNARLS)
You keep saying
that you're gonna be careful each time,
and here we go again.
You can't keep counting on me to save you.
This is the last time.
(MONSTER GRUNTS)
I know. Does it hurt?
- (MONSTER GRUNTS)
- It's weakening you, right?
Yeah, they said that
the stone would do that.
Don't worry, I have a plan.
Look, so apparently,
these little things explode.
So, we're gonna
explode our way out of here.
All you have to do is don't die.
Don't... Just keep alive.
I'm gonna figure out where to put this,
and I'll come get you.
- I'll find you. I don't know.
- (MONSTER GROWLS)
- (SNARLS)
- (GRUNTS)
No, no, no, don't close the...
Door.
(SIGHS)
Well, that's great.
(GRUNTING)
How's your night going?
Well, it's going.
Difficult.
You hurt?
- Can I help you?
- No.
Okay.
But it's bleeding a lot.
It has to be tight and even.
Wow, thank you for that.
Me, I have to get out of here.
Oh, and you think I don't?
I came to get the stone
'cause I want to be rid of my dad,
my stepmother, all of this for good.
Now, I'm stuck in here with some...
Oh, that's tight.
Can I take a look?
It has to be done right,
because if not, it's not gonna work.
You didn't want to fight before either,
did you, running into me?
Then that maniac with the axe,
hell, you didn't fight.
I'm having a hard time believing
you hunted and killed monsters.
Well, I'm not that type of hunter.
At least
not like those esbirros out there.
Yeah, well, neither am I.
No? It's not in your DNA then?
If you're not a hunter,
why do you want the stone?
I don't.
That's not the reason why I'm here.
You know, maybe we can help each other.
If you help me
get the monster out of here alive,
I can get you the stone.
Right, yeah. 'Cause you'll just have
a quick chat with him,
sort it out 'cause you're, what,
the monster's friend?
(SCOFFS)
(GROANS)
So, you don't wanna be
like your father, then?
Careful.
I understand. It must be complicated
to grow up with this family.
You have no idea about my family, none.
I don't.
I can tell you my family was different.
But all families have something in common.
They follow us.
For good, for bad.
They stay, like they become an atmosphere.
And sometimes, we think that
by doing something very specific,
we can change everything,
and not be like them.
(MONSTER ROARS)
Or sometimes,
they're just a pain in the ass
that we have to save all the time.
I don't know.
It's complicated.
We could die here.
You and I, with your family.
It's an option.
It's not my choice, but it's an option.
(GRUNTS)
JACK: What are you doing?
ELSA: When I was a kid,
my dad used to tell me stories
about my crazy Aunt Frances.
He said that if I misbehaved,
she would unlock her tomb
and come out and pull me back in there
with her for company.
She was positive that she'd come back
from the dead at some point, and she knew
that when she did, she'd need...
That's not bad.
Ooh!
...an exit strategy.
Well done, Elsa.
My name is Jack, by the way.
Okay, Jack, you blow the wall,
I'll get him to you.
Okay, I trust you. I'm trusting you, okay?
Just get me the stone and we're good.
Then you're on your own.
Okay. Closest perimeter wall is that way,
straight shot, then two lefts and a right.
There's a massive crack
about halfway down.
As soon as you get there,
turn on the explosive.
Throw it at the wall, then get clear.
Okay.
And, Jack, cross me
and I'll kill you both.
Okay.
Hey, when you run into him, just...
Just treat him like an old friend.
Call him by his name.
Which is?
Ted. He's called Ted.
Ted?
Yeah.
How do you turn this on?
Because I've been trying...
(BEEPING)
No.
(TED SNARLS)
Hey!
(JOSHUA SCREAMING)
(SHUDDERS)
(ROARS)
Ted?
(TED GRUNTS SOFTLY)
You have a lovely name.
And your friend is waiting for you.
(PANTING)
(DEVICE BEEPING)
(DEVICE BEEPING RAPIDLY)
No!
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
Wait!
(SNARLS)
(TED ROARS)
(CHUCKLES)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS SOFTLY)
Well, now, look at this.
The Bloodstone did this to you?
He grabbed it and it threw him back.
My word.
A monster.
Masquerading as one of our own.
Desecrating a sacred night.
(GROANS)
And you? What was the thinking here?
You freed a monster with a monster?
I didn't know that bit.
Well,
I can't wait to find out
what breed of evil you are.
None of you should have the stone.
The hunt decides!
- (CRACKLES)
- (GROANS)
House rules.
No. No, no, no, no...
(SIGHS) No.
Elsa?
Elsa. Are you okay?
Until you rip my throat out,
I suppose I'm fine.
I... am sorry.
I couldn't tell you, you know.
It wasn't safe.
What, did you think it might
cloud my judgment a bit?
Yeah, I know, I'm an idiot. I know.
But I'm also a human.
Perhaps not in the category
that you would call a human a human.
You see, I've got systems
to manage the hurt I could cause...
I don't care about your systems.
Just stay away from me until you can't.
But they work. You'd be surprised.
They actually work.
'Cause I'm not like that.
I'm like this, you know. I'm...
I would never hurt you
or hurt any one of them.
And any hunting that I do is done
by a part of me that is not me.
And that's not the part
you're with right now.
So you got nothing to worry about.
Because I lock myself in once a month,
every full moon.
That's it.
And the next full moon is in five days.
We have plenty of time
to figure something out.
You don't get it, mate.
Why do you think they put me
in here with you?
Five days?
The Bloodstone's capable
of transforming you in five seconds.
Thanks in advance for making it quick.
No, no.
I shouldn't have asked for your help.
Yeah, well, I shouldn't have needed yours.
- This is gonna be really bad.
- Bloody stupid. (SNIFFLES)
(FOOTSTEPS THUMPING IN DISTANCE)
Okay, okay.
So, if this is gonna happen,
I need you to look at me. Okay?
Do not break eye contact, no matter what.
What are you talking about?
What are you doing? What the...
Get...
And this is what?
I need to remember you. (SNIFFING)
Well, does it work?
Once...
I'm asking you, please.
Please don't do this.
Not this way.
Just kill me as I am.
Otherwise there will be no mercy,
I promise.
Mercy?
This may surprise you,
our whole mission is built
on mercy for you,
and those like you,
as well as
all the innocent lives you take.
You'll wanna see this, darling.
Your father died convinced
you'd never come home. I lived in hope.
I wonder how he'd feel
about you hunting me.
Better than he'd feel about your betrayal.
But once this is over,
you'll notice my hands are clean.
His? Mmm, not so much.
It's time for you to show yourself.
(CHANTING IN LATIN)
I'm sorry, Elsa.
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
(GROANING)
(GROANS)
(GASPS)
(JACK GROANS)
(LIMBS CRUNCHING)
(JACK GROWLING)
(JACK ROARS)
(GROWLING SOFTLY)
(SCREAMS)
- (GUARDS CLAMORING)
- (SCREAMING)
My hand!
He won't let go! He won't let go!
He's pulling me in!
GUARD: Get him!
(JACK ROARING AS WEREWOLF)
(SNARLING)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(SCREAMS)
(ROARING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING)
(GUARD GROANS)
(GROANS)
- (ROARS)
- (GUARD GROANS)
(GROANING)
No! No, no, no!
(SCREAMING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(JACK AS WEREWOLF SNARLS)
(YELLING)
- (GRUNTS)
- (SCREAMS)
(PANTING)
(JACK SNARLS SOFTLY AS WEREWOLF)
Jack, you still in there?
(ROARS)
(GASPING SOFTLY)
- (SNARLS SOFTLY)
- (SHUDDERING)
(SHUDDERS)
Elsa! You let him go!
You will now die, as you lived,
a disgrace to your father's memory,
and the hallowed Bloodstone name!
(GLASS SHATTERS)
(GASPING)
(SCREAMING)
(TED ROARS SOFTLY)
He went that way.
(GROWLS SOFTLY)
There you are, mistress.
I only wanted to
make myself available to you.
Brilliant. You can start
clearing all this shit up.
(SOMEWHERE OVER THE RAINBOW
BY JUDY GARLAND PLAYING)
(GRUNTS)
(SOMEWHERE OVER THE RAINBOW
CONTINUES PLAYING)
(TED GROWLS SOFTLY)
(JACK GROANS SOFTLY)
- (GROWLS SOFTLY)
- Oh, yeah, thanks, Ted.
Thanks, man.
Is she okay?
(GROWLS SOFTLY)
Good. That's good.
(LAUGHS)
What? No.
No, I'm the one who comes to your rescue.
What are you talkin' about?
Whatever. No.
(GROWLS SOFTLY)
Man, I cannot think of food
right now. I'm...
Let's do sushi. I owe you that. Yes.
Yeah, you choose. Yeah.