A WONDERFUL LOVE STORY
Okay. We're going to film
my cousin Koldo,
who I’m sure is a little nervous.
Auntie!
Koldo? Koldo?
- Congratulations
- Thanks.
Cousin!
Hey!
- What's up, Cousin?
- How are you?
- Great. What about you?
- Well... Can't you tell?
You're great! You look great!
And no rice...
No, don't throw rice.
The girl wants rose petals.
- How refined
- Come on, give us a hand!
- Koldo! Koldito!
- Hey!
What are you doing lurking
around here?
Hey, do you remember
my cousin Adrián?
Of course I do. But the last time
I saw you, you were only knee high.
Hey, if you film any good-looking girls,
tell me, okay?
Speaking of the devil...
ls Natalie coming?
But aren’t you even going to
give it a rest on my wedding day?
- But is she coming or not?
- She's already inside.
Perfect!
Hey, who.... Who's Natalie?
Natalié, Natalié...
Ales enfants de la patrie.
Let's see. Look over there Okay...
Look, the wedding video man!
Nice equipment!
Hey, what's this for?
That's for stabilising the image and
creating cinema-quality movements.
Otherwise, with all this stuff on your
shoulder, the picture is unwatchable.
Do they shoot films with this, too?
Here, some of them
In America, all of them
All of them?
Look, look, look, look.
Cinema quality.
And what about your camera, kid?
This one's got high-definition HD
with megapixels.
With megapixels?
Hey, can you do me a favour?
Could you get some shots inside,
being as how you’re family?
Yeah, I’m going to film everything,
no worries.
Film what the naked eye wouldn't see.
Dziga Vertov, Cinema verité...
Yeah, of course.
I swear to God I’ll film everything.
- What's your name, sunshine?
- Adrián. And you?
- Atún.
- Okay. Pleased to meet you
Tita, put your cardigan on,
we're going.
See you later, Estela.
- Have you got your keys?
- Yes, dear, don’t worry
And where’s Clara?
Well, she's not upstairs
I don’t know
- What do you mean, she's not upstairs?
- No.
Go and look for your sister
in the kitchen.
No, this way
And put that camera away!
Oh...
Clara! Clara!
Clara, we're leaving!
Are you all right?
Tita, switch off the camera.
I’ve got something to tell you.
I think..
Bye!
Here's Koldo with uncle Pepe Víctor.
Let's see what he’s got to say.
He's always stirring it.
Clara's great. If you change your mind,
I’ll divorce your aunt...
- ...and steal her from you.
- What are you talking about!
Well, that's great, Uncle.
Viva Valencia!
- Víctor, Pepe Víctor!
- I’m coming, Amparín, I’m coming!
Hey, Uncle, what happened
to your hand?
Don't say anything to your aunt.
A dog in the clinic...
- It looked like it was dead...
- What happened?
And it woke up and bam!
He just made a right mess of it
- You mean it bit you?
- Yeah, but don’t worry, I’m..
- Are you all right?
- Can't you tell? Eh?
- Come on! Pepe Víctor, let's go!
- I’ve got a little something for you.
- I’ll come and find you later, okay?
- Yeah, yeah...
Give it to me.
I like filming.
Yeah...
Well, she's a bit nervous, of course.
But she's really beautiful.
You should see her.
All right.
She's coming. Come on, she's on her way
Everybody inside!
Come on, Koldo. Chin up!
Be brave!
Come on, get inside!
- Come on, inside!
- Come on, get moving!
- Where is he? Where's my father?
- Your father’s inside.
- With Mónica, Óscar and the kids.
- Okay, okay, come on...
Come on. Come on, let's go!
Everybody inside!
Go get'em!
At the back!
Come on, let's get inside
- Do you want one, Adri?
- No. No, thanks.
Rafa!
Hey! The boys are here!
Ha ha!
And the fool who's getting married?
Where's he got to, mate?
He's inside.
Where do you think?
Hey, kid!
Hey Rafita...
So good-looking...
Hey Charly! Inside!
Give us a hug!
There... Jumangi!
You're gorgeous!
And so, as you wish to enter
into matrimony, join hands...
Clara, take this ring, as a sign of
my love and my fidelity to you...
Koldo, take this ring, as a sign of
Oh...
You've been tangled up with me
for years in my hands, my hair,
in my head...
And I can't do it any more
I can't do it any more
I should be tired of
your hands, your hair
your strange ways
but I want more
I want more.
I can't live without you.
There's no way
I can’t be with out you.
No way, oh...
You're gorgeous!
Long live the happy couple!
Viva!
Well done, son!
Photo!
And now the family!
Uncle, Uncle, Uncle...
Granddad, how are you?
How are you?
- Okay, so you're going...
- Are you happy?
Oh, yes!
Your hearing aid!
Can you hear me?
Granddad!
Are you hearing?
Can I have your attention, please?
The buses for the reception are
behind the church.
So, there's room for everyone,
but little by little.
Let's not all get there at once,
okay?
Okay, thanks.
Look at them!
You're going to look so cute!
Have you seen your brother?
Hey, kid, have you seen your brother?
The kid's just got married
and he's already sneaking off?
Unbelievable!
There's such a lot of people here!
Well, we're at the reception,
in this marvellous place...
This must have cost them a fortune!
Hi, beautiful.
How are you?
- No alcohol?
- No, it's alcohol free.
- No alcohol.
- What is it?
- Piña colada.
- Piña colada? I’ll have one!
- He knows it!
- I’ll have one!
- All right!
Mother and daughter!
Well, the mother's bit of a MILF,
isn't she?
- Granddad?
- Yes?
- They said it was going to rain, eh?
- Yes. When I went to school...
That hasn’t got much to do
with anything, but yeah..
I missed...
I was saying how pretty your mother
is... but you..
- Yeah, come on...
- It's getting better...
Bye.
Atún!
Cinema quality, mate!
There, there...
That guy's really good!
It has to be edited...
with a touch of fresco,
a touch of Renoir...
a pinch of cinema verité...
Yeah, yeah, right...
- Very down to earth, very online.
- Online?
Uncle... are you all right?
- Yes.
- Yeah?
Look at the love birds
- I’m really happy, very happy.
- Me too.
No. What you are is really pretty.
- I want to tell you something.
- Oh, yeah, right. Sorry.
But you’re so pretty...
I mean, you're usually pretty,
but today..?
Right..
Sorry.
This morning, at my parent's house...
Hey!
Gorgeous!
Well, thanks to everyone
for being here, and...
I don’t know.. Koldo and I...
Koldo and I love you lots and...
it's great to see that you love us
so much and that you're happy
that we’ve found the loves
of our lives.
Bravo!
That's lovely. That's lovely.
That's lovely...
I want a bit!
Get us!
There... there...
Long live the happy couple.
We love you lots...
And for love!
Pour l'amour. Pour l'amour.
Rafa!
Pour l'amour.
Oh, oh!
She's stood you up!
She came, she came...
She got confused and she's gone!
- She got away from you!
- For la France...
Natalié... Natalié...
Ales enfants de la patríe.
That's where I want it.
Hey! Gorgeous!
Hey, Koldito!
Okay, cinema verité.
Let's continue our programme
with some interviews...
Here we have Sponge Bob...
Can I interview you?
Yes, but could we go outside?
I want to smoke a cigarette.
Okay, let's go outside.
There's a room next to the dining room,
where we put on games and shows
so that the kids are entertained
during the banquet.
And how long have you been
doing this?
Well, weddings, for about ten years...
and children's shows, eight.
And what exactly
are you dressed up as?
As Sponge John
That would be Sponge Bob?
No. Well, you see, there was
a copyright problem
and now the costume is called
Sponge John
We are talking about a character
that's got nothing to do with
the one you're talking about.
I don’t want any trouble later on.
I swear to God.
Well, that's it. It’s really great.
Because the kids love it.
Fuck...
There goes the typical drunk!
That's my uncle!
- Oh, sorry kid, I didn’t know
- Uncle, are you all right?
Sorry, I didn’t know
he was your uncle.
What are those doing there?
Once I heard
it was better to spray at night
How strange!
Have the cops arrived?
Oh, Uncle, if they breathalyse you...
Adrián!
I’ve just filmed my uncle Pepe Víctor
throwing up, man. It’s great!
Enough of Pepe,
enough crap and smokers.
Come inside and start
filming the good stuff.
You can’t rush..
You can’t rush things.
You can’t rush things...!
Come on, Rafa!
Atún!
I’ve just filmed Rafa getting off
with the Frenchwoman!
You were made for this, kid!
Oh! Yeah!
Uncle!
What are you doing?
Get down!
Uncle!
That's dangerous!
Stop the music!
Call an ambulance!
Please move!
Call an ambulance, come on!
An ambulance!
Have you seen Clara?
No?
Look, Tita is there!
Hey, come on!
Follow me, Adrián!
This way! Koldo!
Get inside! And lock the door!
Lock the door!
It’s there!
Ah! God!
Clara! Have you seen Clara?
Has anyone seen Clara?
No, I haven't seen her!
Jesus!
- What happened out there?
- I don’t know..
People went stark raving mad and
they just started eating each other.
- Are you filming?
- Yes, everything.
What are you doing?
People have a right to
know what’s going on!
I have to film everything!
- What the fuck are you talking about?
- Stop! Stop!
- Give me the camera!
- Stop!
You are going to..
Break it!
You know you’re paying
for the camera, right?
Try and call Clara, okay?
The stairs! Let's see if there’s an exit.
Come with me!
Come on, come on!
Get back, back!
Lock the door!
- Well?
- I tried There's no cover.
I have to find Clara!
I have to find her!
That's not possible right now!
This is no time to act the crazy husband.
You see how fucked-up all this is.
Shit!
My name's Atún.
From Filmax films.
Koldo.
And this?
My name's Moncho...
What part of Clara's family
are you from, Moncho?
He's not from my family.
SGAE Inspector.
What's that?
I make a note of the songs played
at the wedding.
For the royalties thing.
Hey, come here.
This grille must lead somewhere.
Ah!
Go!
Go, go!
Shit!
You fucking idiot, Royalties!
Hey, lads,
I think there's something over here!
Go on, go on...
Let me help you!
I’m not going to fit in there.
We can’t leave here without Atún.
Don’t be so stupid.
Go on, get in!
We have to go! We have to go!
Here. I’ve put it on night-vision
so you can see inside there.
Don't even think about erasing
anything, eh?
Atún, I swear to God
we'll come back for you.
It’s dark!
I can't see a thing!
Cousin?
Tita, here, take the camera!
Come on!
We don't know what's going on,
but everything will be all right.
We're going to find your sister and
we're going to get out of here, okay?
I promise.
Come on!
Come with me!
- Koldo!
- What’s wrong?
When I was outside, I saw a police car.
We have to find it!
Come on, we have to get help,
no matter what!
Shit!
Hey! Wait!
There is a light!
I think.. I think I there’s a light.
Maybe this leads to the garden.
Come on!
Come on! Come on!
Help me, please!
Please!
What are you doing there?
Come on, come on, Royalties!
Officer!
No!
Royalties!
Royalties! Royalties!
Help me, for fuck's sake!
Come on, Royalties!
Hello? Please help us!
Can anyone hear me?
How the hell does this thing work?
Please, can anyone hear me?
Please... Help!
Come on! Come on!
They're coming!
Come on!
I’m sorry.
Get a move on!
What are you waiting for! Inside!
Run, Grandma. Run!
Close it!
Shut up, wise guy.
They can't get in here.
Heretics! Bastards!
Clara!
Has anyone seen Clara?
Does anyone have a mobile that works?
None of them are working.
We've got to get these people
out of here!
We're safe in here, Grandma.
Why don’t they come in?
They can't set foot in the church,
and holy water hurts them.
We don't know any more.
And I’m not your grandma, dear.
Is there a land line phone here?
There is one, but it doesn’t work
They seem to be going.
Take the kids and get to the coaches,
all of you
I’m going to find Clara.
- Wait, Koldo. We don't know if...
- No, don't say that. Shut up, okay?
- Sir, remember that..
- Shut up! I don't want to hear it.
Koldo...
Clara is alive, I’m sure.
I know, because I can sense her.
What the hell is that?
Koldo.
Koldo, it's me.
And I know that, wherever you are,
you can hear me.
I want to tell you that I’m all right.
Father Losara and me,
we've hidden and we’re okay.
And I know you’re okay, too.
I know you’re alive because
I can sense you, Koldo!
Baby!
I love you!
And, well...
I’ve been trying to talk to you
all day, but...
But we really haven’t had much time
to ourselves.
And, it doesn’t matter
So I’m going to tell you like this.
I’m pregnant.
We're going to be parents, Koldo.
That's too much.
And it wasn’t a shotgun wedding.
For anyone who's listening,
especially from my family.
Just so you know, we didn't get
married because of that
I found out this morning, at home
What's happening?
What's happening? Why did it stop?
Why did it stop? Why did it stop?
Where is she?
The only place with a megaphone is
Central Control
They must be there.
But right now it's impossible
to get to them.
No, there must be away.
There must be away!
Please, help me, God.
St. George.
Where is Central Control?
Koldo, where are you...?
Can you see him?
- it’s too soon.
- What is?
Not yet it can’t be happening!
- What?
- Genesis.
And the angels who did not keep
their dignity,
but abandoned their own abode...
The Lord kept it in darkness...
eternal visions...
where they will be punished
and where they will not come back
until Judgement Day.
Koldo, where are you?
He's here. He's here!
He's here, Father.
Come on, Father.
This is the end.
Come on, Father!
Father! Father!
What...?
I’m sorry,
we have to get out of here
Let's go.
Come on!
What's that?
That's the...
...and now I’m going down
to the engine room...
Rafa?
Oh...
Oh, Clara.
What the hell are you doing here?
You don't know what's going on?
No.
Well, you'll never believe it...
That way
First floor, corridor on the left.
Central Control is down there.
- But do you know where he is?
- No, but we’re going to find him.
- A solution
- What?
They obey orders. I’ve seen it.
They move as one. They do what
a superior, malign being tells them.
Where did you get all that from, Father?
I didn't get anything.
Look at how they behave, and you’ll see.
They tell us in the Bible.
And then you wonder why everyone
thinks French girls are sluts.
They are bodies that...
Come on, let's go.
Let's go. Come on.
Jesus...
it’s her.
Father Albelda is right.
Quickly! Go!
Get going. Don't stop.
Hurry up, go on!
Come on, Clara!
The Lord is my shepherd,
I shall not want...
Though I walk through the valley of
the shadow of death,
I shall fear no evil,
for thou art with me.
Thy rod and thy staff,
they comfort me
Thy kindness and love will always
be with me each day of my life,
and I will live forever in thy house,
I asked the Lord to free me
three times,
but he answered:
"My grace is sufficient,
because my power will triumph
in weakness".
So, I will boast all the more gladly
of my weaknesses,
so that the power of Christ
may dwell in me.
I am content with insults,
hardships, persecutions,
and calamities
for the sake of Christ;
for whenever I am weak,
then I am strong.
Clara?
Jesus, I can't see a thing.
Where are we?
I don’t know
This way
Jesus!
Shit!
Oh Oh Oh Oh!
Hello?
Who's that?
Don’t move!
It’s me, the children's entertainer.
Sponge John
Jesus.
You mean Bob?
Well, there was this thing
with the copyright, and...
Bob, put that down, please.
I took it from the guard.
I don't even know if it's loaded.
Don't hold that lighter too close.
This stuff catches fire easily.
Help me to lift this barrier up.
It’s really heavy.
And this sponge costume doesn’t help
Why don't you take it off?
Well, because I’m not wearing
anything underneath.
Is there a light here?
Yes, there's a control panel
on the wall there.
Clara, what is all this?
I don’t know I don’t know
We'll get out of here Don’t worry
...two and three!
I almost decided not to come.
What?
I was thinking about not coming.
The truth is,
I was surprised you invited me.
We haven't seen each other for ages.
Well, I invited you to be nice.
Because I didn’t think you'd come.
I looked on the Internet and I found
this really cheap low-cost ticket.
Fuck!
I’m sorry.
Oh, no!
Give me the bloody shotgun!
I’m really sorry I invited you
to my wedding.
Jesus!
Natalié, Natalié.
Clara, please!
Clara! Clara!
This way! Come on!
This way!
- Come on, Clara!
- Wait for me!
What’s wrong?
I think I saw something..
Let's go and see.
Come on.
Clara, you stay here. We're going
to see if it’s safe, okay?
Mum?
Clara, leave her. We have to go.
Clara, leave her, we have to go.
This is my mother.
Clara, it's not your mother, okay?
Lether go, we have to leave.
Come on, Clara, they're coming.
Come on!
Come on! Run!
This is it!
Koldo!
Clara!
Come on, Clara!
Get in, quick!
Run!
Stop!
The exit is over there!
Jesus, Clara, why are you stopping.
What’s wrong?
I’m not going without Koldo.
Don’t be so bloody stupid!
We have to go!
Don’t tell me what I have to do!
Listen, Clara...
if Koldo was alive...
he would have given us some sign
to let us know.
I’m sorry.
I’m sorry, Clara...
it’s him.
It’s Koldo.
It’s a sign.
He's in the Lounge.
No, we don't know if it's him.
You said that if he was alive,
he'd give us a sign, didn’t you?
Well, there it is
I’m not leaving here without Koldo.
Move.
Hold my dress.
- What are you going to do?
- Hold my dress!
Wow!
Now, you make your own decision.
But I know where I’m going.
They've got in
Atún?
Uncle, no, no, no!
Jesus, they're already here.
Clara, come on. Run!
We have to go!
No fucking way.
Clara, come on!
This is my day!
Jesus!
Fucking hell!
Oh!
Oh, God!
Rafa?
No!
Clara, Clara...
Jesus, this is really weird.
This is really weird.
I’m sorry, Rafa.
Clara...
Clara!
Clara! I’m here!
I’m here, my love!
I’m up here!
Koldo!
Koldo, my love!
I’m here, my love!
I’m here!
I knew it!
Come up, come up.
There's a ladder here!
My love...
I’m coming, my love...
I’m coming, my love!
Are you okay?
I love you.
We're never going to separate again,
are we?
- No.
- Never.
And we’re going to be parents.
We have to open this.
The screwdriver.
There's a screwdriver
on the Swiss Army knife.
It must be down there somewhere.
You have to find it, baby.
It’s our only chance.
Look for it!
It must be there somewhere.
Look again!
It has to be there.
I’ve got it!
Come on, bring it up!
Here it is!
They're coming, Koldo!
They're coming!
Open it, Koldo!
Open it!
Hurry, Koldo!
Koldo! Koldo!...
Lether go!
Koldo!
- My love...
- Hurry, Koldo!
My love...
- Are you all right?
- Yes, and you?
Yes.
- What's all this?
- I don’t know
And now what do we do?
The tunnel!
The tunnel, the tunnel!
We got out through there earlier.
You would have been
a wonderful mother.
I love you.
In the beginning, God created
the heaven and the earth.
And the earth was
without form and void..
And darkness was on the face
of the deep.
And God divided the light
from the darkness.
And God called the light Day, and...
the darkness he called Night.
They're stopping.
And the evening and the morning
were the first day.
They're stopping. They're stopping.
Why are they stopping?
I don’t know
But let's go.
Let the waters under the heaven be
gathered together unto one place,
and let the dry land appear:
and it was so.
And God called the dry land Earth;
and the gathering together of the
waters called he Seas...
ls this our family?
Koldo...
Not any more.
...in the midst of the waters.
And God said, Let there be light:
and there was light.
And let them be for lights
in the firmament of the heaven
to give light upon the earth...
No, no!
No!
God!
Fuck my granddad and his stupid
bloody hearing aid!
The sword.
Pick up the sword.
Pick it up, Koldo...
Come on!
Do it!
Well done, my love.
You're going to be
a wonderful father.
Koldo, there are people over there!
Stay inside and do not come out!
Stay inside!
I repeat, do not come out!
I repeat...
Put her on the ground!
She is infected!
I repeat,
put her on the ground!
Get away!
She is infected!
I repeat, move away!
Put her on the ground!