APOLLO 18
JULY 20, 1969- APOLLO 11 ASTRONAUT
NEIL ARMSTRONG...
...IS THE FIRST MAN TO WALK ON THE MOON
IN 1970 APOLLO MISSIONS 18, 19, 20 WERE
CANCELLED DUE TO BUDGETARY CONCERNS
7 DECEMBER, 1972- APOLLO 17...
...THE FINAL OFFICIAL LUNAR LANDS
ON THE MOON
IN 2011, 84 HOURS OF CLASSIFIED FOOTAGE
...IS UPLOADED TO WWW.LUNARTRUTH.COM
THIS FILM WAS EDITED FROM
THAT FOOTAGE
This's a lot of at stake here,
you know.
Talking, nation versus nation.
The race's still on.
It's a lot to discover up there.
I guess the call came in on a Friday.
They've never been to a barbecue.
JOHN GREY COMMAND MODULE PILOT
Just few beers you know,
or more than a few.
Could Vince's cooking, he
definitely need few.
Nate took the call from Milton.
And Milton said, "Eighteen is back on"
But it was classified D.O.D.,
top secret.
Asked him "are you OK with that?
And it was like "are you kidding me?"
I come from a family military pilots.
Duty can sometimes pound on
private life.
Make choices. Keep going forward.
NASA already has like 800 pounds rocks.
Nathan Walker; Mission Commander
So why we need more, I don't know,
...but, hey, if it means a
trip to the moon.
Placing cameras, we have these
Westinghouses all over the place.
Well, I think the way it's been
explained is...
...they're using a Saturn 5 to launch
classified D.O.D payload.
...which's meant to be very large
very heavy and...
...apparently unmanned.
Apparently.
Placing these high frequency
transmitters because...
...really warning anti-missile defense
system of Soviyet Union.
These PSD 5 are kind of like
high-tech radar scanners.
They should pick up and track
anything we can't.
To keep an eye on the Russian's air.
It would be nice to tell my wife.
Benjamin Andersen-Lunar Module Pilot
Or been by my side whole time
and then.
She thinks I'm doing training exercise
with the Japanese space agency.
Brian, my boy, it would be nice to tell
him his father's going to the moon.
I'd love brought to him a souvenir.
Maybe, a moonrock.
I don't know, may be one day.
Ben was always the first in his class.
And I was always running at his heels.
I mean, I'm jealous that he will
walk on the moon with Nate...
...while I'm alone in an orbit flight.
My job is essentially to make sure
I'm bringing us home safely.
Look, let's face it. These missions
are result-oriented.
And we can't afford the failure
you know, can we?
Things can go wrong... things to go
wrong happen.
These things you're gonna push
them out of your mind.
It's just not an option.
I'm proud to do for these guys,
and proud to do for my country.
Ten, nine, eight...
seven, six, five...
four, three, two, one.
Apollo 18, it looks good.
Christmas lights.
- Bring the Christmas lights back?
- I don't know. Not me.
- Have you seen anything like that before?
- No, sorry.
It's amazing.
The earth in all her glory.
There is a good-looking boy.
You sure he's yours?
Watch it.
He's a good kid.
It has a large space to fill.
Play on Moon Boots.
Nate, you've waited all this time to
put your foot on the moon...
...and you need to be number 13.
How do you feel about that?
Are you gonna be OK
with staying behind John?
Oh, you know, would be nice to have
some alone times here.
It's crowded in here.
I keep a light on for you boys.
Don't stay out until late.
- In a couple days.
- Roger that.
See you in a couple days.
Houston, this is Freedom. We're
preparing to unboard the Liberty.Over.
OK,18. you can go front
dock in four minutes.
John, is the tunnel vented?
Roger that. The tunnel is vented.
OK, we are ready. We'll send you
an updated state background on that.
Roger Houston. We're coding the data.
The computer is all yours.
I wish you come with us, John.
- Now, you be careful down there.
- Don't worry about it
- Got a good visual around here
- OK, 18. You're ready for that.
We go to the moon.
1400 feet.
44 down.
OK, good. Down to 1000 feet.
54 LPD.
20 feet down. Repeat, 20 feet down.
OK, good.
Mission Elapsed Time:
Four days, 6 hours and 33 minutes.
Roger.
Here we are.
Take it down.
- Carefull with the line. Over.
- Where?
After that next crater.
4 o'clock.
It seems pretty rocky area. Mark it.
430 feet.
Down 15.
Houston, we have a program alarm
1201.
- You have go to 1201 Liberty.
- Roger. Go to 1201.
Do you want to take about
reversing that approach?
Negative. We miss the window.
The moon isn't...
- We're closing now. Three, two, one.
- How does it look?
- We're coming in too fast.
- Try to stabilize.
Negative Houston.
The range is long. We go to manual.
- Contact Light.
- Standby everyone.
Stay. No stay.
Stay where you are Liberty.
Houston, give that man a cigar.
- Looks great.
- Excellent landing.
You talking to me or to Nate?
I'm talking you both, kid.
25 December, 1974.
EMD... 4 days
nine hours, 23 minutes.
Commander, Nathan Walker.
Ministry of Defense, Mission Report 1A.
For day one of our two-day mission...
This is Thomas Young of
Apollo Mission Control.
- Managed to move our 16 mm cameras.
- Copy.
Looks like 5 reels 10,000 feet
Kodachrome.
Houston, we're prepared for OA1.
Copy Liberty. You are go for
decompression chamber.
But not good boys.
We don't want anyone catching cold.
- Copy that.
I look after him.
Hope that the hose is long enough.
Houston...
...we take now the first step
on the South Pole.
I had prepared a speech but
I don't have much audiences anyway.
Do not worry about it.
You will have opportunity soon.
There are rock formations
everywhere.
The sun is low on the horizon.
Maybe.
Freedom, do you hear?
Freedom receiving you loud and clear,
Liberty. Over.
Yeah, yeah, perfect.
You call that a salute?
OK. Let me get a shot of you with
that LEM in the background.
It's more like a naval salute.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
I got to get this.
I promised Lauren and Brian
Christmas to spend with them.
This's all going back to the
Department of Defense.
We're placing Westinghouse
cams.
WESTINGHOUSE MOTION
DETECTION CAMERA
Sounds good, Nate.
Standby.
Motion cencor is tracking you
perfectly, Nate
Captain says that we will
test the audio when you get back.
I'm checking the payload
in the missile unit.
What was that?
Houston, need check that panel
for anything that interferences.
Roger. You need to walk to procedure
location 1 and initiate the procedure.
Copy. We're on our way.
Hey, take a look at that.
Makes you think, doesn't it?
It's dusty.
Leave the camera here, so
you get better view Tommy.
It's hard to believe that the sun
never shines in some places.
Careful now, fellows.
If you are in any of
those craters, you can call to her
- PSD5 in place.
- Copy that.
You recorded signal frequency
on the PSD5 in your training?
- It was without that, wasn't it?
- I thought, it was.
I think they have changed it.
That's the coordinates: 4.3 on Z and...
Inititating sequence is completed.
If we gonna get noise
from the high tech again?
Don't worry.
A good geological sample
and what appears to be...
...an impact crater.
Samples feel...
...strange.
Let's get out of here.
EMD...four days,
14 hours and 48 minutes.
Commander Nathan Walker.
D.o.D mission report 3C.
Day 1, DVA 1 complete.
I'm starving.
What's the menu tonight?
- Carrots or peas?
- I'll take carrots.
- Get the peas.
- Perfect.
I am many proud of you boys.
- You have good time out there?
- You know we have.
There is much noise in this frequency.
See if I can isolate it.
Cleared up a little bit.
Copy that.
Astronaut Brian Anderson,
with his dad, flies through space.
- Honey, what are you doing?
- Just playing mom.
Don't play with your dad's stuff.
- Is this a recording?
- I'm sorry, Dad. I love you.
Beverley is in panic because
hairdresser appointment ran over.
Stan and Gene already over,
nothing is ready, so...
I offered to help in cutting
the peppers.
Couple minutes later I'm in
the bathroom taking a leak...
...and with all these peppers
in my hands...
Next thing I know, my crotch is
on fire.
- So, I'm in the bathroom howling in pain.
- They can not hear you.
They all heard me.
Stan's wife is a nurse, so...
she sends me back into the bathroom,
with a cup of milk.
Hey, I guess you're about to tell me that
you have your balls in a glass of milk?
- Hey, no knock it. It works.
- Jalapeno dick!
I can't believe that you've
never heard that story?
- Beverly's back to Miami?
- Yes. I heard that.
Hear, you divorced because
you snore, right?
I do not snore.
Every time!
- Are you OK?
- Yes.
- Bumped your head?
- Again!
It's big head.
Good night guys.
Great first day.
- Good night, JD.
- Never should told you that, litle prick.
- Nate?
- Yeah, I hear it.
- What can that be here?
- Give me a second.
Should be on the cam.
What is that?
- Hear that?
- Yes.
I don't think it comes from here.
It does not sound right.
- I can't find down here.
- It's army.
You think this interference can
be coming from the PSD5?
We don't see any obvious.
We double check with the D.o.D.
We'll look into it.
You go get some sleep.
I am up.
Turn off the noise.
Good morning, Liberty. We took care of the
interference a couple hours ago.
It should be OK now.
Do you get ready for OA2?
EMD... five days, 8 hours and 34 minutes.
And I'm Ben Anderson.
I need to document this.
Nate says he never snores in his sleep.
I got proof.
Hello boys, just to let you know...
...Freedom, we're going to around the
corner to the back side.
- No communication a while.
- Roger that.
- I've made you breakfast.
- What do I got?
- Scrambled eggs.
- Again.
- What do you got?
- A delicious hamsbread.
It's all yours.
Just like Mom makes.
Hey, did you remove one of my samples?
One of my samples is on the ground.
What does that mean, Ben?
I don't know.
I bagged and tagged everything.
Look, let's go back in there
giving a scoop.
Oh, damn! This one is contaminated.
- I don't understand. How did it get here?
- I don't know.
- This's really bad. How did it get here?
D.o.D's checked around the interference
with the first payload.
So found diagnostics...
Houston, do you copy?
- There is no communication.
- Probably get some blokage.
I see some big craters.
Five days, ten hours, 40 minutes
since we left off.
I'm commander Nathan Walker.
We are on DVA 2.
Initiating day 2 receiver cell.
Activated PSD5 transmission
signal to go.
Houston, do you copy?
This is Liberty. Over.
Still down.
There's something with that frequency.
Communication can't be down like that.
- Not for this like the time.
- Where are you going?
What the hell?
- Nate.
- What is it?
- Tracks.
- What?
That's impossible.
These are not ours.
EMD... five days, 11 hours, 7 minutes.
Alan P. Anderson.
Houston, this is 18.
Do you copy?
Houston, it's 18.
Do you hear?
John is on the back side.
No communication with him either.
Let's see where they lead.
- Impact Crater.
- Feel that?
Yeah, temperature's dropped.
Look at the footprints.
It makes no sense.
Like it runs in circles.
Disoriented.
- How should you do that?
- I don't know.
They go from this direction.
Come over here.
Holly shit!
- It is Russians.
- What the hell?
How can be Russians on the moon
and nobody know about them?
We are on the moon
and nobody knows about it.
Something is not right.
I'll look inside.
The lights are out.
Somebody's lost it in here.
Everything is crashed.
Their system isn't different
from ours.
The power is on.
Oxygen reserve is good.
I can't tell whether they
fully operational though.
- Where the hell did they go?
- I don't know.
- I want to take a look around.
- Stay close.
Those Russians could be anywhere.
What the hell?
There is blood. A lot of blood.
Someone's got hurt pretty bad.
I don't like this.
I think I see something inside the crater.
I'll go down.
Wait, Ben. The suits are no
ready for that kind of cold.
No cape. The crater is so deep.
It's so cold.
I'll see around.
The ground is different.
It is soft.
Get out of there.
Oh, my god!
It's so cold.
Get out of there.
Ben!
OK, I'm get out of here.
Holy shit!
It's a dead cosmonaut.
I'm on my way up.
- Are you alright?
- Yeah, I'm get to go.
What happened here?
- Maybe the other cosmonaut?
- Do you think killed him?
- There is a crack.
- What are you doing?
Get your head out of there.
Wait. Something..
What the hell was that?
It's a rock.
Have it in his jacket down here.
I don't know.
Let's get out of here.
We're on the point of no turning back.
If we don't go now, we're just as dead.
- I don't like someone has died up here.
- I know.
This is a secure line.
I'm just talking to you, right Tommy?
You're just talking to me.
The Russians have been to the moon.
Say that again?
The Russians have landed on the South Pool.
We've found their LK Proton lander.
It has not ended well for the cosmonauts.
- We find the crash of the Russians?
- They didn't crashed.
- We found his body in a crater.
- You found a dead cosmonaut?
Somebody didn't know this?
We landed less than 2
clicks of the Soviets, OK?
You still believe they
did not know we were here.
We know they scrapped a manned
flight programme in '69.
That was the official word.
Did you know they were here?
Tommy?
This is a D.o.D mission Nate.
I'm just bringing down what I need
to know. That's all I can tell you.
Say that prick from the D.o.D
to give me a call.
Get some rest. I get the go D.o.D
over here and talk to you soon.
Tommie is straight here.
I knew something's wrong
from the beginning.
OK, what do you think?
D.o.D's taken over.
Lying to our families.
And the Russians up here for what?
To set up some listening devices?
I don't know.
That makes no sense.
Come on, think about Watergate, Nate.
That was our president for God's sake.
And you don't think the
D.o.D which is lie to us?
So what are we doing up here?
What we're really doing?
This can be spooky a little.
Strange beauty in the backside.
I do not know if my mind plays
tricks on me...
...but every so often you go
to those little windows...
...get this sense as if
something is looking back.
Looking back to you.
Nate, look at this.
- What?
- Look at this!
The flag is gone.
- This isn't right.
- Houston, this is 18. Over.
Houston, Liberty.
Did you see anything unusual in the
Westinghouse last night?
We had some interferences.
Our flag has gone.
Repeat again.
Repeat once.
Maybe the other cosmonaut
took it.
If there is another cosmonaut...
...he would need oxygen for
minimum 10 to 12 hours.
- What do you think, John?
- There is no way.
He can not carry that much.
So, how can he survive?
Maybe there is not a 'he'.
You're saying the Soviet flew
one man mission?
- It would not be the first time.
- One cosmonaut...
But who took the flag?
Who killed the other cosmonaut we found?
Please get the D.o.D online.
Now.
We suspect that the Soviets are
there, but we have no confirmation.
The Intelligence warned that
they might be...
...disguising the machines as
routine satellite launches.
Why the hell did not you tell us?
National security.
We carried out the card pretty close
to the desk. No other option.
I'm sure you can understand.
Maybe a little too close.
We were concerned that they
might ride to the sky first.
That would be a national security disaster.
So, where the hell is
the other cosmonaut?
They're just gonna leave
him here?
Our intelligence suggests
there was only one cosmanaut.
Oh, God!
The mission is complete.
Time to get you boys home again.
So, that's it?
First we return home
and ask questions later.
- What was that?
- Let's get out of here.
It looks pretty good.
Ten seconds.
Wait for my mark.
- Eight...
- Time to go home.
Seven, six...
- That's the alarm.
- We can't go. No go. We are no go.
Save this damn thing.
I try.
I got a power glitch.
Use the spare oxygen.
- We have a leak somewhere.
- I try to isolate the tanks.
See if I can stop it.
Houston, do you copy?
We lost communication.
Dropped out. Closed.
- No, no.
- What the hell is going on?
Houston, this is Liberty. Over.
We just lost communication.
- How the hell did that happen?
- I don't know.
Maybe hit the LEM,
or a meteor rain.
There's no way no tell.
I'm gonna to the air.
Are you sure about this?
We need communication
to get home.
You just stay here and wait.
- Look, I served in the army...
- Shut up.
Go down the platform.
Nothing on the bottom.
EMD...Six days.
13 hours, 46 minutes.
Commander Walker is performing
an unplanned DVA...
...to repair the antenna on the Roover.
We experience...we experience
some unexplained...
...malfunctions.
The whole installation seems damaged.
Could be the brief impact
but I don't see any meteor residue.
- This reaped to pieces.
- Something crashed it?
I can't tell.
We get the same sound each time
we activated the communication..
- Go to a different frequency.
- Frequency is blocked.
I never heard anything like it.
Wait. Wait.
Nate, talk to me. What do you see?
Footprint tracks.
Footprints?
Maybe there is another cosmonaut.
No.
Mission Duration:
Six days, 13 hours, 47 minutes.
Commander Nathan Walker.
We witness tracks that could be
evidence of extraterrestial contact.
Do you know what you're saying?
These tracks are not human.
I found the flag.
It's shreded.
And the motion censor camera gone.
That looks OK.
I'm turning the Roover back up.
The connection looks good.
Try contact to Houston or Freedom.
Freedom, copy?
Houston, do you copy?
Dammit.
- No, looks not working.
- OK. Let me try something.
Wait.
- Something is moving.
- What?
- I don't see anything
- There's something in my boots.
It's in my helmet.
- OK, listen to me. Go back to the lab.
- I can't get it out!
- Listen.Go back to the lab. OK?
- I can't get it out.
There is nothing inside your suit.
Go back to the ship.
It's in my helmet.
Don't take it out!
Nate!
Jesus Christ!
You need oxygen.
Come on Nate! Keep moving.
We're almost there.
Keep moving.
Almost there. Come on.
Come on. Almost there.
Pull yourself up.
The door is closed.
Cabin press auto,
4.5 psi.
You don't get enough oxygen.
Breathe! Breathe!
One.
Look at me in the eye.
You'll be fine.
Two.
Two and a half.
The cabin pressure is stable.
It's okay.
So, you OK?
I'm fine.
What happened out there?
You've started screaming, I've come out
there and you're on your back.
Liberty, this is Freedom.
Do you hear me?Over.
Do you copy?
Houston, this is Freedom.
Do you hear me?
We hear you, John. Over.
I can't receive the Liberty, Tommy.
Copy that Freedom.
We have the same problem down here.
Have you tried to change the frequency?
No. We had some sort of interference.
Could have something to do with those PSD5.
We are not sure yet that PDS5
are the source of the problem.
I want to switch shut down the
receivers to see what happened.
Negative.
Why not? We got two men
down there Tommy. Come on.
Tommy?
Are you there?
We are working on the problem.
We'll keep you adviced.
Oh, you're working on it.
That's great.
God damn it.
Liberty, this is Freedom.
Do you copy?
EMD...
Six days, 16 hours, 12 minutes.
Post DVA 1,5 hours
with Commander Walker
I've already told everything
I remember.
Come on.
Are you paranoid, Ben?
I thought I saw something...
I thought I saw something on
the corner of my eye. I was wrong...
...and then there was a shrieking voice...
...and caught off guard.
I must have hit a rock.
That's it.
You said something was in your
helmet.
You yelled.
I don't remember that.
Christ! You're bleeding.
Look at your shirt.
You bleed.
Jeez.
Take the first aid kit.
You said that something was
inside your suit.
That's what you said.
You said inside your helmet.
I wonder
how did you get that wound.
If there is something in your suit,
where the hell did it go?
Wait a second.
Nate, I can feel it
right here.
Oh, man! Something's inside.
- What are you talking about?
- Look, it's just below the skin.
I need to get that out. OK?
Yeah. OK.
Just make it quick.
Everything is right.
Hang in there!
Damn, it seems to be moving.
Get it out.
- I got it! I got it!
- Get it out!
Jesus!
- Are you alright?
- Yes, yes.
Put this on it.
It looks like one of my samples.
You said you felt something's
moving in your helmet.
I don't understand,
how did this get in...
Goddamn, you contaminated the entire ship.
Liberty, do you copy?
Houston, we hear you.
Dammit Houston, we hear you.
Liberty, do you receive?
They can't hear us.
Liberty, do you hear?
Those PSD5's...
...what if they're not there
to spy on the Russians?
What do you mean?
They told us that the transmitters...
...pick up any frequency,
but they don't.
They're blocking our communication,
transmitting a signal.
Alright.
And why would they do that?
No, keep filming. Keep filming.
We need to document this.
To attract the Soviets, made the tracks is
...whatever killed the cosmonaut.
All these cameras, man...
...they're watching us.
We are alone.
We are guinea pigs.
That's why they sent us here.
We have to turn off those
transmitters.
PSD5's destroyed.
Brilliant.
Nice tracks.
They were here.
Let's check on the other sides.
Liberty, do you copy?
Something's down here.
It's gone.
Hey, what are you looking at?
This was a bad idea.
You need to get rest, Nate. OK?
We're get to back to lab.
We need to get back, Nate.
Oh, Jesus Christ, Nate.
It's in your blood stream.
The previous wound seems to...
...become infected.
Eyes are extremely bloodshot.
I do not know how to treat it.
Houston, this is Freedom.
I haven't be able to reach Nate or Ben.
Communication's still down with Liberty.
We have no communication
with the crew...
...we're receiving data from the LEM.
We're trying to restore the
communication now. Standby.
Liberty, this is Houston.
Looks like you can hear us,
but we can't hear you.
Block the Westinghouse
and survival craft's getting land down.
We estimate 12 hours left
on your live support...
...and we are now sorting out the
engine problems.
We'll do everything we can
to get you home.
... and we are now sorting out the
engine problems.
We'll do everything we can
to get you home.
They're lying.
No, they'll get us back.
Thay'll get us back.
They want that footage.
- What about the Russian ship?
- The poor Russian bastard.
It looks infected.
Just like me.
I'm getting worse.
Ben...
- ...you must leave me here.
- No.
- No one leaves anyone.
- You have to.
Forget it. We won't die uphere.
Fate has renamed.
The men who went to the moon
to export peace...
...remained on the moon
to rest in peace.
What the hell are you talking about?
I feel my toughts...fragmenting.
I can be attracted to them.
I'm so tired.
EMD
Six days, 22 hours, 23 minutes.
Alan B. Anderson. Doctorial
There were no further
communication with Houston.
Oxygen levels are low.
Nate's being sleep for about an hour.
The sickness seems brougth fatigue.
We're not gonna make it here.
If Houston doesn't come up with the
plans in the next couple hours, we'll..
...we'll abandon Liberty and
go to the Russian LK.
Their communications and oxygen
are our only hope.
Just pray to God.
Jesus Christ!
Jesus!
Partial respiration.
Upper left rib...
The infection's spreading.
God damn it.
Must be the same thing that
happened to the Russian.
- Nate!
- I don't let you kill me!
It's me. Listen to me. Look at me.
It's me. Ok?
I'm just trying to help you.
You're getting worse.
Don't ever touch me!
- Nate, please, what the hell are you doing?
- They are everywhere.
- Please, Nate, you'll kill us all!
- Stop watch us!
Nate!
You're not gonna watch
how I die!
What are you doing? Stop!
Stop!
Come on! You...
Stop there!
Stop that!
Liberty, this is Freedom.
Do you read me?
I don't know if you hear me, but
I'm gonna be in the comm range soon.
Guys, we need to get you
out of there. There is...
Do you copy?
Come on, guys,
Don't make me leave you here.
Freedom, you read us?
John...John, can you hear me?
Please, anyone...
can you hear me?
We are leaving Liberty.
- Come on.
- I had to do it.
Take the camera.
We have 25% of the tank.
We can use some reserv.
We'll get there.
I get to get the films.
Black box of the D.o.D
I get to go down.
It's clear.
Come Nate, we go.
They are everywhere.
You can't help me.
You don't have to be here.
That's OK.
- It's gonna be OK.
- Alright. We're gonna make it.
They're waiting for me.
We are not safe here.
- Get rid of me.
- Hang in.
What the hell are you doing?
Hang on!
Nate!
EMD
I don't know...
Roover has been destroyed.
There is no sign of Commander Walker.
American astronaut,
Ben Anderson, Apollo 18.
Oxygen is getting low.
I'm...
I'm gonna search for the Russian later.
Hey, Commander Walker.
Nate!
Go away from here, Ben.
This is where they're coming from.
There's nothing here, OK?
You get to come with me.
God damn it! We need get moving.
Ben, listen to me.
We're running out of time here,
please.
You must find the LK? Their system is
identical with ours. Save yourself.
No, Nate! I'm not going.
You're coming with me.
You have to leave me here.
Just get the John.
- I'm not leaving here!
- You can't help me.
But you can save yourself...
Nate!
Can you hear me?
Answer me!
Do you hear me?
Say something Nate.
Nate, where are you?
No! No!
My god. No!
John, Nate is gone.
Repeat, Nate is gone.
Please, can somebody hear me?
Oh, my God!
Nate!
Come on!
Frequency is completed.
This is an American astronaut.
Ben Anderson, Apollo 18.
Been copy?
This is Apollo 18. Do you copy?
Anyone, do you copy?
Anyone, please. Do you copy?
Anything, anybody, do you copy?
Damn!
Confirming Commander Walker.
- Acknowledge.
- This is Captain Ben Anderson...
Do you copy?
This is Ben Anderson.
Copy, anybody?
Anybody, please! Do you read me?
Captain Anderson, this is the
Deputy Secretary of Defense.
What?
D.o.D? Yes.
Yes, this is Captain Ben Anderson.
We communicate with the Russians
and they're putting me through you.
We're aware of your condition that...
...and we have decided.
- ...we can't you home.
- No. No, no!
Listen to me please.
Nate get a cut on his body. He's infected.
There's nothing on me. Please,
have to come and get me.
We can't get you.
Please...
Listen, I...I...got a family
and I need my family.
We'll let your family know
you died a hero.
I'm sorry Captain.
You have to get me out of here!
And you fucking do it right now!
I will not give up
until you get me home!
Houston, please.
We'll stay in on this channel with you
but the decision is final.
You've done a great service for
your country, son.
EMD...
Still no communication.
Astronaut Brian Anderson, with his dad,
flies through the space.
- Brian, what are you doing?
- Just playing, mom.
Do not play with the your dad's stuff.
- Is that recording?
- Sorry, Dad, I love you.
...love you.
...Dad, I love you.
This is Freedom,
are you hearing me?
- This is Freedom...
- John, it's Ben. I hear you.
Ben, is that you?
Do you copy?
Yes, John, I am.
I hear you.
I got you on the VHF, partner.
Where the hell are you?
- Soviet's LK.
- Yes. Good for you.
They left me, John.
Left me here!
Where is Nate? How's he?
Get sick, he did not make it.
There's something down here, John.
And they knew about it. You hear me?
Those bastards knew about it!
Forget about the D.o.D, man.
Ben, I'm get you out of there, OK?
Did you figure out that thing?
I don't have much choice. Do we?
Powers look good.
And there is plenty fuel.
Okay, buddy. You're gonna be
in the darkness yet...
...you're gonna need to get your
synchronized orbit...
...then you need a little space for.
Safely on board.
How does that sound?
Sounds beautiful Johnny.
Sound very beautiful.
I don't mean rush you partner
but we're running out of time.
Get that thing in the orbit.
We can run into it.
I got it! I got it, John.
Seven. Six.
Five.
- Holy shit!
- Open this door.
Nate, you know I can't do that.
Please, you'll kill us both!
I can't let you in.
- I'm coming there.
- No, no!
Nate, please!
- Nate, stop this Nate!
- What'd you mean? - It's Nate!
- What is happening?
- Come on buddy! Stop!
Stop!
- What's going on?
- Don't do this! -What do you think?
Jesus Christ! No!
Nate!
Oh, my God!
No!
No, no, no!
You can launch.
You must do it now.
Our window is almost gone.
You have to launch.
Dammit, they were kind of
too close.
We're going home!
Ben, listen to me now.
We're going to go home.
Heard that? We're going to go home.
I'm going home.
We lifted up!
Freedom, do you read?
This is the Deputy Secretary of Defense.
Ben has been contaminated.
Do not try to rescue him.
I repeat. You will not recover him.
Contaminated by what?
D.o.D?
- What do you say? Where is Tommy?
- You will not recover Anderson.
This a direct order.
I'm on my way.
John, you're abording the rescue
immediately.
Captain Anderson has been
contaminated.
You knew something was down there
and you sent them anyway!
I'm coming home.
D.o.D to Freedom
If you're not abording in 60 seconds...
...transmittion will be terminated.
You'll not receive updated statement.
You'll run out of life support craft
and you'll not return home.
You have 45 seconds
to abort the rescue.
John, we have no choice.
We're begging you. Do not rescue!
God damn it, Ben!
We're going home.
I'm in the orbit.
Ben!
They tricked me.
John, get out of here.
Ben, you're coming in too fast!
Ben, your impact, slow it down!
Ben!
According to all official reports
Apollo 17 was the final mission.
Official Report
LI. Colonel John Grey...
...was kiiled in a crash during a
training mission over Tallahassee. FL.
His body was never recovered.
Official Report
Cmdr. Nathan Walker's F-14 crashed into...
...the Pacific Ocean near Kadena Air
Force Base.
His body was never recovered.
Official Report
Cpt. Benjamin Anderson was killed...
...was killed during a mid-air evacuation
over the East China Sea.
His body was never recovered.
We chose to go to the moon
in this decade and do the other things.
Not because they are easy,
but because they're hard.
Apollo Missions brought 378 kg Moon Rock
Samples To Earth.
Hundreds Were Given Away To
Dignitaries of Foreign Countries
Many of These "Gifts" Were Stolen
or Are Now Missing
The voyages of Apollo
dramatized the risks.
The men of Apollo identify
the character...
...that accept the danger
and surmounted.
There is the spirit that
built America.