The New South Wales government
has unveiled a radical solution
to the water crisis.
It plans to tap into an abandoned
reservoir under the city.
$95 million will be spent
on a state-of-the-art water recycling
facility in the heart of Sydney.
My name is Natasha Warner
and I've worked in news and
current affairs for well over 10 years.
I knew that I wanted to tell stories.
I knew I wanted to communicate to the public
and, um, that looked like
the perfect place for me.
The NSW Minister for Water and the Environment
has been under sustained fire for 12 months now.
Sydney's water reserves are at an all-time low.
We are a progressive government
and in the face of climate change
we need to look at all possibilities,
and recycling water
is definitely the way of the future.
I first came across a story which was
focusing on the government
that had just announced
some water recycling plans
and they wanted to use
abandoned underground tunnels
in one of our biggest rail systems.
Thousands of people pass through here each day
not realising the state government's
solution to the water crisis
is beneath their feet.
The plan is to build recycling infrastructure
to make use of millions of litres of water
trapped in disused train tunnels.
I didn't realise how vast they were.
There's virtually a whole other city
underneath us.
Welfare groups say the tunnels
are a refuge for Sydney's homeless.
Building underground
water recycling infrastructure
would leave them with nowhere to go.
The new homeless concerns
are likely to cause another road block
for the government's water crisis solution.
In a similar scenario in the US,
hundreds of homeless
were recently evicted from underground tunnels.
It caused a public relations nightmare.
You can quickly see why the government's
having so much trouble evicting the homeless.
I mean, trying to navigate through
this maze of dark tunnels is hard.
Trying to find people hiding in here
is virtually impossible.
The Water and Environment minister says
there is no evidence
of anyone living in Sydney's tunnels.
He says if Labor wins the election,
the water solution will proceed.
After the initial fanfare the story dried up
It was like the whole thing never happened.
That's when alarm bells went off in
my head. Things just don't disappear.
Whenever something's not
spoken about, I've got to ask why.
It's my job as a journalist.
Cheers, John. Happy birthday.
My birthday
What's your birthday message?
What do you have to say?
Uh, John
Actually, I can tell you a story about John.
You guys may not know this one,
it was way back in 1991.
My name's Steve Miller,
I'm a TV cameraman.
I've been working in news
and current affairs since the mid-'80s.
Me and Pete had just started,
and they sent us to the first Gulf War.
So we had to phone home to the office,
to John, who was the news director at the time,
and said, "Send us more cash.
"We need to get some gas masks
and chemical suits and stuff."
So they sent us, like, 10 grand.
We've got this cash in our hand, we've
gone, "Fuck it, let's spend it on piss!"
And the air raid sirens, everyone else
is fucking pulling on their masks,
and we're just going, "Oh, fuck it."
You kind of get married to the job,
so the people you work with,
they end up becoming like family members.
You've met our soundo.
He's an incredibly handsome young
man, but he's not very good at his job.
Come here, Tangles.
What're you talking about?
I'm talking about the time in the States we went
Two weeks you went without headphones.
Remember that?
And did anyone notice?
No-one noticed!
He's a genius.
That's how good I am.
I don't even need to hear it,
I feel it on the knobs.
When you get that gang on the road,
when you get Steve and Tangles out on a shoot,
they're just
They're professional,
but they're also kids.
At the end of the day they like to
muck around and have a bit of a laugh.
I remember Natasha,
she was at another network
and then a couple of years later
they brought her across to us.
First impression?
Just another young person coming in
getting paid too much money,
hadn't really proved herself.
But, you know,
she was the next big thing.
Hey, Pete! Pete!
A business meeting?
Production meeting.
Talking about producing some, uh
.. sea-man.
Well, yeah...produ
How's that? You'd better turn that off soon.
Pete!
Hey?
The one that got away!
I'm not away, I'm here.
Haven't we done that story before?
Come in here, mate.
Pete and I, we had
an interesting working relationship.
He was very determined
in the way he would do his job
and I was very determined in the way
I would do mine.
Sometimes that would work well together,
and sometimes it would
sort of cause a bit of friction.
Whenever her name came up,
the subject was changed pretty quickly.
When you think back on it now,
you sort of go,
"Oh, yeah, there was something going on there."
I came across a YouTube video
which showed some youths
defacing and vandalising
areas around the tunnels.
Sef? Did you do this?
You are fucking kidding me!
Fucking teach them a lesson, then, eh?
I fucking will.
This is what I think of your shit, MK.
Within that clip itself
there was something unknown.
Quite clearly, though, there was
something there in the tunnel.
Fuck was that?
Shh... Shh
What was that?
Shut up.
Fuck, what the fuck was that?
They're still here.
Oi!
Give me the torch...
Sef, come on, let's get out of here.
Just fucking give me the torch, you bitch!
No, don't! Come on!
It's cool, it's fucking cool. Oi!
Think you can tag on my fuckin' work, do ya?
Fuck, Sef, come on.
We've gotta fucking
Fuck.
Sef!
Sef?
Sef? What the hell, Sef? Come on!
Hold on. Sef, ANSWER ME!
Sef!
Fuck this. I'm out of here.
Dez, hold on. Don't go anywhere. Wait.
J, come on!
Dez, stop!
Dez, don't rack off!
What the fuck are you doing? Help!
Sef? Sef, answer me, please!
Once I saw that clip, I thought,
"This is a story I can go to John with."
You know,
"Finally it's got some strength."
Since when does a decent journalist
use YouTube as research?
It was a good clip, but at the time
I thought, "She's crazy."
When I pitched the story to John,
he put Pete on this.
What that meant was
Pete had an upcoming job and story in China
which he was very,
very passionate about.
And I had to give him the news
that he was taken off the story.
I first heard about the tunnels
being a potential story for us
just as we were prepping up
actually to go to China, with Pete.
Hey, mate, there's a focus chart there somewhere.
Can you just hold it up for us?
Yeah, yeah. No worries.
Beauty.
He'd been working on this thing for a long time
and he was pretty pumped
to get over there and get stuck into it.
I think he had some pretty good leads,
which could have blown
his career wide open... it was great.
How's it look, mate?
Mate, it looks pretty good.
It ought to, the amount the repairs cost.
Thanks, Tangles. Nice one.
No more throwing cameras around stairwells.
Yeah, I told you guys it's not my fault, alright?
Hey, um, you happy to go handheld?
The lighter we go, the quicker we move.
Absolutely, mate.
We 're going to China after all.
More room for cheap DVDs,
pirated software
You're all class, mate.
It was purely John's decision
to put Pete on this story.
Well, I was a little uncomfortable
with having Pete there to start with.
Like I said before,
we weren't exactly always gelling.
I was really nervous about talking to Pete.
I didn't wanna tell him.
It's not that exciting,
when you're building your hopes up
for this great big story
and then you sort of get given a shit sandwich.
I thought at that point
I was doing the right thing.
I thought that Pete having to postpone
what he had planned
was worth it in the end for the story.
He did say he went in to see John.
I don't know what happened in that room,
and the contents of that conversation
but, yeah, he had spoken to John about it,
and I think it was from that point on
it was clear he wasn't going to China
and Nat had won the day.
Why did John go the other way?
C'mon. We all know why John was favouring Nat.
Eh?
Once Peter was on the story
we started attending the daily pressers
to try and find out what happened
to the water recycling plans.
Pete was pissed off,
but, you know, Pete's a pro.
Took him a day or two,
then he came round
just like the guy he is.
He started to do his own searching around
He had contacts in the council who he spoke to.
And some rumours started to surface
that not only were there
homeless living in the tunnels,
but there were homeless that were going missing.
You know, at that point
we slowly started to think
there may be something in this.
So we just started
by chasing the then water minister.
The main thing that was apparent
That he was staying quiet on the topic.
He wouldn't talk to us...
no-one would talk to us.
At that point, we were just getting stonewalled.
If it was true that homeless were going missing,
this was a big story.
And it was a really important one.
Where is he?
Through here.
Minister!
Minister, have you seen the report about
the homeless people in the tunnels?
Nothing to say at the moment.
Have you scrapped your plans because
people are going missing in the tunnels?
No comment. No comment.
Minister, should people be worried?
Is there a threat in the underground tunnels?
Well?
Alright... that was alright.
You reckon?
I knew we wouldn't get anything.
I think that definitely on quite a large scale
there was a lot of people in the government
that knew what was going on.
They knew what was going on down there.
You know, with everything
that's happened subsequently,
they were hiding stuff.
I started getting in contact with
a few of the shelters around the city,
and eventually I came across
one particular homeless man
who I had believed
had been living in the tunnels.
So this was...
I mean, this was fantastic.
We had, finally, someone to speak to.
Right, Trevor, just one sec.
I've gotta fix your mike, if that's OK.
I'm not sure how she found Trevor,
but Natasha found Trevor.
We went down to this home,
and we sat him down for an interview.
Yeah, sweet.
Alright, mate. This will be fun.
You'll be on telly.
Alright, guys, I'm sweet.
Trevor, if you don't feel
comfortable with anything
you let me know at any time.
And, um, when I'm asking you the questions,
if you're not quite sure of an answer, that's OK
We can fix it up later,
so don't worry about that.
Good.
Yeah? Thank you.
Well, the interview with Trevor was a tricky one
but something that I am, I guess,
always quite accustomed to dealing with.
Trevor, I understand you've been living it rough
Call me Trev.
Trev? OK.
Trev, I understand you've been living it
rough for quite some time now.
What circumstances took you
to living in the tunnels?
Uh... Well, it kept me and my mates
warm in the winter. Yeah.
It all started out great,
chatting away to him.
He started to tell me a little bit about,
you know, his circumstances,
what led him to live in the tunnels.
He started to really paint a picture
of what it was like there.
And amongst your friends,
Alfie and Johnny and Harry
and some of the others,
do they still live down there... now?
No.
Trev?
Hmm.
Are you OK? You comfortable?
Hmm. Yeah.
At that point in the interview,
I asked Trevor
what he perhaps had been through in the tunnels.
I asked Trevor what he had seen.
Clearly something had happened to him.
Trevor, did you know someone who went missing?
Trevor, did anything happen to you down there?
Trevor
.. are you alright?
NO!
Shit.
Did you get that before?
Yeah. Yeah, I got it.
Oh, my God
Crazy.
I know.
After Trevor's interview, it was clear
we were onto something.
All the pieces of the puzzle were
symptoms of something deeper,
I just didn't know what.
I needed more.
We needed to get down there.
Your call may be recorded for training purposes.
Please advise your operator if you
do not wish your call to be recorded.
Hello, this is Pam.
Oh, hi, Pam, it's Natasha Warner here.
How are you?
I'm well, Nat, and you?
Yeah, good, good, thanks.
Look, I'm just wondering if you can help me out.
I'm working on a story and I need
to get into the tunnels under the CBD.
Who do I need to talk to to make that happen?
Right. What's the story?
Oh, look, I just need half an hour.
Um...just hang on a sec
Nat, sorry... I can't help you this time.
What?
Apparently no-one's getting in there,
and I don't think you'll be getting
any special treatment.
C'mon, Pam, it's me.
Exactly. And people got burnt
last time. I can't do it.
I really need this.
Look, Pam, can you help me out?
I'm sorry, Nat.'Bye.
Look, I just need half
I guess it's easier to look at it now
and say that I was perhaps under
a lot of pressure to get this story.
At the time I just...
I felt I was doing my job.
I was so focused on just doing my job.
There was a lot of rumours kicking around
she was in big trouble, and she
kind of really needed to lift her game
otherwise she was gone.
Well, I think that I'd put
a lot of work into my career
and I think it was all basically
hanging on this one...one story.
You know, I didn't really have a choice.
Hey, Tangles,
how's your head, mate?
Pete, I'm like a fucking shark.
As long as I keep moving, I'll be OK.
Here we go... this is what you looked like
after Steve pulled you out of the loo last night.
Oh, Steve, new toy.
Mate, waterproof, baby! A TG!
All the gear, yeah.
Good at spending the network's money.
It's not just water-resistant,
it's fully waterproof?
Yeah, waterproof, mate.
Yeah, can you roll up for me?
I'll, uh, give it a bit of sound. There it is.
Sure, mate.
Sweet.
Rolling.
Uh, great.
Pete, I'll just get you to say some shit.
Hang on...
One, two.
Here, mate, just say some shit to that.
"Some shit to that."
Um, yes, very excited to be
going down the smelly sewers
Hello. How'd you go?
Haven't got all the permits sorted
but, um, John's got us covered, OK?
When Natasha said that John was covering us
and we didn't have permits
That's kind of a pretty loose arrangement,
you know, you just sort of sit there
and go, "Oh, well, we must be fine."
You sure?
Yeah.
When?
We're on for tonight.
Tonight? OK. So we are up?
Yeah, mate.
Yep, tonight. You good?
Yeah, sweet. Yeah, I'm good, man.
Alright.
The sooner we go, the better, hey?
Yep.
As a crew, it's... it's our job
to film it and get coverage.
It's really not our job to question it.
Hey, Pete, just hang back. I'm just
gonna get a shot of Nat walking in.
Yeah? OK.
Excuse me, guys?
Guys... Hold up, restricted area.
Oh, sorry, mate.
Maybe no-one told you.
We're just gonna be filming for about
half an hour. We'll be out of your hair.
Just grabbing a few shots...
I'll need to see a permit.
Permit?
Yeah, uh
You got a permit?
I've got a driver's license.
Pete... how much have you got in your wallet?
You're kidding me, aren't you?
We're not third world here,
it's not gonna work.
Guys? Everyone, time to leave, please.
Told you.
Fucking hell.
Let's go, come on.
I was that far into it
I couldn't go back at that point.
We decided to find another way in,
with or without official...assistance.
We found some access round the other side.
Yeah, it looked like a maintenance access.
You sure John's got this sorted?
Grow some balls, Pete.
I, at that point,
was starting to feel as though
there was something not quite right.
Um, so I thought,
to cover myself and to cover Tangles,
and really to cover all of us,
I'd just film pretty much everything
that was happening there.
You know, I thought we had to have
some sort of way of protecting ourselves,
should something go wrong.
You know, if we got busted
and fined or whatever, arrested,
um, you know, I had some evidence it wasn't me
trying to push us down there,
and it wasn't Tangles,
but it was Natasha.
Here... take this.
Here we go.
OK, let's go.
You right? You want me to...
Take this.
Yep.
OK, make it quick.
We just were kind of covering
our tracks as we went down
You know, we didn't want to get discovered.
Looking back on that
.. that was probably a mistake.
We OK?
Hey?
Are we OK to be down here?
That's what she said.
She said John's got us covered.
When we start filming a story
When we actually start
"OK, let's get it, let's roll"
Pete and Natasha,
they look after the editorial content,
and, you know, it's kind of
my job to take over there
and look after the pictures.
OK, turn around and come back.
I'll just get you walking past this grill.
You guys just hang back there for a second.
Tangles and I would go off and we'd just start
getting stuck into it,
filming like we always would.
You know, don't really need direction,
we'd just get into it.
Once we got in sort of a little bit further,
there were whole sections of tunnels
that were absolutely,
absolutely pitch black.
It is completely black down there.
You know, you could go in there,
turn the light off, spin around
and you wouldn't know where you were.
'Cause there's junctions,
tunnels going off everywhere.
So I kind of thought
The first time I turned off the light
and stood there, I thought
we're gonna have to keep the light on
and stay across where we are
'cause otherwise it's going to be
pretty easy to get lost down there.
Hey, Tangles?
Yeah?
Just come here, mate.
There's something wrong with
my light. Can you check it out?
What do you mean?
Is it the connection?
Yeah, can you look in real close?
Is there something stuck on it?
Ah, shit!
How did I not see that coming?
Thanks for that, Steve.
My eyes are stuffed.
Great.
Let's go.
Pete had sourced a map of the tunnels,
but the further we got in, the more
we realised it wasn't exactly accurate.
There were whole sections of tunnels
that weren't even on the map.
Just give us some light here, Steve.
OK. So that's the entrance,
that's where we came down before
That's that way. That's not here...
I don't know why that is.
OK, through here.
Yep. That must be the way.
Once we got through
and past the maintenance areas
and we got into a little bit more
of the guts of the tunnels,
my impressions were that...that it was amazing.
It was vast, this place was huge.
That's awesome.
Shit, the sound's great.
Pete? Can I have 10 minutes
to grab some overlay here?
I'll give you five.
Five?
Yep.
We were very close to the station there, so, um,
you know, Pete was trying
to make us pretty low-key.
I was blown away by the size of it...
it was massive, and just eerie.
You know, I think we were all in awe of it.
It wasn't really difficult to get
great-looking shots down there,
you know, 'cause you're really just
painting stuff with your light
and whatever you saw there just was...
it looked really cool.
This is looking really good.
Hey, guys, just hush for a sec.
Alright, looks good. Yeah, sweet.
The history to these tunnels, the ones
in particular that we were looking at,
was just incredible.
I mean, it dates back pre-World War II.
They were to be used as
an underground rail system.
Then in World War II
they were used as air raid shelters.
Come have a look at this.
The current NSW government
is not the first to use these
tunnels for another purpose.
I'm standing in a section of tunnel
that was converted into an
air raid shelter during World War ll.
It's complete with all the amenities
that enabled soldiers to stay
for extended periods.
Various rooms were then, um,
reused and fashioned for training for the SAS.
So time and time again they've,
I guess, been reinvented for their use,
and even to this day with the water
recycling plans that were announced.
I was fortunate enough to
come across an area where
it was evident that there was definitely,
you know, homeless
or, you know, people living down there.
That's good...good just here.
I'm right to go?
Hang on a sec.
Go when you're ready.
We've been walking in
the tunnel for less than an hour,
and already we've come across somebody's home.
Here you can see their makeshift bed, blanket
and empty tins of food.
Coming across the belongings was very important
It was vital to the story.
It was absolute proof
that there was life down here.
While there is no sign of
an occupant at the moment,
it is clear the minister's assertions
of abandoned tunnels are incorrect.
This was something that
the government were denying.
This is something that we could now prove.
Hey, Nat, I'll get a shot of you
going down there, actually.
Yeah, cool.
Oh, hey. Light.
Cheers.
Mate, what's up?
What? Nothing.
It's a bit tight down there, tubby.
You reckon you're gonna make it?
He mustn't like working on the show.
Nat! You alright?
Nat, you alright?
Yeah, I'm right.
Do you need a hand?
No, I'm fine.
Nat? Look, we've already
got the sleeping bags and stuff,
we don't really need to get the lake.
We could probably do the rest up here.
Pete... Pete, I'm alright.
I just think it's a little...
I'm fine!
Just let's keep going.
Alright, you take that.
Yeah.
What's eating her?
Oh, she just really needs the story.
After what happened last time,
she's treading on thin ice.
Yeah, I reckon.
That's why John put me onto this...
make sure she doesn't fuck up again.
If she's not up to it,
why doesn't he give her the arse?
Mate, I think John'd wanna
give her a little more than just that.
Well, he'd have to get in line
behind you, wouldn't he?
Hey, guys, you might
wanna know for future reference
that these tunnels carry sound pretty well.
And as far as I can hear,
you're all arseholes.
Fuck off!
Yeah, give me the torch.
Right, yeah, hang on.
There you go, mate.
Get down there, you arsehole.
Pete, can you just lift that handle up
for me? Get a bit of sound.
Where to? Just
Yeah, nice.
Give it a kick.
Yeah, give it a kick.
Send it on its way.
What are we doing?
Just...just give it a kick.
You call it.
Uno, dos, tres, cuatro.
Thanks, guys.
The lake was just...so...vast.
I mean, this thing runs a kilometre long.
It's bigger than I thought.
Yeah, I get that a lot.
Me and Tangles were mucking around a bit
We like to play jokes on each other.
You know, if I didn't do it,
he would've done it.
So I just grabbed him and sort of went
.. you know, at the edge of the lake,
went to push him in.
You know how you go up,
hold onto their shoulders
and pull them back again?
Which I did, and then I let go of him,
and went to walk back to the camera
In he went.
Shit.
Tangles, are you right?
Yeah, slipped.
There's your dip, mate.
Steve, you...prick.
Oi, this is not funny. It's fucking cold.
Are you gonna give him a hand?
No, fuck him!
This is not... Stop laughing, OK?
How long are we gonna be down here, alright?
Tangles, as much as we used to
joke around and muck around together,
when it came time to work,
you know, he was very serious,
and it wasn't time for joking.
Creative department's ready.
Just letting you know.
OK.
Nat, just come forward a fraction.
So, you know, when he's sort of
giving me the impression
that there were problems,
I was believing him.
I'm standing directly below
one of Sydney's busiest train stations.
Behind me is the forgotten water resource
that's causing all the controversy.
Earlier this year the government
Nat, sorry. Pete, are you making noise?
No.
You weren't whispering?
Alright. Sorry, Nat.
Can we go from the top?
Everyone, just keep it quiet. Thank you.
OK, let's go from the top again.
Let's move.
When you're ready, Nat.
I'm standing directly below one of
Sydney's busiest train stations.
Behind me is the forgotten water resource
Nat, sorry. Are you guys
fucking with me? What's the noise?
What are you hearing, mate?
It's... Hang on, I'll just check the battery.
Sweet, um, I don't know.
Maybe it's your cables.
Yeah, cables don't fucking talk, Steve.
Uh, alright. Sorry, Nat.
Go for it again, I'll see what I can do.
Just go straight through.
If Tangles says he heard something,
I do believe he felt he heard something.
I can't describe how silent the place was,
so at the time I didn't feel that...
he could have been hearing anything.
It...it was strange.
I was just thinking, you know,
it could have been a technical problem,
could have been anything... some
RF interference, anything like that.
But, you know, Tangles was adamant
there was something going on,
and, uh, when he's serious about
something, you know, you believe him.
Earlier this year,
the government announced,
then quietly abandoned,
plans to recycle water from this lake.
The Minister for Water
has yet to give a reason why.
Beautiful. Pete, happy?
I'm happy. How are you, Tangles?
Oh...yeah. Yeah, sweet, yeah.
Alright, let's go.
Let's move, grab the sticks.
After we'd finished our piece at the lake, um,
we decided to head for the bell room.
Righto, Nat.
Basically the bell room was built as like
a air raid sort of alert back in the war.
They would use it to warn people of danger.
When we rang the bell,
it...it was deafening.
It rattled your ribs.
This bell is a relic of World War ll.
It remains here in the confines
of an air raid shelter,
as a reminder of what
imminent danger sounds like.
Shit, that blew my levels
right off the meter, sorry. Um
Hang on. Nat, can you just
hit the bell once more?
Yep. Ready to go?
Yep.
How's that?
Nah, look, if you want me to get that,
it's probably best I boom it from down the hall.
Yeah, OK. Well, if we need it.
OK, cool, two seconds.
Tangles decided to, um, go into
the adjoining room off the bell room
and boom it from there
just to basically kill the sound
of the level of the bell,
which was just making his levels peak out.
I don't really know much about recording sound,
but I did at the time remember
thinking, "That's a bit weird."
You know, why would you do that?
Just turn it down a little bit.
Surely it's that simple?
Uh, Steve, can you do me a favour?
Can you just listen on the cans,
watch the levels for me?
Why don't you get Pete to do it? He can
do camera, he must be able to do sound.
Nah, mate, I've done enough hard work today.
That's good, Nat, yeah.
I'll do it for ya, mate.
Sorry, guys, it's just way too echoey in here.
He asked me to listen to the audio for him,
which was fine.
It's just put on the headphones
and listen to it as it's being recorded.
Here, Tangles. Take that.
Thanks very much.
And then so Nat just went ahead and did it again,
and, uh...that's
That's when, uh
.. that's when I heard it.
Yeah, ready to go.
Bell atmos.
Whenever you're ready, Nat.
What the fuck?
Did you... did you hear that?
Yeah.
Yo, Tangles!
Tangles!
Shit.
Pete, we need some light
down here, mate. Tangles!
Quick, light.
Shit. Steve, where are you?
Down here. Straight, straight, straight.
Just give us the camera, mate.
He's... he's gone.
Where'd he go?
Tangles!
What did you hear in the headphones?
What did you hear in your headphones?
Tangles!
Would he be dickin' us round?
Tangles, come on, mate!
Steve, through here.
Tangles!
Yo, Tangles!
Here, I'll go down here.
Yeah.
You know, I knew there was something wrong.
I knew he wasn't mucking around.
My initial thought was just to get to him.
It wasn't unlike them,
so I guess my first instinct was
that they were having a joke.
What, Nat thought we were
playing a prank, did she?
You've spoken to her?
She thought we were fucking around?
Tangles, you good?
Yep. Ready to go.
Bell atmos.
Tangles!
Maybe through here...
No, that's a dead end.
Tangles!
Watch your step.
Ah, great.
What's up?
Battery.
You alright?
Yeah, fuck. It's alright.
Need the light? You got a spare?
Yeah, it's in here, hang on.
OK.
It became pretty evident, quite quickly,
that we weren't gonna be able to
find anyone or anything without light.
Got it.
We'll get him, mate. We'll find him.
We'll find him, alright?
Tangles!
Now, I had my camera light and I knew I had about
two, maybe three hours tops worth of light.
Steve, where's your kit?
Tangles!
What?
Where's your kit?
It's back in the bell room.
OK. well... all the torches
are back there, aren't they?
This is the only light you've got
and it's fucking around.
We need the torches, mate.
We've gotta go back to the bell room.
But Tangles
It's alright. We'll get him.
We'll find him. C'mon.
Fuck.
C'mon.
Walked back into the bell room
and there was nothing.
There was nothing there.
All the stuff had disappeared.
Now, that was only in a matter of
I don't know, couldn't have been too long.
Shit, everything's gone.
What?
What the hell's going on?
It certainly raised some
concern because I didn't feel
it was something that
Tangles could do by himself.
Fuck!
Hey, we're wasting time, guys. Let's go!
Wait.
C'mon!
Here, take this.
Pete!
Just give me some light, Steve.
OK.
OK, Tangles went through here.
If we follow that all the way round,
it brings us back to this room,
we can scan the whole area.
OK. So we split up and meet back here, yeah?
No, we stick together.
That's the only light we've got.
How many batteries have you got left?
I've got two in my pouch, mate.
Let's go.
Steve... STEVE!
Oh, fuck!
It won't do Tangles any good
if we run round like headless cheeks.
We stick together, alright?
You'd better keep up, then.
Tangles!
Steve, wait!
C'mon, Nat.
Tangles!
Yeah, I panicked.
You know, it wasn't like
I'm trying to be a hero or anything.
You know, the smarter thing might
have been to do something else
but it was just instinct just kicking in.
Tangles!
So, what do you think?
Think of what?
You know, Tangles,
is he dicking around?
No, he wouldn't dick around for this long.
Who took our stuff, then?
Who took it? I don't know.
Could have been the homeless, junkies
I heard it, Pete.
You heard what?
Whatever it was, mate.
Well, what was it, mate?
Steve?
Look, let's just get going, OK?
Steve? Steve? What was it?
Shit.
Watch your step.
What's in here?
Oh, fuck.
You right?
Yeah.
Nope, nothing.
Pete, we've been here twice before, mate.
The only other place has got to be the lake.
Maybe he went back from where we came.
Maybe he's waiting for us.
Oh, sure, mate. He's fucking
walked out in the pitch-black.
He's at fucking Harry's, scoffing a pie.
I don't mean that.
I mean he can't contact us.
Maybe he's waiting for us.
No, Steve's right, OK?
Tangles is down here.
He's got to be at the lake, mate.
Well, how much light have you got?
I've got enough.
Alright, then.
Shh! Do you hear that?
Shh.
Shh!
Let's go!
Go.
Tangles!
This way! Tangles!
I heard him through here. Tangles!
Tangles! I'm coming, mate!
Oh, fuck it!
In here!
Give us a hand. Quick.
Get down and grab it at the bottom.
Fuck it! Get it off! Get it open!
Grab that back. Grab that.
Oh, shit. Steve, help.
Jesus.
Steve, light. Light.
Jesus Christ.
Steve...
Yeah?
His torch.
It's his torch,
but it doesn't mean it's him, mate.
I can't really describe it,
it was just
There was blood and
.. over in the corner was...Tangles's torch.
I... I sort of thought of myself
as his older brother.
You know, that was
the kind of relationship we had.
And, uh, he was sort of entrusted to me.
That's the way I felt about it.
Let's go.
Could be anyone.
C'mon. We've got to move.
She's right. He could be close, mate.
What about Tangles?
Whatever that fucking thing is,
it could be nearby.
Come on.
It's Tangles.
Let's go.
Wait.
What?
Wait, where's my camera?
Just over there.
It's not where I left it.
What?
Before we entered the room Nat put the camera,
the night vision camera, on the ground
just outside the door.
Um...and then we went in the room.
We wouldn't have been in there
for more than two or three minutes,
and then she came out,
we all came out together,
and she noticed the camera had been moved.
My instinct was to check it
and see if it had recorded something.
Play it back.
Tangles!
Get down and grab it at the bottom.
Fuck it. Get it off! Get it open!
Grab that back. Grab that.
We played back the footage and, uh,
someone had picked up the camera,
it had come off the ground,
and there were shots of us in the room.
It's his torch,
but it doesn't mean it's him, mate.
Let's go.
C'mon. We've got to move.
She's right. He could be close, mate.
Whatever that fucking this is,
it could be nearby.
It's Tangles.
Come on.
Let's go.
And then we turn to come out
and...the camera goes down
and we just catch a glimpse...
it was just like one frame.
It happened in a split second.
I didn't know what it was, mate,
but it was quick and it was fucking frightening.
Fuck.
Oi!
This isn't good.
We've got to get out of here.
Mate, I am not fucking leaving him down here
with whatever the fuck that was.
Steve, listen, listen to me.
I'm not fucking leaving him.
Look, right now my priority is with you and Nat.
I'm not going to let what happened to
Tangles happen to both of you, alright?
We have to get out to the top.
You go on your own. Leave me here.
Steve, we need your light. Come on.
You've got your own fucking light.
Listen, Steve, listen to me.
Listen to me!
Fuck off!
I'm not done!
Don't fucking touch me, man!
Listen, listen!
Listen, listen, listen to me.
Whatever that fucking thing is
it's going to have a harder time
taking us out if we stick together.
That's bullshit.
Listen. We need to get to the top.
We need to get help.
If we get more help down here,
the better chance we 're going to find Tangles.
Fucking Tangles, man.
I know, mate.
Hey, mate, I'm with you.
I'm with you.
Come on.
Pete made sense,
but I couldn't help but feel like
I was leaving Tangles behind.
It was the hardest thing I've ever had to do.
Is he OK?
Just give him a few minutes.
So, what's the plan?
We get the fuck out of here
is the plan. Get back to the top.
What?
I think we should stay and look for Tangles.
You're not here for Tangles.
Fuck!
Just through here.
Back it up, back it up!
Hit the light. Kill the light.
Fuck!
Shh!
What is it, mate?
Shh, shh!
Anyone down there?
It's the guard.
Shit, it's the guard.
Who's there?
Hey, mate, it's us. It's the film crew.
I told you guys not to come down here.
Yeah, look, I know, we're sorry.
It's just our friend, he's gone missing.
Someone... something's taken him.
Right, I want all of you to come with me now.
Hey, come on!
Mate, what's happening in here?
Mate, tell us what's happening in here!
Nat, give it a break, Nat.
We're leaving. LET'S GO!
Is he going to help us?
Go! Go! Run!
Keep moving!
Keep going.
Keep going, Nat.
Fuck!
Not that way.
Here. Through here.
Kill the light.
Hey?
Steve, kill the light!
Shh!
Where are we?
What was that?
I don't know.
Just keep it down,
it could be close.
Did you see it?
No.
But whatever it was,
it was fucking huge.
Nat... turn it off.
Everybody alright?
Mate, mate, I'm alright.
How about your arm?
Give me the camera.
Let me see.
I hit something when we were running. It's fine.
Shit, Steve. It looks bad.
Nah.
Here, Pete, I need to see.
Here, show me.
Fuck. Doesn't look good, mate.
I can't see.
There it is. You got it.
Just there, yeah.
Sorry, you right?
I'll be fine, yeah.
Right, buddy?
Thanks, though. Thanks.
You guys ready to move soon?
We can't stay.
I just need a minute. Hang on.
What if that thing comes back?
I don't know.
Could we take it?
I doubt it.
Only thing we've got to worry
about now is getting out of here.
Hey, guys, I think it's gone.
Right, let's get moving.
Steve?
Yeah?
You right, mate?
Yeah, mate. Yeah, I'm good.
Let's go.
Just keep it quiet.
Give me the camera.
Just keep it quiet, OK?
OK, let's go.
Stay close.
Through here.
OK.
Just hold on, hold on, hold on.
Oh, fuck.
Pete...
Shit!
This wasn't here before.
Pete.
What are you doing?
It's not on the map.
What do you mean it's not on the map?
It's only got one way.
This has got two.
Pete, you've got to figure it out, OK?
Just chill the fuck out.
It's not easy, alright?
You've got to fix this.
Just shut the fuck up and let me get through it.
Nat, calm down, Nat.
It's through here. We came back
through there. It's through here.
OK, what if it's not the right way, mate?
Well, then... we find the safest room
and we wait it out.
Oh, yeah, that's a good plan.
John will figure out that we haven't called
and he'll send someone down to find us.
John knows we're here, right?
Nat
Fucking tell me John knows we're here.
Oh, you're fucking kidding me.
I can't...
Are you fucking serious?
I... I needed you guys, OK?
I knew it!
I needed you guys in this.
You need us?
Yeah.
We just lost a friend.
You still need your fucking story?
No.
Huh?
Fuck you.
Keep you voice down.
You think you're a fucking journalist.
Shh!
We came down here to get a story, didn't we?
And now we've got an important one,
and you're fucking running scared!
Shhh!
Here's your fucking story.
Here, you want your piece to camera?
Come on. Let's go.
What's your piece to camera for this one, huh?
Do you want to tell us how...
how you lost your friend
because of your fucking stupidity?
Come on.
Waiting.
Fuck you.
Come on, Nat.
Come on.
The best journalists can work under any pressure,
any sort of circumstance, come on.
See, you can't say shit, can you?
You know why?
Because you're not there, Nat.
You're just not there.
You're fucking pathetic.
Here. Through here.
Yeah.
Oh, shit.
Listen.
Shh!
What the fuck...?
What?
Shh.
What is it?
Hear that?
Through here.
Kill the light.
Shh!
Open the door, Nat.
Open it up. Open it up.
Guys, the lake's just here.
Fuck!
Shh!
Let me see, let me see.
Is it Tangles, mate?
Shh, shh.
What is it?
It's not Tangles.
What's happened to his face?
Oh, Jesus.
It's his eyes. Oh, Jesus.
What's happening?
We've got to help him.
Let me see.
Shh.
Shh!
Oh, fuck. It's seen us.
We got to go, come on, come on!
Come on, let's go!
Steve!
Fuck! Let's go. Ah!
Go, go, GO!
Just move it!
Jesus. Which way? Which way?
This way?
Go! Go now!
Where? Where?
Here, here, here. Through here!
Steve!
Go!
Come on! Keep moving!
Steve! Is he still behind us?
I think we lost him!
You sure?
I think so!
Shit.
I think we lost it!
I don't... I don't think it followed us.
In here. There's a light in here.
Here, here.
There.
What's that?
I think it's the Cross City Tunnel.
Hello?
This is a bad place to stop.
No, it's fucking pointless.
Hello?!
Shit, Pete.
Shh!
Hello! Hello!
Shh! Shh!
You've got to keep it down.
There's no-one there,
there's no-one there.
Please, someone... help. Hello!
Shh, shh.
Hello! Help!
Help!
Shh! Nat, please. Let go. Please.
You have to be quiet!
Help!
Shh!
Shh! Nat, Nat, Nat.
Hey, you guys.
Help!
You've gotta keep your voice down.
Shhh!
Shut her up.
Shh. Shh.
You get anything?
Can you see anything?
Chuck the light.
Chuck the light over there.
Nuh.
It's alright.
I'm sorry.
Hey?
It's alright, don't be sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
Shh.
It's OK, shh. Shh.
Everything was unravelling.
It... it was because of me.
I never meant for things to get so out of hand.
Well, I didn't mean to let Pete down. I mean, I
I had thought I'd made
the right choice at the time
and I didn't mean to let him down.
Steve, through here.
Quick, quick. Come on, move it, mate.
Up here.
Nat. Up.
Come on. Shh!
Here, Nat, take this.
Ohhh!
Mate, get up! Come on!
Ugh!
You know, my natural instinct
was to turn around with the light,
see what was going on.
We'd just heard this sound,
Pete yelling out, and, uh,
as soon as they sort of fell
into the pool of light
the thing just...disappeared...
upped and left
And that sort of dawned on me then
that the light was our way
of keeping it away from us.
Shit. Are you OK? You OK?
Come on!
Fuck! Did you see that?
It took off.
Let's get out of here. Let's go.
It didn't like the light.
Well, keep it on, then.
Hold on. Nat.
Nat!
Ah!
No!
Come on, come on!
Come on, you fucker!
Pete! Pete, don't.
Come on! Come on!
Go! Come on!
It was almost like it was
trying to get us in a position
where it could get to us as well.
It reminded me of a lion trying to
cut one animal out of a pack, a herd.
You know, get the weak one out,
easy to attack.
Ah! Oh, fuck! Fuck.
We're losing the light!
Oh, fuck!
- Steve!
Oh, shit!
Back, back, back!
BACK! Fuck!
Go through.
What's the matter?
No, it's a dead end. It's a dead end.
Jesus. Oh, Jesus.
I thought that was it...
it was over.
There was nowhere left to run.
Then I saw this tiny bit of wall
that looked like it had broken away.
Pete, take this, take this.
Take it!
Oh, shit!
Give her a hand, Pete. Get in there.
Hold the light still.
Easy, Nat.
Shh, keep it down. Keep it down.
Keep it down.
Here, come through, Steve.
Huh?
Come through.
Go, go, go.
Go on, you go first.
Come on, Nat.
Good girl.
Here, take this... quick.
Here, Nat.
OK.
Shh, shh, keep it down. Shh!
This isn't good.
Steve.
Steve, is that...? God.
This isn't good.
Steve.
Yeah?
We've got to go.
Fuck!
Light, mate, light.
Sorry.
It's gone.
Batteries.
Steve
Fuck, I need some light over here.
Quick, Nat, light.
Nat, the fucking light, Nat. Fuck!
Give me the torch.
Oh, shit! That one's dead.
Oh, Jesus.
There's only one left.
Come on. Come on,
come on, come on.
Steve, we need that light.
We need the fucking light.
Steve, I need the fucking light!
Come on!
OK.
Oh, Jesus.
OK, now
RUN!
Steve.
Steve. OK, OK.
Come on. It's going for her.
It's going for her.
We've got to go.
Come on. Come on.
Nat!
Let her go!
Let her go, you fucker!
Nat!
Take her. Take her!
OK.
Go. Just go!
Come on, Nat. Alright, let's go.
Oh, shit. Come on.
- Come on!
Come on, you fucker!
Come on, Nat.
Come on, let's move!
No...
Move!
No.
Come on.
Wait!
But Pete...
Come on!
No. Steve, we can't leave.
We got
Nat, keep moving.
Keep moving!
No.
We've got to keep moving!
You can't leave Pete.
We can't! We've got to go!
Come on, Nat.
We've got to keep moving.
I think that Pete was looking out for us
and I didn't want to leave him there.
Come on! Come on.
Pete wanted us to be safe...
I understand that.
But I didn't...
I didn't want to leave Pete behind.
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
- Guys!
Guys!
Shit!
Oh, fuck. It's Pete. Fuck.
Come on, man!
When I heard Pete's voice
coming down that tunnel,
out of the darkness, uh
I mean, I wasn't expecting
to hear his voice again.
Pete, no...
I can't
No
Let's go.
Let's go!
No, Pete...
- Nat!
Pete, are you OK? Stay with me.
Help! Get some help! Someone!
I need a phone! I need a phone!
Give me a phone! Give me a phone!
Hey.
Hello. Police, fire or ambulance?
Hello?
Yes. Hello?
Do you need police, fire or ambulance?
Hello!
Help! We need help, we need help!
OK, miss, we'll get you some help.
What's happened?
We're on platform one.
We're in the station.
Please, you gotta get someone here now.
My friend is dying. He's bleeding.
Please calm down, miss.
I need you to tell me exactly
where you are and what's happening.
I don't know... we're in the station
and something...
something took our friend.
OK, please stay calm.
You said you're at the station?
Which station are you at?
Help me! Somebody HELP me!
What are you doing?!
Hello? Hello?
Hello? Are you there?
Hello?
Pete... Hey, Pete.
Pete
I'm sorry... Pete! PETE!
Yeah, it's kind of hard to...
to talk about it now.
But I didn't know he was dying at that point.
You know, I thought we were all gonna be fine.
I mean
.. it had been so difficult to get
to that point where we got there,
and then, you know, I thought
we were going to be OK.
There was people around us,
there was light.
I...you know... I would have been doing more
if I thought he was lying there dying.
I...I feel that I could have
done more to help Pete.
You know, it's, um...it's easy to say
that you would do things differently,
you know.
It just didn't seem...very fair.
I got told by the first paramedics
that, you know...
they'd sort of given up working on him,
they sort of...you know...
took a while to get Nat away from him.
And, uh,
it slowly, slowly dawned on me
about that point, you know.
They sort of walked away from him.
He was just lying there,
and he wasn't moving,
and I was... I just thought, "Fuck."
I feel...I feel...I feel responsible.
I don't want to say that
I felt like it was my fault.
I don't know exactly how
I've changed since that night.
I can't help thinking we were so close.
Help was right there.
I go over it again and again.
Just constantly.
What would I do differently?
I was just pissed off with everyone, everything.
The government
.. the police
I mean, how much evidence do you want?
It's just sad now, thinking about it.
It's pointless.
It's just fucking sad.