Just one sec.
Hasta El fuego.
Please hold.
Okay.
This way.
Here you are.
Your server
Hey, Jason.
Hey.
Hi. Do you know what you want?
- Uh, yeah.
- Cool.
Thanks.
Hi!
Um...
Okay.
- Another shot?
- Yeah, sure. Okay. Um...
Hi. Hi, Reggie.
Laura, hi.
Hello. Um, so nice to phone-meet you
in this
incredibly embarrassing way.
Oh, you know, no... no problem.
It's fine.
This is what I get
for picking a trendy place
Yeah, why do they do
that here? I don't know.
I've only been in the city
for a few months.
Me, too! No way! Yeah. Oh, wow.
Well, um,
it's a very cool restaurant.
Is it on Hudson? Yes.
Am I on Hudson? I don't know.
I am not on Hudson. Shit.
Uh, I am now
walking towards Hudson.
Okay. I am so, so sorry.
This is not
the first impression
on a college professor.
Oh, pfft. Associate professor,
and it's just
film studies, so...
Oh....you're safe.
Film studies? That's...
Cool.
You say that,
but try teaching a class
to a heap
of hungover 19-year-olds.
Slashers, huh?
What's your favorite
scary movie?
Um, not that one.
So why slashers?
Well, I just, you know,
I think it's interesting.
You can really examine
the culture of the moment
by looking at
the tropes of the time.
Like, um, the masked killer,
the final girl,
the different rules:
Don't split up. Don't have sex.
Don't answer the phone.
Exactly, exactly, exactly.
It's all cliché.
But out of those clichés
comes an opportunity
for outsider art.
A voice for the voiceless,
you might say.
Mmm.
Jesus Christ.
Yeah, I'm more of
a rom-com guy,
Okay, I think I'm on Hudson.
Okay. Um...
What color is the outside
of the restaurant?
I-I think it's red.
I don't see anything red.
I, um... I could be wrong.
Let me just, um...
Let me go have
a little look-see.
Oh, okay. Thank you.
All right, um...
Yep, it's definitely red.
Yeah, I'm not seeing
anything red here.
Sure you're on Hudson?
Um... oh, crap,
I'm still a block over.
It looks like there's
an alley I can cut through.
Is the restaurant near an alley?
Um...
Yes! Yes.
There is an alley.
Oh, perfect.
I'm coming down the alley.
I don't see you.
Wait. Really? Are you sure?
Uh...
Let me just...
Uh, there are some dumpsters
about halfway down.
I see them, but I don't see you.
Yeah, I don't see you, either.
This is creepy, right?
Uh, a little bit.
20th-century slashers, huh?
Yeah. Are you sure you're
walking towards Hudson?
I'm sure.
Oh, wait, I think I see you!
Can you wave?
Can you see me?
Uh, the person I'm looking at
isn't waving.
They're just staring at me.
Are you sure?
Okay, this is weird.
Um...
Now they're moving towards me.
Are you okay?
Shit. He's following me.
I don't see anybody.
Holy shit! He's after me!
Where are you?
He's got a knife! What?
And that's not the worst part.
The worst part is...
You teach a class about slashers
and you still walked
into a dark alley.
Alone.
Okay, that's not funny.
No.
It's not.
Now I see something red.
Hey, girl, you look great!
You're not wearing
a costume? Come on.
No, I wouldn't
- have done that.
Jason.
Are you and Greg gonna come
to the okb party?
Well, if he finishes his
Spanish project in time,
Is your sister coming?
No, Sam wouldn't be caught dead
at a frat party.
There's a first time
for everything.
Not tonight, though.
- Can't convince her?
- No. That's not my problem,
- Save me a drink!
- All right.
Honey, I'm home!
Greg?
I'm sorry, okay?
I...
I just got massive blue balls,
and I... I had to practice.
Please don't be mad.
How mad are you?
Oh, I'm not mad, Jason.
Dude.
We said we wouldn't
use the voice on each other.
We said a lot of things.
This is Greg, right?
Who else would it be?
Where are you?
I want to tell you about it.
Oh, by the way,
we should go to that frat party.
Tara's going.
What was it like? Not on the phone, man.
Seriously, turn off
the fucking voice modulator.
I'm just trying
to get the voice right.
You got to have your practice,
I get mine.
Whatever.
Just tell me what it felt like.
Then maybe I'll come out.
Dude, I know you're not here.
Humor me.
All right, fine.
It was even better
than we ever could have imagined.
I mean,
when the knife went in her,
it's like
she wasn't human anymore.
Just an animal.
And every time it went in,
she was less and less human.
And then,
she was just meat.
But she wasn't just meat, Jason.
She was a person.
Our film professor.
Yeah, well,
fuck her.
She gave me a c-minus
on my giallo paper.
Is that why you killed her?
Because of the c-minus?[Sighs]
Who's next, your grade-school
vice principal?
You know who's next.
Why are you being like this?
Come on, Jason.
How long
have we known each other?
You tell me.
Eight years.
We met in junior high.
In Atlanta.
I just want you to tell me
why you think
In your words.
We're finishing Richie's film.
That's right,
by killing Sam and Tara.
Why are you fucking with me?
Why won't you tell me
where you are?
Why do you keep asking me that?
I already told you.
I'm here.
Let's play a game.[Sighs] shit.
Do you know warmer, colder?
Come on, find me.
And then we'll go and cut up
the carpenter sisters.
Are you using
the fucking cameras?
Yeah. The cameras.
And at the moment,
you're very, very cold.
All right, douchebag,
let's play.
Cold.
Heating up.
Warmer.
All right, you know what?
This is stupid.
I'm gonna hang up now.
But you're getting warmer.
Colder.
Warmer.
You're on fire!
Oh, fuck!
Do you feel
like an animal, Jason?
Please, stop!
Like meat?
But we have to finish the movie.
Who gives a fuck about movies?
♪ In my head ♪
♪ let it begin ♪
♪ push it away
but it's pulling me in ♪
♪ trying to pretend ♪
♪ I'm not aware
when I do it again ♪
♪ I know the signs ♪
♪ I see the pattern
in front of my eyes ♪
♪ something inside me
open it wide ♪
♪ stretching me ♪
♪ in my head ♪
♪ I can feel it getting closer ♪
♪ breathing heavy
on my shoulder ♪
♪ and I'm trying to fake it ♪
♪ but there's no way
to escape it ♪
♪ in my head ♪
So how are the new meds
treating you?
Okay, I think.
Still not seeing anyone
I shouldn't be.
What I'm really worried about,
though, is Tara.
What I'm really
worried about is you.
You've been coming here
for six months now,
and all we've
really spoken about
is how your sister
isn't dealing with
whatever happened to both of you
a year ago.
Now, you've alluded
to an abusive relationship,
issues with your father,
but every time I push you
for specifics, you shut down.
I have trust issues.
Okay.
If I'm going to help you,
um, I... I need you to
give me the details.
Okay.
My father was Billy loomis.
He was a famous serial killer.
They made a movie about him.
Yeah. Mm-hmm.
Certainly did.
Last year I found out
that my boyfriend
was also a serial killer
and only dating me
because he idolized my father.
- Uh-huh.
- Him and his psycho girlfriend
killed a bunch of people.
And when it got out
that I'm Billy's daughter,
this crazy rumor started online
that I orchestrated
the whole thing and framed them.
Huh?
Richie was my boyfriend.
But you didn't.
- Of course not.
- Okay.
He almost killed my sister
and me,
before I stopped him.
Okay, and how...
How-how did you stop him?
Well, I stabbed him 22 times
and slit his throat.
And then I shot him in the head.
But that's not why I'm here.
Why are you here?
Because...
It felt right.
I... [clears throat] Uh...
I think we're done here.
What? No, you said
give you details. I'm just...
I... I'm not equipped
to deal with this kind of thing.
Please, Dr. Stone.
I'm asking for your help.
By law, I'm required
to report this
Report it? Report what?
I didn't say
I was gonna do anything.
Not explicitly, no.
You know what?
Forget it.
You're just like all the others.
Hey, you've reached Tara.
Why aren't you texting me?
You know you're supposed
to pick up when I call.
I got out of therapy early,
so I was thinking
If you want.
I'll see you soon.
Hey!
Tara?
Oh, yeah.
Quinn?
Oh, shit.[Quinn's lover] come on!
Were we being too loud?
Not at all.
Have you seen Tara?
Um...
Don't be mad.
- Why would I be mad?
- Because you get mad.
Is that Paul?
Who the fuck is Paul?
Life, I have found,
is about variety.
Okay.
- Uh, this one's yours.
- Thanks.
Where's Tara?
She went
to the omega kappa beta party.
I begged her not to go to that!
And we've now arrived at mad.
Do you know if she at least
took her taser?
I cannot speak
to how heavily armed Tara is
at this fraternity party.
Babe, you coming back? "Babe"?
I don't know.
Ooh,
is cute boy shirtless again?
- Who's cute boy, babe?
- Always you... sweetie.
You guys have been checking
each other out for months.
Why don't you just talk to him?
Because that right there
is about all the romantic
interaction I'm ready for.
- I'm gonna go find Tara.
- Okay.
- Be right back.
- Bye.
[Whispers] Damn.
♪ And for the last 300 months
I made 16 albums... ♪
Chug, chug, chug, chug!
♪ Two singers
and ten comedians ♪
♪ and I'm still gonna yell it
every time you see me in ♪
♪ what's my favorite word... ♪
What up, man?
Where can I get another beer?
Who's drinking?
Let's party!
Hey, guys.
Oh, my god, Lou, how are you?
♪ Blow the whistle ♪
♪ blow the whistle ♪
It doesn't bother you?
Being at a house party
after you were almost
brutally murdered
at a house party?
No, I think of it
like being struck by lightning.
The odds of it happening twice
to the same person
are extremely low.
Ah.
Guess I should stay close
to you then.
Shit, I'm sorry.
Watch out.
Hi.
How are you doing, t?
You're lying.
No, last one's kicked.
We got some hard stuff
in the kitchen, though.
Frankie.
Tara.
Lead the way.
You omega beta zeta?
No, not yet.
But I might rush it.
Oh, freshman. Right on!
Where from?
Michigan.
All right.
You know what?
I got a bottle of fireball
up in my room.
Fuck it. Yeah, go.
- Uh... oh, I don't love that.
- Mm-mmm.
Hey!
You want to call it a night?
No, uh...
I think that I'm actually
still gonna hang,
but you guys don't have
to wait for me.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of her.
I'm Frankie.
And I'm spectacularly uninterested
in knowing anything about you.
No, dude, Anika,
I'm not that bad.
But I appreciate you
looking out for me.
Let me see it in your face.
Mmm. Mmm.
- Closer. Closer. Ooh. Uh.
- Ooh.
All right, all right.
Cheers, man, to the dynamic duo
of hortense tower,
third floor, room 315.
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
Oh, man.
Time to start making moves.
Yeah, get you out there.
Introduce you to some girls!
What about her?
She's gorgeous.
- Great. Ask her out.
- No, I can't.
Ask her out. Ask her out.
Shut up!
Got to have confidence.
Plus, look at you, man!
You're a snack!
Practically an entire meal
all on your own.
- Really?
- Yeah. You're Ethan Landry.
Hey, excuse me!
- Chad.
- Howdy. How you doing?
My friend here,
he's a snack, right?
- What did that mean?
- No, it's good.
- What?
- It's not bad.
There's room for improvement!
Hey, big guy, you're needed.
See ya.
Aren't you that girl involved
in that "stab" shit
in California last year?
No.
That's a different pirate.
Hey, partner!
Tara's good down here.
Sorry, bro, I didn't catch that.
Yeah, you did.
No, Chad.
- It's fine. I want to.
- Yeah, see, Chad?
- It's okay.
- She wants to.
Come on.[Winces] ow!
- Get your fucking hands off her.
- Get the fuck off me!
Guys!
Who the fuck are you,
risky business?
Stop![Sam] guys, guys!
Sorry to interrupt.
I'm just gonna tase you
in the balls real quick.
Don't ever lay hands
on my sister.
You fucking bitch!
Sam.[Frankie] Fuck you!
Are you fucking kidding me?
You're stalking me now?
Holy shit,
it's that psycho girl!
That's her?
Tara. Will you stop?
I cannot believe you did that!
You embarrassed me.
That guy was a dick.
He was gonna
take advantage of you.
- So?
If I want to hook up
with an asshole,
that's my decision!
- It's my decision.
- Okay.
It's not about you!
You're out of my life
for five years,
and then you can't
leave me alone for five minutes.
Because you're not dealing
with what happened to us.
Have you even gone
to see the counselor once?
No, I'm not going to.[Sam] why not?
Because I'm uninterested in
living in the past like you are.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Guys, come on.
It means I'm not gonna let what
happened to us for three days
define the rest of my life.
So you're just gonna
pretend it never happened.
What are you doing here, Sam?
In New York.
You're working two shitty jobs
to help with rent, whatever,
but what's your plan?
I know what I'm gonna do.
Okay? Because I'm gonna
keep going to college,
I'm gonna get my degree,
and I'm gonna live my life.
My life.
Okay? I know.
You just followed me here,
and you won't let me
out of your sight.
I'm just trying
to look out for you.
I...
I know.
I know you are.
You can't do it
for the rest of my life, though.
You have to let me go.
Hey!
Murderer!
What the fuck is wrong
with you, bitch?
You got a problem with me?
You guys should stay away
from her.
- She knows what she did.
- I didn't fucking do anything!
Sure, bitch.
Walk away!
I'm so sick of this shit.
Hey, calm down. Come on.
Hey, I have tissues
if you want tissues.
I have, like, three tissues.
♪ Don't you know too much
already? ♪
♪ I'll only hurt you
if you let me ♪
♪ call me friend
but keep me closer... ♪
[Quinn] Hey.
I'm sorry I told Sam
where you went.
It's fine. I just...
She's all the way up my ass.
Like usual.
I know what it's like
when they hold on too tight.
After we, um...
Lost my brother,
my dad wouldn't leave me alone.
He even transferred to the NYPD
when I got into college, so...
Stalker much?
I'm gonna go,
let you guys... chat.
[Tara] Thank you.
You can, um,
go back to your dorm.
I'm pretty sure
the fighting is done
That's too bad.
I was actually looking forward
to getting some shots in
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
Bring it.
Um...
Thank you
for not letting me go
up those stairs.
♪ ...you'll be a dream ♪
Yeah, I don't know,
I think I was just
more messed up
♪ And I watch you float
cross the floor
Survivors got to
stick together... you know.
And besides,
you can do a lot better
Tara, you're...
I think you're really special.
♪ Maybe we're only strangers
on mystery trains ♪
♪ you're only a ghost
who has stolen my heart away ♪
I'm not messed up anymore.
Just so you know.
Okay.
♪ Now, if you need me... ♪
I forgot my phone.
- Did I cock-block you?
- What did you just say?
- I cock-blocked you.
- No.
I cock-blocked you,
didn't I? Immediate no.
Please stop saying
the word "cock."
What did you need?[Quinn] my phone.
Don't ever enter a room
- like that again.
- No, it was rude.
- I'm gonna go.
But get some rest, get sober,
and please don't kill
your sister, okay?
She loves you very much.
Good night![Tara] bye-bye.
Quinn...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Fuck.
♪ Maybe we were always strangers
on mystery trains ♪
♪ you were only a ghost
that has stolen my heart away ♪
[Whispers] Careful.
Someone might see us.
You always say
the most romantic things.
- Danny.
- What?
Can I help it if my kink is
"woman who's ashamed
Come on.
You know it's not that.
I'm just not ready for...
I know, for your sister
and your friends to know
that you enjoy
physical contact
I get it, I do.
Your secret is safe with me.
A little thing...
It's not a big deal...
I just can't help but notice
that you're covered
Um, I'm pretty sure
it's diet cherry coke, actually.
- Oh.
- What, you don't like it?
No, I love it! I do.
It's a very sensual,
aromatic choice.
Was that another conspiracy nut?
Being famous
isn't all it's cracked up to be.
And Tara's pissed at me.
- Again.
She says she wants me
to let her go.
Yeah, family can be rough.
Sam!
Get up here right now!
I'm standing in front
of the apartment building...
What's going on? ...Where
the mutilated bodies
of two students... Cute boy. Nice.
Were discovered.
Their names have just
been released by police.
Jason carvey and Greg bruckner.
Holy shit, that's that chode
from our film studies class!
The one obsessed with
argento. Also found at the scene
were various ghostface costumes,
a character popularized
by thestab movie franchise.
Pack a bag.
We leave in ten.
Sam! Wait, Sam!
- We're getting out of the city.
- What?
Thank you, suspicious new guy,
but we got it from here.
Have a good night.
Get home safe.
Go, go, go.
Sam!
Sam, wh...
Hold on.
- Come on.
No, wait, let's talk
about this for a second.
'Cause this might not
have anything to do with us.
- Are you serious?
- It's a big city!
It's Halloween.
Everybody's wearing masks!
- You don't know.
- Tara,
- You knew him!
- Barely.
Chad, mindy, back me up.
It is a little bit... close to home.
See?
Quinn, your dad's a cop, right?
Can you call him
and find out what's going on?
Before you make
the unilateral decision
to abandon my college education
and flee the fucking state!
- I'm calling him now.
- Thank you.
Who is it?
Why did everyone just freak out
when her phone rang?
You got to keep up, my dude.
Sam?
My dad wants to talk to you.
Mr. Bailey, hi.[Mr. Bailey] hey, Sam.
I was actually just about
to call you.
Well, my sister thinks
I'm probably overreacting.
No, unfortunately, you're not.
What do you mean?
What's going on?
I'm afraid I need you
to come down to the station.
Sam, slow down.
Tara, no.
Get back inside, lock the door.
Are you serious?
Now you don't want
to stick together?
Fine.
What the fuck?
I never deleted his contact.
This is coming
- from his number.
Just let it ring.
Sam.
Who is this?
Hello, Samantha.
Did you miss me?
I want you to think
long and hard
about whether you really
want to do this.
Because the last two people
that fucked with us
ended up dead.
You should be thanking me, Sam.
Jason and Greg were gonna
kill you and your sister.
I gutted them
before they had the chance.
So what?
You're protecting us now?
Not quite.
I'm going to show the world
who you really are:
A liar and a killer.
I'm going to punish you, Sam.
You shouldn't believe
everything you read
Don't be cute.
You're gonna pay
And I'm not gonna stop
until I butcher you.
You and anyone
who gets between us.
You and Tara
better watch your backs.
You better watch yours.
No! No!
Run!
Come on!
- Help! Please!
- In there!
Please help us!
- We were just attacked.
- Call 911!
There's a fucking line here,
girls.
I'm telling you, sir.
Could you...
You got a problem here, guy?
Hey!
- Go out the back!
- Thank you!
Fuck, it's locked.
- Keys! We need your keys!
- Look out!
- Watch out!
Wait.
Wait, wait! No, no, no!
Run! Go! Run!
Let's go.[Officer 2] going round back.
This was found next to the body
at the apartment crime scene.
DNA says that it belonged
to someone named Richie kirsch.
Does that ring a bell?
We're familiar with him.
But the one that attacked us
had a different mask on.
It was kind of more beat up.
Like it was older.
Uh...
I got to ask...
Do you have alibis
for earlier tonight?
I was at a party
with my friends.
I was at my therapist's.
I can give you his information.
You can call to check
And then I met Tara
at that party,
where I tased someone.
Unrelated.
Was that before
or after this happened?
Murderer!
What the fuck
is wrong with you, bitch?
You got a problem with me? Before.
The point is,
we were with people all night.
So, our roommate's dad
just happened to pull our case.
That'd be a crazy coincidence, right?
- Yeah.
- The detective who had the case,
he offered it to me
because it involves Quinn.
Um, but I can totally give it
back if you're uncomfortable.
It's up to you.
It's fine.
So if the man who attacked you
did steal your license
and plant it next to the body,
it'd probably be somebody
close to you.
How long have you known
your friends?
Well, we moved here
with mindy and Chad
for summer semester,
like, six months ago.
So, Quinn, um, Ethan, Anika...
All since then.
I think I can vouch for Quinn,
so that's one less
Do either of you have anyone
that might want to target you?
Not anyone who's still alive.
Yikes.
FBI's here,
claiming jurisdiction.
Where are they?
Can I help you?
Special agent Kirby Reed, FBI.
I work out
of the Atlanta office.
Oh. You lost?
Your two vics
were residents of my city
before they moved here
for college.
I have been investigating
their online activity
for the past few months.
Wow.
Why?
I take a special interest
in ghostface attacks.
- Kirby?
- Hey, Sam.
What?
Tara.
You're the FBI? Mm-hmm.
- You guys know each other?
- Yeah.
We went
to woodsboro high together.
She was a senior
when I was a freshman.
We share a certain history, yeah.
I'm not trying to get into
a jurisdictional
pissing contest here,
I just want to help.
I'll show you mine, et cetera.
Thank you.
He left this mask at the bodega.
DNA traces of two individuals,
Charlie Walker, Jill Roberts,
both deceased.
The ghostface killers of 2011.
Charlie Walker gave me this.
Like I said,
I take a special interest.
Is this the mask he was wearing
when he attacked you?
No.
So he's leaving them on purpose.
Which means whoever's doing this
is a student of the killers
who came before.
Maybe he believes
Sam is the latest
in a long line.
Yeah, good luck with that.
We're getting out of town.
I'm sorry, that's not possible.
You're both persons of interest
in a double homicide,
so you're not allowed
to leave town. Sorry.
- Are you serious?
- He's right.
But if we work together... we're going.
Samantha, do you have an alibi
for last night's murders?
Tara, do you feel safe
around your sister?
Tara! Tara!
Gale weathers, channel 4.
Do you ladies
think you're the reason
the ghostface killer
has come to the big apple?
Nice try, sweetie,
but I've done this dance before.
Stay away from us.
Are you still mad at me?
You said you wouldn't write
a book about what happened.
And then you wrote a book
about what happened.
Oh, come on.
Somebody was gonna write
about it!
It's what I do.
I heard you couldn't sell
the movie rights.
It's all about true-crime
limited series these days.
After everything
we went through together.
What would Dewey think?
- That's a low blow.
- So was your book.
You called me "unstable"
and a "born killer."
- That's taken out of context.
- That's literally a quote.
You don't think
what you wrote
with what's happening to us?
Come on.
Hey, I talked to Sidney.
She's not coming here,
- is she?
She sends her love,
but she's taking Mark
and the kids someplace safe.
She deserves
to have her happy ending.
On that much, we agree.
Hey, I want to catch this fucker
as much as you do!
Maybe.
Or maybe you're just afraid
that without ghostface
in your life,
you're gonna fade away.
You fools! You're in danger!
Can't you see?
They're after you!
They're after all of us!
Our wives,
our children, everyone!
They're here already!
You're next!
You're next! You're next!
Who is it?
You're a day early
for trick-or-treating, you know.
♪ Take a little walk
to the edge of town ♪
♪ and go across the tracks... ♪
Okay, nerds, listen up!
As terrifying as this all is,
I'm actually glad
I get a chance to redeem myself
for not calling the killers
last time.
- Yep.
- It's fine. Okay.
The way I see it, someone is out
to make a sequel to the requel.
Um, what's a requel?
You're beautiful, sweetie.
Let's hold questions to the end.
Stab 1 took place in woodsboro.
Stab 2 took place in college.
So we think that
the killer is trying
That is one possibility.
Heroes now in college:
Check.
Suspicious new characters
brought in
and/or body count:
Check, check and check.
But it can't just be
about stab 2.
- Why not?
- It would make sense
if this were just a sequel.
But we're not in a sequel,
because nobody
just makes sequels anymore.
We're in a franchise!
And there are certain rules
to a continuing franchise.
- I had a feeling.
- Rule one:
Everything is bigger
than last time.
Bigger budget, bigger cast,
bigger body count.
Longer chases, shoot-outs, beheadings.
You got to top what came before
to keep people coming back.
- Beheadings?
- Beheadings.
Rule two:
Whatever happened last time,
Franchises only survive
by subverting expectations.
If the killers last time
were whiny snowflake film nerds
with letterboxd accounts
instead of personalities,
you can bet
the opposite will be true here.
And rule three:
No one is safe.
Legacy characters?
Cannon fodder at this point.
Usually brought back
only to be killed off
in some cheap bid for nostalgia.
It's not looking too good
for Gale and Kirby.
Oh, and that's
not even the worst part!
This is the part where she
tells us the worst part.
The worst part is
franchises are just
continuing episodic installments
Which means main characters
are completely expendable now, too.
Laurie strode, Nancy Thompson,
Ellen Ripley,
Sally hardesty, Jigsaw,
Tony stark, James Bond...
I mean, even Luke Skywalker...
All died so their franchises
could live on.
That means it's not
just the friend group.
Any of us could go at any time,
especially Sam and Tara.
Wait, any of us?[Mindy] Yeah.
Am I in the friend group?[Mindy] yeah.
Am I, like,
one of the targets?[Mindy] mm-hmm.
Am I gonna die a virgin?
That was a weird overshare.
But it brings us
to our current suspects:
Ethan.
The shy, dorky guy
who no one suspects
because he's so shy and dorky.
Why am I on the suspect list?
Because I'm randomly
Chad's roommate?
Roommate lotteries can be juked.
You could have fixed it
to get next to us.
Quinn.
The slutty roommate.
A horror movie...
Classic.
"Sex positive,"
but... thank you?
Mm-hmm. Um, how did you come
to live with Sam and Tara?
I answered their ad online.
Okay, say no more.
You've already implicated
yourself enough.
It was an anonymous ad, mindy.
And you know we vetted her.
Plus her dad is a cop.
And that makes it more likely
that she's the killer,
because having a cop dad
is a great cover.
Do you not remember
how these movies work, Tara?
Is she always like this?
And finally... Anika.
Never trust the love interest.
Okay! So, we have our rules
and we have our suspects.
But wait.
What about you guys?
I mean, I think it's pretty safe
to rule out the four of us
who went through this last year
in woodsboro.
- Agreed.
- Um, not agreed.
What if the trauma
you all went through
caused one
or more of you to snap?
Yeah, or the fame you got
from the killings
I mean, let's be honest here,
some of the theories online
about Sam are...
Don't you fucking dare.
Okay, she's right, though.
I mean, face facts...
If we're all suspects,
you're all suspects.
Remember Samantha carpenter's
- alibi, the therapist?
He was stabbed
- to death. Through the nose.
Through the nose.
How messed up is that?
It's pretty messed up.
He turned her in
for making threatening remarks,
ended up dead.
And guess which patient's
notes were stolen?
So Sam kills her own alibi and
steals her own session notes?
Maybe.
Another mask
was found at the scene.
It's a DNA match
for Roman Bridger.
The ghostface
who was directing stab 3.
It's like he's leaving us
real-life franchise easter eggs.
Like dropping
the killers' masks in reverse.
Almost like he's counting down
to something.
What happens
when he gets to one?
So we've had nine
ghostface killers so far.
Nine. I thought in the movies...
Forget about the movies.
The movies don't matter.
Look. Last year was
Amber Freeman and Richie kirsch,
whose masks we found
at the first crime scene
along with the bodies
of two film students
who killed their professor
earlier that same night.
Then it was Jill Roberts
and Charlie Walker...
Theirs at the bodega.
Roman Bridger was the only
single ghostface.
Kudos to him for ambition.
His mask
was found at the shrink's.
Which leaves Mickey altieri,
Nancy loomis, stu macher...
And Billy loomis. Number one.
And the father
of our chief suspect.
Well, whoever's doing this
is leading us back to Sam.
I will check in later.
And tell your daughter
to stay sharp.
Proximity to the carpenters
is proximity to ghostface.
Hey, Jack? Would you call
the Atlanta field office?
Dig up what you can
on agent Reed.
I think you should
get out of the city.
You know, considering
what happened to you
I... I wouldn't blame you
if... you wanted to go.
That's very thoughtful of you,
but, um,
I don't think
I'm going anywhere.
Will you two
just make out already?
That is so inappropriate,
- dude.
Get it over with!
Here you go.
Sam?[Sam] Yep?
We do not have to stay here.
Well, too bad. I insist.
Safety in numbers.
This'll be so fun.
A little slumber party
with the core four!
- "Core four"?
- Yeah.
- Did you give us a nickname?
- I sure did.
We've been through
a lot together,
and it's a pretty cool nickname.
- That's debatable.
- It's extremely debatable.
You can't just give yourself
a nickname, dingus.
Of course I can, dingus,
because I just did.
- Core four, up top!
- No.
- Down low.
- Get that away from me.
Please,
- for the love of god.
I would like a little more
respect and support
from my fellow members
of the core four.
Guys. What the hell?
We're hearing from sources
inside the homicide division
that the prime suspect is none
other than Samantha carpenter,
one of the survivors of
the woodsboro killings in 2022,
seen here attacking a woman
on the street last night.
Is wrong with you?
You got a problem with me?
Knock it off!
Stay away from her.
She knows what she did.
In the wake
of the woodsboro tragedy
rumors sprouted online
that carpenter was actually
responsible for the killings,
blaming the crimes
on her boyfriend, Richie kirsch
and teen Amber free...
I know you're not a fan
of the way
and that I've been giving you
a really hard time.
But I can say
that none of us can relate
to what you are experiencing.
And I'm really, really sorry
that you have to do that alone.
It's not your fault.
And I know I shouldn't care
what people think.
It just sucks being this hated.
Hey. Hey. Just a reminder,
not a single person
in this room hates you.
Okay?
We have all been through
and we are
coping with it differently.
But, I mean,
we moved here together
for one very specific reason.
We are a team.
We are
the core fucking four.
- Thank you very much.
- Ah, I hate myself.
You said it.
That is what I'm talking about.
It's the core four.
Say it.[Tara] I'm not gonna say it.
I mean, yes,
we're a team, but...
It's got a nice ring to it.
I've been sleeping with cute boy
from across the hall.
- Boom!
- I fucking knew it!
- I knew it, I knew it.
- You called it.
I knew it from the day
you had that hickey.
Sales
of the ghostface Halloween mask
across the tri-state area
in the last 24 hours
I've got my mask.
What about you, Jay?[Jay] you know it.
It's gonna be
one spooky Halloween.
I'll say. Now, let's get over to guy
for a look at our weather.
I know she's my roommate,
but you're, like, the police.
Yo.
[Quinn] No, I know.
Hey!
Fuck.
Hey, yeah.
Wassup, bitch?
I see you, motherfucker.
Sam! Samantha!
I feel like we should high five
or something.
The core four high five...
May we, please?
Don't call it that,
but we'll do the high five.
Come on.
Sam! Samantha!
Sam, what the fuck?
She's really
freaked out and paranoid.
Babe, you gonna join me?[Quinn] hang on.
No. And don't use
my good face wash.
It's ph-balanced for women.
Pick up your phone, baby.
Is that him?
- No, Tara. Not right now.
- Hey, what are your intentions?
[Chad] That's right.
It's fine. I'll call him back.
Poor guy.[Chad] okay.
Quinn and her gentleman caller
are back at it again.
She's getting it,
too? Okay.
Help! Stop!
Tara, wait, wait!
Run.
Oh, shit!
Guys, come on!
Oh, fuck.
[Anika] Mindy!
Stay the fuck back!
Hey!
Wait, wait, Chad!
- They're still up there.
- Shit!
Fuck.
- Sam!
- Do you have the keys?
No, I left them inside!
Mindy, bathroom door. Hurry!
Oh, fuck! That guy's dead.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck.
Hey!
Shit.
Don't worry, I got you.
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- You have a better idea?
Fuck. No.
You have to come one at a time.
- You two go first. Mindy!
- What? No.
Someone needs to hold the door.
I'll send Anika next. Go!
Sam, come on.
Eyes on me, baby.
Keep your eyes on me.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my god.[Danny] I got you, baby.
Baby, come on!
It won't hold me.
Okay.
It ain't going anywhere.
It's gonna hold you, I promise.
Danny.
I got you.
You ain't going nowhere.
- She's losing a lot of blood!
- Say something more positive!
Eyes on me, Sam.
Come on, baby.
[Danny] Come on. I got you.
Come on, I got you.
Okay.
- Come on!
- Let's go!
- Come on, mindy!
- Let's go, we got to move!
Anika, come on!
Anika![Danny] Go! Come on!
You have to go first.[Anika
whimpering] I can't.
You have to go.
Mindy, no! I'll be
right behind you, I promise.
Mindy, come on.
You got to get over here!
Let's go!
We got you.[Sam] that's it. Mindy.
Slow and steady.[Sam] we got you.
Oh, god.
Baby, you can't stop.[Sam]
get over here right now!
Anika's coming right behind you.
Anika, come on![Danny] go!
You can do it![Mindy] come on, Anika!
Oh, god!
I can't do it, I can't do it.
Don't look down![Mindy] look at me!
You can do it!
You're doing good.
What?
Anika, you have to move
right now!
No, god! Please, no!
Anika, you got to move!
No!
You have to make it!
Baby, I don't want to die!
No, Anika.
Anika, give me your hand.
I got you.
No!
So are you
pullin' anybody for interviews?
How far along are you on that?
Uh, just got two.
Okay.
Hey. You okay?
This isn't your fault, Sam.
But it is.
Someone took our knives,
so we couldn't fight back.
I don't know who I can trust.
Then don't trust anyone.
Not your friends. Not me.
Not anyone.
I have
a few more questions for you.
Just this way, Danny.
Chad.
- Where were you?
- What? When?
- Last night!
- What?
I had econ.
You know this.
Bullshit, man!
You disappear,
and my sister
almost gets killed!
Dude, I was in a study hall
with a hundred other people.
You can ask any of them.
Fuck, man.
Oh, my god.
Who?[Chad] Anika and Quinn.
Mindy, I'm so sorry.
Step the fuck back.
You're at the top of my list.
I had econ!
Go right ahead, sir.
I'm gonna be right back.
I'm really sorry about Quinn.
Thank you.
Both my kids are gone.
My whole family...
Is gone.
They took me off the case.
But I'm not gonna stop
until I find him.
You fuck with my family...
You die.
Agreed.
Hey, are you okay?
I came as soon as I heard.
Gale, I swear to god...
Truce, okay?
I'm here for whatever you need.
Okay. Nice try.
Really, I am.
Okay, fine.
Off the record, okay?
Okay. Thank you.
I'm sorry I punched you.
No, you're not.
I'm not.
You're the cop, right?
I did some digging
on your first two victims
and I found something.
I know where the masks
are coming from.
Show me.
Ladies.
Kirby?
Gale.
She's with the FBI.She's a child.
When did they start
letting children into the FBI?
- I'm 30.
- Well, you look like a zygote.
I have a gun, Gale.
Okay, fine. You're gonna
want to see this, too.
Jason and Greg
were little Atlanta rich boys.
Apparently, they used
fake names to rent this place.
How did you find it?
It's called
"investigative journalism"
How didn't you find it?
Weren't you tracking them?
I went through
their financial records
This was not in any of them.
Doesn't make sense.
Don't worry.
I'm just really good at my job.
You'll get there.
What is this place?
What's with all the security?
It's a movie theater.
It's not just a theater.
It's a shrine.
Whoa.
They've got
the whole goddamn franchise.
- Chad?
- Mmm?
This was uncle Randy's.
They've got everything.
Is that... the knife I was stabbed with.
You all have been through
so much.
Who drew all these?
Dewey.
Hey, how'd they get
all this stuff?
Isn't this evidence?
Well, cops like money,
and evidence can get lost
pretty easily.
Present company excluded,
of course.
Um, why am I here exactly?
My alibi checks out.
So I can keep an eye on you, roomie.
The killer must have
found this place
before he murdered Jason
and Greg.
And then he took the masks
off the mannequins.
All nine, from stu and Billy
to Amber and Richie.
Hot damn!
How fucking cool is this place?
Fuck, no.
Fuck, yes.
Come on, Sam,
you got to be excited
to get our murder on again. Together.
Billy and Sam.
Team loomis.
Get ready to slice up
more motherfuckers.
What are you doing?
I don't know.
So,
somebody killed
these chucklefucks
and took over?
Someone who believes that Sam
masterminded woodsboro.
If this were
a normal stab movie,
this would be the killer's lair.
Which means this isn't
a normal stab movie.
The TV that killed stu macher.
If you believe he's dead.
I hear you're a horror fan.
- It's been said.
- Mmm.
Mmm.
Best nightmare on elm street?
The original.
Best Friday the 13th?
Part ii.The final chapter.
Had a crush on Corey feldman.
Okay. Respect.
Psycho ii is...
Underrated.
Candyman.
the original or requel?
Both.
Okay. Okay.
Game recognize game.
Hmm.
You okay?
Sam, when do I get
to be a normal person again?
I don't know.
I don't want
to be a part of this.
I don't want to be a part
of some stupid legacy
because i'm... because of me.
I'm sorry.
Just drop it, Sam.
Tara.
I got her.
That seemed intense.
Ever since I came back
into her life, I've just...
Made a mess of it.
Hey.
Where's your mother in all this?
She cut me off
when I told Tara
Then Tara cut her off
because she wouldn't talk to me,
so now neither of us
have a mother.
I'm sorry to say this,
but fuck her.
My parents sucked, too.
But you can still
make your own family.
Even if it's just
with one person.
And if you lose that one person?
You just... you keep going.
And maybe
you find another loner,
and you look after each other.
How'd you get past
what happened to you?
I almost died
after I was stabbed.
Technically, I did die.
For four minutes.
When I recovered...
I got mad.
I didn't want
to spend the rest of my life
I wanted the monsters
to be afraid of me.
I like that.
[Bailey] Sorry to interrupt.
Think I might have an idea
about how to turn the tables
on this creep.
Yeah. We're in.
Sorry, Gale.
No press allowed.
Police business.
I'm good at my job, too.
You should have stayed
with the others.
That's not gonna happen.
There's no point in both of us
putting ourselves at risk.
I'm not.
I'm your backup.
So we're really doing
the phone tracing thing
that never works in the movies.
It'll be all, "keep him talking,
Sam. Two more minutes,
I've almost got him."
And then he hangs up just
before we can get a lock.
I can trace a call
in under 15 seconds.
Well, you've got them
out there as bait.
Because the killer usually calls
from somewhere nearby.
And you think they're safe
because it's broad daylight
in a public place?
Look, I am here, okay?
And so is Bailey.
This is exactly
how our uncle Randy died.
Broad daylight.
Public place.
Yanked into a Van.
Stab, stab, stab. No more Randy.
Huh.
Hey, Sam?
Stay frosty out there, okay?
We're good.
You're gonna die, you know.
No, you're gonna die, Samantha!
Choking on your own blood
while I hack up your sister.
Unless we find you first.
For a mastermind,
you're not very bright.
Waiting for me to call,
desperately hoping I'm nearby
so the police can grab me?
But I'm not nearby.
I'm a step ahead.
Be seeing you, Samantha.
- Did you get it?
- Yep. Geolocation
He's on the upper West Side.
He's inside
an apartment building,
halfway across the city.
- On west 96th?
- How did you know that?
Gale.
"No press."
Bitch, last time I saw you,
you were in glee club.
Forgive me if I don't trust you
to keep them safe.
- Here you go, baby.
- Thanks.
My friend Danny works
on the upper West Side.
He can get there quicker.
Yeah,
or he could finish her off.
Is it possible he's the killer?
Fuck.
We have to get there now.
It's 50 blocks away.
We don't even know if it's true.
- Sam, wait! Take a minute.
- We don't have a minute.
You have to trust me,
we got to make the right call.
He's already... [Tara] Sam!
Get in.
What's she doing?
Hey, get out of my car!
What do you think you're doing?
That's an official vehicle! Hey!
Should we use the sirens?
Did you think
we'd steal a police car
and not use the sirens?
- Do you have a license?
- Fuck, yeah.
What are you doing?
It's a cop car!
You can't steal a cop car!
That'll be our food.
Hello?
Not the food. It's for you.
Who is it?
May I ask who's calling, please?
He says it's the killer.
Hello?[ghostface] hello, Gale.
Strange that you and I
have never spoken on the phone.
This is long overdue.
I agree.
Call the police.
I figured after all these years
you'd want an interview.
Well, you figured right.
So, what's your motive
this time?
You angry at the movies or you
just trying to stay relevant?
I could ask you the same.
Don't you know
the legacy characters
Nobody cares
about last century's heroes.
Then why bother with me at all?
Call it nostalgia.
Or maybe
you deserve to be punished
for all that money you made
off the misery of others.
Maybe it's time
someone made a buck
You know you're like the tenth
guy to try this, right?
And spoiler alert,
it never works out
for the dipshit in the mask.
Oh, but they certainly
leave a Mark
Richie and Amber
managed to butcher Dewey.
Carved him up
like a Christmas goose.
How does it feel
to lose the only man
Fuck you!
How does it feel to know
that you weren't
there for him at the end?
Not there to give him comfort
as he died screaming
in his own guts.
You're the one
who's gonna die screaming.
Maybe. But you won't
be around to see it.
You couldn't stop
what happened to Dewey.
Just like you're not
gonna be able to stop this.
Oh, god!
How's that for nostalgia, fucker?
You missed.
Sure I did.
You win.
I'm in the elevator
heading for the ground floor.
Sure you are.
Maybe you did hit me.
Maybe I'm wounded.
Or maybe I'm wearing
a bulletproof vest.
That's why I'm gonna shoot you
in the fucking head!
You would've made
a good killer, Gale.
Sidney never would've
made sense, and Dewey
But you
cracking under the pressure
and turning into ghostface
would've been a great twist.
Keep talking, asshole.
Sure.
What do you want to talk about?
You never got to be
the leading lady, did you?
It was always all about
poor sweet Sidney,
sucking up all the oxygen.
What did that leave you to be?
The brains and the sex appeal.
Sorry about your boyfriend.
All those muscles
didn't help much.
They sure didn't.
Can you hold, please?
Huh?
Fuck you!
Hey, fuckface!
Gale!
Oh, shit. Gale?
Gale.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I should've known that he was
gonna come after you.
I'm so sorry.
He didn't get me.
Tell Sidney
he never got me.
Gale?
- Gale.
Gale? Please.
Out of the way!
- Out of the way!
- Move. You got to move. Move!
No! No!
Okay. Get them back,
please.[Tara] Sam, please!
- They need to move now.
- Excuse me. Please step back.
Call it in.[Paramedic 2] right away.
Checking.[Tara] come on, Gale.
Got a weak pulse.
Get the backboard.
We need to move now.[Paramedic 2] yeah.
Backboard! Let's move.
Hey. Hey.
I got here as fast as I could.
Did you?
I'm scared, you guys.
I really don't want
to get hurt again.
Neither do I.
I don't want you
getting hurt again, either.
I know. I know.
So what do we do now?
Maybe he gets to win this time.
He wants to punish me.
Me.
So maybe I let him.
I'll just give myself up.
If this is what I have to do
to keep you safe,
it's worth it.
No, we're not doing that, Sam.
You went back to woodsboro
to protect me.
Every single day, you make
the decision to protect me.
None of us would even be alive
if it weren't for you.
You have to let us
protect you this time.
- No.
- Yes.
We're a team, remember?
Actually,
we're a family.
Let's go! Core four!
Come on.
- Core four.
- Come on.
- Core what?
- It's an us thing.
He's gonna keep coming after us.
Isn't there somewhere safe
we could just hole up in?
No, he's gonna keep finding us.
Great.
We could use that, though.
I'm getting my ass chewed out
for not dropping the case
We want to lure him
to a secure location
And then what?
We execute him.
Are you gonna help us?
Let's kill the son of a bitch.
Now, I'm stuck here,
but Gale gave us
the keycards to the theater.
It's got heavy surveillance
and security cameras,
but we can use that against him.
I'll tell Kirby
to meet you there.
I'll join you as soon as I can.
- Got it.
- And remember, travel in public.
The more people around you,
the less chance he has
to take a shot at you
before you get there.
Is this even a good plan?
You don't have to come
if you don't want to.
So we just peel off
and the killer picks us off
Let's just get to the theater.
Come on, in here.
Yes, because it'll be
much less scary
at the serial killer
movie theater.
Fuck.
Wait, hey, hey! Chad!
Hey! Fuck! Chad!
Tara!
- Wait, where's mindy?
- Chad! Sam! Hey, Sam!
Mindy! Mindy! Mindy!
Let's go. Shit.
Fuck!
Fuck.
Get your ghostface ass
away from me, ghostface.
The next local one train
to south ferry will arrive in...
Go away.
Five minutes.
- Where's mindy?
- She missed the train.
I was gonna wait for her,
but cute boy here dragged me on.
- Trying to keep us together.
- By pulling us apart?
It's okay.
It's fine. She's with Ethan.
She'll meet us there.
This is a south ferry bound
local one train.
Oh, shit.
The next stop is 79th street.
How many stops do we have?
Ten.
This is 79th street.
This is a south ferry bound
local one train.
The next stop is 72nd street.
This is a south ferry bound
local one train.
The next stop is 79th street.
Sorry!
Still nothing from mindy.
This is 72nd street.
Guys?
Dude!
Watch yourself, man.
The next stop is 66th street,
Lincoln center.
Hey.
Fuck you.
This is a south ferry bound
local one train.
The next stop is 66th street,
Lincoln center.
This is 66th street,
[Announcer] As you exit,
please be careful
of the platform and the train.
Oh, shit.
Mindy! Fuck!
Shit, shit. Mindy!
Fuck, that's a lot of blood.
Help! Somebody help!
Fuck. We got to get you
out of here, okay?
Damn it.
Come on![Mindy] fuck.
Shit. Somebody call 911!
Oh, my god.
- Yeah, I'm so good.
You're gonna be okay.
Goddamn it.
I got it wrong again.
What the fuck?
Help!
We need medical assistance.
We're at
the 66th street station.
Fuck this franchise.
Hey.
I talked to Bailey.
I've got everything set up.
- Where are mindy and Ethan?
- They're five minutes
Let's get you all inside.
- Not you.
- What?
Don't trust anyone, remember?
We don't know you.
Not really.
You know me.
You're not woodsboro.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's okay, I get it.
Be safe, okay?
Okay?
You, too.
Good call.
I cleared the whole place
before you got here.
So, this is the only way
in or out.
He steps in
through the first door,
both doors lock automatically,
trapping him inside.
We turn it into a kill box.
- Weapons?
- One gun,
I am the only one
with a badge here
and that's the way
it's gonna be.
We're safe here.
I'm gonna check in with mindy.
See if they're close.
Come on, come on.
Hey, you've reached me.
Leave a message.
You know you're not safe here.
Whenever someone says,
"we're safe here,"
it means you're not.[Sam] not now.
But you're smarter than this, Sam.
Grab a weapon
and clear this place yourself.
You know I'm right.
Excellent choice.
My favorite.
Kirby?
Kirby!
Hello?
Get everyone out of there, Sam.
You're not safe.
I heard
from the Atlanta field office.
They said agent Reed's been
on a downward spiral
ever since the woodsboro
- murders last year.
They fired Kirby two months ago
for being mentally unstable.
What? she's no longer with the FBI.
Listen, asshole.
No, you listen,
you little bitch.
Hang up on me, I'll gut you
like a fish. Understand?
What do you want?
To see
what your insides look like.
Oh, shit.
When was the last time
anybody used this place?
It's so old.
Um. I'm sorry,
you can have them.
- Take them.
- No, I mean...
If you want them, you have them.
- You think I want these?
- Kind of.
They're a hundred years old.
Maybe that's your thing.
I actually...
It's maybe embarrassing
how long I've wanted to do that.
Yeah, you should've done that
a lot sooner.
I know.
But you could also do it
a lot more times.
Tara!
Tara, let's go.
Come on, come on!
Come on, go, go, go!
It's Kirby. She's the
killer.[Chad] no shit!
- That's locked. Come on.
- Are we trapped?
She made this whole theater
a kill box. For us.
Hey, what about that?
There's an exit door.
Maybe it leads to the roof
or something?
There's only one way
to find out. Let's go.
Bailey's on the way, but...
Oh, fuck!
Beheadings!
Tara! Come on.
Smile for the camera,
motherfucker!
This way! Come on!
She should
be running out the front door.
Get fucked!
Tara, go! Go!
No!
Chad!
Run.
Go.
This way. Up here. Come on.
Everybody's a suspect.
You're not scared, are you?
Oh, Sam!
It's a lot scarier
when there's no motive.
Ready?
I need you to be ready. Ready?
Look at me.
I'm ready.
Come on, motherfucker!
It's okay!
- Stay the fuck back!
- We know it's you, Kirby.
One of them knocked me out.
Kirby, stop!
Get away from the girls!
What are you doing?
Did you kill Quinn?
Did you kill my daughter?
Jesus Christ!
Whatever he's been saying
to you, don't listen to him.
He's probably the killer.
Behind you!
Great job.
Both of you.
- You?
- Yeah, of course me.
Frankly, I expected more
from the two of you
after what you did to us.
What do you mean, "us"?
Ta-da!
Mindy was right.
It was easy to juke
the roommate lottery.
All I had to do to meet you
was room with a conceited,
condescending Alpha
literally named Chad.
Fuck, it felt good to kill him!
This was your grandmother's,
Sam.
Nancy loomis?
Really runs in
your fucking family, doesn't it?
Speaking of family... wait for it.
My name's not Ethan Landry,
is it, dad?
"Dad"?
Wait. If it's you two,
that just leaves...
Mindy?
Hey, roomies.
You didn't see
that one coming, did you?
- Yeah, because you died!
- Kind of didn't, though.
It was a good way
to get off the suspect list.
Stab Gale weathers,
stab mindy on the train.
That sort of thing.
Yep, and I just made sure
I was first on the scene
so I could switch her body out
with a fresh one.
Little fake blood, a prosthetic.
You'd be amazed at what
a grieving father
I got stu macher's mask.
He was my favorite.
Nice. That's number three.
That's two.
Which leaves...
Your father's.
This is what we've
been counting down to, Sam.
I'm gonna need you to put it on.
Fuck you!
Ooh!
Stay the fuck away from her!
Come on.
- What? What is this?
You did this as a family?
Hell yeah, bitch!
You should know
better than anyone.
They're still not getting it.
I don't know what you believe,
but I didn't commit
those murders in woodsboro.
We know that.
Of course you didn't.
You think this is based on
some bullshit conspiracy theory?
Come on. Who do you think
started the rumors about you
Do you know how easy it was
to turn Sam
from the hero of woodsboro
How easy it is
to convince the world
to believe the worst in people
rather than the best?
Because it's not enough
to just kill someone these days.
You have to assassinate
their character first.
So when dad here "discovers"
your horribly mutilated bodies...
Posed with Sam
wearing her father's mask,
he'll say some poor dumb bastard
read on the Internet
and took matters
into their own deluded hands.
Exactly! That's why
it's the perfect alibi.
And all the best lies
are based on the truth.
And you're a killer.
- Just like your father.
- No, I'm not!
Yes, you are, you motherfucker!
You killed our brother!
What are you talking about?
You said your brother died
in a car accident.
No, no, no,
you sweet, dumb thing.
He died in woodsboro
at the hands
of your bitch sister.
You're Richie's family.
Yeah.
Ding-ding-ding-ding!
She's finally starting
Now! It wasn't
until I saw that photograph
of what you'd actually done
to him that I knew.
That I knew you had to fucking
die! You had to be punished!
Along with anyone else
who stands in our way.
There she is.
There's the fucking killer.
Great parenting job, by the way.
Shut your whore fucking mouth!
Shit.[Sam] you okay?
Have I been a perfect dad? No.
Have I maybe overindulged
Richie's love
Yeah, maybe.
For me,
they're just a little dark.
But...
Richie really loved them.
He loved them!
He even made a few of his own.
Did you know? Did you know?
So you think I didn't post
a holiday special.
Well, I tried to.
I really did try.
That I could interact with.
There's a very special bond
between a father
and his first son.
Which is why I helped him
build this collection.
This was all his?
Yes, he's
a very passionate collector.
And he inspired others.
We had to kill those two
wannabe film students
because, well,
we had to kill you first, Sam.
I put the theater in their name,
then good old detective Bailey
but I didn't have to because,
by golly,
that Gale weathers
is one hell of a journalist.
I built a tribute to my son.
Which is why this is
where you have to die, Sam,
surrounded by all the things
he loved the most.
What happens next?
After you're done with us
you just disappear?
No! We got to hurry
over to the hospital
and make sure mindy
and Gale don't pull through.
Everyone who had anything to do
with the death of my son
- Fuck yeah, they do!
- Yeah!
Now put on the mask.
He was...
So pathetic.
- That's not true.
- Yeah, your son,
he was a man-baby
who made his girlfriend
do all the killing.
He was a strong,
virile young man!
He was a limp-dick little fuck
who cried
before I slit his throat.
Shut the fuck up!
Sam, come on!
Recognize this?
Fuck you!
Sorry, but I kind of need this.
Fuck 'em up.
What are you gonna
do about it, bitch?
Ow! Fuck!
Sam!
I'll get help.
Be careful.
Come on.
Go get her.
Get her!
I can't grab you.[Sam] it's okay.
I can't grab on.
No!
I've always wanted
to stick something in you, Tara.
- Fuck you!
You guys are so fucked now!
Sam.
Sam?
- Let me go.
- No!
Yeah, let her go, Sam, come on.
Fuck!
Trust me.[Ethan] fuck!
You have to let me go.
Gotcha!
Now die a fucking virgin.
Looks like you're down
another brother.
Always got to
shoot them in the head.
Oh, fuck.
Do you see
your boyfriend anywhere?
I don't even have
a boyfriend right now.
Would you like one?
I don't even know you
and I dislike you already.
Hello, detective Bailey.
I've got one question for you.
Oh, yeah?
What's that?
What's your favorite
scary movie?
"Favorite scary movie."
I'm asking
because you're in one now.
You're in my movie.
Oh.
I see you've
put on your true face, huh?
Your birthright.
Poetic that you're
gonna die in it.
This is what you wanted,
isn't it?
Now you know the truth, huh?
Murder's in your blood!
Stop fucking around
and show yourself!
Be careful what you wish for.
All right,
I'm a fucking police officer.
How do you think
this is gonna go, Sam?
Who do you think
they're gonna believe, huh?
Probably the one
who's still alive.
No! No!
My father was a murderer.
No matter what you think,
I'm better than that.
Thank you.
But you did
fuck with our family, so...
- Nice.
- Thanks.
You okay?
No.
♪ Take a little walk
to the edge of town ♪
♪ and go across the track ♪
♪ where the viaduct looms
like a bird of doom ♪
♪ as it shifts and cracks ♪
♪ where secrets lie
in the border fires ♪
♪ in the humming wires
hey, man, you know
♪ Past the bridge
past the mills
Thank you for letting me go.
♪ On a gathering storm... ♪
I knew you could
take care of yourself.
♪ In a dusty black coat
with a red right hand... ♪
I want to be in your life,
but only as much
as you want me to be.
I want you to be.
I promise you I'm gonna get
so much therapy after this.
I'm serious.
We're gonna get through this.
Together.
I saw that
in a scary movie once.
Sam. Hey.
Two over there.
Let's go.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
I thought you might need
some reinforcements.
And I called mount sinai,
and mindy and Gale
are gonna be okay.
Mindy's on her way here now.
They couldn't stop her.
Not bad, cute boy.
Thanks.
If you ever need me, call.
We're all part of
the same fucked-up family now.
And legacy doesn't always have
to be a bad thing.
Okay.
Hey.
It's just Chad.
Hey, we got another one here!
Watch out, coming through.
Oh, my god.
- Chad! Chad!
How are you alive?
Core fucking four.
Mmm. Mmm.
Sorry. You probably need that.
Oh, my god!
Are you guys okay?
I know who the killer is!
It's Ethan and Bailey.
- And Quinn.
- And Quinn? Fuck!
Did I miss the monologue again?
Are you okay?
You don't look okay.
Oh, my god, we all survived.
It's a twist on a twist.
They gave me a lot of drugs.
You guys should
get some of these drugs.
I can't feel anything
below my shoulders.
Sam.
Coming?
♪ Still alive ♪
♪ woke up under water
throat chained at the collar ♪
♪ couldn't get any farther
from the daylight ♪
♪ was I still dreaming
stuck to a machine ♪
♪ or choking and screaming
with my hands tied? ♪
♪ Callin' and callin'
but nobody comes ♪
♪ fallin' and fallin'
no air in my lungs ♪
♪ don't know how
I opened up my eyes... ♪
Not every movie
needs a post-credit scene.