Subtitles by explosiveskull
That guy is so creepy,
you guys.
He keeps following me around.
Okay, can we just, like,
can we go home now?
Get your scares while you can.
Orange Grove Community Fair
Horror Night
is coming to a close.
I don't know why you're so freaked
out, you're with us, don't worry.
This better be worth it.
Okay, just stay
in front of me. You go first.
Get your scares while you can.
Orange Grove Community Fair
Horror Night
is coming to a close.
That thing
is so cheesy.
You guys, it's a dead... End.
Seriously?
It's not funny.
Enter if you dare.
Great. It's a dead end.
Shit. Another scare?
Wait.
You're the one that's been following
me all night, aren't you?
Okay, stop!
I'm scared, okay?
Is that what you wanna hear?
Now, leave me alone.
Thank you so much.
Nat? Oh, my God!
What? You're here!
What? Oh, my God!
- How are you?
- I'm good! How are you?
- I'm good.
- Yeah.
- Yay.
- Wow, why is she here?
Well, hello, Grade School.
It's good to see you.
How's life?
- It's great.
- Mmm.
Yeah. Why are you here?
Oh, she didn't tell you?
Dude, I live here now.
It's awesome, right?
I'm so glad you're here.
I was just telling Taylor
how I hoped you'd make it.
Such a surprise!
Huge surprise.
Why?
Why is it surprising?
Well, I mean,
just last time we talked,
you said you were studying.
So I didn't know if...
Studying?
Dude, it's October,
it is fun time.
You save that for December.
Well, some of us have
scholarships, Taylor.
- Kinda need to keep mine.
- Mmm-hmm.
You kinda need to get laid.
Brooke, your bestie needs
to get some,
and lucky for her,
Gavin's coming tonight!
You remember Gavin.
Brook already told me
you've wanted
to ride that D
since you first
laid eyes on him.
- Wow.
- Yeah. See, I listen.
I really wish you didn't.
"Ride that D," huh?
Her, of all people?
God, she's never liked me.
I don't know why you would
tell her about Gavin.
Hey, can't stay mad.
Can't stay mad.
Ugh!
She calls me "Grade School,"
for God's sake.
- I think it's endearing.
- No! It's not endearing.
It's bitchy, maybe.
No, it's not.
Look, she's not replacing you.
Nothing could ever
replace you, okay?
Please tell me I don't have to
hang out with her all weekend.
Uh... Tonight she's coming,
but that's it.
And then, it's just
you and me. Promise.
Unless...
Unless what?
Unless, you know,
you and Gavin
want some alone time
this weekend.
- What did you tell him?
- Nothing, I promise!
He's just the one that got us
the VIP passes to Hell Fest.
What is that?
Dude, it's so
fucking dope! Okay?
Like, it's a traveling
horror night.
People totally lose their shit
in there. It's really fun.
You're not
selling me on it.
No, it's great!
It's gonna be fun!
Tickets sold out
the minute they went on sale.
But your boy Gavin came through
and got some tickets for us.
Okay, we don't need
to do this dance now.
And he's been
asking about you.
- Really?
- He was like...
"Hey, Brooke, is your hot
friend coming this weekend?"
Wait, he called me hot?
Apparently, someone made
a great impression on him
this past summer.
Why is that surprising?
He was like,
"Hey Brooke, uh...
"You know, I should get
"an extra ticket
for Natalie, right?
"She's coming.
She's coming, right?"
"Hey, Brooke,
I know this is, like,
"really awkward and shit.
But, like,
"do you think that
after Hell Fest,
"Natalie will sit on my face?"
Shut up, he did not say that!
- Did he?
- I don't know!
But, um...
You're not wearing
that, right?
Why? What is wrong
with what I'm wearing?
Nat, it's Halloween!
It's the one night
out of the year
you're allowed to let out
your inner slut.
Yeah, I don't think
I have one of those.
Hey, babe... Oh. Whoa.
Natalie!
- I didn't think you were gonna make it.
- Can you knock?
Hi! Yeah, no, I'm here.
I don't know why everyone
thinks I'm not gonna be here.
What? No. I knew
you were coming.
Brooke was the one
who was like, "It's iffy."
Can you not do that?
- What are you in here for?
- I'm just... I'm ready.
You guys ready?
You ready for Hell Fest?
- You look ready.
- Baby, we need 10 minutes.
We have to meet Gavin at will call.
We're gonna be late.
Babe, you gotta go.
I need 10 minutes.
- Okay. I'll see you in 30.
- See you in a bit.
- Love you.
- Okay, so...
We need to find you
something good.
And make up for lost time.
This is dope!
Oh, my God!
This is awesome, guys!
- I know!
- It's gonna be fun!
Nat, don't worry! I will totally
protect you from being murdered.
Oh, thanks. I didn't realize
that was a possibility, but...
Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa.
Do not be flippant.
It happens,
like in Orange Grove.
Oh, yeah, that was
fucked up.
Wait, what?
Oh, well, a couple
years ago,
a girl got completely gutted
in a haunted house,
like, for real.
The killer left her body
in the park for three days.
No one found her
until she started to stink.
They thought she was
a freaking prop!
- Wait, that's brutal!
- Man, what can I say?
Some people are just evil.
I mean, they're monsters.
To them, every single day
is Halloween
and they dress up,
so that we don't know.
Know what?
That they walk among us.
Nat, they're fucking
with you!
- Okay, dude...
- Are we?
Oh, yes, you are!
- Okay, murder twins, we get it. It's scary.
- I know.
Whatever.
- Oh, my God!
- Quinn!
Welcome to Hell Fest!
Hell Fest! Hell Fest!
Yes, I'm excited.
Okay, let's go, let's go.
I'm so excited! Yes!
Hey, murder twins,
wait up!
Welcome to Hell Fest!
All right. Let's go.
Beyond these gates,
your inner fears
will come true!
Whoa. Is that her?
- Asher's here?
- Yeah. Come on.
Oh, yeah.
You might actually
have to pretend
- you have game tonight.
- Asher!
Hey, boo.
Asher, this is Natalie.
Natalie, Asher.
- Hello, pleased to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
Why didn't you tell me
you were coming?
- Hey. It's been a while.
- Hey.
You look great.
It's good to see you.
- Hell Fest!
- Welcome to VIP, bitches!
VIP, bitches!
There you go.
I can help you put yours on.
- Oh, thank you.
- You're welcome.
Thanks. Yeah, Brooke tells me
I have you to thank for this.
- So...
- Yeah, no. No problem.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
No, she said you were
coming to town, so I just...
I wanted us to do
something fun.
Great.
- Hey, you guys ready?
- Yeah.
You guys ready?
Hell Fest, guys!
Let's do this!
Hell Fest!
Look it, work it
for me, baby! Work it!
Oh, shit! Okay!
Hey!
Oh, shit!
Good Lord!
Wow!
And then there's that.
So, just so you guys know,
fear is an aphrodisiac.
Yeah, it stimulates
something...
- The more you know.
- Deep in those lizard brains
and it reminds you
that life is short
and an organism's only true
purpose is to, uh, reproduce.
Okay. That's great.
Thank you.
It is. All right, I will let you guys
think about that and I'll be back later.
All right.
Thanks for the master class.
You're welcome!
I'm starting to get
the feeling our friends think
something's gonna happen
between us.
Really? No, I didn't
notice that at all.
- Oh, really?
- Mmm-hmm.
You don't get
that vibe at all?
- No, I don't.
- It's very subtle.
Just you're picking up
on that.
Yeah, it's just me.
Hey, well, I'm actually...
I'm glad you came.
I think it's gonna be fun.
It's been a while
since we've hung out.
Yeah, I was bummed
that I had to bail.
I just had a bunch of shit
that I...
Jesus Christ!
That came so close to my face!
No!
You're good, this is it.
It's not that bad.
- It's just...
- Not the worst thing, I guess?
- It is time for shots!
- Shots!
- Yes!
Please, let's go!
Come on!
Raise your arms.
You're good.
Why do you always
switch them?
Thanks, man.
Asher! Hurry up
with those shots!
- Whoa. Shots!
- Yeah!
Nice! So we got VIP tonight,
so lines aren't gonna be
an issue. We are here,
but we need
to focus our shit,
'cause I'm trying to hit
everything tonight.
Let's do the Zombie Maze.
- Boom.
- Why?
Yo, Gav, what are you, five?
We didn't come here for slow.
If you want that,
go trick-or-treating.
We came here to be terrified!
The Zombie Maze
is fucking scary, it's...
I'm good with the
Zombie Maze. I am.
No, I wanna do Deform School
because I've been
a very naughty girl.
And I hear Deform School
is one of the scariest mazes
outside of the Deadlands.
- Wait, what are the Deadlands?
- What?
No, it's a part of the park
where they can all touch you
or something. Right?
Wait. For real,
they can touch you?
Yeah. That's where shit's
gonna get crazy.
Sounds fun, right?
Plus, it's the only way
you get to go into Hell
which is the scariest maze,
so...
Yeah?
Please?
Come on.
Sure.
- To Hell Fest!
Oh, my God!
Dude, you don't scare me!
Go back to the other freaks!
I just wanna go back home...
What is up with
all these assholes?
You think you're scaring me?
Ooh, you're so scary.
No. Move.
Wait! You guys,
what the fuck?
Come on, come on!
You don't
have to run, like...
- I don't like being fast.
- I don't like being...
- I don't like that. At all.
- I can't see anything.
Okay, we can do this.
It's okay, we got this.
Fuck this shit!
Oh, my God!
Okay. Hi,
thank you very much!
Oh, my God!
Holy shit.
- Brooke! Okay, okay...
- Go, go, go!
Oh, my God!
It's everywhere!
That was so stupid!
Picture,
picture, picture!
He got her
more than me. Thank God.
Let's go.
Cobwebs.
You go, you walk first.
Dude, the more scared
you seem,
the more they're gonna come
after you. You gotta like...
- You have to play it cool.
- Just relax and...
Yes. You... Shit!
Oh, my God!
Yeah, no, just play it cool.
I'll remember that.
That's great.
No, that...
I have a very specific phobia
of demon clowns.
These are my people.
Jesus Christ.
Come on,
come on, come on!
VIP!
Sucks to be you.
Okay, I'm sorry.
VIP band, just showed it off.
Tay, they pace it out
so we each go on our own.
Oh, can we go? Can we go?
And, wait, wait.
- Go, go, go!
- Thank you!
Okay. Are you ready?
- Yeah.
- You that ready?
Yep, I'm ready.
Go, go, go!
See? I didn't need that
in my life.
Don't do that! Oh, my God!
You know what? He deserves
at least some dignity in death.
- Let's give him a boner.
- Definitely.
Oh, God!
The last thing I need to do
is relive high school.
She can keep me after class.
Ow! Hey, Gavin.
You like paddles, right?
You said you had a fetish
or something.
She's got a paddle.
I've never said that
in my entire life.
Oh, freaky.
I don't like paddles.
They're fucking with you.
I mean,
if you do, man.
- I never...
- You don't like paddles?
- You're such an asshole.
- Hey, guys.
I don't think everyone here
is completely dead.
I mean, part of this guy
is very much alive.
Are you sexually harassing
a zombie right now?
Because I feel like
that's just a lot.
Look, all I know is
I definitely know
how to make the dead rise.
You know how
to make everything rise, baby.
- I guess we're going that way.
- We're going that way.
We're supposed
to follow that?
Oh.
Hurry up!
I'm trying. Hold on.
Oh, shit!
Oh. All right. No.
Ruined the damn photo.
I'm scared.
Oh, God! One of these guys
has gotta be real.
- Oh, yeah!
- Yep.
If you could
go first, that'd be great.
This...
- Okay, you have to look at their hands.
- Why?
Then you can tell
which one is real,
if you look at their hands.
Okay, but I don't like
looking at the hands,
because then you can't see
their skin and their faces.
- Yeah, that's the one.
- There you go.
Busted, sir. Or, ma'am.
I can't really tell.
How dare you assume?
I don't know, honestly.
They're all kind of...
Neutral.
Oh, hey.
This place is
kind of lame.
- Yeah, bummer.
- I like all the art...
Fuck! Come on!
Nope! Okay, go!
- Did they just ditch us?
- What the fuck?
- Oh, my God!
- Of course they did. Wait.
Wait.
Wait, wait.
Don't you spill my tequila.
Wait, no, no, no!
I just figured it out.
Look, she just came
out of here.
Somebody else is gonna come
out of here and freak us out.
Oh, great,
thank you for confirming.
Really?
Look, and then she's gonna
jump out here, too.
Yes, thank you. Thanks!
You're ruining this for me.
No, I'm telling you.
Now someone's just
gonna come out of this door
right here.
- All right, let's see.
- Let's see.
Stop saying things
at the same time.
And Grade School
overthought it.
And, three, two... Shut up.
Three, two, one.
Help me! He's following me.
- Please!
- Oh. See, your timing was off.
And location.
Please, help me. Please.
Oh, my God!
He's coming!
Okay. Well, I was still
kind of right.
So melodramatic.
Oh, hi, buddy.
Hello.
He got the...
Okay.
Class deceased.
If at first you don't
succeed, die and die again.
He's got the wonky eyeballs.
He's been through some things.
Yeah, you're not scary, dude.
- Okay.
- Did you see that?
Okay, just get back on script,
guy. Your girl's over there.
With the big arrow.
Where it says, "Don't look." She's
in that thing, you should...
No, no. Just stop!
Please.
Help me! Please! Please!
No, no, no!
Stop it!
Yeah, no, fuck that. I'm good.
Yep. Let's go.
Stop!
Stop it! No!
Okay, just do it.
That was
fucking insane.
I know. Now you know
why I wanna come here.
Yes, I get it.
This is fucking...
- I know!
- Jesus Christ!
Hey, you good?
What took you so long?
That was really fucking real
in there at the end.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Yeah! Really intense.
You need some?
Yes.
Go Grade School.
- Shit!
- Jesus Christ!
I love this place
so much!
Come on. Let's go.
She just, like, walks away?
You ditched us.
What do you want?
Looks like you made a friend,
Grade School.
Well, at least I wasn't crying
like a baby in there, College.
Okay! All right,
I might like you.
Let's keep going.
Keep it up.
I like this sassy side.
Wait, does she still snore
like an outboard motor
when she's drunk, because...
Like a fucking buzz saw.
You two are getting
a little too close, all right?
Well, you can't
stay mad, so...
Oh, one night at Hell Fest,
and you're coming out
of your shell.
It looks good, right?
It suits her.
Yeah.
Look, is that the same guy
from the Deform School?
- Hey!
- Don't do that.
- Why?
- Jesus Christ!
He's an actor. He gets paid
minimum wage to follow us.
But he's only following us.
It's stalker-ish.
- Yo, let's go.
- Keep it moving.
Yo, guys, this is the same
dude from Deform School.
Nat, he's just an actor.
They fuck with everyone.
Seriously, ignore him.
He'll get bored.
It works with Brooke.
Yeah, no, no,
that's great advice.
That always works
with stalkers. Thanks.
Hey. Listen.
If he gets too close,
I'll fuck him up for you.
Oh, my God!
That's adorable. I got it.
You guys are gonna
handle this one?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, of course. We got you.
Dude, I told you
it'd be fun with her here.
I know! You're right.
She's awesome!
- This is amazing.
- This is dope!
Oh, crap.
Oh, look, it's you.
It's your future, Ash.
Okay. No, no, no!
Oh, shit.
Come on, girl, let's go
win you some cheap-ass prizes.
That is so antiquated
of you, Ash.
- They have funnel cakes!
- Off we go!
Have fun, you two.
Hey, Gavin...
Great. That's...
Thanks, Quinn.
That was so subtle of you.
Thanks for that.
- I'm sorry.
- Um...
Here. Let's play a game.
- Are you ready for this?
- I am. Are you ready?
Ready as I'll ever be.
Mine.
You are really close.
Maybe it's just your...
I just need to stop
overthinking it.
No look.
- What you wanna do?
- I'm doing it, too.
Prize time. Dang it.
Are you sure
you're not left-handed?
- Who won? Who won?
- Yes!
Oh, wow.
Let me show you how it's done.
Well, now I just wanna
keep this.
- For my queen.
- Thanks, babe.
- Oh, wow!
- Shit!
You definitely took
that somewhere.
- I'm sorry about that.
- Ready, one...
Two, three... Go!
This is painful, bruh.
- Okay. Thanks.
- It's not that bad.
It's pretty bad.
- That was close!
- It was. Thank you.
- It was...
- Yeah.
- No, no, no!
- No, I got another one
- It's more than okay.
- It's really not.
We don't have to...
It's been, like, five games.
You know how good
you're gonna feel
when you have a teddy bear
of your very own?
Sometimes you just have to
accept that it's not for you.
I'm sorry,
I'm so shitty at ring toss.
It's okay.
I was honestly
trying my best.
But I think my game of choice
is the one where you're like,
"Here's five dollars."
And the guy's like,
"Here's a pretzel."
So you pay for things?
Yeah, but at an incredibly
fast rate.
Okay.
I think that's my game
of choice. Hello.
Oh, hello!
What? Can I?
May I? Thank you.
Wow! It's so coiffed.
- It really is.
- It's so beautiful.
I think you should
get one of those.
I was gonna say
I think you should.
Well, I can't, so...
So what do you think so far?
Of the pretzel?
- Uh, no, not the pretzel.
- Good. Could use mustard.
I do want a piece of this.
- Oh, you're a mustard kind of girl?
- Mmm-hmm.
I meant of Hell Fest.
What do you think? Like hanging out?
Two of us?
- I like hanging out with you.
- Okay. Good.
I'm sorry that I've been
so flaky actually.
I've just been having a really
tough time with school
and work, and life, so...
It's just nice to be here.
- Nice to be in Hell.
- Yep. It's nice to be in Hell.
- It's the best place to be.
- Yeah.
- Come here.
Oh, God! But that was
a perfectly good pretzel.
I'm sorry.
It was not salty enough.
Oh, God, I am so bad
at these things.
Oh, we have to pay
under here.
Yeah. Okay.
- What do we...
- Um...
Smile.
Just smile like an idiot.
Not that you're an idiot.
No, that's really the only way
I know how to do it.
Uh, drunk face?
Uh, sure, okay. I don't
really have a drunk face.
I don't, either.
I'm a stoic drunk.
Yeah. I'm a
very composed...
Um...
No, no, you don't touch it.
Just your...
Well, I didn't know
if I was supposed to...
With my tongue?
What do you want me to do?
How could you not know
that I was going
- for the nose-tongue picture?
- I don't know
- how many people...
- How dare you.
I didn't know there was
a type of picture you take.
Yo!
What the fuck? Hey!
Is that Brooke?
- You sure? Was that Brooke?
- Brooke?
What the hell?
That guy just
took your photos.
- What?
- Babe, here.
- Whoa. Whoa!
- Hey!
- Brooke.
- Babe!
- You guys, come on!
- Hey!
What's going on?
- Did you two just...
- Come on,
- let's make fun of him!
- Take pictures together.
Yo!
Oh, so you're hiding now?
You gonna scare me?
Hey, I told you to...
Stop.
Shit!
When did you become
a tough guy?
Listen, I scared him off.
Let's go.
Did you?
Did you get the photos?
No, but he's gone.
Here, take this.
That's gonna
consume her.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Hey, guys! I found
Nat's security guard.
Hey, did you get the pictures
back? What happened?
I took care of it,
like I said I would.
- Is that what you did?
- Yes.
It's the same guy, right?
- Wait, Deform School guy?
- Yeah.
He's just going
for Employee of the Year.
He's doing pretty damn good.
I mean, look at both
of your faces right now.
All right, fuck this place
anyway. It is Deadlands time.
I wanna be touched.
Yes. Thank you!
Let's go, let's go.
All right.
Deadlands. I'm in.
Yeah, you guys go
and then I'm gonna
- catch up with you, okay?
- What?
Just go, and then I'm gonna
catch up to you guys.
- What, what are you...
- Just go.
I wanna
get her a toy.
Just go really quick,
and then I'll meet up.
Do what you gotta do.
- Okay, do you want company?
- No, no, no.
Me and the bearded lady,
we exchanged this look.
I think she's gonna
give me beard lessons.
So, I'm gonna go
get her number.
That's not a thing.
I can just come with you.
It's totally a thing.
Okay.
So, we'll meet you
in line then?
Yeah, dude,
if you're not there
by the time
we get to the front
of the line,
I'm going to Hell
without you.
Yeah, I'll meet you there.
Just be really fast.
'Cause she really likes you.
You know?
And, she thinks
you're really hot.
She doesn't wanna
do Deadlands without you.
That wasn't uncomfortable
at all.
- We're going. Let's go.
- You're not hurrying!
All right. Bye.
Let's go.
Let's go. Come on.
Excuse me? Hey, um...
We're VIP, can we just...
Babe, this is VIP.
- This whole thing is VIP?
- Yeah.
Hey, don't worry about Gavin.
He's probably pooping
or something.
Okay, I did not need
to picture that.
What? Everybody poops, Nat.
Birds poop, bees poop. Honey!
That's where it comes from.
No more drinks for you.
Hey. You remember me? Earlier?
I was here playing
the ring toss?
And you were terrible at it?
That was me.
Thank you. Yeah.
Um, hey, listen,
I spent like $50.
Could you just help me out
and give me one of those?
Nah. I'd lose my job.
All right. Hey, thank you.
Thanks so much.
Wait, what actually happened
with that guy that you chased?
Mmm.
It got real intense,
so I just bailed.
I can't figure out what
his fucking deal is.
Me either.
But, hey, no,
you're having a great time,
Gavin's totally into you,
you're stepping out
of your comfort zone...
- He's cute, right?
- Hell yeah!
Hey,
are we good on stock?
Yeah, we got
plenty of stuffed animals
back in the locker.
We're good.
It just slipped out.
Uh, why do we keep
waiting in line for rides?
I thought we were doing mazes.
B, this is the ride that
takes us to the Deadlands.
It's the only way
to get there.
Why are we signing a waiver?
I mean, they can touch us
and liability is a bitch.
That's really extreme.
Extreme is what we want, Nat.
That's why we're here.
Plus, if you don't sign
you can't go in.
Oh, come on, Nat,
just sign it.
I was just starting to like
the new you.
Huh?
Just let me text Gavin
and let him know.
You sign. I'll text.
Damn.
Okay, Asher.
Oh, yes.
Okay...
Hmm.
That's good.
Oh, shit!
It's you again? Seriously?
You're following me now?
Nice. All right, you take
your job way too seriously.
Hope you know that.
You know, actually,
it's great that you're here.
Can I get
my pictures back? Or...
All right.
Dude, drop the character,
you're offstage.
Cool.
What the fuck
is your problem, man?
Come on, come on,
come on!
And...
- Thank you!
- Yes!
Wait. Nat, where is he?
I don't know.
Just text him again.
Okay? Come on.
Come on.
- Come on, guys!
- Yeah, we're coming!
- Sorry.
- Wait, slow down!
Nat, come on!
I'm coming.
Beware! Night Bumps
leads to the Deadlands,
where no soul is safe.
- Night Bumps!
- Yes!
Wait, wait, wait.
Nat, come on. You gotta get on
or you lose
your place in line.
In or out?
Sucks to be Gavin.
- Great to be us.
- Okay.
Let's go. Come on,
come on, baby.
- Wait, Brooke.
- Oh, um...
- What?
- Hey.
- We should wait. No.
- No, no, no.
No, Gavin assured us,
he would be there.
- It's fine. Come on.
- No, wait.
- He'll be right here.
- Wait. Really?
Nat, I don't wanna
split up, so...
Gavin'll meet us
on the other side, okay?
Yeah. He will be there.
I promise.
Okay?
Yeah. Love you.
See you in the Deadlands.
Beware the things that go
bump in the night.
Night Bumps!
I hope she's okay.
Babe, she'll be fine.
Thank you.
Night Bumps!
Oh, okay. Hey!
Oh. Yummy.
I don't like that.
Mmm-mmm.
Oh, my God! Wow!
- I'm so scared!
- Oh, shut up.
Crap!
Okay! Did you see the head
on that thing?
Jesus!
Fuck you, man!
Jesus Christ!
Shit!
Okay. Great.
Well, there goes that mood.
Are you shitting me?
Hello?
We are currently experiencing
technical difficulty.
Please remain calm while
we attempt to fix the ride.
Excuse me?
Do you know how long
this is gonna take?
Please remain calm
and try not to lose your head.
Hello?
Hello, there's somebody
in here.
Hello?
Security?
Help me!
Okay... What was that?
Yo, did you guys
hear that?
Yeah. It sounds like
Grade School freaking out.
No, she's not just
freaking out, that's beyond.
She's just getting into it.
See? Here we go. Oh.
You are now
entering the Deadlands.
The Other will guide you
on your journey.
That's awesome.
That's brilliant.
- Are you kidding me?
- No! No, no, no!
Nat, it was part of the ride,
get it?
They fake breaking down
and then they climb in
with one of the single riders.
- That's awesome!
- This has been terrifying,
- you asshole.
- Terrifyingly awesome!
- No, it's pretty good.
- Nat. Relax.
Get that out of my...
I hate you all.
Dude.
Asher, Asher!
Oh, shit!
Ah, it's so cool!
What the fuck is this?
The hell is that?
Oh, shit!
That girl got wrecked!
I hope that washes out.
So, guys,
uh, what do we do?
Do we just wander around?
I don't know. I feel like
we should wait for Gavin.
All right, Nat, real talk.
I don't want
to ruin it for you.
But Gavin is out getting you
one of those stupid
stuffed animals.
He's just gonna take a while.
Because he sucks. Right?
Damn it. Really?
Yes, he likes you, okay? He's
gonna catch up when he does,
but we're here now. So let's
have some fun, all right?
Hey, guys...
I think we gotta
check this thing out.
He likes you
and we know he's not pooping.
Oh, that's nasty.
I think they're in there.
- Step up, Q.
- Yeah, nope.
- Go for it.
- No.
- No. No.
- What?
You're such a wuss, Q.
Yes.
You okay, Ash?
Yeah.
- Then hurry up, man.
- You look good.
I'm good. Hold on.
Come on, baby.
That's gross.
That's in there.
That's why
I didn't do it.
Okay. Hold on.
That's nasty.
I think I got
something.
Does he always
make those noises?
- I'm almost there.
- You find it yet?
Oh, shit!
Holy fuck!
- He got you!
- Look at your face.
Shut the fuck up.
Take the stupid map.
- Shit!
- Oh, shit!
- Okay. What the fuck?
- Hey!
Let me down!
What the fuck? Put me down!
Uh...
- What just happened?
- Asher!
I don't know.
I'm gonna need her back, dude!
Hey, Taylor.
Tay! Taylor!
I get touching somebody,
but picking them up
and taking them away
from their entire group
is kinda fucked up.
- Taylor!
- Tay!
I'm gonna barf.
That guy smelled like
a hobo's asshole.
Wait, how do you know
what a hobo's asshole
smells like?
Because it smells
like Quinn's mom.
- Oh!
- Where did that guy take you?
I know, that's why I
know what I'm talking about.
They smell so bad,
I'm gonna die.
Oh, shit.
Mmm-mmm. Mmm-mmm.
Um... I guess
we're going with them.
It's all right.
We can do this.
Fuck.
Okay.
All right.
- This is awesome!
- Hi.
Um, maybe somebody
should text Gavin.
- Guys!
- Oh, yeah, he's not...
Where the hell is he?
I can't see anything.
I know.
Yo, this is dope.
Welcome to your first trial.
Will you conquer your fears
or will your fears
conquer you?
Oh.
Okay, bye.
Thanks for not killing us.
- That was creepy.
- Right?
Okay, guys, I think
this is the triple maze.
Sleep Like a Baby.
Very Bad Dreams.
Your Worst Nightmare.
- Your Worst Nightmare!
- Sleep Like a Baby.
Tay, wait up.
We'll see you girls
on the other side.
Hope Gavin catches up. Whoo!
Flashlights?
Whoa.
There is no way the girls' maze
is better than this one.
- Is that a baby face?
- Yeah, where is that...
On the ass?
This is so gross.
Shit! Go, go, go!
Yo, yo. They changed.
How did it do that?
- The girl. Look at the girl.
- The veins.
- Whoa.
- Detail.
This is gnarly.
Whoa.
Oh, now that is just awful.
Oh, shit!
Damn! She got me!
Listen, I'm not
going first anymore.
Go, Taylor. Stop laughing.
I don't wanna go first.
Go!
What?
- Whoa. Be careful.
- Okay, this is really cool.
Dude...
That's crazy!
This is dope.
I like all the swirlies.
This is so dope.
Like, this is insane.
It's probably...
- Shit!
- Jesus Christ!
What is that? Oh!
Shut up, Taylor.
Oh, damn!
All right.
Just look at the hands.
Hey, Taylor,
you should go first.
Oh. I hate you
so much right now.
- What if I just...
- No!
Just keeping you
on your toes.
Yay. That does
not look comfortable.
Okay, is it just me
or is it getting...
No, it's definitely
getting closer.
Yeah, but are the hands longer
or are the walls just...
Maybe both.
The walls might be
closing in.
All I know is
think little thoughts.
Think little thoughts.
All right, you know what?
First of all, woman.
Second of all, not that bad.
Yeah.
Let me go!
Get off!
Wait! Brooke! Taylor!
Yo, man.
Yo, my flashlight
went out. What about you?
Mine too, dummy.
Hurtful.
Q, it's probably a part
of the gimmick.
Whoa. Wait, wait, wait. Whoa!
That thing's not
slowing down, man.
- No. I know, I know...
- Oh, shit!
Ash! Wait up, man!
Leave no bone unturned
when looking for illumination
on the way out.
Gross.
Leave no bone unturned
when looking for illumination
on the way out.
Leave no bone unturned
when looking for illumination
on the way out.
Leave no bone unturned
when looking for illumination
on the way out.
- Yo! What took you so long?
- That same fucking guy was in there.
- What guy?
- What are you talking about?
The guy!
The guy from Night Bumps.
Well, news flash,
he's been everywhere.
- Remember, we saw, like, 20.
- No! No, not that.
The guy that I was telling you
about before,
he was in there,
he was fucking taunting me.
He was banging
against the Plexiglas.
Nat. Hey.
Look,
when Asher gets out,
we'll go find someplace else.
Yeah. Just give him a second.
Knowing him, he's probably
having the time of his life.
Quinn!
Q!
Oh, shit!
Just get the fuck off me!
The fuck?
Stop!
No!
Hey, it's okay.
Just breathe.
I'm just, like, I'm done.
I know. You've made it through
the majority of the night.
Of the fucking night?
You've gotten through a lot,
all right?
Fuck!
Oh, shit!
Fuck me!
You got Brundlefly'd!
What the fuck is that?
That's awesome!
Well, that's kind of funny.
Oh, really?
It's your shirt, so, fuck you.
Damn! Shut up!
Let's go to the bathroom.
Oh, shit!
This isn't how
I wanted the night to go.
It's just been a long time
since I've seen you
and I wanted it to be
like it used to be.
I knew this place
was gonna be creepy,
I just didn't know
it was gonna be that intense.
Right.
But, hey, are you...
Are you good?
I just worry about you.
And I love you.
And I miss you.
I love you, too.
I'm sorry I haven't
been around lately.
We gotta see each other more.
Let's go to Spain.
- You're not serious.
- I'm serious.
We've always talked about it.
- Let's just do it.
- You wanna go to Spain?
Yeah, you said I need a break.
You're probably right. So...
You wanna go to the Prado
and get tapas?
Sounds like you're saying
"topless," but...
I mean, we can do that, too.
You can do that. No thanks.
We're going to Spain?
- Yeah.
- You promise?
I promise.
Okay.
I'll meet you out there.
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
We're going to Spain.
We're going topless in Spain.
Ugh. Gross.
I'm calling the cops!
Fuck!
Brooke.
What?
What's wrong?
Yeah, I don't know
what to tell you. It's empty.
No, I'm telling you
that he was just here!
I just had to crawl under this
thing to get away from him!
- He was grabbing at me!
- All right, look...
I know the scarers
aren't supposed
to be in the bathroom,
but if you can't even
identify him,
I don't know what
you want me to do.
I don't know. Shut down
the park. Call the cops.
- Do something other than this!
- Are you hurt?
- What?
- Did he physically hurt you?
I mean, he grabbed at me.
I'm not injured.
Unless there is
an actionable charge,
- there's nothing I can do.
- What?
No, you're not understanding
a thing that I'm saying!
This guy has been stalking us
since the second we got here!
- Which guy?
- The guy with the mask
from the Night Bumps ride!
You just described 15 people
that work in this park.
You know how many complaints
I get like this a night?
Great. Well, mine's valid,
so what are you gonna
do with that?
- Holy shit!
- What?
It's the photos
of you and Gavin.
- Oh, my God.
- Okay, no, no, wait.
Who's Gavin?
He's our friend that was
supposed to meet us,
like, an hour ago.
He must have Gavin's phone.
Yeah, I think your friend,
Gavin, is pranking you.
All right, look,
you came here
to be scared, right?
I can't arrest people
for doing their job.
Welcome to Hell Fest.
We've got to find him.
Quinn. Quinn, we need to go.
- Now.
- What?
- We need to go. Now.
- Why would we leave?
I'll tell you later.
Where's Asher?
I haven't seen him.
Then where's Taylor?
She volunteered.
Welcome,
children of the night!
Are you ready to leave
the land of the living
and enter
into the darkness?
Into the world of monsters?
Whoo!
In order to open up
the gates of Hell,
we must spill the blood of...
Wait for it,
wait for it,
a virgin.
So, about that
whole virgin thing,
I think we might have
a problem.
What is your name, child?
Taylor Ann Smythe, your honor.
You're accused of doing
the Devil's work.
What say you?
- Totally did it.
- And what are your crimes?
Well, how long
do you have?
'Cause I've actually done laps
around the seven deadly sins.
Oh! Impressive.
But you must pay
for your transgressions.
Ooh, what is it?
Your head.
Ooh.
Executioner!
Yeah!
Oh. Okay. Well, bye-bye.
- Something's not right.
- What?
Something's not right.
What do you mean?
Yeah!
That's him.
Wait, the guy
from the bathroom?
Yeah, that's...
That's him. Oh, God! Taylor!
Nat, wait!
Taylor!
Nat, it's okay.
It's okay.
Oh, my God,
that was so much fun!
Hell Fest!
Hey, can someone get me
out of this thing?
Hey, you got her?
Please exit
the stage area.
Oh, hey. Sorry about the, uh,
screaming girl.
Yeah, that's my best friend's
best friend.
She doesn't really get horror,
so...
What can you do?
Can you get me out?
Please?
Yes! Awesome, thank you.
Ow! What the hell, man?
I said out, not forward.
Ow!
And not tighter. Dude, did you
just skip training day?
'Cause you're really
not doing this right. It's...
Okay, that's really tight.
This isn't a funny joke.
Ow! Okay.
Jesus, can you not hear
when I say "Ow"?
This is not comfortable.
Ow!
Okay, too tight.
This is really not funny.
I don't like this.
This is really uncomfortable.
Brooke!
Quinn!
Somebody help me!
Are you happy now?
'Cause now we're gonna have
to call the cops on you.
Yeah, no, that's exactly what
I want you to do!
Two of our friends
are missing!
No, two of your friends are
somewhere in the park, drunk.
No, they're not!
Help me!
Shit! Quinn!
Come on!
Oh, my God, someone help!
Help me!
Help me, please!
Please help me! Please!
- Help me!
- You suck at this shit!
- Guys, I think it's Taylor.
- Who's...
- Hey, where are you...
- Fuck out of my way!
We got a situation
in the Deadlands.
He's trying to
kill me! Get out of the way!
Get out of the way!
Somebody, help me,
please! Help me!
Please help me! Please!
Get out of the way,
he's trying to kill me!
What are you doing? Don't...
Hey, man, what are you doing?
- Quinn, Quinn!
- Brooke. Brooke. Brooke!
- Quinn! No!
- We gotta go.
Brooke, we gotta go.
Get down on the ground!
We got him! Got him!
- Nat! Are you okay? You okay?
- Yeah.
Please find the nearest exit.
Come on, we gotta go.
Due to unforeseen
circumstances
the park will be closing.
Please find the nearest exit.
Due to unforeseen
circumstances
the park will be closing.
- Nat, over here.
- Okay.
I think
this is an exit.
You are
at the entrance to Hell.
It's another maze.
Welcome to Hell.
Can you make it out
the other side?
We gotta go, we gotta go.
Welcome to Hell.
You are
at the entrance to Hell.
Can you make it out
the other side?
You are at the entrance
to Hell.
Can you make it out
the other side?
You are at the entrance
to Hell.
Can you make it out
the other side?
Welcome to Hell.
Wait!
- Wait, wait, wait.
- What? What?
Look, these are triggering
the rooms.
This is what's making
the noise.
- Come with me.
- No. Nat.
Brooke, I'm telling you...
We gotta go that way.
Shh, listen, you have
to trust me, okay?
Listen. We have to go.
Come.
Okay, come on.
Come on.
There's a closet back here.
I can't get reception.
Me neither.
It's not working.
Okay.
Come on, come on, come on.
You are
at the entrance to Hell.
Can you make it out
the other side?
No.
No, this can't be happening.
No, wait, wait. Wait, wait.
Please, somebody, help!
Please! Please!
We're gonna have
to go through, okay?
Listen. Shh! We're gonna
have to go through.
We can do this.
Together, okay?
Okay. Okay.
- We can do this.
- Okay.
We gotta go.
Fuck.
It's all fake.
Brooke.
Okay. Okay. You okay?
Yeah.
We can do this.
- Okay.
We left that open.
We left that door open.
He's not in here.
- Fuck.
Okay. Okay.
Don't
look at their faces, Mommy.
More dolls.
Let's just get the fuck
out of here.
Don't look
at their faces, Mommy.
Brooke!
It's a dead end.
Clever, clever.
You've found the hidden path
to Hell.
Clever, clever.
You've found the hidden path
to Hell.
Brooke, go!
No!
Brooke?
Nat! Help me, please!
Please, no, please!
Why are you doing this?
Please, please,
why are you doing this?
I won't tell anybody!
Please!
No! Wait, wait!
No!
Go to Hell!
Hey, back up!
He was
right behind us.
We looked everywhere,
but we couldn't find him.
Wait, what?
No, no, no,
he was right there.
Don't worry. We're gonna
keep looking, okay?
They're gonna find him.
Tragedy at Hell Fest tonight.
Police believe
that the suspect
may have entered
the park anonymously
with the rest
of the attendees.
Four fatalities
have been confirmed
with two of the bodies
being hidden
within mazes inside the park.
All of this leads police
to connect tonight's murders
to the killing of a girl
at an Orange Grove haunt
just a few years ago.
If you're just tuning in,
tragedy...
Daddy, you're home!
Did you bring me anything?
Subtitles by explosiveskull