Ted:
He bought this place
a while back.
Ted:
Meant something to him.
He spent all his time out
he before--
Damn.
Tina wanted to come. She's--
She's stuck in that
damned training for...
two weeks in Montreal.
Dad told me about that.
Ted, we never talked about Tina.
What's to say?
It was five years ago, Brad.
Yeah,
and we haven't talked since.
Look, I never told you that
I am sorry.
Ted:
Just leave it.
I guess you need a ride back
into town, huh.
Glad to see big brother's...
finally growing out of
his clumsy stage.
Ted:
That's weird.
About thirty feet.
So you think
Dad knew about this?
I don't know.
-He never said anything to you?
-Nope.
So we're going to do this now?
We're doing it now.
Ted, I just got here.
That's why we're doing it now.
-Can I at least go change first?
Ted:
-Nope.
Damn.
So we're just going to
Batman it up and down
this thing...
without any harness or gear,
right?
Why not? I won't stop you
if you'd rather jump.
Brad:
Maybe there's treasure
down there, huh.
Hell no. No.
You gave yourself a black eye
in the 8th grade...
by popping a zit.
I'll make sure it's safe first.
Hey. Touchdown.
Is it cool?
Get down here. Hurry.
Generator.
Ahh. Hey, it works!
It's barely putting out
any power but--
It works.
So what the hell's going on
down here?
I don't know.
Brad:
This stuff looks like it's
been sitting here for decades.
Yeah,
but these light bulbs are new.
I bet the gas
for that generator is too.
Brad:
Man,
what was Dad doing down here?
I don't know.
He never said a word about it.
Hey!
Hey, if anybody's in there,...
we're not here
to steal your tools.
We're just exploring.
You still claustrophobic?
Hey, what gave me away?
Just hang on.
We're almost there.
Where's that wind coming from?
It feels good.
Brad:
Hey, it looks like
it opens up back there.
Turns off to the right about
fifteen feet back.
You know what? I bet nobody's
ever been back there.
That's a virgin passage.
How do you know?
Cause nothing bigger than a dick
can squeeze through the hole.
No, I mean,...
how do you know
there's not another way in...
on the other side?
I don't know.
I've never heard of
any caves over that way.
Look at that.
It's only
a couple of inches thick.
This is just too creepy.
What?
You hear that?
Yeah.
What is it?
Waterfall?
No, no.
A lot of work has been done
to this cave.
The lights. The gravel.
All of this.
Uh-huh.
Why do you think no one has
bothered to open up that hole?
I'd just check
what's back there.
That's why
I was the college athlete.
And you collected Boba Fetts.
Let a real man pop this cherry.
Ted:
We're going to need
a bigger boat.
Uncle Charlie.
Bradley! Bradley!
How the hell are you?
Look at that, Bradley.
Let me look at you, Bradley.
You got bigger, Bradley.
You're not flat footed at all.
He lives right up the hill now.
Dad and I take care of him.
Charlie:
Hey buddy.
Hey, your daddy's coming back,
Bradley.
On Sunday, okay?
Yes.
Yeah,
I think we'll go fishing again.
All of us together like before,
okay?
My brother's coming back
on Sunday.
No, I don't think so,
Uncle Charlie.
I mean,
it's four days from now...
and I'm not sure how long
Brad's planning on staying.
No, T-Bear. T-Bear. Bradley.
Bradley's staying.
-You're staying, Bradley.
-I'm staying.
-You're really staying.
-Okay. I don't have to...
start work till September
so I was going to...
hang out a couple weeks.
If that's okay with you guys.
Okay, Bradley, stay. Okay.
We go fishing. We go fishing.
Hello?...Oh, hey, honey....
Yeah. No, I'm sorry.
There was no coverage
out there...
Yeah, I'm standing with Ted and
Uncle Charlie right now. Yeah.
Tina says hi.
Oh, hi, Tina Tina.
Brad:
Uncle Charlie says hi, too.
I love you too...
Okay, I'll talk to you soon.
Bye.
Bradley, was that Tina Tina?
Yeah, Uncle Charlie.
You remember Tina Tina,
don't you?
I remember Tina Tina.
She got me my bicycle.
T-Bear, you remember--
T-Bear. Weren't you the one...
who was supposed to marry
Tina Tina?
It was a long time ago,
Uncle Charlie.
A long time ago.
-Come on here, Bradley...
-No, no, no, no.
Charlie:
Okay, okay, Bradley.
Come on. We'll go to my house.
Check this out.
Holy shit!
Damn, don't touch it!
Well, it's too late now.
Who needs back breaking manual
labor when you've got this shit.
Hey, put it back.
I don't want to get blown up...
on account of you.
At least we'd go together,
big brother.
Well, hooray.
Okay. I charged a couple of
batteries last night...
so I think
we should work in shifts and--
I'll have us in by dinner.
Go, Tarzan.
You know this will take days.
Okay, this officially
just became a bad idea.
So why do we give a rat's ass
what's back there anyway?
Yeah. I mean, we already know
what's back there. More cave.
Yeah, just a bunch of rocks.
-In the dark.
-Yeah.
Damn, that breeze feels good.
Yeah.
Hey--
-Hey, what was--
-Shh.
Brad.
I think it was a... I think
it was a rock slide back there.
Right...
I don't think that noise
we heard earlier...
was a waterfall.
Why not?
'Cause I don't hear it anymore.
No.
It's just normal
cave type stuff, right?
And what do
we know anyway? Right?
We don't know anything.
It's gonna be a pretty long haul
getting through there.
You sure you're up for it?
Pick me up tomorrow morning
at seven thirty.
You're going to hire us a
Sherpa too, huh?
Come on, man.
We got to do this up right.
We get to be
Indiana Jones today.
Oh, Indiana Jones.
A dull American
Allan Quartermain rip-off.
Blasphemy.
Oh, nerd heads going
caving, eh?
You two need a steady hand of
a pro at the helm.
That's where I come in.
Been in every cave in the state.
Well not this one, Churchill.
No one's been where we're going.
-Virgin?
Brad:
-Yes, virgin.
Let me tag along.
I'll be a Short Round
to your Dr. Jones.
I'll worship at your altar.
I won't do anything gay.
But that's about it.
You're working, aren't you?
Bollocks to this place, man.
I'm no good.
You saw that yourselves.
Sorry, mate.
Oh, so that's how it is.
You selfish dicks!
Tough tourists.
Hey, Allan Quartermain?
He sucks my ass.
Hey, come back here and
say that!
Ha ha! You'll be back.
You'll be back.
Yeah, you better run!
No.
It's not going to happen.
You know, just a little bit more
and we're in.
One more day's work, max.
Oh shit.
Holy shit, that is tight.
Brad:
Have you ever heard of
Floyd Collins?
He got stuck and
died in a place just like that.
They never got him out.
Okay,
in honor of Mr. Collins,...
let's name this passage
Floyd's Tomb.
You think you're gonna fit.
You think you're just gonna
squeeze right in there, huh.
Ted:
Should be okay
through most of it. I mean...
in the end it's a little tough,
though.
Well you know I'm probably...
not going to be
able to fit in there...
Brad:
What if you get hurt in there?
What if you just
twist your ankle?
I'm not going to be in there
to help you.
You'll be completely
on your own.
Ted:
Yeah, I'm used to that.
I'm just glad you're here now.
I was wondering
when you'd go off again.
Brad:
-Are we in?
Ted:
-We're in. Ha, ha, ha.
Whoo! How do you like that?
-How you like that now!
-How do you like that! Whoa!
Come on, we did it!
Wait...
You think Dad would be proud?
Let's get a rope,
tie it around my legs.
I'm going in. Come on. Come on.
You know Dad used to always
come up and see me play...
when I was at Tech.
He never missed a home game.
Yeah, he was proud.
You were always welcome, too,
you know.
Thanks.
What'd you play again?
-What position?
-No. What sport?
-Seriously?
-Yeah.
-Baseball. Center field.
-Cool.
Hey, I'm sorry, man.
I was just never
really into that stuff.
Okay, let's go.
All right, lift my legs up.
Brad:
Ha. Ha.
Ted, you're totally in.
How is it?
It's no fun.
Hey, can you make it?
I don't know.
It's getting pretty tight.
-Oh, god. Hey, Ted.
-What?
I just realized
you literally have a...
mountain resting on your back.
I mean one,
one tiny shift of earth and...
All right, Brad, I got it.
Brad:
You're breaking shit, dude.
It's getting hard to breathe,
Brad.
I'm stuck, man,
I can't go any farther.
-I'm coming out.
-Okay, careful.
I can't.
I'm stuck. I'm stuck.
I can't get out.
I'm stuck!
I'll get it. Hang on. Hang on.
The last part's just too tight.
That's cool.
Ah, we gave it
one hell of a try, though.
Where's the drill?
Help me out! Help me out!
Pull me out! Pull me out!
Come on! Come on!
A mountain lion maybe?
How can anything like that
get back there?
Maybe it was an echo then.
Something weird.
And we never-- we never drilled
from inside there before.
Oh shit.
I left Dad's drill down there.
I will buy you a new one.
Hey, there's no way we're
going back in there, right?
You know that, right?
That's the best I can do.
It could be enough.
I'm going to go for it.
Okay. Okay.
Just give me your feet.
No. No.
Either I make it all the way
or I get stuck trying.
Okay. Okay.
Okay, let's do this.
Okay it's time for this thing.
This is all on you.
This is what we've been
working for. You got that inch.
You got nothing
stopping you now.
Okay now breathe, breathe.
Come on, breathe! Breathe.
Okay, we can do this now. Okay?
We can do this.
All right, you're gonna make it.
You're gonna make it.
You're just going to squeeze
right in there. Okay?
Just take it easy.
Take it really easy
and you got it.
Nothing's stopping you now,
okay?
This is all yours. All right.
You ready?
-Yeah.
-You ready?
Okay.
Arms not over.
Arms on my side this time.
Brad:
Okay, just breathe, okay?
You're totally gonna make it.
Come on, you're gonna make it.
Damn.
It's tighter than I remember.
It's cool. You just--
hey, you just gotta
relax yourself.
Just relax.
I cannot believe
we're doing this.
He can be killed doing this.
You doing okay?
This is stupid.
This is really stupid.
Come back out, Ted.
Come on. This is stupid.
No.
No. Ted, come back.
I still can't make it.
Well just back on out then.
Okay, we'll just go home.
Brad:
Now just come on back out.
Please.
Brad:
Just get out of here.
I don't want to be here anymore.
I'm gonna have to
let all the air out of my lungs.
And then just scoot forward
to get on from here.
No, that's insane.
No, let's...
look, let's just go home.
Brad:
We've done everything
we can here.
-Here goes.
Brad:
-No, Ted, damn it.
Get out of the hole!
Come on. I believe you.
Come on. You don't have to
prove yourself anymore.
Brad, I don't need this
right now, okay?
Ted:
Not now.
Just be with me here. Please.
Just be with me this time. Okay?
Okay, I'm with you.
I'm with you big brother.
Okay. Okay, you can do this.
Okay, you can do this.
Brad:
Just take it really slow,
okay? You be careful.
I can't breathe!
-Okay, I'm coming to get you.
- No. No.
Okay, you push through.
I can't breathe.
Damn it, Ted. You push through!
You son of a bitch...
Don't you give up on me now.
You break through.
Ted:
I did it.
Ted, please, push forward.
-Ted!
-Ahhh!
Hi. I'm through!
You made it! Ha, ha, ha. Whoa!
Brad:
Whoa! Shit, you made it!
You did it! Yes, you did.
What are you so damn
excited about?
I'm the one
who was stuck in the hole.
Oh my god you made it,
you crazy son of a bitch.
Yeah. I was there, remember?
Hey.
Hey. Hey. What's back there?
Ted:
There's this big corridor.
It's beautiful.
I'm going to go take a look.
Hey.
Just--just don't
get out of earshot, okay?
'Cause I won't be able to
hear you...
if you get hurt or anything.
Aye aye, Captain.
All right. Got it.
Hey, you okay?
Yeah.
You okay?
Brad!
Brad:
Ted.
Ha. Ha. Ha. Ha.
Magellan returns.
Damn! Coming back's easier.
-You okay?
-Yeah.
It's a boy!
At least that's what
he keeps telling me.
-So how was it?
-It was awesome, man.
I didn't get that far in,
though.
Sound travels like
shit in there.
There's a lot more to explore.
You're not going by yourself.
It's too dangerous.
We got to find
someone else to go with you.
I know just the guy.
-No.
-Yeah.
-Yes.
No!
Yes!
Yeah, okay, thank you.
Thank you. That's great.
There's a long way down
that hole.
So watch it.
I'm not taking your ass
to the emergency room.
Prepare to be blocked in tight.
The wall's a bit slick.
Sharp rocks down there
so be careful..
What's with the arts and crafts?
All my stuff's handmade,
you wanker.
You got to improvise down there.
Sometimes right on the spur
of the moment.
Now you two amateurs...
probably haven't been caving
long enough...
to burn through your first baby
nine volts have you?
But see...
This way...
I don't have to worry about
batteries going south now, do I?
Blow me.
There's one more in here. Oh!
That's hilarious.
Speaking of going south,
if you'll excuse me...
I've got a date
with a lovely hole.
Joe:
Ugh. Yeah...
I'd hate to hand
anything to you, Ted.
But you must have a massive
set of the old wrinklies...
to stuff yourself
through that thing.
It's tighter than a nun's ass.
All right, I'm coming in.
Make you famous.
-Come on lard ass.
-Got it.
Man, take a look
at these beauties, mate.
Joe:
Formations for days.
As virgin
as a box of broken beer bottles.
Ted:
-I told you.
Brad:
-Okay, here it comes.
Ted:
Okay.
Ow. Oh god.
What the hell was that?
Forest Chump here tried to
fight a rock with his skull.
-Is he okay?
- Oh god.
The rock won.
Hey, Ted, come on back through.
Ted:
Hell no. We didn't put in
all that work to let...
somebody else go first.
I'm going.
Oh bullocks to that Dr. Quest.
You are unfit for
the unknown today, I'm afraid.
Joe:
You're going.
You're going home.
Slither away, Dr. Jones.
Slither away.
Quartermain's here
to pick up your slack.
Oh, this little piggy
went to market.
-You're not helping here.
-This little piggy...
slithered home.
This little piggy in shame.
Ted:
Shut up Joe.
Joe:
This little piggy
didn't know which way to go.
Joe:
This little piggy said,
"Bye bye, Joe."
Joe:
Can you blokes
see my ass from there?
Joe:
I'm walking into
virgin territory.
Joe:
-Oh, look at that!
Brad:
-Will you shut up, Joe!
Joe:
It's absolutely gorgeous.
I just figured out...
Joe:
why Indy Jones wears a hat
all the time.
Joe:
To cover the bump
on his Yankee head.
Hey, we'll come back tomorrow.
Joe:
Hey, Ted,
can you do me a favor?
Tell me, who was the second man
on the moon?
I have no idea.
Exactly.
Be back in an hour, Joe.
One hour.
It's an hour and
forty five minutes.
Joe! Hello?
Joe, what the hell is going on
back there?
Brad:
What, did he stop for tea time?
So how much do you remember
about Mom?
Damn.
I was only three when she left,
so, not much really.
Ted:
I was five.
I guess I should
remember more,...
Ted:
but all I really have
is the day she left.
It was stupid kid stuff but...
I've spent a long time wondering
what I'd done to make her go.
No. Things got too rough for her
and she left. Okay?
Nothing more to it than that.
There's a lot of
that going round in this family.
You know I'm here now.
So you can give me some
damn credit for that at least.
It doesn't matter.
Just forget it.
Yeah, I would like to...
if you would take
your own advice..
and stop pulling this shit
out of the blue every time we--
That's enough.
Where's that limey
bastard anyway?
Hey, if you have something
to say to me, then have at it.
Otherwise, get off my back!
Get off your back?
What about my back...
you son of a bitch?
-Mine! Mine!
-Okay.
-I see it, okay?
-For five years...
you did whatever the hell
you wanted.
With whoever the hell
While I rotted down here taking
care of Dad and Uncle Charlie.
All right. I see how it is.
Okay, I see.
-And I told you I'm sorry.
-My back's the one that's...
been stepped on, Brad.
Not yours.
You think you can come in here
with your 'I'm sorry's'...
and everything's going
to be okay? I don't--
Joe?
What's in there?
What are we hearing?
Let's get out of here, please.
-Shh. Get back.
-We got to get out of here.
Brad:
What if we see something.
We should have said
something to him.
Ted:
-Let's just go!
Brad:
-Just stop.
-I have to go get him.
-No. Don't do it.
-I have to get him.
-Don't.
We brought--we brought him here!
Brad, we--
Shit.
Joe.
You all right, Joe?
What happened?
What happened, Joe?
Hey man.
What was that noise?
What was the noise?
Ted:
Joe! Hey, wait up, man.
Come on.
What's going on? Joe!
Joe, don't do it. Come on.
Stop! Stop! Joe!
-What did you see, Joe?
-Come on, man, tell us.
Ted:
-Talk to me.
Brad:
-What did you see?
Hey, you forgot your stuff.
You left all your stuff.
Brad:
Yeah.
He still won't answer.
Brad:
I know. I just called the store.
They said
he didn't come in again today.
Ted:
-Brad?
Brad:
-Yeah.
Ted:
We have to go back.
Brad:
Tomorrow.
Okay. Bye.
Hey, Joe. Open up, man.
Joe. Come on, man.
I know you're in there.
Hey, Joe. I can see you, man.
Ted:
Joe, just open the door.
Open the door, man. Come on.
Ted:
Come on,
man I see you right there.
Just tell me
what was in the hole.
Joe, you're really scaring me.
What did you see, man?
Hey, hey.
Hey, you know what?
I am one lying bastard.
So I go into the local grotto
this morning...
and I convince them that I'm
this real caver or something.
So they let me borrow
this real deal equipment.
Check this shit out, dude.
So they said the walkies'
might not work there.
But if you're wired
it's guaranteed.
Just plug it in
when you want to talk.
You nervous or something?
Maybe just cold feet.
Well Joe spent
a lot of time in there and
he came out fine, right?
I mean he was a little spooked,
but. I mean they also said--
the guys at the grotto said
he's a drama queen.
Superstitious and what not.
I bet the echo just spooked him.
You ready?
Hey, just check in
from time to time.
Just keep me on the up. Okay.
Hey, dude, you okay?
You want some aspirin?
I think I--
Well
you're in a foul mood today.
You can be a little
more appreciative.
Do you know
what a pain in the ass...
it was to get this stuff
for you?
Brad:
Well how long do you plan
on looking around back there?
Hey, Ted. Ted!
What is with you today?
Okay, did I say something?
You heard me.
Brad:
Oh, damn it I was just
trying to protect you, okay.
Brad:
I didn't think
you were ready for all this yet.
Yeah, I was. You weren't.
Full of shit as always.
Just come back here, okay?
Let's talk about--
Pass me the radio. Hurry up.
No, I'm not.
Not until you come out...
and we talk about this,
okay. I--
Pass me the radio right now...
or I'm going in without it.
I don't care.
Brad:
Not here, okay?
If I get stuck in there,...
I won't be able to get
in touch with you.
It'll be your fault, Brad.
Your fault!
Look, just come back out, okay?
Don't do this, not right now,
okay?
Let's talk this through.
We just need to talk about this.
Brad:
You know
I cannot follow you back there.
-I know.
Brad:
-Please.
Ted, come back out
and we can talk about this.
Brad:
Ted, come back.
Ted, I just wanted to
make sure the phone worked.
It works.
Brad:
Just be careful.
Come on. Come on!
Brad:
Hello?
What are you sleeping?
Brad:
Well not now.
Ted:
That's it, man. Dead end.
There's nothing back here.
Coming back.
Brad:
All right.
Brad? Brad? Brad?
Ted:
Brad!
Brad! Brad!
Ted:
Brad!
Brad! Brad!
Brad:
-Ted!
-Help me!
Please, Brad,
pull me out of here!
-Ted, what's wrong?
-Come in here with me.
Come on, hurry.
Hurry, hurry, Brad. Help me.
Come on, hurry! Come on.
You're almost there.
Brad! Help me, Brad!
Okay, come on.
Brad!
Grab me. Help! Pull me out!
Oh god, help me, it's here.
Brad:
Come on.
Come on!
Get it off.
Ted, let go.
Let go. Let go. Run. Run.
Cut the damn rope. Come on.
Cut the rope.
-Just do it.
-I am!
Faster, Brad! Do it!
-Let's go. Let's go.
-I'm trying. I'm trying.
Get it off. Get it off me.
Cut it!
Ted:
Go for it.
Charlie:
Hello. Hello, Ted the Bear?
T-Bear, you mad at me?
Charlie:
You-you won't answer
your phone again, okay?
Charlie:
Brad won't come out
of his room, T-Bear.
Charlie:
Did I do something wrong?
Ted the Bear. My brother...
Charlie:
He has his
birthday party in three days.
Charlie:
Already got his present.
It's a pretty one too.
I made it myself. Okay?
Charlie:
I want to see my brother!
Let me Ted the Bear. Okay? Bye.
Damn.
Oh!
Ted:
Go for it.
Joe:
Ted, it's Joe. I'm...
Ted:
-Joe!
Joe:
-Ted! Ted! Ted!
Get them off me.
Hey Joe!
Hey, Dude.
This dude is dead. Dead.
Dead? No. What? When?
I found him yesterday, man.
Some kind of meth head deal.
He was all cranked up out
at the house.
Frigging tweaker.
What.
What, you know this guy?
You, you his family?
Are you his family?
Be up here. Over there.
I think, yeah.
They can see if from the door.
Right there.
I thought you weren't
leaving till Monday.
Yeah. Well, I didn't see
the point in staying.
And you won't talk to me.
At least- at least things--
things getting all worn out--
I have to board
the hole back up, Brad.
No, I'm not going back there,
Ted.
Okay, we have to go back there.
We have to put it right.
We have to make it like it was.
Why don't we just--
let's get out of here, okay?
-We'll take Uncle Charlie--
-Joe is dead.
Oh this is not our fault.
It's not our fault, okay?
-It's not our fault.
-What?
What is not our fault, Brad?
What is not our fault?
Oh shit, man.
It's just a coincidence, okay?
We didn't do that, okay?
That is not our fault.
They were camping.
Look where they were?
-No. I don't believe it, okay?
-The area where we were.
We got to make this right.
We got to put it back
like it was.
-No, okay?
-We have to.
No, I won't go back there, okay?
We have to try to make it right!
-We don't even know if it was--
-We have to make it right, Brad.
I will not go back there.
I just want to go home.
Okay,
I got a family to go home to.
We're not your family, huh? Huh?
I'm not your family, Brad?
Come on...
Brad:
Ted, she's pregnant.
She's pregnant.
Brad:
We found out right before
I came down here.
I got to go home to her.
Go home, Brad.
Go home to your family.
Maybe I'll see you
at the next funeral.
I knew you'd run away.
Let's just hurry up.
I want to get this done
before dark.
I'm scared, Ted.
I've never been this scared
in my whole life.
I'm scared too, Brad.
Do you have the tools
we need at your house?
A lot of what we had
is still in the cave.
Yeah.
Do you really think
boarding this thing up...
is going to do any good?
I think the real problem is
what's behind that round rock.
There's nothing on Earth...
that can make me go back
in that cave.
This is going to have to do.
Yeah.
Well, it didn't work for Dad.
Yeah look it. Perfect.
I'm telling you
we don't need that.
Ted:
Yeah, we do.
Just grab the tools.
This is way too much. Okay?
We don't need to take as much.
Ted:
You want to get out there
before dark, let's go.
Brad:
Yes, because I'm leaving
as soon as we're done.
Ted:
All right.
Let's get it done then.
Can we hurry up?
It's getting late.
Here. Just in case.
Come on.
No, no, no, no. no.
No, Charlie, no.
Pick up the phone, Charlie!
Pick up the phone!
Ted:
The map's gone.
The map-- it's not here, Brad.
It's not here!
-Charlie!
Charlie!
-Charlie! Charlie!
Do we have any lights here?
This is serious. Charlie!
Charlie!
Brad:
Ted!
-Charlie!
-That's all we got here.
-That's it?
-That's it.
-Charlie! Charlie where are you?
-Charlie! Charlie!
-Charlie!
-Ted!
Ted:
Come on, okay. Come on.
Come on, the thing's in here,
Ted.
The thing's in the dark.
Oh god. Charlie's in there.
-Charlie!
-Charlie! Charlie!
-What do we do? What do we do?
-Charlie!
Here we come, Charlie.
Ted! No, wait!
Charlie!
Oh shit.
Ted, come back! Ted, come back!
Hurry, come back!
Jesus.
Ted, what's going on?
Ted, talk to me, please.
Ted!
Ted, I'm coming!
Charlie! Where are you? Charlie!
Come back, Charlie!
Ugh!
Ted!
Brad:
Damn it. Come on. I can't move.
Help!
Help! Help!
Ted, I'm coming!
Stop them! Stop them!
Stop moving!
Charlie! Ted!
I'm in the hole.
You son of a bitch!
Uncle Charlie! Ted!
Charlie:
Come get us.
He's not coming back.
Norman's not coming back.
Please stay still. Please.
Ted:
Hurry. Hurry.
The flare's going lower.
Run. Run.
Ted.
Ted:
Stay still. Stay still.
I got it. I got it.
No. Wait. Wait.
Uncle Charlie, stop!
Ted!
I'm going to go in.
Come on! Get up.
Get out.
Ted.
Get him!
-Here. Light it. Burn it.
-Okay
Throw it in. Now! Right now.
-Come on.
-I got it.
No, Charlie, no!
No, Charlie, no! No, no!
Come on!
Let me go. Let me die.
No!
You'll be the best man.
-Charlie!
-Don't let go!
-No!
-Charlie!
Charlie!
Ted!
I hope this is enough light
to keep us safe.
Ted:
Is that all we have left?
Ride it through.
You're my brother.
So what's it going to be, huh,
a boy or a girl?
-I don't know yet.
-You don't know.
You want to know what's
the most beautiful thing...
I ever saw?
It was your swing. Your swing.
Your swing that night you hit
that grand slam against State.
It was a wonder.
Your batting average was
328 that year.
Your junior year.
You hit 32 home runs,
86 RBIs and...
-Forgive me, I can't remember.
-It's okay.
How many stolen bases you had.
It wasn't just Dad.
I never missed
a home game either. I just--
I just never wanted you to know.
I forgive you.
I forgive you, little brother.
Please forgive me.
It's time to go home, Brad.
It's time to go home.
Come on, I'll help you.
No, get up. Get up.
Stop. Stop.
Listen. Listen.
There's just enough left.
You can make it out if you run.
No. No, you're not going to
leave me. Listen!
You have to make it
out of here, okay?
We have to make sure.
You're gonna have a baby soon.
The future's in front of you.
You get to be a dad.
No, no, no.
You're coming with me.
Stop! Stop!
See. See.
Don't worry about me.
I'm right behind you.
I'll be right behind you.
Now go.
-No. No.
-Go!
No!
Brad:
Ted! Ted!
Don't step on this, Brad.
I'm riding it.
Brad:
-Ted!
-You'd better run.
Ted!
Don't, Ted. Don't!
Ted! Ted! Ted! Ted!
Ted:
Go home, Brad. Go home.
Ted! Ted!
Ted, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm so... I'm so...
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.