(MUSIC PLAYS IN CAR)
♪ If you want
to know who we are
♪ We are gentlemen of Japan
♪ On many a vase and jar
♪ On many a screen and fan
♪ We figure in lively paint Our
attitude's queer and quaint
♪ You're wrong if
you think it ain't ♪
(CHUCKLES)
DAVID: Hey, come on.
Embrace living
in the country.
Driving on the open road,
singing Gilbert and Sullivan.
What's more
American than that?
First of all,
Gilbert and Sullivan
were English.
I knew that.
You knew that.
Want me to put on
something else?
♪ Before the mighty troops
The troops of Titipu! ♪
No. Not on your life.
♪ Before the mighty troops
The troops of Titipu! ♪
(WINDSHIELD WIPERS THUMPING)
(RAIN PATTERING)
DAVID: Isn't this cool?
We're actually using four-wheel drive.
Bet we're the only one of our
friends that can say that.
David, I'm wondering how the
trucks made it back here.
I'm sure they did.
Yeah, I gave them
directions.
But I also said we'd
be there to supervise.
I didn't know we were gonna be
stopping for strawberries...
I wanted to stop.
Peas...
I've never done the whole
roadside stand bit.
Spinach...
Thought it was important for Lucas.
And asparagus.
He should know
where food comes from.
David, food comes
from farms, not stands.
They both have farmers.
I think I see a light.
Where are we?
Hey, we're home, peanut.
LUCAS: It's really dark.
Where are all
the apartment buildings?
They don't have apartments
in the country, baby.
Babe? Dana.
It's a good move.
Believe me?
Yeah, I believe you.
New beginning.
(KISSES)
Ugh.
DAVID: It doesn't get better than this, babe.
(LUCAS LAUGHING)
All right.
(LUCAS GROANS)
LUCAS: Oh.
Shit.
DAVID: Oh, my God,
you kidding me?
Thought they were supposed to put
everything inside the right rooms.
DANA: Well,
obviously they didn't.
(BOTH GASP)
Hey, peanut, last one to find the
bathroom has to go wee in the woods!
I'm on your heels, I'm on your heels.
Here I come, here I come.
Please be careful!
(LUCAS LAUGHING)
DAVID: Here he goes!
Here he goes!
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
DAVID: Hey.
Hey.
Who puts mirrors
like this here?
Oh. Some guy
who's got a hot wife
and wants as many
of her as possible.
LUCAS: Daddy!
Can't find my toys!
(WATER DRIPPING)
(DANA EXHALES)
(BABY CRYING)
(BABY CONTINUES CRYING)
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
(WATER DRIPPING)
(WATER CONTINUES DRIPPING)
(GLASS TINKLING)
(RAIN PATTERING)
(THUNDER CRASHES)
Hey.
This kitchen
has potential, huh?
Yes.
Is there any coffee going?
Oh, if you want coffee, you're gonna
have to find the coffeemaker first.
Found her.
Fuck you.
Is that a threat?
Or a promise?
Uh, could be
a promising threat.
Or a threatening promise.
Where's the peanut?
He's upstairs,
waiting for his waffles.
Oh. And we have a leak
in the breakfast room.
LUCAS: I don't know.
I don't know.
We have to wait and see.
No, she's a nice mommy.
The nicest mommy
in the world.
DANA: Lucas,
who are you talking to?
Baby, I asked you
a question.
Who were you
talking to just now?
Lucas, turn around.
Oh, no! Lucas!
Oh, where did you
even find that thing?
He lives here.
This is his home.
Ugh. Well, I'm sure he'll be even
happier when we take him outside.
He said he'll protect me!
Baby, I'm sure he did.
(CAT MEOWS)
We've talked about this before, okay?
No pets.
Please, Mommy?
DAVID: Hey,
where'd that come from?
Hey, hey, hey.
Let me have a go
at that.
(GROANS)
(CAT PURRS AND MEOWS)
Hey, you stink,
little guy.
Guess what? I just saw a mouse
downstairs and it was huge!
And he had his nose
in the waffle cupboard!
So guess we could use
a good mouser, babe.
Yeah, he's a really
good mouser.
(MEOWING SOFTLY)
DAVID: Hey. Hold still, you little rascal.
Hey, how about Rascal?
Rascal's a good name.
Yeah, I think
it's a cool name.
Ooh.
(GIGGLING)
(DAVID MIMICS YOWLING)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(CAMERA CLICKING)
(CAMERA CONTINUES CLICKING)
(FROGS CROAKING)
(GROWLING)
DAVID: Hey, Dana!
What do you say
we drive into town,
get some groceries,
lay of the land?
DANA: David,
there's something out here.
We live in
the country now, babe,
all kinds of crazy
critters out there.
Like what?
Maybe it's a raccoon.
The occasional
zombie redneck.
Hey, Dana, come on.
I'm sure the locals
are eager to sneak a peek
of the new lord
and lady of the manor.
Not bad, huh?
Not bad at all.
This is cool, huh?
LUCAS: Where's
the movie theater?
They don't have one, peanut,
but what they do have
is a 6-plex up the road in New Bern.
Afternoon.
Oh, afternoon.
You see that? Friendly.
Look at that. That's a
genuine barber shop. Huh?
Oh, friendly
neighborhood gun store.
And we'll go wild turkey shooting.
How about that?
Did you forget?
I'm a vegetarian.
I do not like
killing animals.
You don't? That's okay. We'll
shoot watermelons instead.
Hey! I've heard about this place.
Oh.
Yelp says that this place has the best
ice cream this side of the Mississippi.
No way! Really?
Yeah, better than the Ice
Cream Factory in Brooklyn.
(DOOR BELLS JINGLE)
WOMAN: Afternoon!
Hello.
Hey.
I bet I know
who you all are!
DAVID: Oh, I bet you do!
You all bought
the Blacker House.
Yeah, that's us.
(LAUGHING) Welcome!
Welcome! Welcome!
Oh, I'm so happy to see
some new faces around here.
We're happy to be a new face.
Hey, I'm David.
David.
This is my wife, Dana.
DANA: Hi.
How are you?
And this little
sugar addict over here
is our son, Lucas. Hey, get up.
(WOMAN LAUGHS)
Marti Morrison! And the
pleasure is all mine.
And hi, Lucas.
LUCAS: Hi.
MARTI: What's your
favorite ice cream?
Strawberry.
You are so in luck.
I just made some strawberry this morning.
Is that okay?
Yeah. That's fine.
Sure.
All right,
let's get scooping.
(LAUGHS)
You know, nobody has lived
in that old house
for quite some time.
I'm afraid that you all have
your work cut out for you.
Yup. Got a leaky roof
for starters.
Oh. Now, listen, if you need
some help with the big stuff,
I mean, I'm happy to recommend
some honest, hard-working people.
You know, actually we're...
Ben Philips, Jr.
Now, that's not to be confused
with Ben Philips, Sr., who drinks.
Enough said.
But Ben, Jr. now, he knows
his way around a hammer.
And he is not bad
to look at.
I said that out loud,
didn't I? That's awful.
Get behind me, Satan.
That's terrible.
You know, actually we were hoping
to do most of the work ourselves.
Oh, is that right? Well, are you
some kind of architect or...
Well, funnily enough...
Look at you!
Oh, I guess that you're a man who
knows his way around a hammer, too.
I do. I'm actually
the architect.
I'm gonna be doing most
of the work on the house.
Is that right?
Yeah, that's right.
It's a big job.
Big job.
And what is it
that you do?
In between my naps,
I enjoy watching her work,
playing Xbox.
Oh, huh?
We actually just
came in to say howdy,
pick up a few things
for the house.
Well, howdy.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
And just look around, let me know
if you can't find something.
And good luck
with your house.
(WATER DRIPPING)
(FOOTSTEPS)
(CREAKING)
(BIRDS SQUAWKING)
Lucas?
Lucas, what is it?
There's a dog out there.
It's probably
just a stray.
I'm scared.
Oh, it's all right, peanut.
I'll protect you.
Mommy will protect you.
Mommy?
(LUCAS PANTING)
(GASPS)
Mommy.
Oh, my God, Lucas! Lucas!
(GASPS)
David.
DAVID: Hmm?
(SHUDDERING)
I had
one of my dreams.
(LOON CALLING IN DISTANCE)
(CAT PURRING)
(MEOWING)
(GATE CLANGS AND CREAKS)
(SIGHS)
(BIRD CALLING)
(DOOR CREAKING)
(CREAKING)
(GRUNTING)
(GASPS)
(BATS SCREECHING)
(GASPING)
Shit.
(GRUNTING)
DAVID: Dana, are you okay?
Yeah, David, I'm up here.
I need your help.
Where's the Lion
and the Witch?
Well, technically it's
called a "chifferobe."
DAVID: Yeah, chifferobe, huh?
What's it made of, lead?
You're positive you saw
a light up in here?
Yes. And then it went off.
May I ask what you're doing outside in
the middle of the night, young lady?
I was getting some air.
DAVID: It's probably just
a faulty wire or something.
DANA: Well, all the more reason
to check it out.
Oh, wow.
Cool.
(PANTING)
Our own secret room.
Of course.
Locked?
Yeah, or stuck.
See anything?
No, it's too dark.
Hey, Dana, come on up.
We'll find a locksmith in
the morning to get it open.
Hey, Dana.
Hey, Dana, come on.
Dana, it's late. Stop.
What?
Hey, you okay?
Yeah.
You got that look
that concerns me.
You want me to call
Dr. Ashby in the morning?
No. No. I'm just... I'm
getting adjusted. Sorry.
It's just that room's
not on the floor plans.
It's bugging me
a little bit.
(LUCAS LAUGHING)
(DAVID MIMICKING ROAR)
DAVID: I'm feeling
Wolverine hungry!
(LUCAS SCREAMING PLAYFULLY)
LUCAS: Never!
You parsley-looking mutant!
(LUCAS YELLING PLAYFULLY)
(TICKING)
God damn it!
(SIGHS) Fuck you, too.
(LOCK CLICKS)
(DOOR CREAKING)
(DOOR SLAMS)
(GASPS)
David?
Lucas, is that you?
(FOOTSTEPS)
Lucas?
(LOW RUMBLING)
(SHRIEKING)
David, please let me out of here!
Please let me out!
(SCREAMS)
David! David! David! David!
(DOG BARKING)
Let me out of here! David! David!
Please let me out! David!
David, please!
(DISTANT SCREAM ECHOES)
(BREATH TREMBLING)
GIRL:
He doesn't want you.
(DOOR UNLOCKING)
(GASPING)
(MUSIC PLAYING ON TV)
MAN: (ON TV) That,
gentlemen, is my wife.
Mad, and the offspring
of a mad family.
(DAVID SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY)
DAVID: Get it back around.
Reverse. Reverse.
That's right, move it back.
Move it back.
Back room, back room, back room.
(LUCAS SHOUTING)
(PANTING) Hey, baba.
Where'd you come from?
Where were you?
I needed you, David.
Babe, I'm right here.
I've been right here.
(SOBBING) I was locked up.
I was locked up there for hours...
I don't... Dana, Dana, I don't...
...and hours!
You didn't notice
I was missing?
Dana, I swear to God...
I was upstairs, David.
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
I was upstairs, David. I was locked
in that little room in the attic.
Hey, wait, wait.
You got in?
Yeah, I found the key
and I went inside and then...
Dana.
...somebody...
Somebody closed the door.
Somebody locked me in.
Nobody would do that.
Who was it, David?
I don't know!
There's no one else here.
(GASPS SOFTLY)
I was screaming
for help for hours.
Dana, we have been
down here the whole time,
and we did not hear a thing.
Honest to God.
We didn't hear a thing, Mommy.
We didn't.
Hey, you having
trouble sleeping?
No, no. I'm not having
trouble sleeping.
Please don't look
at me like that.
Like what?
Don't get sick again, Mommy.
I'm not getting sick, baby. I
never felt better in my life.
(TIMER RINGS)
(GASPS)
DAVID:
Hey, Dana.
It's okay.
Hey. Where's Daddy?
He had to make
a phone call to Japan.
Well, I was thinking, um,
I could set up your house
for you if you want.
I mean, you could
help if you want.
Okay.
DANA: Okay, you remember
how this goes together?
LUCAS: No.
It's okay, it's complicated.
As were the clients, if your
mom remembers correctly.
Okay, first things first.
We start with the base.
You gonna do it by yourself?
You do it all by yourself.
Very nice.
How about... That one?
That.
Good job. And...
LUCAS: That big boy.
Couple more pieces to go.
What do you think? Yeah?
That one. Yeah.
DANA: You got it? Okay.
LUCAS: Yup.
That one. You got it?
Yes. Very good.
Yes.
Lucas?
Yeah.
I just... I just
wanted to tell you...
I just wanted
to say I'm sorry.
That's okay.
Sometimes bad things happen
and you don't know why.
(SIGHS)
Yeah.
Yeah, that's very true.
I think sometimes
maybe I'd like
a sister again.
(SIGHS)
You would?
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
LUCAS: Tickle the toes.
Tickle the toes.
DAVID: You don't speak baby?
LUCAS: No, not anymore.
DAVID: No?
(DAVID BABBLING)
(BABY COOS)
Baby selfie, baby selfie.
Aww.
(BABY COOING)
(DANA LAUGHS)
(WOMAN WAILING)
(WOMAN CRYING)
(PURRING)
(SOBBING ECHOES)
WOMAN: Don't come back here!
(WOMAN CACKLING)
(DOG SNARLING AND BARKING)
(GASPING)
(WHIMPERING)
You think that child
was begotten
of my loins rotten?
(BABY CRYING)
He won't let us out.
Not a chance in hell.
LUCAS: (WHISPERING)
Mommy. Mommy.
Can I have my
breakfast, Mommy?
Yes, Lucas, you can
have your breakfast.
(BABY CRYING IN DISTANCE)
(PANTING)
(CAT MEOWS)
Oh!
(GASPS)
God.
Sorry. Sorry.
Oh, for God's sake.
I really am sorry, ma'am.
I hope I didn't scare you too bad.
That was not my intention.
I'm sorry, who are you?
And what are you doing sneaking
around on my property?
Answering your prayers.
DANA: See, it's gone
unchecked for a while.
Lucky it didn't cave.
Lucky I stopped by
when I did.
Well, and lucky for you people
around here like to gossip.
(CHUCKLES)
That they do.
Also heard you were an
architect or something.
Yeah, or something.
Well, maybe we should
talk about money.
Well, that's
a little premature.
(CHUCKLES) Come again?
You haven't been hired yet.
No?
No.
There's nothing I can do
to change your mind?
DAVID: Hello.
David...
Uh, this is
my husband, David.
David, this is
Ben Philips, Jr.
Yes, the legend. Hey.
Nice to meet you.
Likewise.
Mr. Philips is here
about the leak.
Right.
Ben works fine.
Great, Ben,
when can you start?
No, that's still
up in the air.
Soon as you pull
the trigger.
We should probably get on
to this right away, babe,
don't you think?
David.
The next couple of weeks are
kind of busy, but I am free now.
DAVID: What is this?
This is water damage, right?
Does this floor
need to go?
Yes. Look, we get
a dehumidifier in here,
we can actually
save most of this wood.
Just say the word.
DAVID: Great.
Well, yes, we want you to
start as soon as possible.
BEN: All right.
No,
what I would like is for Mr.
Philips to come back here
when it hasn't been
raining for a few days,
and the two of us can get up on
that roof and see what's what.
That way, once
the situation's been
thoroughly and
properly assessed,
then we can talk
about hours and materials
and scope of work
in a manner that's
not been pulled
directly out of our asses.
And what I'd also like
is to agree on a deadline,
which if not met, means revisiting
the terms of our contract
with the probability of
penalties paid to us by you
for each day of work exceeding
the original agreement.
Now, if that all
sounds acceptable,
I'll be happy to resume
this conversation
at a later date,
but in the meantime,
it was a pleasure
meeting you, Mr. Philips.
And, um, my husband,
David, will show you out.
David, if you
wouldn't mind.
Ben.
DANA: July 5th.
I'm sorry.
What are you sorry for?
I should've let you
take the lead.
It's not a big deal.
(CHUCKLES)
Yes, it is. I was totally
caveman about the whole thing.
It was a full-on phallus fest.
I mean,
my God, what was I doing?
I don't know anything
about fixing a fucking roof.
I want to leave this house.
Something isn't right here.
Dana...
Whatever you're feeling or
think you're experiencing,
it's just you adjusting.
It's not the house.
The Blackers had a daughter
who died July 5th.
That's the same day, David.
The same day,
that's not a coincidence!
Their daughter's still
in this house.
That's not possible.
You know that.
You're still taking
your medication?
Yes, I'm taking it.
I don't want to stay here.
We agreed to give it a year
of our time in this house.
Dr. Ashby told us
how important it was
for Lucas to have
stability right now.
We bail on this house,
we're not giving him
a fair chance
at a normal life.
We owe him that.
God knows we owe him that.
In a year's time, we're
gonna look back at this
and know that this move
was the right thing to do.
Believe me?
Yeah, I believe you.
I can cancel
this trip in the city.
It's just two days. Finalize
the sale of the company,
help with the transition.
I can reschedule. No. No, I
don't want you to do that.
Lucas and I can
spend the time together.
That'll be good for us.
I want you to keep an eye on your
mother for me while I'm gone.
Look after her.
You want me to pick up some
Juniors for you while I'm gone?
LUCAS: With strawberries!
No raspberries!
DAVID: Yes, sir.
DANA: Be careful.
LUCAS: Oh, wow.
Look at that bear!
Look, there's our house.
Oh, yeah.
Good job. (GASPS)
WOMAN: May I help you?
DANA: Oh, uh...
Yeah, I'm Dana Barrow and I...
Dana the architect!
It's nice to meet you, Dana.
I'm the one who sent you the
photographs and records of your house.
Oh, thank you.
And who might you be?
What's the matter?
Cat got your tongue?
This is Lucas.
They call me Ms. Judith.
Say hi.
I'll just go put these away.
Okay.
You can play over here.
I'll just be few minutes.
I just... I wanted
to ask you about this
little room that I found
in the attic.
It's got a metal floor and
a window that won't open
and, um, a door that just
only locks from the outside.
Um, and it really...
It frightens me and it wasn't
on any of the plans and I...
You know, I don't know
what to make of it.
But it's ridiculous.
Maybe.
Maybe not.
What do you mean?
Dana, it sounds like you
have a disappointments room.
A what?
A disappointments room.
Well, what does that mean?
There was a time,
not so long ago,
when children who were born
with certain difficulties
were considered
embarrassing.
Especially if the family was well-to-do.
Prominent socially.
Sometimes a decision
would be made
to keep that child's
very existence a secret.
Go on.
So, confined to a room much
like the one you described,
tended to only by the parents
or perhaps a trusted servant,
that boy or girl would spend their
lives, however long those might be.
No one to talk to.
No one to play with.
Never feeling the sun or the
rain on their little faces.
These children were...
Disappointments.
Their time on this Earth was
frequently brief, God willing.
Then when it was over, they were buried.
Discreetly.
Some say their spirits
could remain behind.
So, I've been
researching the presence
of disturbed spirits
in these old homes.
And?
And...
I think I've watched
Poltergeist too many times.
(CHUCKLES) People say
I'm full of shit and whiskey.
Hello?
Hello yourself!
What are you doing
up there?
Thought you said to come
back in a few days.
So, what are you thinking? DANA:
I think all this needs to go.
I say we demo the existing and
build a new one with pitch.
Better drainage.
Standard per foot?
Quarter inch.
Fir strips, plywood, new
flashing, new tar paper.
Top of my head, I'd say
it's a four-day job.
I'd say a two-day job max.
Well, I bill 80 bucks
an hour.
Well, you'll get 60.
So, two days,
60, 500 for materials,
that's $1,460 max.
You don't talk
like an architect.
My father worked as a general
contractor for over 40 years.
Is that right?
That's right.
And he didn't like leaving
me with babysitters,
so, I've spent
a lot of time on-site,
and a lot of time
around young men like you.
So then you're used to seeing
people smoke on the job site.
When did you start
working for your daddy?
DANA: When I was old enough.
Doing what?
Whatever he'd let me do.
He must have been proud.
Of?
Of you, getting a degree,
becoming an architect.
Actually, he had
a heart attack on the job
a few months after
I graduated, so...
Sorry to hear
about that.
He died getting
his hands dirty.
Just like he wanted?
I guess so.
So, what about your mom...
LUCAS: Mommy!
Do not come up here, Lucas!
Stay right where you are.
I'm hungry now!
I'll be right down. Just get
off that ladder, please.
LUCAS: Okay.
Where's his father?
He's in the city.
Coming home soon?
Yeah, in a few days.
Yeah, bet it's scary
at night.
Tucked up in bed
all by yourself.
Congratulations.
You just found the line.
Oh, yeah? So, now what?
Now you can
back the fuck up.
You can start in the morning.
I'll expect you around 8:00.
♪ This is the garden
of make believe
♪ A magical garden
♪ Where flowers chuckle
and birds play tricks
♪ And a magic tree
grows lollipop sticks
♪ Here in the garden
what we say and do
♪ We'd like you to
join us and do it, too
♪ Can you crow like a rooster?
Cock-a-doodle-doo!
♪ And clap your hands
and stamp your shoe
♪ It's a funny place
but it's surely true
♪ That we'd like to
share it all with you
♪ If you sing for me
La-la-la-la-la-la
♪ I'll sing for you
Lu-Lu-Lu-Lu-Lu-Lu
♪ If you cry for me
Ooo-hoo-hoo-hoo
♪ And clap your hands
and stamp your shoe
♪ It's a funny place
but it's surely true
♪ That we'd like to
share it all with you
(SIGHS)
♪ If you sing for me
La-la-la-la-la-la
♪ I'll sing for you
Lu-Lu-Lu-Lu-Lu-Lu
♪ If you cry for me
Ooo-hoo-hoo-hoo
♪ I'll cry for you
Boo-hoo-hoo-hoo
♪ If you scream for me
(WOMAN IN TV SCREAMS)
♪ I'll scream for you... ♪
(DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
(GASPS)
Lucas!
Rascal! Rascal! Rascal!
Where are you, Rascal?
(PURRS)
Lucas! Are you up there?
(DOOR CLOSES)
Lucas!
Lucas, we're not playing
games right now, honey.
(CREAKING)
Lucas?
(DOOR CREAKING)
(GASPS)
(NAILS SCRATCHING)
Oh, my God.
(SHUDDERING)
What's your name?
Can you tell me your name?
Laura.
He doesn't want you here.
Who?
LUCAS: Oh, there you are!
I've been looking all over for you.
(SIGHS)
(LUCAS SHOUTING AND LAUGHING)
(PANTING)
LUCAS: Oh, there it is.
My book, I was looking
all over for it.
(GROWLING)
There, I can read.
(SNARLS)
(PANTING)
(LUCAS SCREAMS)
Lucas!
(BARKING)
Lucas! Lucas!
(LUCAS SCREAMING)
Lucas!
(GRUNTING)
(LUCAS WHIMPERING)
Lucas!
Oh, Lucas...
(PANTING)
Did you see that?
Never mind. Come on.
Let's go inside for lunch.
Mommy, wait! I need Rascal.
He came out with me.
Wait, wait, wait.
We'll go together.
Rascal! Rascal!
Rascal!
Hey, baby, why don't you
go look in those trees?
He's a really good climber.
Okay.
Rascal! Rascal!
Where are you? Rascal!
Rascal!
Come down wherever you are.
Come down, kitty, kitty.
Where are you?
Mommy, I can't see him.
Why don't you look over there?
I think I heard him.
He's not out here, baby.
He's probably back in the
house skitching about.
We'll find him?
Yeah, we'll find him.
Oh, shit.
(GRUNTS)
(POUNDING ON DOOR)
DAVID: Dana!
Dana! Dana!
Shit! Stop! Hey.
Hey. I got you. Hey, Dana.
DAVID: I feel like
she's slipping.
She had a few episodes
where she completely
lost track of time.
I mean, she thinks that odd
things are going on in the house.
PSYCHIATRIST:
Odd in what way?
She started to imagine things that
aren't really happening again.
Catherine's birthday would
have been Sunday, right?
Yeah.
We both know that
you tend to bury
your feelings for
the greater good,
and that is not
good for you, either.
Being out in that big house way outside
of the city is very isolating.
Why don't you have
people over on Sunday?
She doesn't need advice.
She needs friends.
Okay.
Um...
There's a gravestone
out back.
It's probably an old dog's,
but it scares Lucas.
Would you dig it up
and make sure it's nothing?
I don't want David to know.
Yeah. Then I'll do that.
Sure hope he
appreciates all this.
I said I sure hope
he appreciates all this.
I hope he appreciates all
that you're doing for him.
What am I doing?
Leaving the city, buying the
old house in the country,
fixing it up so you can
throw some big dinners.
Everyone gathered around your
beautiful Stickley table.
Eating vegetables
you grew out back
or bought at the corner
at the farmer stand.
Wasn't that the plan?
Yeah, or something.
How would your girlfriend feel
about us sharing a smoke?
I don't have one.
If I did, I probably wouldn't
care what she thought.
Why not?
I don't live my life worrying
about things I can't control.
And how is that
working out for you?
(CHUCKLES)
It works out just fine.
Keep me working around here long
enough, you might get to see or
feel how it works out,
for yourself.
Well, it's a shame
we're almost finished.
We don't have to be.
(GASPS)
David! I thought you weren't
home till tomorrow.
I was.
Then I thought I should be home
with my wife and my son. Hmm?
How did you get home
from the station?
Oh, I got a cab.
You know, I think the driver doubles up
as the town's dentist in his spare time.
Was it a productive trip?
Yeah. Yeah, I guess it was.
Was it productive?
Yes. It was productive.
Those paintings are incredible,
huh, don't you think?
I mean, I can't imagine.
I can't fathom why would someone
would want to cover them up.
I can.
Are we taking our...
No. No, I'm not.
That's probably
not the best idea.
No, it's probably not.
But they make me feel...
Fuzzy.
I should get back to work. Lucas
will be happy you're home.
(GRUNTS)
MAN: (ON PHONE)
Chill that wine, buddy.
We just crossed
into North Carolina.
We should be there
around 5:00.
DAVID: Yeah, great.
(SIGHS)
(PHONE RINGING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(CONTINUES RINGING)
Oh!
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Ah!
So, where exactly is Dana?
(PANTING)
(SOBS) Oh, you poor thing,
out here all by yourself.
Oh!
Dana!
Lucas?
(WIND WHOOSHING)
(BALL BOUNCING)
Lucas?
(SNARLS)
Oh!
(BARKING)
(GASPS)
DAVID: Shit.
Dana!
I will put her
out of her misery.
We have allowed this curse
to linger too long.
Don't. Don't! I beg you!
(BARKING)
(SCREAMING)
Ah!
(WOMAN SCREAMS AND SOBS)
(SHUDDERING)
She will embarrass me
no more.
You are
a miserable mother.
And you will fail again.
A daughter,
and now a dead son.
No!
Amos!
(SNARLS)
(PANTING)
(GROANING IN PAIN)
(GRUNTS)
(SNARLING)
(DOOR CREAKING)
(MUFFLED SHOUTING)
(NECK SNAPS)
(LUCAS GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
Dana! Dana! Dana!
(GRUNTING)
Dana! Dana!
LUCAS: Mommy!
DAVID: Dana!
Dana! Dana!
Put it down!
(MUFFLED GRUNTING)
Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop.
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
I got you. It's okay.
It's Daddy, it's Daddy.
I got you.
I got you. I got you.
LUCAS: (CRYING) Mommy.
It's a bad dream. It's a bad dream.
It's okay, it's a bad dream.
It's a bad dream.
(WIND WHOOSHING)
(GRUNTS, GASPS)
(LUCAS SCREAMING)
Are you out of your fucking mind?
What the fuck?
Are you trying to destroy
everything we ever had, Dana?
Everything? Are you?
Is he okay?
Yeah, he's fine, Dana. He's fine.
He's asleep in our bed.
He thinks it was
a bad dream.
David, I think
I can't tell anymore
what's real
and what's not real.
There was no one there.
Nobody was trying to hurt Lucas.
Dana, it was just...
It was just you.
I almost killed him.
I killed Catherine.
(WAILING)
(GASPING AND SCREAMING)
Oh, God!
No.
No, that was an accident.
That was a horrible accident.
That's all it was.
And you know that.
Baby, come here.
We need to get back home.
No more running.
You will get better.
There's nothing
we can't overcome.
(INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE)
(DOOR LOCKS)