The girl is born.
This joy shall fill the world.
SADAKO 2 -3D-
Five Years Later
Kagome, Kagome, the bird in the cage,
when, when will you come out?
In the evening of the dawn,
the crane and turtle slipped.
Who stands right behind you now?
Look, Nagi's all alone.
Hello? How is it?
Oh, I see...
I get it. Okay, I'll be waiting.
What? A girl's voice?
Huh?
There's no child here.
Okay, bye.
No!
Yuki Kindergarten
My mommy's coming for me soon.
Your mommy, Nagi?
Why's she never here?
Is she dead?
Say something!
Nagi, for you.
Fuko's here.
What did you do today? Draw pictures?
Is she your friend?
What's her name?
What do you want to eat?
Hello? Where you at? Movie theater?
Why YOU picking up then?
Anyway, about that. You see...
What?
- What?
- Sorry.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong, Nagi?
A weird kid grabbed me.
Let's go.
You sure?
Asakawa General Hospital
Hey!
Ando, there you are.
A power problem at the nurses' station.
Go check it out.
Okay.
Hey-
By the way, your sister called just now.
Get a mobile already.
Sorry.
Aren't you hungry?
I know, how about some rice balls?
I want Mom to cook for me.
Nagi, your mother isn't here anymore.
Hello? Takanori?
You called?
Yeah. Nothing urgent, but...
- Today...
- How's Nagi?
Uh, well...
- She enjoyed her dinner I...
- I see.
The psych test result:
instability and introversion.
Well done.
Now on the three steps of
psychotherapy used in Counseling:
psychoanalysis, Rogerian approach and
cognitive-behavioral therapy.
In psychoanalysis, you dig deep
into the patient's mind.
To look for traumatic experiences
they may be suppressing.
Nagi...doesn't know Akane. Her long
lost mother. She died after giving birth.
But of course, I can't be Nagi's mother.
Nagi has this emptiness in her heart.
Hence, the drawings.
Just relax.
Children her age have a wild imagination
we adults can't imagine.
Still...
Here.
Ando,
aren't you just
projecting yourself onto Nagi?
You lost your mother to suicide.
Children like to blame
themselves to ease their pain.
You're still blaming yourself
for your mother.
Stopped dreaming about her?
Yes.
I see.
Then don't worry.
You can bring her anytime. Nagi, I mean.
I've had enough.
Sure, they pay me but still!
Right?
So creepy.
Let's see...
Seiji Kashiwada arrested
for multiple murder five years ago.
The verdict was announced today
without his testimony.
Kashiwada kidnapped and murdered
a number of women around Tokyo,
disposing their bodies in a well.
So, why isn't your mommy here, Nagi?
Tell me, why?
Let's go.
Kagome, Kagome, the bird in the cage...
Who stands right behind you now?
Yuna!
Yuna! Yuna!
Nagi?
Cut it out. Don't point the flash at me!
Sorry, sir.
Hey. You okay, Kakiuchi? Are you ready?
I'm fine, sir.
May I?
Sure. She cut
her own tongue off.
Smashed that
and committed suicide.
So many messed up
suicides lately.
I mean...
Huh?
This here...
She had a kid over?
Maybe...
The cursed video clip?
What?
Huh? No, never mind. Excuse me, sir.
Fuko, I've had enough!
I do have a life, too, you know?
Sorry,
Ms. Igarashi. I'm close.
I'm leaving!
Hey you!
Hands off that. It's not for kids.
What?
I'm leaving now.
What's with her?
Nagi!
Nagi! Nagi! Nagi!
Thank you for coming.
Kakiuchi of the Metropolitan Police.
We finally meet, Mr. Koiso.
Those who see something on
an electronic device commit suicide.
Just like your case.
It's happening all over again.
What's the "cursed video clip"?
Why do those who watch die?
People with absolutely
no reason to die have died.
Who made it?
Why is it killing people again?
Sadako.
Sadako...?
A girl who died decades ago.
She was different, had special powers.
But she was feared by others for that.
She was thrown into a well alive.
What's a girl who died decades ago
have to do with a deadly video clip?
A deep grudge-
Is there anyone else
who was involved in the case?
Akane Ayukawa.
Akane Ayukawa? Who's that?
A woman whose body Sadako desired.
Mr. Koiso,
I don't get a thing you're saying!
Thank you, sir.
Sadako...
Laboratory No. 11
Fumika Kamimura
Who's that?
Why are you drawing it?
Cos you'll die.
What?
You're lonely.
You draw to forget your loneliness
about your mother.
I can understand your loneliness.
No, you're lonely.
No one's there. You're always alone.
You're devoting yourself
to work to forget that.
You scared?
Scared of me?
No, I'm...
Everyone will die.
Professor?
Here.
She's a great girl.
She has the signs of a parentless child.
Blaming herself a bit.
But she'll get over it.
Yes...
She's such a sweet girl.
A nice girl.
Nagi?
Nagi!
A train is arriving.
Please stay behind the yellow line.
Doors are closing.
Please stand clear and
wait for the next train.
Nagi!
This way.
Stand back! Let us through!
You know it.
You know, right?
Know what?
Too many disasters around her.
The kindergarten girl,
Ms. Igarashi... The train, too.
Nagi's always there.
Why?
I'm scared of Nagi.
I'm more scared of you for saying that.
She's causing them, isn't she?
Who is she, really?
Is she really yours and Akane's child?
Mr. Ando? Takanori Ando?
Who's asking?
Kakiuchi of the Metropolitan Police.
Mr. Koiso told me.
Where is Akane Ayukawa?
Akane died...
Sorry to hear that.
Is that it?
Akane Ayukawa had a daughter?
She's such a cute girl.
How old is she?
Around four?
I'm in a hurry.
To Takanori Ando
How is Nagi?
How is Nagi? How is Nagi?
Seiji Kashiwada
Kashiwada... Seiji...?
Fuko Ando.
How do you know who I am?
How is Nagi?
How do you know Nagi?
And your letters?
I am Nagi's fan.
What?
You're scared.
Scared?
Of what?
Nagi.
Saw the cursed video clip?
What clip?
Not yet, it seems.
Nagi likes you, perhaps.
What do you mean?
You watch, you die.
You came to me for help, right?
What?
You've always sought Salvation.
No, I...
That's why you came.
Your mother's suicide in the tub.
How...?
You forced her into suicide.
When she needed help.
Stop...
You couldn't help your mother.
Stop ¡t!
I got off track.
Nagi...
Who is she?
You think she's really Akane's?
What do you mean?
If Nagi's not Akane's,
whose child is she?
Sadako.
Sadako?
Who is she?
Despair.
Five years ago,
she sowed the seed of despair.
With the cursed video clip.
And the seed of despair kept growing,
now budding, ready to bloom.
That's...
Sadako's child.
Sadako's child?
You'll live that terror.
No...
You already have.
I know two ways to end that terror.
Want to hear?
One is...
Fuko, you die.
The other...
Pick the bud, soon to bloom.
You...
...kill Sadako's child.
The terror will keep growing.
Fumika Kamimura
Professor?
No!
Why won't you help me?
Mom!
Mom!Mom!
Don't go, Mom!
Mom!
Why won't you help me?
Nagi...
Sadako...
Auntie.
I'm hungry-
Why won't you help me?
I'm sorry... So sorry...
Hey, Fuko!
Fuko, what's wrong? Tell me.
- I killed her! I killed Mom!
- Fuko!
Fuko, get a grip!
Mom killed herself! It wasn't your fault!
You were small,
but tried to help her.
It's okay, Fuko.
Mom's suicide wasn't your fault.
I know that for sure.
Takanori...
Sorry I left you alone.
Listen, I quit my job.
I'll be with you from now.
So you won't be alone.
Really?
Yeah. Everything will be alright now.
With Mom...
And Nagi, too.
Let's have dinner. Nagi's waiting, too.
Yeah? What is it?
No!
You kill Sadako's child.
Let's go home.
Where are we going?
Auntie?
You'll kill me?
You don't like me?
Why's everyone scared of me?
I want to see Mom.
I'm so sorry...
So sorry...
- Sorry...
- I'm scared.
I can see people's deaths.
Help me, Auntie, help me...
You know, we haven't spoken
like this in ages.
When you're home, you avoid me.
I'm busy.
I need to go.
Nagi needs your help.
Nagi...
She said so.
She may not be ordinary.
But that's not what she wants.
I... I want to help her.
Tell me the truth.
Is Nagi...
...Sadako's child?
Akane...
She's alive.
Five years ago,
Sadako appeared before Akane and I.
Akane has special powers.
Sadako tried to use Akane's body
to be born into this world.
But Akane...
She trapped Sadako in her body.
Soon after,
Akane got pregnant.
That's Nagi?
Akane is still fighting all alone.
Nagi has been drawing Akane's picture.
Nagi has...
...always wanted to see her.
Can't they meet?
No, if Nagi sees Akane,
Sadako will be resurrected.
But that's...
They had to be separated.
That's why Akane...
She has taken on everything
and stayed here.
Akane has been...
...preventing Sadako's power
from reaching Nagi?
Yeah.
Then the recent cases
weren't Nagi's fault?
It's not Nagi.
Then who?
Nagi! Nagi's missing!
Nagi's missing?
Nagi...
Takanori!
So... she is alive?
Akane Ayukawa.
Don't move!
Nagi...
I'll kill them both.
Somebody must end this!
Nagi, run!
Nagi... Nagi! Nagi... Run...
I said, don't move!
Yeah... me, too...
I finally saw it.
The cursed video clip.
It was her.
My wife was...
Killed by her!
The cursed video clip... it's her doing!
No, it's not Nagi!
Both she and her mother have evil blood!
No, they don't!
Before I die,
I'll end her.
Nagi?
Is Mom here?
Why?
Why can't I see Mom?
Nagi.
Let's go see her.
Mom...?
Nagi...
I'm glad you came.
No...
Mom...
Now, it's over.
Nagi!
Nagi...
Auntie...
Nagi.
Do it again.
Ready?
I want you to witness my death.
It's not really death
unless witnessed by others.
And what you've told me,
I finally understand.
Death is merely a passing point.
That's right,
death is merely a passing point.
You can control the world
more after death than when alive.
The seed of despair is growing,
budding now, ready to bloom.
And that's...
Sadako's child.
Miori Takimoto
Koji Seto
Itsumi Osawa
Kokoro Hirasawa
Takeshi Onishi
Satomi Ishihara
Yusuke Yamamoto
Ryosei Tayama
Executive Producer
Shinichiro Inoue
Executives in Charge of Production
Takeshi Yasuda
Yasushi Nagai
Toshio Ota
Satoru Iwazaki, Tsuneyoshi Harada
Akira Nakao
Based on the Novel "S" by
Koji Suzuki
Music by
Kenji Kawai
Screenplay by
Daisuke Hosaka, Noriaki Sugihara
Director of Photography
Nobushige Fujimoto
Lighting Director
Yuji Wada
Sound Recording by
Akihiko Kaku
Production Designer
Shin Nakayama
Edited by
Tsutomu Miyazaki
Theme Song "SCREAM" by
TVXQ! (avextrax)
Presented by
KADOKAWA, Kansai Telecasting
Tokai Television Broadcasting
Shizuoka Telecasting
Television Shin Hiroshima System
Okayama Broadcasting
A Tohokushinsha
and KADOKAWA Production
Directed by
Tsutomu Hanabusa
English Subtitles by Chieko Nakai
(c)2013 "SADAKO 3D 2" Film Partners