A lot of the better
bowlers really--
Got another one, Dad.
Leave it outside.
Can I get paid?
You know
where the register is.
Mountain Vista Motel.
Why are you calling?
One room will cost you $22.
Yes, that does
include towels.
And, um, yeah.
Towels and free heat.
Mr. Parker, we had
a lean couple of months.
Well, summer's here.
High season.
Um, you know,
a few good months and, um,
and we'll be back on our feet
by September, I promise.
And I'll have a payment
to you by October
at the very latest.
Mr. Parker, please.
If you could ju--
Nice of you to call.
Thank you
for your understanding.
Mm? Yeah.
Good boy.
I got another one!
You--
You gonna have to
take an IOU, Ted.
You're the only one
makin' any money here.
Why don't you, um--
Why don't you clean up
Rooms 1 through 5 today?
There's nobody in there!
Don't forget
to feed the chickens.
And don't leave
the feed bag out
this time.
Deer keep getting in.
This is our honeymoon suite.
Perfect for a lovely couple
like yourselves.
This is our honeymoon suite.
Perfect for a lovely couple
like yourselves.
Hey, Ted!
Dinner.
Hey, Ted?
Oh, there you are.
Grab a seat.
Noodles and hot dogs.
Your favorite.
You know what today is?
- My birthday.
- Yeah. Yeah.
You know how old you are?
I'm nine.
Yeah. Hard to believe,
isn't it?
Okay. Hold on.
Just stay right there.
I was hopin'
to surprise you.
Here we go.
There.
There you are.
Turn it off!
Oh, you loved this song.
We used to sing it to you
every night before you--
Ted.
Oh, come on.
Te--
Shut up!
Come on. Come on.
Ted! Ted!
Get those lights.
Okay. Here you go.
This is our honeymoon suite.
Listen. We got a--
We got a hospital
just 20 minutes from here.
It'd be wise
if I tried to get you there.
No. I'm okay.
I just--
I need to lie down.
Well, look, um--
I'll get you
some more towels.
You're gonna need those.
Come on, Ted. Now.
Checkout's at 11:00
tomorrow.
Did you see what happened?
No.
All right.
Oh, that poor thing.
Why don't you stand back?
Do you see
what I'm about to do?
Do you understand why?
All right?
Um--
Kind of a shame
to waste all this meat.
What do you think?
I'm a little rusty
at this.
Ted, why don't you
drag that over here?
Okay.
Why don't you just put it
right under here?
Would you hold
your light up?
Okay. Now look.
Here's what you do.
You just...
just slide it in.
And then you cut down.
You don't want to...
rupture the stomach.
Then I gotta take
all the organs out.
Get into that stomach.
Oh, you see that?
You gotta get
all of that out.
Will you
hand me that saw?
Here.
A souvenir.
Leave the man alone, Ted!
I see you.
Haven't seen him this morning.
Should still be in there.
- Should still be?
- He should.
Mr. Colby.
Mr. Colby, this is, uh--
This is Deacon Whit.
Oh, sorry to bother you.
But, uh,
I'd like to ask you
a few questions, if I might.
A little out of it.
I can understand that.
Um,
so what brings you to town?
Just passing through.
You traveling alone?
Mm, yeah.
I'm gonna need to see
your license and registration,
if you don't mind.
It's in the car,
wherever you guys towed it.
Mind if I have a look
in the car?
I'd prefer you didn't.
Hmm.
Anything else?
Looks like you got
banged up pretty bad.
You might want to have
someone take a look at it.
It's been nice
chatting with you.
Yup.
Thank you for comin' by.
You got it.
Room service!
Close the door.
Need any
fresh towels?
No, thanks.
Want those clothes
cleaned?
I can try
and get the stains out.
You want it, kid?
You want it?
How did you do that?
That's a secret,
little man.
You have any secrets?
Maybe.
Probably not.
You wouldn't happen to know
where they towed my car,
would you?
There's a junkyard
down the road.
What ya doing, Whit?
Oh, just poking around.
Looking for anything
in particular?
I don't know really.
I could look the other way,
if it'd make you feel better.
No. Don't bother.
Perfect.
We've been driving forever.
All right.
I could use somethin' to eat myself.
Okay. Why don't
you guys hang here,
and I'll go check us in?
Okay, hon.
We got you--
We got you in Room 5.
Right down here.
We'll have a fresh pot of coffee
brewing for you in the lobby,
first thing in the morning.
Okay.
So if you need anything else,
don't hesitate to call on us.
All right. Uh, a place to eat?
Do you know if
there's anywhere nearby?
It's a bit of a drive
to the closest diner.
I'll tell you what.
My son and I were just about
to have ourselves some dinner.
- Why don't you join us?
- I don't know.
And-And tomorrow morning,
you're not gonna believe
this view.
And over there,
we've got ourselves a pool.
Your son's
gonna love that.
How y'all
like it cooked?
Medium would be great.
Thank you.
How long you guys
owned this place?
Well, Ted's granddad,
he built this
with his own hands.
Back when this was
a destination spot.
People used to
drive here from all over,
just to--
Just to see the view.
This-- This is
all gonna be Ted's
one of these days.
Isn't that right, Son?
Mornin'.
Honey, not too close
to the highway.
Honey!
Oh!
Oh, Jesus.
Hey, you comin' in
or what?
I don't have
a bathing suit.
Go in in your shorts.
Okay.
Ready.
And away we go.
Fuck.
Come on.
I'll be right back.
Well, best I can do
is call a mechanic.
How long you think
that will take?
Mmm.
Long as it takes,
I guess.
- Yeah.
-             Are you kidding me?
Appreciate it.
Sure.
Okay, you can come out now.
Shit. Get in.
Okay.
Got it.
You want it?
Guests always
leave their junk behind.
- Yeah, like what?
- Old magazines and things.
Weird adult stuff.
Occupational hazard,
I suppose.
Where do you live?
Nowhere now.
I guess you're staying
with us for a while.
If I didn't know better,
I'd say you stranded me here
on purpose.
What's in the box?
When people die,
they either bury 'em
in the ground...
or they're burned down
into a box like this.
There's a person in there?
How do they do it?
In an oven?
Yeah.
Do you watch them?
Can I see?
No.
- Why not?
- You know what?
We better get goin'.
Come on.
It's just
you and your dad here, huh?
Yeah.
Mom's in Florida.
Oranges grow there
all year, and there
are 27 types of palm tress.
Hmm. Sounds nice.
I don't really
remember her much.
Left with a trucker
that was staying
in Room 5.
Florida, huh?
Never been.
Wanna go?
Can't say I know
where I'm going exactly,
but... you never know.
If we drive straight through,
we can make it in two days.
Or we can stop at a motel
for a night.
What kind of car
do you have?
What kind of car do I have?
Yeah.
I have a totaled car.
That's what kind of car I have.
Smashed to bits.
Thanks again.
Drive safe now.
We got a customer?
Inside, Ted.
We need to talk.
How's it goin'?
Get your hands
out of that drawer.
Listen. We got ourselves
a little business
coming our way this weekend.
What kind of business?
It's called a prom.
You remember that
from a couple years ago?
Isn't that the dance?
That's right.
We're gonna
have a dance here?
We're gonna have
the after-party at least.
An after-party?
Just a little harmless fun.
Let boys be boys.
Let girls be girls.
You understand
what I'm saying, Ted?
Just for one night.
All right?
Keep your hands
out of there.
Sorry about earlier.
I didn't mean
to scare you.
It's okay.
Wanna see somethin'?
I promised my mom
I'd stay close to the hotel.
It's a motel not a hotel.
All righty.
Well,
it's an electrical issue
is all.
Wire'd come loose
and your fuse box
shorted out.
So, replaced the fasteners
for good measure.
Oh, thank you.
Don't mention it.
Good thing y'all were here,
'cause, car conkin' out on you
on the highway,
you could be in trouble.
Yeah.
Is it fixed?
All fixed, ma'am.
Whoo-hoo.
All right. Yeah.
Benny--
Let's get goin', baby.
Grab that stuff.
Yeah.
In you go.
Thanks again.
No problem.
Come visit us again!
Room 5 just checked out.
And look what they
left behind.
Oh.
Can I keep it?
They might come back for it.
Nobody ever comes back.
Ted, the only one who's lived
here longer than you is me.
I know how lonely it gets.
And I know you wish
you had friends
your own age.
Right?
I have friends.
No, customers
don't count.
Look, when I was, um--
When I was your age,
the only memories I have
are of my dad... workin' here.
I would follow him around,
eyes and ears wide open,
lookin' up at him.
It just seemed like he was
carryin' this whole place
on his shoulders.
You know, your eyes,
they're gonna see more than
I've seen in my entire life.
I know we talked about you
runnin' this place some day.
But--
Some things--
You know--
Some things just don't--
Oh, hell. You can keep it.
'Course you can.
Why don't you, uh,
go ahead and break down
the bedding in Room 5?
Do I have to?
Those linens aren't gonna
change themselves.
Here, boy.
- Here, boy.
-         Here, boy.
Hey!
Shut the fuck up, Sid!
Can I have one?
You guys got bats.
Yeah. I know
where they live.
Wanna see?
Oh, hey.
I wanted to pay for tonight.
Cash?
Yeah.
Any word on my car?
Not yet.
I'll, um--
I'll give 'em a call.
'Preciate it.
Yeah.
Hey. Look at that.
If this damn screen
lets in one more mosquito--
You wouldn't happen to
have an extra, would you?
I, uh,
try not to smoke
in front of Ted.
Don't want him
picking up any bad habits.
I swear,
the kid's got eyes growing
out the back of his head.
Yeah.
Can't do
anything around here
without him watching.
Must be hard
growing up out here.
Uh-huh.
People here,
they come and go.
Hard not to get attached
to the guests.
That so?
Yeah. We had this one time
a while back.
We had a family
stayin' here,
and Ted, he got
a puppy-dog crush
on one of their girls.
He was following her
around everywhere.
Yeah, that poor kid,
he had his heart broken
when they finally checked out.
He climbed in the back
of their station wagon
when no one was looking.
And that family,
they drove for about
an hour before, uh--
before they realized
they had themselves
a little stowaway.
Dad turned his car around.
Had to drive all the way back,
drop Ted off.
Sobbed
the whole way home.
I'll make sure to double-check
my trunk before I leave.
Boy can't help it.
What would make my life
a lot easier...
is if you
kept some distance.
Lot of responsibility
running a motel.
Must be hard to find the time
to be a dad.
Boy's growing
like a weed.
Won't be long before
he's bigger than me.
I'll call the garage
for you.
Won't be much longer I bet,
and then I, uh--
I guess
you'll be on your way.
You stole my money!
It's called
freezing your assets.
- You stole it!
- Tough titty.
I'm keeping it for you.
You're a flight risk.
Hey!
Go put fresh towels
in Room 2.
No!
You go clean up Room 2
right now.
What did you just--
Say it again, Ted.
Say it again.
No!
You--
Whit, you there?
Yeah.
Did some more digging
into those plates you ran.
The owner's wife
has been deceased
as of two weeks now.
Circumstances of her death
are pretty suspicious.
Go on.
Firefighters picked up a 10-80.
Figured it was
an electrical fire.
Nobody home.
They found a body
in the kitchen.
Now they're suspecting arson.
Still there,
Whit?
'Preciate that there, Jim.
There's an open investigation.
William Colby
is a person of interest,
but there's
no solid evidence yet.
Seems like this couple
has a history
of insurance claims.
They've been on a watch list
for the past--
Mind if I join you?
Everything
all right?
Can't wait to get
outta this place.
I don't know.
You got everything
a kid could ever want
right here.
My wife grew up
in a place like this.
You have a wife?
Had.
Where is she now?
She's the one in the box.
How'd she die?
There was...
a fire in our house.
I couldn't get to her in time.
When you leave,
can you
take me with you?
Maybe next time.
You said you'd take me
to Florida.
My wife and I wanted
a son like you.
Your wife is nothing
but a pile of dirt now.
What did you do with her?
Huh?
Dad!
What did you do
with her?
Dad!
Where is the bag?
Where's the bag?
Ow! I don't have it!
Ow!
Listen up.
I am not fucking around!
Where is she?
In the junkyard!
I hid her in the junkyard.
Show me!
Okay.
Where is she?
It's back there.
Where in the fucking back?
Give me
the fucking bag.
Ted.
Do you have any fucking idea
what I've been through?
Don't do this, Ted.
Ted.
Where'd you put the bag?
Give me the fucking bag!
to all you couples out there
on the dance floor.
Let's give all you seniors
a night to remember.
But don't forget.
When prom's over, let's all
try to be responsible...
and get home safe and sound.
To the graduating class of 1989,
this one's for you.
Take it away, seniors.
Whoo-hoo!
There you go.
- Enjoy yourselves.
- Thanks.
What about Room 2?
Oh. Occupied.
Thought you said
we'd have the whole place
to ourselves.
No, I said
that we have a customer...
might need to stay
another night or
a little longer, and--
Sorry about that.
The fuck you're sorry.
We had a deal.
Well, you got
the rest of the place
to yourself.
Listen, old man,
I can take my party
elsewhere.
So...
you either cut me a deal,
or I'm gonna get outta here.
I've already
given you a discount.
Okay.
I've given you a discount. Sir--
Okay, listen. Hey.
Come back here.
All right.
I'll knock off 10%.
Ted, show him his rooms.
Pretty sure
I can find it.
Oh, yeah!
We're running a dead motel, Son.
These rooms
just don't know it yet.
What could we do?
You're the one
with the business sense.
Maybe you could figure it out.
We could leave.
You take after your mother.
- Is that a freshman?
- Hey.
Hold up.
You're that kid
who lives here, aren't you?
Do you have any extra soap?
Come on.
Just a little sip.
It'll put hair
on your chest.
Oh.
It burns.
- Holy shit.
- "It burns. It burns."
You put fire
in my throat.
Come on.
We were just playing.
Come back!
Marcus. Shots.
Fuck you doin'?
Let's go.
Forgot my beer.
Fuck.
What the fuck?
Holy shit.
- What the fuck
were you doing?
Let me go! Let me go!
The fuck was that?
Get up!
He was groping Sarah!
Ow! Ow!
What the fuck
were you gonna do?
Let me go!
Hey.
Stop it.
Whoa, man, check it out.
Ow!
What the fuck?
- No! No!
- Stop it!
Stop it.
What the fuck
is your problem, asshole?
Marcus! Marcus, stop!
Please! No!
Marcus! Marcus!
Fuck off!
Get the fuck out!
Are you okay?
Dad!
Dad! Dad!
Dad?
Ted?
What--
What did they do to you?
Dad--
Oh, my God.
What did they do to you?
Ted--
Oh, goddamn it.
Why? Huh?
Why couldn't you
listen to me?
Ted, what did I tell you?
What did I say, huh?
You just leave 'em alone, right?
You leave 'em alone!
Huh? You gotta
do everything your own way!
Right? Oh, Ted--
All right, you--
You wanna do things
your own way?
You wanna run this place?
Is that it?
Huh? All right,
well, here's the first rule.
All right.
Here's the first... rule.
You leave
the customers alone!
Ted?
You leave the goddamn
customers alone!
Goddamn it, Ted.
Ted?
Ted!
A sophomore, right?
A rising sophomore.
Turn that music louder.
Come on.
Fuck, yeah!
Chug, chug, chug, chug!
Chug! Go! Go! Chug!
Come on!
Sarah.
Wake up. Wake up.
Welcome to
the Mountain Vista Motel.
Hope you had
a lovely stay.
This is gonna sting
a little bit, buddy.
All right.
Hold still.
It's okay.
Yeah, that's okay, buddy.
When was the last time
you saw the man in Room 2?
A few hours ago.
He was looking in some windows.
Didn't he say
his wife died
in a fire?
We gonna need to do
a whole sweep of this area.
Put out an APB
on a William Colby.
C-O-L-B-Y.
Sorry to hear
about your dad.
You have
any other family?
I have a mom in Florida.