Shh-shh-shh.
- Hey.
- Peter...
Shh, just a dream.
Shh.
It's just a dream. Hey.
Go on back to sleep.
Back to sleep.
Shh.
And what's your
line of work, Felix?
I'm a musician.
Jazz?
What other kind of
music is there?
You play anywhere?
Place called Ellington's.
Ellington's, on
Brunswick Street?
Uh-huh.
You mean you used
to play there.
No... no... I played
there just last weekend.
Ellington's - the place with
all the statues out the front?
That's the one.
If I'm not mistaken, that
place has been gone for years.
Look, I... I really don't
know what you're getting at.
Can you tell me
who the President
of the United States is, Felix?
What sort of a
question is that?
Just curious.
Ronald Reagan.
And what year are we in?
1987.
Right?
Have we... have we met before?
Yes. Right here, last week.
So how's the new job?
Oh, don't get me
wrong, Duncan,
I appreciate you
passing a few cases,
but assessment work is like...
It reminds me of
being your assistant.
- You miss Sydney?
- No.
I miss analysis.
I miss my patients, even
more than I thought I would.
What do you think? You need
more help than they do now?
It's not easy, facing things.
And how would you face things?
Pete, I'm here to
help you face it.
And I really appreciate it.
I wasn't even sure
you'd be alive.
Well...
You marry the prettiest
girl on campus,
you take off to
Sydney and you...
...you disappear for years.
Oh, you know, life.
Life.
So how's Carol been
through all this?
Devastated.
Are either of you able to...
are you able to say her name?
- Yes.
- Say her name, Pete.
Evie.
Ev... Evie.
Ow!
Oh, baby, cut yourself?
Oh, shh. Hmm. You'll live.
What was it that
caught your attention?
What?
You said you took your
eyes off Evie that day.
What exactly was it that
caught your attention?
Can't... can't remember.
It'll come to you.
I just need to sleep. I want
to close my eyes and...
Just need to sleep.
I'm starting to hate people.
I don't
want to be manic.
And it was so awful...
the black, I mean.
- Am I boring you?
- I'm listening.
People ignore me all
the time, you know.
- Like who?
- Benny.
- Who's that?
- My daughter.
It's not a real name,
it's just what I call her.
Although I don't know
why I call her anything.
Sometimes I think
I'm invisible.
Well, I see you.
I wonder what I'm
doing here sometimes.
- What do you mean by that?
- You know what I mean.
You mean you have thoughts
of killing yourself?
I just can't do it.
Hello.
Who are you here to see?
Oh. Is your mum or your
dad here with you?
Want to come in?
Come in.
I'm Dr Bower.
You can call me Peter.
Have a seat.
Take your pick.
Good
choice. The comfy one.
Have they given you a letter
or something for me to read?
Elizabeth Valentine.
Lovely name.
Hello, Elizabeth.
Can you speak?
Well, I know you can read.
Can you write?
Don't worry. Don't worry.
It's just a train.
Hey, wait.
Wait, wait!
What are you doing?
Nothing. Just... looking
for an old... case file.
In her box of things?
- I'm sorry.
- There's no need to apologise.
- Did I wake you?
- No.
- Been taking your pills?
- I slept all day.
I'm beginning to wonder if I
shouldn't stop taking them.
So we can have a
repeat of last time?
I'm sorry.
Stop apologising.
Please.
It's her
anniversary next week.
Anniversary?
Anniversary is
something you celebrate.
Why did we move here, Peter?
You know why we moved here.
To move on.
Shit!
Elizabeth?
How did you get in here?
What is it?
Elizabeth.
What do you see?
Hold on.
Elizabeth, listen to me.
Just try and speak, OK?
What is it? What is it?
What's over there? Huh?
Hey, no...
Come on.
Hey.
Elizabeth?
I've got to be honest
with you, Pete.
All I hear is a train,
a lot of racket
and you talking to yourself.
If it wasn't for this doll,
you'd have a pretty hard time
convincing me that you didn't
just... imagine all of this.
Why would I... why
would I imagine it?
- How old would Evie be now?
- Come on, Dunc.
Elizabeth Valentine.
That was her name, wasn't it?
Yes. That was on
her train pass.
- Where is her train pass?
- I gave it back to her.
I just want you to
think for a bit.
- Just take her initials.
- Whose?
The girl's, Elizabeth
Valentine's.
- Take her initials.
- E-V.
What about the doll?
Where did that come from?
Anywhere. It could be...
Could be Evie's. Have you been
through her things lately?
You're making it...
You're making it sound
like something it's not.
Sit down.
- It's OK, Pete.
- Doesn't feel OK.
Good.
As Jung would say, 'Now
we're getting somewhere.'
So, just relax, and tell me
exactly what you're feeling.
That's funny. I never
noticed that before.
What?
That painting.
I've been having
dreams about that.
Winter Landscape
With A Bird Trap.
Simple title.
But when you look
closely at a Bruegel,
you usually find
there's something odd,
some devil in the detail.
It's the bird trap.
You can't see the bird
trapper hiding in the window.
That's what disturbs
me in the dream.
The dream is
asking a question.
Who's pulling the string?
Who is it that you don't
want to see, Peter?
What?
Who is it in that window?
We have her.
Who?
Evie.
Missed your stop.
Erica. Your patient.
- Erica...
- You've been sleeping.
What was the last station?
Do you remember
what we talked about
in your room the other day?
I've been thinking about it,
how I can't kill myself.
- Have you?
- I'm sorry. I need to...
I've realised why.
It's simple. I'm already...
Duncan, it's Peter.
Please...
I know it's late.
Please give me a call.
Please.
The really weird thing is
they all seem to have died
within a day of each other.
- July 12th?
- Yes.
Does that date mean
anything to you?
- No.
- You're sure?
Just think.
Look, Dunc, I wouldn't be
bringing this up to you
if I didn't think it was
crazy myself, but...
Look...
These are the patients.
Here's the list.
You're not saying anything.
I know if I...
I think logically...
...I must be hallucinating
the whole thing.
Like there's a
kind of breakdown.
But there are things
that don't add up,
even if that were the case.
Like what?
Like the fact that you
referred me these patients.
Well, if I referred
you your patients...
...what would that make me?
1987.
- Well...
- Hi, Dad.
Come in.
Aren't you supposed
to be busy?
You drive up?
No, took the train.
How's work?
Work's... whatever.
You ever throw anything out?
So what's happened?
- What do you mean?
- What's really going on?
You turn up
unannounced, no car,
an overnight bag,
without Carol.
You two OK?
- I thought I was the shrink.
- Yeah.
I'm the cop.
- Retired, remember?
- Mm.
- I've still got a nose.
- Yeah.
I saw you took down
the photos of Mum.
It's been ten years.
Don't touch that.
What do you do in here anyway?
Man stuff.
Man stuff!
You were always in here when
I was a kid, avoiding us.
Sorry I didn't come
to Evie's funeral.
I was too upset.
Is that what you're
calling drunk these days?
- How long are you staying?
- Couple of days.
Guess you want your room back.
Want something to eat?
Nah.
Don't wait up.
Hi, Baz.
Jesus Christ.
Fuck, mate.
You've had a really
shit couple of years.
It's good to see you, though.
Fuckin' life, ey?
I mean, I... I can't
even imagine...
...what it is you must
be going through.
It's made me think a
lot about my past.
Addressing it, you know...
the things I've done.
I wanted to talk to
you about something.
What?
About what happened.
What are you talking about?
1987.
1987, you know.
You're not talking about...
- Shit. We promised...
- Yeah, we were young.
...we would never
talk about that.
- We were teenagers.
- Exactly. We were just kids.
I... can't help but think...
...Evie's death
had something...
some kind of...
...I don't know...
- What?
Some kind of what?
Look, I don't even really know
what happened that night.
And neither do you.
- People died.
- Can we please just drop this?
- People died!
Right, so, you come
all the way back here
just to dig this shit up.
I don't know... maybe.
Maybe I just had to
clear my conscience.
With who? With who?
With the police?
- I don't know...
- Look.
I'm not you, alright?
I'm not rich.
I can't afford lawyers.
They put people in jail
for this sort of shit
for fucking years.
I got to live in
this bloody town.
Do you believe in ghosts?
You know what?
Fuck you, Peter.
Fuck you!
You stay the fuck
away from me. Got it?
Remind me again.
Why are we doing this?
Because we're
14 and we're virgins.
If this is a make-out place,
don't we need chicks?
As if you'd
know what to do with one.
How do you know
about this place anyway?
- Steve told me.
- Your brother?
- And you believed him?
- Why wouldn't I?
- He hates you.
- What would you know?
Just trust me.
You coming?
Oh! Check that out. Jackpot.
Dinner and a show.
How do you know it's not
two blokes in there?
What's wrong with you?
I don't know. Maybe we
shouldn't be watching this.
OK, Richie
Cunningham. Then go.
I'll let you know
how it ends.
What was that?
Shit.
- Do you think they saw us?
- Shh.
- I think they saw us.
- Did you hear that?
- Hear what?
Listen.
- Train.
- Shit, the bikes!
Barry!
Daddy.
Look.
Evie!
So you were the
only one involved.
That's right.
You're... you're not related
to Bill Bower, by any chance?
I'm his son.
Wasn't your dad
sergeant at the time?
You never mentioned
this to him?
No.
So why bring it up now?
I just want to...
put things to rest.
Properly.
Can you excuse
me for a second?
Sorry about that.
- Is that your mum?
- Yeah.
She died in the accident.
- I'm sorry.
- Well, it's no secret.
It... it must have
been very hard
for you to hear my statement.
Well, it's my job.
- I meant, you know...
- Yeah, I know what you meant.
Not many people could have
faced up to what you did.
I really appreciate
your honesty.
I'll file a report
with the coroner.
I can't imagine
there'll be any charges.
You were just a teenager.
It was an act of
negligence at worst.
Thank you.
I...
I came to your house once.
Your dad invited me over
right after the accident.
Mum was the only local
who died in the accident.
He was very kind
to me, your dad.
I think it was after that
I wanted to be a cop.
Hi, sweetheart.
I'm... I'm at my dad's.
I'm sorry I haven't
called until now.
I had to come back and put
something to rest here,
something that happened
a long time ago.
Things will get better,
Carol. I promise.
I love you.
Thank you for
using this messaging service.
Press star to continue
or just hang up.
Dad?
How's the throat?
Stay away.
That's no way to talk
to an old friend, Peter.
Wha... what do you want?
It's not what I want.
We're your ghosts, Peter.
You're the one that's
holding on to us.
I put it to rest.
I told the truth.
Then why are we still here?
Two bikes
derailing a train engine.
Do you really think
that's possible?
Listen, some memories
are so unacceptable,
we'll do anything we
can to forget them.
And if that doesn't
work, we change them.
Look at you.
You barely remember your
own daughter's death.
What does that have
to do with this?
Well, I don't know, but
you must, somewhere inside.
Peter, what distracted you?
You said you looked
away the day Evie died.
What was it?
What is it you
don't want to remember?
Barry!
Senior Constable Henning.
Don't touch a thing.
I'll be right there.
So here we are again.
What happened?
I just found him
there like that.
No, that's not what I meant.
This isn't a coincidence, is it?
We both left our
bikes on the track.
I told... I told Barry
last night that...
I was going to make a
statement to the police.
He begged
me not to mention him.
So what am I supposed
to believe now? This story?
He begged me.
Or the one you spun
me this morning?
He's a friend. I didn't
want to drag him into this.
I'm sorry.
When you get your head
clear, I expect a call.
Take him home.
Found this at the scene,
some trinket between
the floorboards.
Looks like it's been
there a while. Goodnight.
G'night.
I think she
wasn't on the train.
I think I remember seeing
her running from a car
just before the accident.
You think you
remember seeing her.
How do you know
what she looks like?
You're going
to think I'm crazy.
I...
I lost my daughter
last year.
I think... I think it
opened me up to something.
I... I don't know.
But I see them...
...the people from
the accident.
Look, I'm asking
you to help me.
I don't think I can help you
in the way that you need help.
Your mother, Erica,
has an English accent.
She called you Benny.
She's got quite a temper.
Look, I don't know what
you're playing at, Peter...
How would I know that? How?
Am I right?
You're not helping yourself
or anyone at the moment.
You need to go home.
Just leave here and go home!
Please... show me.
Elizabeth...
Elizabeth Valentine.
Jesus.
Barb. What time is it?
It's late.
If you're looking for
Peter, he's not here.
It's probably a good thing.
Can we talk?
- Thanks.
- What's on your mind?
I pulled out your old
report on the train crash.
Do you remember it at all?
You're talking about something
that happened 20 years ago.
You're right. I just want
to clarify a few things.
Listen, Barb...
I understand you lost
someone in the accident.
It's personal for you. But
whatever was done is done.
And whatever way you cut it,
it was still just an accident.
And I'm still obliged
to investigate
your son's statement.
Especially in light
of Barry's suicide.
Two boys mistakenly leave
their bikes on a train track.
It's, at best, manslaughter.
The State can't
prosecute a manslaughter
four years after the fact.
I'm not sure it happened
exactly like that.
You say here that you received
a call at the police station,
and you proceeded to
drive to the accident.
- Yes.
- What road did you take?
Well, there's only one road.
Oakstone.
- Oakstone?
- Mm-hmm.
The level crossing at Oakstone
Road was completely blocked
by the wreckage.
So... how did you drive
across the tracks?
The only way your
car could have been
on the other side
of the tracks...
...is if it was there
before the accident.
They found this in the
signal box this evening.
And I'm pretty sure it
belongs to... this girl.
Elizabeth Valentine.
Missing schoolgirl.
You remember
the case, don't you?
You were in charge.
After they found her
body in the wreckage,
you closed the investigation.
Out of all the victims
in the coroner's report,
hers was the only
inconclusive cause of death.
Come here.
I think your son saw
something that night.
And I think you
know what he saw.
Well, you'll have to ask
Peter what he thinks he saw.
I stand by my
original statement.
Do you mind if I
wait here for Peter?
Be my guest.
Another cup of tea?
- No, thanks.
Yah!
Please leave
a message after the tone.
What are you doing up?
I was worried.
You took my car.
Where have you been?
What have you been up to?
- Remembering.
- Remembering what?
I remembered everything.
What are you talking about?
Elizabeth Valentine.
I saw you...
rape and kill her
and throw her body
in the wreck.
That's... That's crazy.
You're talking crazily.
You're upset. Come
inside. It's freezing.
I'm giving you a chance, Dad.
I want you to call.
- Call who?
Confess.
You're all mixed up.
Do it or I'll do it for you.
Who are you calling?
Don't do this, son.
I'm warning you.
What have you done?
Get in the garage.
I said get in the garage.
Hold your hands out.
How did it feel
letting me believe
it was my fault
all these years?
Do you think
you're so innocent?
You kept quiet about it too.
Apple doesn't fall
that far from the tree.
I said hold out your hands.
How many other
girls did you kill?
Go ahead, Dad. It's not
going to make it go away.
Help!
Somebody, help!
Yah!
Bill?
Bill, let me out of here!
Bill!
Come on!
Shit!
Ah! Shit!
Bill!
Peter! Help!
Help me!
Bill!
Son!
Get down!
What are you thinking?
About kids.