Woman: THIS IS CODY'S
SPECIAL DAY, NOVEMBER 11TH.
Boy: JUMP.
DAD! DAD!
Father: WELL, THERE HE IS.
WAIT, IS IT
YOUR BIRTHDAY TODAY?
Cody: YOU GOT TO MAKE IT!
YOU GOT TO MAKE IT!
[FATHER CHUCKLES]
Father: I TOLD YOU.
I TOLD YOU I WOULD GET IT.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
[GUN MAKES ELECTRONIC SOUNDS]
NEXT BIRTHDAY WE'LL HAVE
A WHOLE TEAM OF GUYS HERE.
WE'LL ALL BE PLAYING BASEBALL
TOGETHER.
- GET SET.
- [GUS BARKS]
GO!
Father: ARGH!
Father: I PULLED A MUSCLE.
GOT TO DO--
- Mother: WHAT--
- Father: WHAT THE HELL
WAS THAT?
- CODY?
CODY? CODY!
NO!
NAH, I DON'T THINK HOYT
HAD ANYTHING TO DO WITH IT.
UH, SAD BUT TRUE,
KIDS ARE KIDNAPPED.
WELL, RIGHT AFTER IT HAPPENED,
'CAUSE, YOU KNOW,
THEY HAD TO, LIKE, DRAG HIM
INTO COURT AND ALL THAT STUFF--
SO HE'S KIND OF FORCED
TO BE AROUND EVERYBODY
AND ALL THAT STUFF--
THERE WAS A DIFFERENCE.
AND THERE WAS SOME MEAN
IN HIM THEN, YOU KNOW.
I DIDN'T CONSIDER HIM,
UP UNTIL THAT TIME,
A DRUNKARD OR ANYTHING.
I DIDN'T TALK TO HIM AT LENGTH
ABOUT IT, BUT, YOU KNOW,
WE WERE DELIVERING HAY,
AND HE WAS JUST BROKE UP.
YOU KNOW, SHOW IT TO ME
AND THEN I'LL BELIEVE IT.
YOU ASK ME, I THINK HE'S--
HE'S GUILTY.
MAYBE EVERYBODY'S PROJECTING
THEIR FEAR ON HOYT.
MAYBE THAT'S WHAT'S GOING ON.
THAT'S WHY HE'S LEFT ALONE.
BUT HE'S STAYING THERE
UNTIL HE FINDS HIS BOY.
I MEAN, IT'S SAD.
IT'S SAD AS CAN BE.
I'VE GOT KIDS AND GRANDKIDS.
AND IF AN 8-YEAR-OLD GRANDKID
OF MINE DISAPPEARED, I'D BE--
YEAH, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I'D DO.
CODY WAS IN MY
LITTLE GIRL'S CLASS.
I'VE BEEN HAVING TO GO IN
AND SLEEP WITH HER
ALMOST EVERY NIGHT,
YOU KNOW,
'TIL SHE FALLS ASLEEP.
SO, YEAH,
IT'S BEEN HARD.
OF COURSE, I KNOW CODY, MAN.
HE'S A GOOD KID. FUNNY.
LITTLE WIRY. HE WAS GONNA GROW
INTO THEM FEET ONE DAY.
YEAH, MAN.
YEAH. I KNEW CODY.
I MEAN,
I'VE FOLLOWED IT QUITE A BIT.
I DON'T REALLY BUY EITHER ONE.
I'M NOT INTO
THE PARANORMAL STUFF.
I'VE NEVER SEEN THAT TAPE.
AND I'VE NEVER SEEN
A WOLF LIKE THAT.
UM...
BUT IT COULD HAPPEN.
COULD HAPPEN AROUND HERE IF
IT'S GOING TO HAPPEN SOMEWHERE.
THAT'S--I DON'T BELIEVE
ANY OF IT, YOU KNOW.
I GOT TO SEE SOMETHING
TO BELIEVE IT.
I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYTHING
LIKE THAT.
YOU STICK AROUND, MAN,
YOU'LL SEE SOMETHING.
[CLEARS THROAT]
MY NAME IS SAM GREEN.
I'M A PH.D.
IN SOCIO-CULTURAL ANTHROPOLOGY
FROM THE UNIVERSITY OF CHICAGO.
I'VE BEEN WORKING FOR MDE
FOR ABOUT SIX MONTHS AS
A FIELD SCIENTIST.
- [VEHICLE APPROACHES]
- SORRY.
MY MAN!
HEY, SAM!
HOW ARE YOU, BUDDY?
- GOOD TO SEE YOU, MAN.
- YOU, TOO.
MY NAME'S CAMERON MURPHY. UM...
I'M AN INVESTIGATIVE JOURNALIST
FROM LOS ANGELES.
SAM AND I GREW UP TOGETHER.
HE CALLED ME ABOUT A MONTH AGO.
TOLD ME HE WAS HEADING UP
AN INVESTIGATION
TO SOME STRANGE CATTLE RANCH.
ASKED ME IF I WOULD COME OUT
AND OBSERVE IT
FROM A THIRD PARTY PERSPECTIVE.
HEY, THIS IS OUR VIDEOGRAPHER
BRITAIN.
HEY, MAN. CAMERON.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
MY NAME'S BRITAIN SLOAN.
I'M A FREELANCE CAMERAMAN.
NORMALLY DON'T LIKE TO BE
IN FRONT OF THE CAMERA.
SO I'LL MAKE THIS SHORT.
I'VE DONE THIS KIND OF WORK
BEFORE WITH OTHER GROUPS.
AND WE'VE NEVER COME
ACROSS ANYTHING STRANGE
OR OUT OF THE ORDINARY.
SO I HOPE THIS TRIP
IS A LITTLE DIFFERENT.
HEY, MAN, WOULD YOU GRAB
HIS BAG FOR HIM?
YEAH.
- THANKS, MAN.
- HOW ABOUT A LITTLE TOUR
OF THE GROUNDS?
- YEAH.
- ALL RIGHT.
HOYT!
I WANT YOU TO MEET
MY FRIEND CAMERON MURPHY.
- HEY, CAMERON.
- HOYT, PLEASURE.
HOYT MILLER. THAT'S MY NAME.
HOYT MILLER.
AND, UH, I BOUGHT THIS, UH...
THIS RANCH, OH, FOUR YEARS--
LITTLE OVER FOUR YEARS AGO--
WITH THE IDEA OF TURNING IT
INTO SOMETHING, YOU KNOW,
SPECIAL OR...SAY, UH...
DO I HAVE TO DO THIS?
CAN I--DO I HAVE TO TALK
TO THE CAMERA RIGHT NOW?
I DON'T REALLY FEEL LIKE IT.
- NICE TO MEET YOU.
- ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS BE UP
IN ABOUT 45 MINUTES.
WE'LL HAVE THE ATV READY.
- SOUNDS GOOD.
- COME ON, GIRL.
THIS IS
OUR MAIN VET TECH LISA.
LISA, CAMERON.
OH, CAMERON,
I HEARD A LOT ABOUT YOU.
MY NAME IS LISA MOREAU.
I'M THE FIELD VETERINARY TECH.
I'VE WORKED LOCALLY FOR YEARS.
I JUST STARTED WORKING
WITH MDE A COUPLE MONTHS AGO.
THIS IS MY FIRST BIG CASE
WITH THEM.
THEY BROUGHT ME ON BECAUSE
I'M SO FAMILIAR WITH THE CATTLE
MUTILATIONS IN THE AREA.
IT'S DISTURBING.
I'VE SEEN A LOT OF SICK AND DEAD
ANIMALS IN MY LINE OF WORK.
BUT...THE CATTLE MUTILATION
PHENOMENON IS...
I DON'T HAVE
AN EXPLANATION FOR IT.
IS THE HORSE STILL ACTING
UNUSUAL?
UH, NO. THE HORSE'S MOODS
HAVE STABILIZED.
THEIR BEHAVIOR'S
BEEN COMPLETELY ERRATIC.
SO, IT'S FINE NOW.
BUT TALK TO ME IN 10 MINUTES.
- ALL RIGHT, I WILL.
- OK.
UH, YOU SEEN MATT?
YEAH, I THINK RAY HAS HIM
SETTING UP SOMETHING
BEHIND THE HOUSE.
- LISA, PLEASURE.
- NICE TO MEET YOU.
THAT'S A LONG TIME
TO BE IN AFGHANISTAN, MAN.
ACTUALLY, I WAS EMBEDDED WITH
A GROUP OF ABOUT 10 SOLDIERS
FOR A PERIOD OF NEARLY
THREE MONTHS.
- HOW'S IT GOING?
- YOU MEAN, MOTION SENSOR HELL?
HI, I'M MATT JOHNSON.
AND I WORK IN THE MEDIA LAB
AT MDE,
WHICH IS HOW I MET SAM,
WHO BROUGHT ME ONBOARD
THE PROJECT.
WE BOTH SHARE A PASSION
FOR THE PARANORMAL.
AND, UH, WELL,
I REALLY HOPE THAT THIS PROJECT
HELPS LEGITIMIZE THE FIELD
A LITTLE BIT.
ALSO I'M HERE
AS THE TEAM'S DRIVER, COOK,
AND RESIDENT BITCH.
YOU READY?
[WALKIE-TALKIE BEEPS]
Man: COPY.
Man: WHAT WAS THAT?
MY HAND, OVER.
Man: WALK IN FRONT OF IT,
YOU STUPID ASS.
THAT'S RAY.
LET'S GO MEET HIM.
RAY, I WANT YOU
TO MEET CAMERON MURPHY.
HEY, MAN.
YOU HERE TO HELP
WITH THE SENSORS, MAN?
RAY REED. EX-MILITARY.
HERE FOR THE SECURITY
AND WIRES AND SHIT.
IF LADY LUCK SHINES UPON US,
THIS PLACE IS GONNA BE
A GOD DAMN FORTRESS.
THAT'S ALL I GOT. WE DONE?
HMM.
Sam: HOW ARE THE CAMERAS COMING?
THEY'RE ALMOST SET UP.
WHEN YOU GUYS ARE DONE,
WHY DON'T YOU POP ON BY
AND I'LL SHOW YOU.
Lisa: AFTERNOON, HOYT.
Hoyt: READY TO ROLL?
Man: LET'S GO.
[ENGINE STARTS]
ALL RIGHT. EVERYBODY IN?
Cameron: WHERE WE HEADED?
Lisa: HOYT FOUND A DEAD DEER
ON THE PROPERTY.
SAM WANTS TO CHECK IT OUT.
WHAT'S THE ACREAGE?
ABOUT 1,000 GIVE OR TAKE.
Sam:
WELL, IT'S NOT CLEARLY DEFINED.
BUT PARTS OF SOUTHERN IDAHO,
THE UINTAH BASIN, FOUR CORNERS,
ALL THE WAY TO NEVADA
AND CALIFORNIA IS CONSIDERED
THE PARANORMAL MECCA
OF THE UNITED STATES.
LOCAL TRIBES WON'T EVEN SET FOOT
ON THIS LAND TO THIS DAY.
THERE'S EVIDENCE FOR THIS?
WE GOT, UH, EVIDENCE GOING
BACK TO THE 1800s
WITH THE FIRST DOCUMENTED
UFO SIGHTINGS.
ROSWELL CRASH IN '47.
FIRST REPORTED CATTLE MUTILATION
IN '67.
DUGWAY IS BASICALLY
THE NEW AREA 51.
NEVER HEARD OF IT.
YOU PASSED IT
RIGHT ON THE WAY UP HERE.
GROUND ZERO
FOR U.S. MILITARY RESEARCH.
I MEAN, WE'RE TALKING EVERYTHING
FROM REMOTE VIEWING
TO PSYCHOLOGICAL WARFARE.
Hoyt: JUST OVER
THE RIDGE HERE.
[ENGINE STOPS]
SAM, I'M SORRY
TO BURST YOUR BUBBLE.
BUT SHE DIED OF
NATURAL CAUSES.
DO YOU SEE THE DISCOLORATION
IN THE TONGUE?
IT'S A CLASSIC CASE
OF HEMORRHAGIC DISEASE.
Sam: TAKE A SAMPLE ANYWAY.
SURE, WHATEVER YOU WANT.
HEY, UH...
WE'D BETTER GET BACK.
WE GOT A BIG STORM COMING.
Sam: THANKS, HOYT.
ALL RIGHT.
ALL THE FEEDS RECORD DIRECTLY
INTO THE SERVER HERE.
JUST IN CASE, I GOT IT
ALL BACKED UP ON THE C-70.
IT'S GENERATOR POWERED.
IT'S ALL INDEPENDENTLY WIRED,
AND IT'S SET TO RECORD 24/7.
CAMERA ONE'S A WIDE SHOT
OF THE ROAD
SO WE CAN MONITOR
EVERYONE COMING IN AND OUT
OF THE PROPERTY.
CAMERA TWO
IS WIDE OF THE HOUSE.
CAMERA THREE IS OF
THE WESTERN PASTURE.
CAMERA FOUR
IS OF THE CORRAL.
CAMERA FIVE IS
THE BARN EXTERIOR.
AND CAMERA SIX
IS INSIDE THE BARN.
THAT'S IT FOR
THE EXTERIOR CAMERAS.
Cameron:
WHAT HAPPENS AT NIGHT?
THEY ALL SWITCH
TO INFRARED.
Matt: THIS IS THE X-RAY
I WAS TALKING ABOUT.
Ray: NOT REALLY MY THING.
Lisa: OH, LET ME SEE IT.
Matt: WELL,
JUST PASS IT ALONG.
THANKS.
IF I COULD,
I'D LIKE TO PROPOSE A TOAST.
UH, I JUST WANT TO, UM...
THANK YOU ALL
FOR COMING UP HERE.
UH...
SINCE MY BOY'S BEEN GONE,
THE HELP'S BEEN
FEW AND FAR BETWEEN.
AND I JUST--
I REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
AND I WANT YOU TO KNOW THAT
WHATEVER THIS THING IS,
I BELIEVE IT'S STILL HERE.
AND IT'S REALLY SMART.
AS A MATTER OF FACT,
I WOULD BET MY ARM THAT
IT'S WATCHING US RIGHT NOW.
SO...
OH, NO.
DON'T LEAVE ME UP HERE.
CHEERS.
- Matt: CHEERS.
- Lisa: CHEERS.
Matt [over walkie-talkie]:
WHERE DO YOU WANT ME TO GO?
Ray: JUST WALK
AND I'LL FIND YOU.
Matt: COPY.
Ray: THIS IS
THE LIVING ROOM?
Hoyt: YES.
SAY HI TO BIG BROTHER.
SAY IT.
HI.
Ray: BEDROOM ONE.
BEDROOM TWO.
THE DINING ROOM.
KITCHEN.
HEY, MATT, CAN YOU GO DOWNSTAIRS
FOR ME, PLEASE?
Matt [over walkie-talkie]:
YOU GOT IT.
Ray: HOYT'S ROOM.
CODY'S ROOM.
GOT THE BASEMENT.
AND THIS IS
THE OLD BUTCHER ROOM.
OH, MY GOD!
I'M SORRY. I'M SO SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN--
JUST THE CAMERAS.
AND I THOUGHT YOU KNEW
I WAS HERE.
IT'S ALL RIGHT. JUST DON'T
SNEAK UP ON PEOPLE LIKE THAT.
I KNOW. IT WAS STUPID.
I'M SORRY.
- ALL RIGHT.
- THIS WORKS. GOD DAMN IT, RAY.
THE BLIND SPOT'S GOING
TO BE ON YOU, MAN.
IF YOU GUYS NEED TO REVIEW
ANY FOOTAGE, JUST LET ME KNOW.
AND I'LL SET IT UP
RIGHT HERE.
I GOT MOTION DETECTORS
ACROSS MOST OF THE PROPERTY.
SO IF SOMETHING MOVES,
WE'RE GOING TO KNOW ABOUT IT.
ALSO I PROGRAMMED
MOST OF THE SENSORS TO DETECT
ONLY LARGE OBJECTS.
I DON'T WANT
THE LOCAL WILDLIFE HAVING US
CHASE GHOSTS ALL NIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
[CLEARS THROAT]
AUGUST 2nd.
IT'S MY FIRST OFFICIAL NIGHT
HERE AT THE RANCH.
[KNOCKING AT DOOR]
- Lisa: HEY.
- HI.
ARE YOU IN HERE
TALKING TO YOURSELF?
UM, NO. ACTUALLY
IT'S THE CAMERA.
I USE IT AS
A VIDEO JOURNAL.
OH. WHAT HAPPENED TO THE DAYS
OF THE MIGHTY PEN AND PAPER?
IS THAT STILL A THING, OR...
SADLY, THEY ARE GONE.
HMM. WELL, AS LONG AS YOU
DON'T USE THIS THING
FOR ANY MIDNIGHT PHOTOGRAPHY...
SCOUT'S HONOR.
Lisa: OH, GOOD.
- I GOT THAT ON TAPE.
- YOU DID.
- AND TAPE.
- RIGHT.
Cameron: SO HOW LONG
HAVE YOU KNOWN SAM?
Lisa:
A COUPLE MONTHS.
LISTEN, UH, I ACTUALLY WOULD
PREFER THIS TO BE OFF.
Cameron:
IT'S ACTUALLY THIS BUTTON.
Lisa:
WELL, THAT IS GOOD TO KNOW.
[HIGH-PITCHED SOUND]
[MEN SCREAMING]
[MUFFLED SCREAMING]
[SCREAMING,
HIGH-PITCHED SOUND STOPS]
Man: WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?
[RATTLING ON ROOF]
Hoyt: THEY'RE ON THE ROOF!
SHH.
WHAT THE HELL IS IT?
IS THAT THE--
Cameron: SHH.
Man: SHIT.
[RATTLING CONTINUES]
Matt: OH, MY GOD.
YOU GUYS. YOU GUYS!
I'LL GET THE LADDER.
CAREFUL GOING UP, BRITAIN.
Matt:
WAIT, LISA, WHAT--
Lisa: MATT, DON'T.
RABIES.
Ray: YOU EVER SEEN ANYTHING
LIKE THAT BEFORE, HOYT?
HELL NO.
NOTHING LIKE THIS.
THERE'S NO TRAUMA.
THE INTERNAL ORGANS ARE FINE.
IT WAS DEFINITELY THE TONE
THAT MESSED WITH THEIR SONAR.
UH-HUH.
THIS IS JUST THE BEGINNING.
[SLOW COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYS]
Cameron:
I'M GONNA GET SOME SLEEP.
GOOD LUCK WITH THAT.
Matt: I'M GOING TO DOCUMENT IT
AS THE TONE.
YEAH, ABSOLUTELY.
I NEED YOU TO CHECK MORE.
Matt: WE'VE ALREADY CHECKED--
[PHONE RINGS]
[RING]
Machine: HELLO. PLEASE LEAVE
A MESSAGE AFTER THE TONE. [BEEP]
HELLO, MR. MILLER,
THIS IS DR. DAVID
AT WHITE OAK PSYCHIATRIC.
I WANTED TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT YOUR WIFE'S PROGRESS
OVER THE LAST MONTH.
IF YOU COULD GIVE ME A CALL
AT YOUR EARLIEST CONVENIENCE,
I'D APPRECIATE IT.
[CLICK, BEEP]
Matt:
OH, MY GOD. SORRY.
Lisa:
OK. IT'S OK.
- Sam: YOU GUYS ALL RIGHT?
- Matt: YEAH.
Sam: GOOD. 'CAUSE I'M GOING
TO NEED YOU TO FOLLOW ME
OUT TO THE PASTURE.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
Ray:
MDE NEVER MENTIONED ANYONE ELSE
COMING UP TO THE PROPERTY.
I DON'T THINK THAT'S THEM.
HE'S BEEN SITTING OUT THERE
ABOUT 35, 45 MINUTES.
THERE'S NO PLATES ON IT.
Matt: IS THAT THING MILITARY?
Ray: I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S HARD TO TELL.
Lisa: WELL, MAYBE IT'S SOMEONE
WHO GOT LOST.
Matt: HE'S ON THE MOVE.
HE'S TURNING AROUND.
SAM, WAIT. HANG ON.
I HAVE A QUESTION.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, RAY?
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT IT'S NOT RIGHT.
NO. IT SURE AIN'T RIGHT.
I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYBODY
OUT THERE LIKE THAT. NO WAY.
[CROSSTALK IN BACKGROUND]
Sam: LOOK, I'M TEAM LEADER
OF THIS THING.
Hoyt:
IF YOU ARE THE TEAM LEADER,
THEN YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO KNOW--
LOOK, HOYT, I DON'T KNOW
EVERY VEHICLE THAT'S GOING
TO COME ON TO THE RANCH.
Ray: HEY, CALM DOWN.
LISTEN, FIGURE IT OUT.
OK, SO I RAN AN ANALYSIS
ON THAT TONE FROM LAST NIGHT.
TURNS OUT THERE WERE ACTUALLY
TWO SOUNDS ON THAT TAPE.
THERE WAS THAT HIGH-PITCHED
NOISE THAT WE OBVIOUSLY KNOW,
THE ONE THAT WOKE US UP.
BUT BELOW THAT
I FOUND TRACES OF INFRASOUND.
Lisa: INFRASOUND?
YEAH, IT'S A FREQUENCY
BELOW THE AUDIBLE RANGE
OF THE HUMAN EAR.
SO WHAT COULD CAUSE
SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
I MEAN,
INFRASOUND CAN OCCUR NATURALLY
OR IT CAN BE MANMADE.
YOU KNOW,
AT CERTAIN CYCLES PER SECOND,
THE MILITARY HAS ACTUALLY
SUCCESSFULLY TESTED INFRASOUND
TO CAUSE THINGS LIKE VERTIGO,
DEPRESSION, FEAR, ANXIETY,
PHYSICAL LESIONS,
THROAT PRESSURE,
ALL SORTS OF AWFUL SIDE EFFECTS.
AND, I MEAN, THOSE ARE JUST
THE ONES THAT WE KNOW ABOUT.
OK. AND HOW ABOUT NATURALLY?
ALL THE BIG NATURAL DISASTERS
THAT WE KNOW OF--
VOLCANOES, EARTHQUAKES,
AVALANCHES.
IT'S WHY ANIMALS ARE ABLE
TO DETECT EARTHQUAKES
BEFORE PEOPLE DO.
THEY PICK UP THE VIBRATIONS.
ANIMALS--WHALES--
THEY USE INAUDIBLE SOUNDS
TO PARALYZE AND CATCH CERTAIN
PREY, LIKE, YOU KNOW, FISH.
I'M JUST SAYING
THAT THE SOUND WE HEARD
THAT MATT'S TALKING ABOUT
COULD'VE BEEN CAUSED
BY A LIVE ANIMAL.
WE HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT WE'RE DEALING WITH HERE.
Ray: HOW THE FUCK
WOULD A WHALE GET UP HERE?
SO WHAT ARE WE DOING
OUT HERE?
OH, IT'S REALLY
WELL DOCUMENTED THAT ATTEMPTING
TO COMMUNICATE WITH
PARANORMAL ENERGIES DIRECTLY
REALLY INCREASES
LIKELIHOOD OF CONTACT.
FOLLOW ME.
AFTER YOU.
SAM HAS ASKED ME TO COME AND DO
A BLESSING ON THE PROPERTY
TO COMMUNICATE WITH THE ENERGY
THAT SPEAKS FROM THIS EARTH.
BUT YOU NEED TO KNOW.
THIS LAND IS FORSAKEN
BY MY PEOPLE.
AND IT'S ONLY TO TRY
AND BRING YOU SOME PROTECTION
THAT I'VE AGREED TO COME.
THERE ARE LEGENDS OF WARRIORS
HUNTING IN THIS VALLEY,
RETURNING TO THEIR TRIBE
DISTURBED AND CHANGED.
STORIES OF WHOLE TRIBES
DISAPPEARING.
THERE IS A DARKNESS
IN THIS SOIL.
I WOULD NOT FEEL RIGHT
IF I DIDN'T SUGGEST
THAT YOU LEAVE NOW
OR TO SAY THAT THIS PLACE
HAS NOTHING FOR YOU
BUT SUFFERING.
I ALSO KNOW
THAT YOU'VE CHOSEN TO STAY.
AND I'LL DO WHAT I CAN TO
BRING SOME LIGHT HERE,
NO MATTER HOW SMALL.
I ASK FOR SILENCE NOW
WHILE I REACH OUT TO
MY ANCESTORS.
[SPEAKS NATIVE LANGUAGE]
[SINGS IN NATIVE LANGUAGE]
AHH. AHH.
ARE YOU OK?
CAN YOU BREATHE?
SAM.
THERE'S NOTHING
I CAN DO FOR YOU.
YOU NEED TO GET
THE FUCK OUT OF HERE.
UH, 1:00 A.M. ON THE 4TH.
UM, ALREADY LOW ON SLEEP AFTER
THE EVENTS OF THE OTHER NIGHT.
SAM SEEMS TO THINK
WE'RE CLOSE TO GETTING
SOMETHING CONCRETE,
SOME--SOME KIND OF EVIDENCE.
I ADMIT THE SOUND,
THE DEAD BATS--
STRANGE, CERTAINLY.
PARANORMAL?
I'M NOT SO SURE.
[KNOCKING AT DOOR]
HANG ON.
SO WHAT'S UP?
RAY'S GOT SOMETHING.
COME ON.
SO WHAT DO WE GOT?
JUST A SECOND AGO,
SOMETHING VERY LARGE SET OFF
ONE OF THE SENSORS
IN THE BLIND SPOT.
ZONE THREE,
SPECIFICALLY.
SO WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
SOMETHING BIGGER THAN A DEER.
TRY THE SIZE
OF A GOD DAMN HELICOPTER.
Sam: ALL RIGHT.
CAMERON, CHECK THE FAR SIDE
OF THE FIELD.
THE REST OF YOU GUYS,
COME WITH ME.
[THUNDER]
Cameron:
OVER HERE!
THIS IS NOT A NATURAL DEATH.
WHAT ABOUT
AN ANIMAL ATTACK?
OH, NO. THERE ARE NO BITE MARKS,
NO CLAW MARKS.
THESE INCISIONS,
THEY'RE PERFECT.
SORRY, GIRL.
NO BLOOD.
IT'S ALMOST SURGICAL.
SHIT.
ALL RIGHT,
I WANT TO BAG THE WHOLE THING.
MATT, GET THE BAG.
[HIGH-PITCHED SQUEAL
IN DISTANCE]
WHAT IS IT?
COME ON, SAM, IF YOU'RE GOING
TO DO IT, DO IT QUICK.
[WIND CHIMES
CLINKING]
[WHISPERING]
HI, LISA.
HEY, SAM. HEY, BRITAIN.
Britain: HEY.
BLOOD?
OH, YEAH.
I HAD A NOSEBLEED LAST NIGHT.
YOU PRONE TO NOSE BLEEDS?
UH, NO.
AND I'VE HAD A COUPLE
SINCE I'VE BEEN HERE.
I'M THINKING
IT'S JUST THE ELEVATION OR...
Sam: MAYBE.
[SETS PLATE DOWN]
COME ON, BRITAIN.
Ray: AND YOU KNEW
TO CHECK THE TAPE BECAUSE
SHE HAD A FEW BLOODY NOSES?
Sam: JUST A HUNCH.
I DON'T THINK
WE CAN TELL HIM.
TELL HIM WHAT?
HOW WOULD YOU EVEN EXPLAIN THIS?
YOU DON'T. YOU WANT TO SEE
SOMETHING EVEN CRAZIER?
THIS IS A TAPE
FROM THE 9TH.
AUGUST 8TH.
Cameron:
OH, MY GOD.
Ray: AUGUST 7TH.
11:11 EVERY NIGHT.
Sam:
RAY, WHAT TIME IS IT?
IT'S 11:09.
Sam:
WHAT TIME IS IT, MATT?
Matt: IT'S ALMOST 10 AFTER.
RAY, CHECK THE CAMERA.
Lisa: YOU GUYS,
WHAT'S GOING ON?
Matt: WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
SAM, WHAT'S GOING ON?
MATT, I NEED YOU TO GIVE ME
AN EXACT COUNT UP TO 11:11.
- Sam: YOU UNDERSTAND?
- Ray: ALL RIGHT, CAMERA'S GOOD.
- Lisa: WHY?
- Ray: CAMERA'S GOOD.
- WHERE ARE WE AT RIGHT NOW?
- YOU'RE AT A MINUTE RIGHT NOW.
- WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
- CAN YOU COME OUTSIDE
FOR JUST A SECOND?
SURE. SURE. YEAH. WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
WAIT A SECOND! THIS IS MY HOUSE.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, THE LAST COUPLE
OF NIGHTS AT EXACTLY 11:11,
ENERGY HAS MOVED
THROUGH THE HOUSE.
Matt:
SAM, YOU'RE AT 45 SECONDS.
- Hoyt: AN ENERGY IN THIS HOUSE?
- Sam: YEAH.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN "AN ENERGY"?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
[PUMPS SHOTGUN]
- NO, WE DON'T NEED--
- YOU DON'T NEED THE GUN!
[CROSSTALK]
WHERE WE AT?
30 SECONDS?
ALL RIGHT,
NO MATTER WHAT YOU SEE,
NO MATTER WHAT YOU GUYS SEE,
THE CAMERA GOES FIRST.
Hoyt:
I'M PUTTING IT DOWN.
OKAY.
Matt: OK, WE'RE AT
10... 9... 8...
7... 6... 5...
11:11.
NOTHING.
[GHOSTLY WHOOSH]
CODY! CODY!
HEY, CODY! CODY!
CODY, BUDDY, IT'S DADDY.
Cameron:
SAM, GET BACK.
CODY!
CODY.
CODY?
MATT, LISA.
GET IN HERE.
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
MATT, YOU GO GET HER KIT.
WE NEED TO CAST
ALL THESE PRINTS.
LOOK AT ALL THESE TRACKS.
WHERE DID THEY COME FROM?
THESE ARE DEFINITELY
CANINE PRINTS.
BUT THEY'RE ENORMOUS.
ANYTHING?
NOTHING YET.
HOW'S HOYT?
Cameron: FOR BETTER OR WORSE,
HE'S GOT A LOT OF ALCOHOL
IN HIM NOW.
BUT IT SEEMS LIKE
HE'S CALMED DOWN.
YOU GUYS,
I GOT SOMETHING. UNH.
IT SAYS
"FOR EMERGENCIES ONLY."
Ray: WHAT THE HELL
IS THAT, SAM?
MAKE A CALL RIGHT NOW.
SAM!
NO ONE'S PICKING UP.
DO YOU HAVE
ANOTHER NUMBER FOR THEM?
NO.
- SAM, SOMEONE'S--
- WHAT DO YOU WANT ME
TO DO, LISA?
- I'M JUST SAYING--
- [PHONE RINGS]
YEAH.
I DID CALL, YES.
WELL, WHAT WE HAVE--
YOU'RE SAYING THEY WERE HERE?
- FROM '67 TO '71.
- DOING WHAT?
LOOK, YOU GUYS ARE LOOKING
AT THIS THE WRONG WAY, OK?
THEY ANSWERED
ALL MY QUESTIONS.
THEY OFFERED TO PROVIDE
DOCUMENTATION.
THEY'RE NOT TRYING
TO HIDE ANYTHING.
THEY DID? THEY ANSWERED
YOUR QUESTION--YOUR QUESTIONS?
WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
THEY ANSWERED
ALL MY QUESTIONS, HOYT.
MY GOODNESS GRACIOUS,
THEY DID?
THEY DIDN'T FIND ANYTHING, OK?
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU
FOR A SECOND.
THEY WERE HERE.
- Matt: WAIT. WAIT.
- Hoyt: JUST LISTEN TO ME
ONE SECOND!
- Hoyt: LISTEN TO ME!
- Cameron: MATT!
THEY WERE HERE?
YOU'RE TELLING ME
THEY WERE HERE.
THEY WERE HERE
BEFORE MY BOY WAS TAKEN.
Matt:
...BETTER SCIENCE.
Hoyt: YOU'RE JUST TALKING.
YOU'RE JUST TALKING.
YOU'RE NOT SAYING ANYTHING.
YOU JUST SAY,
"BLAH, BLAH, BLAH."
THAT'S THE WAY YOU LIVE
YOUR LIFE. YOU JUST TALK.
I'M TALKING ABOUT SOMETHING
REAL HERE.
I'M TALKING ABOUT MY BOY.
LOOK, WE HAD NO IDEA UNTIL I
JUST HAD THAT PHONE CALL.
BUT THEM BEING HERE
HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH YOUR BOY.
YOU UNDERSTAND, HOYT?
WHY? WHY DOES IT HAVE NOTHING
TO DO WITH MY BOY? TELL ME.
DO--DO YOU HAVE AN ANSWER?
EXCUSE ME.
Matt:
LISA, YOU ARE A SCIENTIST.
WHAT ARE YOU INVESTIGATING?
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO FIND?
ARE YOU TRYING TO FIND
MY BOY?
ARE YOU TRYING TO
FIND MY SON?
JUST LOOK ME IN THE EYE
AND TELL ME THAT YOU'RE TRYING
TO FIND MY SON.
ARE YOU TRYING TO FIND MY SON?
- I'M TRYING TO HELP YOU.
- HOW YOU TRYING TO HELP ME?
YOU'RE TRYING TO HELP YOURSELF.
I'M ON TO YOU.
YOU'D BETTER WATCH OUT.
YOU'D BETTER WATCH YOURSELF.
PUT IT DOWN.
THIS IS WHAT I WAS
TELLING YOU ABOUT.
GUYS, I FOUND TWO MORE
CONTAINERS BURIED IN THE SHED.
NOW, ONE WAS EMPTY
LIKE THE FIRST ONE I FOUND.
BUT THE SECOND HAD THIS IN IT.
- WHAT IS THIS?
- IT'S A U-MATIC TAPE.
MOSTLY USED IN THE LATE '60S
AND EARLY '70S.
AND, SAM, THAT WOULD CORRESPOND
TO THE TIMEFRAME
THAT MDE SAID THEY WERE
ORIGINALLY ON THE PROPERTY.
I'M NOT SURE OFFHAND
IF WE HAVE ANYTHING ON SITE
I CAN CHECK THIS WITH.
I'LL SEE WHAT I CAN
PUT TOGETHER, ALL RIGHT?
[EXHALES]
LATE NIGHT.
AUGUST 12TH.
APPARENTLY MDE WAS OUT HERE
IN THE '60S
LOOKING INTO THIS THING.
THE BOX WE FOUND IN THE SHED
SAID "FOR EMERGENCIES ONLY."
AND IT WAS EMPTY.
I WOULD, UH, PROBABLY BE
MORE CONCERNED ABOUT THAT
IF I HADN'T SEEN
WHAT LOOKED LIKE HOYT'S SON
TEAR THROUGH THE HOUSE,
GO INTO A SHED,
AND COMPLETELY DISAPPEAR.
HE WAS GONE.
I...I CAN'T EXPLAIN IT.
I FEEL LIKE SAM IS SO OBSESSED
WITH FINDING EVIDENCE
ABOUT WHAT'S HAPPENING HERE
THAT HE WON'T EVEN QUESTION
MDE'S MOTIVES.
- [ROAR]
- AAH!
Cameron:
SO, LISA, YOU'VE NEVER
SEEN ANYTHING LIKE THIS?
Lisa: NO.
THAT'S IT, THEN.
LET'S GO HUNTING.
Sam: THERE SHOULD
BE TRACKS, RIGHT?
Lisa: I THINK WE SHOULD BE
LOOKING FOR THE TRACKS
WE FOUND IN THE SHED.
IT HAS TO BE
THE SAME ANIMAL.
AND JUST JUDGING BY THE SIZE
OF THE WOLF WE SAW,
I'D SAY IT WAS EASILY
500 POUNDS,
WHICH IS FIVE TIMES LARGER--
Matt: GUYS!
THAT THING IS HUGE.
[SHOTGUN PUMPS]
[GROWLING]
COME ON, LET'S GO GET IT.
COME ON, THAT'S WHAT
WE'RE HERE FOR. GO!
[ENGINE STARTS]
Hoyt: WE GOT TO GO
THE REST OF THE WAY ON FOOT,
HE'S RIGHT OUT THERE.
Cameron:
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO.
Hoyt: EASY NOW.
EASY NOW.
[GROWLING]
Cameron: LOOK AT THAT.
Lisa: I WANT TO GO BACK NOW.
[GROWLING]
- OK.
- [SHOTGUN FIRES]
Cameron: EASY. WAIT. SLOW DOWN.
I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
CAREFUL! CAREFUL!
HOYT, WHERE'D IT GO?
I DON'T SEE IT.
BE CAREFUL.
GUYS, OVER HERE!
Matt: WAIT, SAM,
DID YOU SEE THE LIGHT?
- Lisa: WHAT IS IT?
- Matt: THERE WAS A LIGHT.
Matt: I BET IT'S A CAVE SYSTEM.
I GOT SOME ROPES IN MY TRUCK.
LET ME GO GET 'EM.
- Matt: ALL RIGHT.
- Hoyt: YOU GUYS BE CAREFUL.
THAT THING'S STILL OUT HERE
SOMEWHERE.
SAM, YOU'RE GONNA WANT
TO SEE THIS.
Cameron: HOW OLD
DO YOU THINK THAT IS?
JESUS, SAM,
WHAT'S GOING ON REALLY?
Hoyt: WHAT THE HELL
WE EVEN LOOKING AT?
RAY, LOOK AT THIS!
LOOKS LIKE
WE FOUND OUR ARTIST.
SHH. SHH.
HOW THE HELL WOULD THAT THING
EVEN GET DOWN HERE?
[GROWLING]
OH, GOD! GO!
COME ON!
[GUNSHOT]
[GUNSHOTS]
MATT!
COME ON! COME ON!
I SAID HURRY! LET'S GO!
MATT, THE ROPE!
Cameron: BRITAIN FIRST!
COME ON, TURN OFF THE CAMERA.
AUGUST 13TH.
WE JUST...
[GARBLED]
...THE WOLF,
I DON'T KNOW...
[GARBLED]
...COME AND TAKE A CLOSER LOOK
AT THE ARTWORK IN THE MORNING.
COULD BE A VIMANA, RIGHT?
Ray: A WHAT?
A VIMANA.
HUH?
IN INDIA, THEY'VE UNCOVERED
ALL THESE ANCIENT TEXTS
AND DOCUMENTS THAT DESCRIBE
A FLYING SPACECRAFT
CALLED A VIMANA.
AND I MEAN, IT LOOKS--
IT LOOKS JUST LIKE THIS.
EVEN THOUGH THAT STUFF IS,
LIKE, 6,000 YEARS OLD
AND A LOT OF PEOPLE THINK
IT'S MYTH,
EXPERTS IN OUR FIELD
THINK THAT, YOU KNOW,
BASED ON THE SCHEMATICS
AND THE FLIGHT PLANS
AND THE DESIGN
THAT IT'S AS MODERN AS ANYTHING
YOU'D SEE TODAY.
ARE YOU SUGGESTING THAT
OUR NATIVE PAINTED A SPACECRAFT
ON THE INSIDE OF THIS CAVE?
YEAH.
JUST, I KNOW EVERYTHING
WE'VE SEEN.
THAT JUST SEEMS
PRETTY ASTOUNDING.
- WELL, IT'S, LIKE,
A PERFECT MATCH.
- AND THE WOLF?
THIS IS BIGGER THAN
A WOLF OR MISSING KID.
HOW DO YOU EVEN KNOW
HE'S BACK HERE?
HE'S WORKING ON THE ATV.
JUST WANTED TO SAY I COMPLETELY
LOST MY PERSPECTIVE BACK THERE.
AND, UH...
I'M REALLY SORRY.
STUFF LIKE THAT
HAPPENS SOMETIMES, YOU KNOW.
YOU KNOW, UH...
CODY, ON HIS BIRTHDAY,
HE WOKE HIS MOTHER UP
WITH A HANDFUL OF WILDFLOWERS
HE PICKED IN THAT FIELD
RIGHT OUT THERE.
AND SHE LOOKED AT HIM,
AND SHE SAID,
"SON, WHAT--IT'S YOUR BIRTHDAY.
WHY--WHY YOU GIVING ME FLOWERS?"
AND HE SAID,
"WELL, BECAUSE YOU'RE
THE REASON I GOT BORN, MA."
THAT'S THE KIND OF KID HE WAS.
HE IS.
THAT'S CODY.
LISTEN, UM,
I'M SORRY I GAVE YOU A HARD TIME
THE OTHER NIGHT AT THE TABLE.
IT'S JUST...I DON'T...
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
YOUR TECHNIQUES. AND, UH...
I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW
I APPRECIATE YOU'RE HERE.
AND, UM,
I MEAN, IT'S THE ONLY THING
THAT GIVES ME ANY HOPE.
[WHIRRING]
[WHOOSH]
NOTHING.
[DISTORTED MUSIC PLAYS]
Hoyt: THAT DOESN'T
MAKE SENSE AT ALL.
[RUSTLING]
Cameron: SHH!
[METAL CLANKING]
- [OWL SCREECHES]
- AAH!
[DOG BARKS]
[BARKING]
[BARKING CONTINUES]
[YELPS]
Sam: WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
THE PASTURE CAM'S DOWN.
MATT, TAKE THIS WALKIE
AND GO OUT THERE.
WON'T EVEN TAKE YOU
TWO MINUTES, MAN.
- ALL RIGHT, SAM, CAN YOU--
- JUST DO IT, MATT!
[DOOR CLOSES]
Sam: TAKE ME THROUGH
ALL THE EXTERIOR CAMS.
ALL RIGHT.
- [WALKIE-TALKIE BEEPS]
- DO YOU COPY?
Ray: GIVE ME 30 FEET BACK
FOR FOCUS. THANKS, BUDDY.
MATT?
MATT!
Lisa:
AAH! OH, MY GOD!
Ray: GO!
MATT'S UP AND ABOUT.
HE'S PRETTY BEAT UP,
BUT HE SHOULD BE FINE.
I HAVE NO EXPLANATION
FOR WHAT HAPPENED TO HOYT'S DOG.
CAMERON, DID YOU HEAR ME?
YEAH, I'M...SORRY.
Matt: SERIOUSLY, SAM,
JUST BACK OFF.
I MEAN IT!
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
WHAT THE HELL
IS WRONG WITH YOU?
I WAS JUST PICKED UP
AND THROWN.
AND WE DON'T HAVE
A SINGLE EXPLANATION AS TO
HOW THAT'S EVEN POSSIBLE!
LOOK, LET ME TELL YOU
WHAT'S GOING DOWN.
I'M GOING TO THE E.R.
THEN I'M BOOKING A FLIGHT
OUT OF HERE.
AND IF YOU GUYS HAD, LIKE,
AN OUNCE OF COMMON SENSE,
YOU'D ALL COME WITH ME!
YOU NEED ANOTHER DRIVER SO BAD,
YOU HIRE SOMEONE ELSE.
[ENGINE STARTS]
BE CAREFUL, GUYS.
SERIOUSLY.
YOU'RE AN ASSHOLE, SAM!
YOU KNOW THAT?
ASSHOLE!
WE STILL HAVE HOYT'S TRUCK.
WE CAN GO IN HOYT'S TRUCK.
SO WHAT'S GOING ON, RAY?
ARE YOU GUYS AWARE
THAT MATT FOUND ADDITIONAL
MDE MATERIALS IN THE SHED,
INCLUDING A VIDEOTAPE?
YEAH, HE MENTIONED IT.
BUT I THOUGHT IT WAS
TOO OLD TO PLAY UP HERE.
NO. IT TURNS OUT I WAS ABLE
TO FIND AN OLD DECK
AND TRANSFER IT
TO A HARD DRIVE.
OK. SO WHAT WAS ON THE TAPE?
I THINK IT'S BETTER
IF I JUST PLAY IT FOR YOU GUYS.
Man: THERE. RIGHT THERE.
REBECCA, CAN YOU HEAR ME?
[RADIO CHATTER]
WE'RE ON OUR WAY BACK IN
WITH REBECCA.
ABOUT EIGHT MINUTES OUT.
MOMMY? MOMMY?
WHERE'S MOMMY?
Man: THAT'S WHAT WE'RE TRYING
TO FIGURE OUT, REBECCA.
YOU REMEMBER THE LAST TIME
YOU WERE WITH HER?
[WHIRRING]
Woman: HOW FAR OUT WAS SHE?
Man: WELL BEYOND THE PASTURE.
Woman: AND THE DOG?
Man: NO.
Man: WHAT'S SHE DOING?
MICHELLE!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
AHH.
AAH!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[ROAR]
RAY PLAYED US THE TAPE
THAT MATT HAD FOUND IN THE SHED.
THERE'S SOMETHING UNEXPLAINABLE
OUT HERE.
IF THAT TAPE
IS TO BE BELIEVED,
THEN I JUST WITNESSED
THE KILLING OF AN ENTIRE TEAM
OF PEOPLE
BY SOMETHING
COMPLETELY UNKNOWN.
WHY WOULD THEY SEND US
OUT HERE?
SAM IS SO OBSESSED
WITH WHAT'S HAPPENING,
WE'RE HESITANT TO EVEN
SHOW HIM THE TAPE.
AND HOYT...
[GARBLED]
I THINK WE SHOULD GO.
WE HAVE TO GO.
BUT I DO NOT THINK
THAT HE IS IN A PLACE
TO MAKE DECISIONS RIGHT NOW.
WHAT THE HELL ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO DO THEN?
I SAY WE LEAVE TONIGHT.
WE HAVE HOYT'S TRUCK.
[GROWLING]
GET BEHIND ME.
GET IN THE TRUCK.
GET IN THE FUCKIN' TRUCK!
GO! GET IN THE TRUCK!
HEY!
WHERE IS IT?
LISA!
[ROAR, GROWLING]
[LISA AND CAMERON SCREAMING]
Cameron: SHIT!
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
WHAT THE FUCK IS IT DOING?
AH, SHIT!
WHERE DID--WHERE DID IT GO?
HE JUST RAN OFF.
ARE YOU OK, LISA?
ARE YOU OK?
AAH.
LISA, NO! NO!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING? STOP IT!
LISA, STOP!
I DON'T REMEMBER ANYTHING.
NOTHING.
WE SHOULD'VE LEFT WITH MATT.
WE'RE GETTING UNPRECEDENTED
FOOTAGE, GUYS.
THIS IS WHAT WE WANTED.
THIS IS WHY WE CAME HERE.
THIS IS WHAT WE WANTED?
PEOPLE ARE GETTING HURT.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT, SAM?
LOOK, I THINK THE THING
IS A SINGLE INTELLIGENCE.
OH, FOR--YOU KNOW SOMETHING?
YOU'RE OUT OF YOUR MIND.
LOOK, WE ARE SO CLOSE.
WE ARE RIGHT THERE.
CLOSE TO WHAT?
WHAT IF THIS THING CAN TURN INTO
AN ORB OR A WOLF OR EVEN CODY?
OR ME?
SAM, SERIOUSLY,
IT'S FUCKIN' DONE.
I DON'T WANT TO BE HERE
ANYMORE, SAM.
I CAN'T BE HERE ANYMORE.
GO PACK YOUR BAG.
I'LL MEET YOU AT THE FRONT DOOR
IN FIVE MINUTES.
OK, WE ARE LEAVING.
YOU'RE NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
CAMERON, PLEASE!
GET YOUR HANDS OFF ME.
IT'S DONE, SAM!
- WELL, I'M NOT LEAVING!
- IT'S OVER! STOP!
CODY.
CODY!
I GOT YOUR BAG, BRITAIN.
I'M READY.
WE READY?
WHAT ABOUT SAM?
HE WON'T LISTEN.
WE'LL SEND SOMEBODY BACK.
WHO GIVES A SHIT ABOUT SAM?
Lisa: RAY?
[CRASH]
WHAT THE FUCK IS THIS, CAMERON?
OH, MY GOD. OH, MY GOD!
COME ON. COME ON.
LET'S GO, LISA!
GO!
THEY'RE SENDING A VAN
FIRST THING IN THE MORNING.
IN THE MORNING?
THAT'S THE SOONEST
THEY CAN GET HERE, LISA.
THAT--THAT'S GREAT, SAM,
CONSIDERING WE WERE JUST
OUT IN HOYT'S DRIVEWAY
AND HIS TRUCK WAS COMPLETELY
DISASSEMBLED
AND WE DIDN'T HEAR
A GOD DAMN THING.
- LEAVE ANYTIME YOU WANT.
- HOW?
DO YOU FIND IT ODD
THAT THE MOMENT WE ARRIVED
ON THIS RANCH
IS WHEN ALL THIS SHIT
STARTED HAPPENING?
HE'S RIGHT. WE COULD BE
PART OF A MDE EXPERIMENT--
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YOU SHOULD KNOW BETTER.
HOW DO YOU EXPLAIN
WHAT'S BEEN HAPPENING HERE?
HOW DO YOU KNOW MDE DOESN'T KNOW
EXACTLY WHAT'S HERE, SAM?
I NEVER SHOULD'VE ASKED YOU
TO COME HERE.
OK. WE'RE GOING TO GET HOME.
LOOK AT ME.
WE'RE GOING TO GET HOME.
CAMERON, THERE'S SOMETHING
WRONG WITH RAY.
RAY?
WHOA. PUT THE GUN DOWN, RAY.
ALL RIGHT? JUST...OK.
I DON'T WANT...
Cameron: NO!
[LISA SCREAMS]
OH, MY GOD!
[CRACKLING]
Lisa: AAH.
[CREATURE GROWLS]
[PEOPLE SHOUTING]
GO!
COME ON NOW!
OH, GOD!
OH, SHIT.
[WHOOSH]
LISTEN TO ME. YOU GO.
YOU GET THE ATV.
GO! GO!
[LISA YELLING, KNOCKING AT DOOR]
OPEN THE DOOR!
OPEN IT!
GET BACK!
[WHOOSH]
SHE'S GONE.
Sam [over walkie-talkie]:
IN THE BARN. HURRY!
[WALKIE-TALKIE BEEPS]
SAM!
WHOA.
COME ON. COME ON.
Sam: CAMERON!
Cameron:
HANG ON, SAM!
SAM!
[SAM INDISTINCT OVER RADIO]
AAH!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
["HOW WE WOKE UP"
BY MOTH & THE FLAME PLAYS]
THE FUTURE'S HOLDING ON
OH, SUSPEND ME IN MY PAST
AND THIS IS HOW I WOKE UP
ALONE
YOU'RE DANGLING BY A STRING
ABOVE EVERYTHING
YOU COULD BE
AND THIS IS HOW YOU WOKE UP
ALONE
SHARPEN THEIR TEETH
ON YOUR NECK
REMEMBER YOUR FLAWS
LIKE A BAD DREAM
YOU WANT TO WAKE UP
PLEASE WAKE UP
OH, PLEASE WAKE UP
OH, PLEASE WAKE UP!
OH, THERE'S STILL TIME
JUST FOR A MOMENT
AS WE STARE
PROJECTING OUR THOUGHTS
INTO THE AIR
AS IF
WE HAD PRACTICED IT BEFORE
OUR MINDS DANCED
HAND IN HAND
AND CHOREOGRAPHED
BY BOTH OUR LIVES
TOLD LIKE STORIES
TO OUR EYES
ALL OF THE WORLD FROZEN
IN TIME
AND THIS IS HOW WE WOKE UP
AND WE REMEMBER WHO WE ARE
WE WERE PASSING IN THE DARK
AS IF WE'RE SOMETHING
IN THE LIGHT
WE'RE LEFT YOU KNOW
LEFT YOU KNOW!
WHEN YOU WON'T EVEN FAIL