AMNESIA
Translated by chris91
Translate by chris91
Dear...
..wake up
Finally wake up.
Happy to see your eyes...
- Where am I?
- At home.
Where?
You're unconscious.
Because of what happened.
- What happened?
- Terrible accident.
Bumping windshield.
The doctor said you might
have memory problems...
temporarily
Who are you?
Dear...
I'm your wife...
I will help you feel better.
You know, noodle
is not found by an Italian?
Although popular in the West,
they are created by Chinese.
Doctor says to make your mind as calm as possible
It was not so bright.
Not much to see.
It was a terrible accident.
I don't remember.
- How did it happen?
- A mistake, dear.
There is plenty of time to answer questions,
but now you need to rest.
Dear,
don't move out of bed.
You need to rest.
Well, what happened?
People disappear all the time.
If found dead,
Means another small town
complained about this city.
What else is there?
Men chaotic?
Okay, send it.
What are you writing?
I will tell what will be done.
I will enter your notes in my notebook.
It's time, sleepyhead!
I'm afraid I'll never
see your beautiful eyes again.
How long have I slept?
- Two days.
- Yikes.
The doctor said it's okay
for someone like your circumstances.
Doctor?
I hear voices...
I saw shadows
while sleeping.
Where is the doctor?
See? It's better.
Will prepare dinner.
Dear, don't need to get out of bed
.
.. My leg fracture ..
You drink painkillers.
Will not be so pronounced.
I feel confused.
Everything is new for me.
Like a cat...
I heard a cat.
I don't remember we have a cat.
Yes, but we have.
Because you've been down here,
Do you want to eat dinner together as
spouse, as before?
Yes.
Well, I cook your
favorite.
My favorite?
Sorry. Sometimes I forget
you can't remember.
Roasted beef.
you like roasted beef.
When did we moved here?
- Shortly before the incident.
- And you have to go through all this?
- You don't need to take care of me.
- don't have to, but I want...
You're my husband.
Now let's eat.
Come on, puss.
Elephant died due to blood clots ..
what ..?
In the forest...
Death is more due to
lack of food and water.
The pressure that kills them.
Do you remember?
- No.
- You don't remember about the elephant?
- No, I can't think.
- What do you remember?
I can't remember where I grew up.
You can't remember our
dance party?
You kissed me in the river?
You don't remember?
I want...
I'm sorry....
Did you know that the first can opener
discovered 50 years before
cans are produced first time?
I miss you.
Are we...
happy?
You'll have to ask ..?
I think I've just
remind you about it.
Should I remind you again?
How was the first time we met?
It was love at first sight.
Where did we go
honeymoon?
To the north.
north, where?
I wish the accident had no effect on memory.
How did it happen?
- Why did not you hurt?
- I was thrown from the car.
But let's not talk about it
, baby
it just makes you sad
I want to be happy again
There was a car accident on the road 83
the victim was not found
but had taken blood samples ,
- Did you check the number plate ??
- Yes sir.
The car was not registered since the 60s.
Light blue Thunderbird.
- How many casualties?
- Still don't know.
From the results of the examination on the car
2 adults and a daughter.
- How is the weather?
- Good.
- It's raining?
- No sir.
Good.
- Should...
- give me the address? Yes.
- Now?
- Yes.
Good. Thank you sir.
Dad...
What are you doing, dear?
I'm looking for you.
No need to be like that.
Please, I'm very worried.
Especially after what happened.
You're right .., sorry.
Why don't you take off your clothes
upward?
I'll be here for a while and
prepare your bath.
No, no need.
I can do myself.
This is a wedding.
We help each other.
Okay, I'll wait
above.
Yes
This is part of my nightmares,
I can't get rid of it.
Repeated.
He ..
girl...
called me ..dad.
Have you noticed that the battery
sold its size "A" "C" and "D"?
Why there's no size B?
Battery "B" does not work well
among consumers,
so that customers leave.
Still can be found in Europe.
..used for bikes' light
Tell me about yourself.
I want to know more about you
Do you have other relatives?
What about me?
I want to know you.
The woman I love.
I hate talking about the past.
You know that.
I want to focus on our future
This is my movie room
place where I made a movie
I don't remember.
I don't remember any of this.
I don't know what you got,
what I got.
Where I can go and not.
Sometimes I forget.
It's okay.
That's why I got this room.
Full of memories.
Help me to remember.
I know it's hard for you.
Will you help me to remember?
Yes...
- What's in that room?
- Only room.
Bedroom else?
It's just a room.
I thought I saw someone there.
How?
Door.
I think there is a person.
Just curious.
You know what they say about curiosity
.
I'm just trying to remember.
I know, dear. I know.
I will stop at the store after work.
I need to examine my patients.
Do you agree?
- Yes.
Pregnancy Tests
Animal Hospital
What is it, dear?
I go to the basement.
I saw someone. I see what you're doing.
- I said don't ever come down.
I never made a secret with you my first husband
Who are you?
I am a woman who loves you,
who cares about you,
feed you,
bath you,
make love to you.
I'm your wife.
You seem a little depressed
Honey, you know about electroshock therapy
,
known as "shock therapy"?
Back to the 16th century in Eastern Europe,
but became popular in the 30's in America.
Although this therapy is controversial,
it still used in this country and around the world
as a cure for depression.
I think it would help you, honey.
I really believe.
No, no!
See? It was not so bad, right?
Did you know that Conway Tweety
has 55 hits?
Even more than Elvis Presley.
Do you realize how
importance is family?
Strong family is the backbone of the community
.
There is nothing more beautiful than
relationship between husband and wife,
raising children at home.
I just want to see in the future.
That's all.
Forget the past.
- My body...
sick.
Shock therapy has side effects.
Please stop.
Make it stop.
Do you love me?
Yes.
I love you too.
Do you want to quit?
Yes
Then, I want something.
I want a baby.
Does not every woman wants from her husband?
A baby...
I want a child.
From my own family
you want me to stop?
- Yes.
- Give me a family.
To get, you have to give
That's called a good marriage.
Memories are something great,
isn't it?
I know you are curious ..
so you see my family album
I always know when you touch
my stuff because it is changing.
Why is there no photo of us?
Where is it all?
It was not your picture.
None of them is you.
Hi. How are you, Dave?
Always well, when I can see you.
- Oh sweetness...
I got a registered letter. You must sign ..
.. Briefly Why not get in?
I'm going to the kitchen, I'll be back.
- Good.
You must maintain an attitude,
when we have guests.
This is better.
Everything is okay?
- I'm looking for a pen.
Thank you!
I will take it.
What are you doing?
You want to know more about me?
Look at me when I talk to you
Do you want to know about my past?
Or do you want to know more about us
?
What?
- What happened on the night of the incident.
When would you like to tell me?
Do you really not know?
- No.
How can I?
Dear...
something to euthanize my job... living
And they don't wake up,
Did you know that?
I don't care at all!
This is what dreams about
One day you would expect,
you care more about her.
Who is she?
I still see it ..
In my dreams...
is it my daughter?
Our daughter?
Please tell me she's okay.
I have a job.
Listen, I got a lot of work.
I would stay in office.
Bring patrol car passes Bird Street,
.. Magpay with Mokingbard
check.
what do you think?
I think he had a heart attack and died
..
in the bushes with a pile of letters has not been sent.
Okay, keep me posted.
Help!
Help! Help me!
Help
Help me!
I'm here!
Help! I am here!
Help!
No!
He should not interfere in our family
.
You know, bottle caps
more expensive to produce than the bottle itself?
I got up from my chair,
I hope this is something important.
I don't know, maybe he just ran off with
letters
Did you call the office?
did you go to his house?
No?
actually..he sleeps at his house with his children.
Or with others,
he was not on duty.
Okay, I'll stop by to some
house while I'm gone.
But if I disappear
must know something.
I'm going to die.
Want to know more about you.
I hope you're ready.
It's okay.
don't cry.
Gosh.
You can't even remember
your daughter, Audrey?
don't say, at least
you remember.
sHe became naughty girl.
I have to lock him in the kennels.
Please, don't hurt her,
You can't do that.
Depends on you.
- Let her go.
I will,
Once you agree
make me pregnant.
I need another child.
Audrey overgrow.
Everything will be fine, right?
Whatever you want.
But please let her go
This is a good start.
You're going to be good, right?
Nice
Come on.
don't you pretty?
don't ruin your makeup.
Dear,  I got a surprise for you.
don't you have the perfect family?
Come on, honey.
I think it's time to tell father
what happened in the night of the incident.
Help me, please!
If you want to call,
close the phone and try again
I'm thirsty
Family forever.
No matter what...
During your life ..
claim the happy moments...
others as if yours...
your life...
memories .. ..
What do you want...
Did you know that Walter Freeman
creating a lobotomy?
Freeman took a knife and stabbed
just above the tear ducts
and moved into the vicinity.
From 1936-1950...
Scientists roam the countryside with a car called lobotomobil.
In order to demonstrate the procedure of treatment
This is a major advance in the science of surgery.
Believed to be the cure for all mental illness ..
including delinquency in children.
I've never done before
lobotomy.
And I would never do
for the first time in Audrey.
I know that is a bit extreme
I don't intend to do that,
but I think if I did not do,
you will never be happy here...
At least, accept, naturally do
the first time with you, not at Audrey.
I want to know who is calling
here at night like this?
Sorry to interrupt, ma'am.
I'm here for
missing person investigation.
I'm sorry to hear that,
but I don't see anyone.
I was in the shower can excuse? Thank you.
You make the floor flooded.
You ruined my floor!
Dad...
Calm. You're safe now.
How is my child,
what happened to her?
This...
- What?
- You're lucky to be alive.
Is she okay?
What is wrong with her?
I'm her father
Where am I?
What... What happened to my child?
Stay with this question.
- This question?
Is she okay?
My daughter... Is she okay?
does she here?
sHe's... she's okay?
What ..?
My daughter... my daughter is well
, right?
Now rest
I need my daughter.
I have to see it.
Must...
I'm her father
I am detective that investigating the case.
I need your help, Detective.
Obviously not.
Did you know how to get here?
No
Hold your hands and remember?
Let's start with Audrey.
My daughter...
Why do you think she was your daughter?
Indeed daughter
How do you know that she was your daughter?
sHe told me.
Who?
My wife.
Who is your wife's name?
I don't know.
What is your name?
All I know is,
I have a daughter named Audrey.
she's not your daughter.
Audrey Williams is the daughter
Mason Williams.
The man who is very rich.
When she disappeared,
emerging demand ransom by mail
You can do this.
We need money for medicine.
If you want a child, let's do
.
If I want to have child?
If ..we .. want to have children...
This will make us happy family
What can you tell me how
handwriting on the ransom demand letter?
I had this
handwriting samples from your home.
No, no...
We know you took her.
Audrey admitted.
Hello, dear.
We've just here, and we got lost.
Can you mind helping us?
Thank you.
You face difficult moments...
Moreover
three murder victims who was found in the basement
This is life.
I've never killed anyone.
You don't remember your name
how do you know you did not kill them?
He did.
He has not been found.
It puts you in the right
place at the wrong time
Or the wrong place at the right time
Or the wrong place and the wrong time.
There are both wrong.
True?
I did not do it.
People do many things now, have child.
I don't want to do that.
Bad idea I'm going to return ..
This is a gift for us.
You want to help you remember?
There are many choices...
expensive way for couples to have a family.
All fertile drugs  is here
Along with the accumulated bills.
This is a desperate move.
He wanted to have child at all costs.
And you've been planning the abduction,
to give it to her.
So this is my memory?
Yes.
Dad... I want my dad.
I want my dad.
Doctors say keep your mind as calm as possible
This means subtract the bright light.
Not much to see.
Dear...
I put things to bed life
..and they don't wake up,
you know that?
Translated by chris91