What's your first memory?
Here's mine, ready?
All my life, I knew I was
destined for one thing.
To be a great artist.
From the very beginning, I knew
exactly what my medium would be
and I knew, with every
fiber of my being
that... that my
creations were going
to be tremendous works of art.
They'd touch people in
the deepest of ways,
make them see
things differently,
see themselves differently.
Make them say to each other,
"this here, this
is truly great."
But somehow,
something, somewhere
along the way went, I
don't know... Wrong.
Herman!
It's 3:00 in the morning,
what are you doing?
Mom, I'm working!
Lady, I would just prefer to
show my work to
Ms. klein herself.
Look, if you want
Ms. klein to see it,
it has to go through me first.
That's just how it works.
Fine, okay.
It's a commentary
on how our country's
eco-imperialist policies
directly correlate
to the rise of carbon monoxide
in the earth's atmosphere.
It's a mobile.
I'm making your favorite.
I think you spend too
much time down there.
You need to get out more.
I need to work.
What work?
You don't work.
If I had a job, then when
would I have time
for my art, mom?
Besides, making mobiles is the
only thing that I'm good at.
Maybe it's time you
found something else.
What do you want me to do, huh?
You want me to quit?
Oh, hermann.
Bring me the skins,
will you, dear?
What about your uncle?
He can give you
some good advice.
Why don't you call him?
Uncle Felix?
Crazy uncle Felix, who
makes jewelry out of shells?
What?
Come on.
What "come on"?
He make beautiful earrings, see?
He doesn't even
make those himself.
He exploits these poor
villagers to do it.
He exploits them, he
pays them pennies,
and then he turns around and
he sells his art for hundreds.
He's a total hack.
You show respect.
Ever since your father died he
sent a check every Christmas.
He's a good man.
He's a hack.
Helps with the bills
more than you do.
I'm not calling him, okay?
I'm just saying for
your own good, hermann!
You know, you're not
getting any younger.
Can you crank, dear?
Hermann.
Joel, where's your piece?
- Not finished yet.
- Pfft.
I know what you're thinking.
You see, it's all part
of my new technique.
I call it "instantaneous art."
The whole notion of
the tortured artist
investing months in one piece.
It just seems so... Historic.
You don't have a piece, do you?
You ever been
struck by lightning?
Great art is like lightning.
It's effortless, only
takes an instant to create.
And when it hits you, wham!
Know what I mean?
Pretty pictures!
Hiya, chief.
I didn't know you had
a showroom in this neighborhood.
I branched out.
Want me to try selling
some of your work?
You get a fair cut.
Yeah, I make real art,
not, uh, whatever this is.
Oh, I see, you make real art.
I ever tell you about
my friend Marlon?
Have a seat, chief.
Marlon was a painter,
poor son of a bitch.
He was convinced he
was the next kandinsky.
Only it turns out, he couldn't
paint worth half a damn.
I mean, it's plain to
everybody he stinks.
Only no one has the guts
to tell him, you know?
Sure.
So the guy struggles
his whole life.
Only it's not working,
he can't sell a thing.
Ate his insides out.
One day, he comes by talking
about some lizard he found.
He got obsessed with
the way they can
break off their tails, you know,
to escape from danger.
Survival mechanism.
Anyway, it must
have got to where
he couldn't take it anymore.
So one day, he just snapped.
Took out a pair of
garden shears and
cut his fingers clean
off, all of them.
I guess he just needed
to stop the pain.
Anyway, he's a lot happier now.
His brother takes care of him.
He gets monthly checks from
the government, no biggie.
I could never sell
his stuff anyway.
Mom?
Oh, hey, you must be hermann.
Did not wake you, did I?
There's a man in my bathroom.
Oh, that's Mr. Shariff.
He says he always tests a
shower before renting a place.
You're renting out my room?
Hermann, we need the money.
But where will I sleep?
With me, we'll be like roomies.
I love it, Zig, I'll take it.
Who is this?
Hey, uncle Felix, it's hermann.
Hermann who? I
don't know any...
oh, of course, Jackie's kid.
Well, ain't that a
kick in the pants.
How the hell are ya?
How's your mom?
Fine, uh, listen,
uncle Felix, I was...
hey, bun-bun, rum gimlet!
I, um, I was hoping I could
ask you for some advice.
Um, you know, on account of
you being a successful artist.
Um, oh, yeah, I get by.
Yeah, it's just
I'm an artist too.
And it's just not working out.
Hm, oh yeah?
Yeah, and I have the chops.
I mean, that's... that's not it.
It's just that something's
wrong, you know?
Like something's missing.
Stop right there.
I had the same problem
when I was starting out.
- You did?
- Absolutely!
Let me guess, you feel like
something's just not right.
Like there's this nebulous
dark cloud surrounding you.
Am I right, or am I right?
Yeah, yeah.
Are you all wound up tight?
Feelings of apathy,
depression, trouble sleeping?
Yeah.
Yup, I went through
the same thing.
I know exactly what you need.
You do? What?
Take down this address,
my old studio apartment.
Uh, okay, you
want me to go there?
Dammit, I want
you to live there.
What you need is your own
space to work, uninhibited.
And this place is perfect.
It's where I was holed
up at the precise moment
that success struck me
like a bolt from the blue.
Pow! Changed everything.
Yeah, I mean, that's
exactly what I need.
Aw, dammit, I said "gimlet."
Ice, rum, lime juice.
I tell ya, down here, these
are a beautiful people.
Yeah, um, thank you so much
for letting me stay there.
When can I move in?
Right away, 800 a month.
Oh, uh, I... I uh...
What, what's the matter?
I just... I can't afford that.
Come on, I'm renting
you well-being, freedom,
and at a very good rate for
a studio in that location.
You know what I think?
You can't afford to pass
it up is what I think.
I I just... I don't
have that kind of money.
Hermann, what can I tell ya?
Success doesn't come cheap.
You sleep on it.
Who knows, maybe you
can sell some blood?
I'm going to need
a lot of blood.
Artist Joel Windle has found
a new take on collaborative art.
He allows his buyers
to sign the artwork
and they even receive a portion
of the profits when
the next buyer signs.
I'm letting them
take part in the art.
I just made $20.
I just made two grand.
Okay, how is that
not a Ponzi scheme?
It's a small price for them
to pay to become an artist.
It's cheaper than
art school, anyway.
Devora.
- May I?
- Of course.
Ladies and gentlemen
of the art world,
I have a little announcement.
I am very excited to
announce that Joel Windle has
just signed on as the devora
klein gallery's newest artist.
Our group show is in a month.
He'll be my crowning Jewel.
Devora? Ms. klein?
Look, I am so sorry about
what happened back there.
That... that shouldn't
have happened, okay?
That wasn't part
of the art piece.
I, uh, I brought you some water.
Look, I... that isn't
1/10th of what I can do.
If you just give me a chance...
haven't you done
enough already?
You have to put me
in your next show.
- Please!
- Are we done here?
- A little more.
- I'll do anything, okay?
Just give me a chance,
just one chance.
I'll... I'll lock myself
up for two weeks.
And... and... and if I
don't produce something
startlingly, truly amazing,
then... then I'll...
Quit forever?
Yeah, yeah, I'll quit forever.
Fine, you do that.
Thank you so much, Ms. klein.
I... I won't let you down, okay?
Hey, uncle Felix,
hey, it's hermann.
Could you rent me the
place for two weeks?
It's all I've got.
H hi, I'm... I'm here
about the apartment.
You must be hermann.
I'm Layla, the manager.
Your uncle's told
me all about you.
You're the artist.
Yeah.
So...
I'll show you the apartment.
Uh...
You know, since I've
been manager here,
I don't think anybody's
ever lived in this unit.
Well, my... my uncle
lived in it, I guess,
until he bought the apartment.
Well, here, it's around
the corner and on the left.
Okay.
And garbage pickup's Fridays.
- Thanks.
- M-hm.
Hi, hermann, how's
your art coming?
Fine.
Aren't you going
to invite me in?
I'd love to see your work.
I don't like to show
works in progress.
Of course, I
understand completely.
Anyway, I was just baking, and I
accidentally made an extra pie
and I thought you
might be hungry.
You made a pie?
Peach. You do like
peach pie, don't you?
Yeah, uh...
Thanks.
Hermann, I just wanted
to tell you if you ever
need any help, not to presume
that I know anything about art
but if you ever need
any, I don't know,
moral support or something,
or anything, just let me know.
I should get back.
Don't worry, I'll
be back later for the plate.
Oh, okay, come on.
Ow.
I'm going insane.
Yes?
Hey, devora, it's, uh,
it's me, hermann haig.
Um, two weeks ago, I...
i said that I would
have something amazing for you.
And, well, it's...
it's been two weeks.
Right.
The one with the...
with the blood.
Yeah, yeah, right.
You know, this
really isn't the best time.
Thanks.
Uh...
Hello?
Hey, it's me.
Just if... if you'd
let me show you,
I think you're really
going to love it.
I mean, really, it's like...
It's like nothing
you've ever seen before.
I'm not taking on
any new artists right now.
Thanks.
What?
Um, I don't understand.
Two weeks ago, you said,
"come back in two weeks."
Why would you... why would you
say that if... if like, uh...
when what,
when I didn't mean it?
Because I wanted you
to get out of my face,
and that's what I'm asking
you to do right now.
Walk away, do not come back.
Your art is terrible;
Please don't buzz me again.
Uh, I see, thanks.
Ladies and gentlemen,
hermann haig.
Here, maybe you can sell it.
Sure, chief.
Stupid, stupid, stupid Herman.
Yeah, two weeks, come on by.
What is it?
128, 129.50,
135, 2, 275, 280, 280.
300.
300? This is a
one-of-a-kind work of art.
- 400.
- - 2,000.
2,000.
2,000, going once, going...
Sold.
Aw, man.
It's really quite exquisite.
Back there, I owe
you an apology.
I'm sorry.
You know, it'd be a shame if the
art world lost a
voice like yours.
Whoo! Yeah!
Yes!
Whoo!
Well, how did it go?
You're not dreaming.
I'm still here.
It was incredible.
You won't believe what happened.
Not only did the
piece sell, but guess
who wants to sign me
as her newest artist?
Did you get bigger?
Who wants to sign you?
Devora klein.
Devora klein!
That's great,
I knew you could do it.
It wasn't me, it
was what you gave me.
Thank you.
God, I still can't believe it.
I have more, you know.
You do?
Because, well, de... de... devora
wants to put me in a show.
And, well, if she
does that, then, uh,
I'm going to need
a lot more mobiles.
I have many, many more.
I get lonely here all by myself.
How about I help
you make mobiles,
and in return, all you have
to do is spend time with me?
That's it?
That's it. Partners?
Uh, yeah, yeah, partners.
If you had a hand, I'd shake it.
Why don't
we seal it with a kiss?
Think of all the incredible
art we could make together.
How was that?
Perfect.
All right, well
tell me some of
the bigger names.
Pollock, Warhol, Nagel.
Wait, you helped Nagel too?
Yeah, what can I say?
The Duran Duran guy?
Yes.
Who else?
It's not important.
Oh, hi.
I just came back
for my pie plate.
Oh, right, one sec, okay?
Here you go.
It was delicious.
- I'm so glad you liked it.
- - Yeah.
I'll make you another.
Oh, no, no, no,
no, no, that's okay.
It's no problem.
Hermann, I don't
mean to pry, but
is there someone else
staying here with you?
Hm?
Well, it's just that
I could have sworn
I distinctly heard
a female voice.
Uh, I'm the only one here.
It's just me.
Good.
That is a lovely dress.
Wow.
- You're back.
- Hi, uh...
I've been thinking
about our next piece all day.
Shall we get started?
Uh, yeah, um, I
thought I told you.
I'm going to Devora's tonight.
Yeah, she's got these fancy
new art collectors in town,
and, well, she said it'd be a
good idea if I met them, so.
I see.
You should be happy.
She's showing our piece.
It's a good thing.
I hope they like it.
We can work when you get back.
Yeah, um, I don't know
when I'm going to be back,
so you probably
shouldn't wait up, uh...
See ya.
Bye.
- Hermann.
- - Hi.
- Come on.
- Oh, okay.
Hermann, nice to meet you.
Hermann?
I have a present for you.
I guess I'll just
leave it outside.
Hermann?
I'm going to bring it inside
so... so nothing happens to it.
Okay, I'm coming in now.
Coming in...
A movie, right.
Will you excuse me?
Back off, Percy,
this one's mine.
You're excited?
I invited some of my
biggest collectors
to see your piece tonight.
Yeah, so don't blow it.
I just came by to
pick up my stuff.
I didn't know you
were having a party.
Your attention please?
Thanks.
This is a very
important moment for me
because the work
you're about to see
is from a man who
is proving to be
one of the most gifted
artists I've ever discovered.
It gives me great pleasure
to present to you...
Hermann Haig's "permission."
Hermann, I've never
seen anything like it.
They really like your piece.
What do you think of it?
What do I think?
I think I just
sold it for 50,000.
To who?
Them.
You know, when I made
it, I was thinking of you.
Well, whatever you're
doing, keep it up.
With something like
this, you've got
to strike while the iron's hot.
Well, you'll have to
do a one-man show.
- Really, me?
- Yeah.
How soon can you make four more?
- Uh, four?
- A month?
Uh...
I already sent out
the press releases.
Uh, yeah, I mean, I
think... I think I can.
Yeah? Because,
you know, you and I,
we could have a really
great future together.
They'll be ready in a month.
Good, we're going to make
a great team, you and I.
Tell me, hermann,
'cause I wanna know,
how does a guy like you get to
be so talented all of a sudden?
Aren't you going to
ask me how it went?
How did it go?
It was unreal.
All these fancy people there,
just... just to see my artwork.
And the way they reacted,
uh, you'll never guess.
Orgy?
How'd you know?
And she sold it.
Oh, god, she is so amazing.
She wants me to
have my own show.
Me!
Can you believe it?
Are you crying?
I was afraid.
I started thinking you'd
leave me, never come back.
You're not serious?
You don't know what it's like.
Before you, I was all
alone, withering away.
It was unbearable.
I won't go back
to that, not ever.
Look, I... I'm not leaving you.
Okay? I...
I could... I could
never leave you, okay?
Just a little more.
I'm trying.
Well, push harder.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
I don't know,
I just can't do this today.
But our deadline,
we're already behind.
I'm sorry, hermann.
Sometimes I just get blocked
up when I'm feeling lonely.
Even I need inspiration
once in a while.
But we're so close.
What if... is there
anything I can do?
Well, there is, actually.
At least, it would
put me more at ease.
What? Tell me.
I can't, not out loud.
You're joking, right?
No, that is... that is way too...
What?
I just... I just
think that we should
keep things between us
professional, all right?
Well then, I guess that's that.
So tell me, what's
devora going to say
when you go to her empty handed?
Who am I kidding?
I'm just the artist, right?
No, not like that.
Your shirt, take it off.
Now, kiss me.
Slow.
Touch me, slow.
Here you go.
How are the new pieces coming?
Fine.
"Art news nation" called.
They want to do an interview.
Okay.
Devora, have you ever gotten
involved with someone where
you're just a little bit unsure
that it's the right thing?
What do you mean?
Like you... you get mixed
up in a relationship, right?
And at first, it
seems so perfect.
But then...
Percy's been talking
to you again, hasn't he?
- No, no, no, no.
- Trying to steal you from me?
That's not it, it's, uh...
You want more
money, is that it?
I mean, I can write
you another check.
No, no, it... it's fine, okay?
Just... Just forget it.
Hermann, we've
come so far together.
You're a great artist,
and I sell great art.
Is that all we have?
I want to show you something.
What do you think?
What do I think?
Uh, well, I think a
three-year-old painted these.
I mean, they're not even
horrendous in an
interesting way.
They're... They're
horrendous-bad.
I mean, why would
you keep these?
Who's the artist?
Me.
Oh, I'm... I'm so
sorry, I didn't know, I...
no, you're right,
they're awful.
I know.
You don't know what it's like.
But when it comes to
selling other people's art,
I'm the best there is.
You have real talent.
I'd kill for that.
But all the talent in the world
won't get your artwork seen.
That's something I do.
Understand?
You and I...
We're meant for each other.
Good morning, hermann.
I wanted to surprise you,
but I guess you found me.
Relax, it's still me.
It's you, you know.
Your love is making me grow.
How wonderful.
Uh, uh, we should get started.
Are you sure
you wouldn't rather sleep in?
You got home pretty
late last night.
No, no, I'm... I'm fine.
Great.
I'll just get...
I'll just get changed.
Don't I
get a kiss good morning?
Well?
So, tell me, is
she better than me?
Is who?
You know who.
What are you
talking about, devora?
Uh, well, you know, we
had some... some things
to go over, some
details about the show.
I'll bet.
What does that mean?
Where is this coming from?
Do I need to draw you a map?
You know, I think I'm
just going to get some air.
Wait, don't go.
I'm sorry.
She doesn't care about
you, you know, not really.
I see what you're
doing, and it won't work.
She and I, we have
something, okay?
We have something special.
Hermann, what about us?
What about us, huh?
What about us?
What kind of relationship
could we possibly have?
You're not even fucking human.
I'm sorry.
I...
I gotta go.
Hi, Herm.
This isn't hermann.
Who is this?
His partner.
We need to talk.
Hello?
Come in.
The power's out.
Where are you?
Over here. Sit.
So, you're devora.
Where are you exactly?
Behind the wall.
You'll have to
forgive me, I'm shy.
Who are you?
I'm the source
of Hermann's inspiration.
You've seen his work
before he met me.
You must have noticed
the dramatic improvement.
Actually, I did
wonder about that.
I'll cut to the chase.
You make a killing
selling Hermann's art.
But if it weren't for
me, there'd be no art.
I have a proposition for you.
I'll make sure you get one
masterpiece after another.
All you have to do is
stay away from him.
Well, I'd love to,
but hermann needs me.
But in a way, I'm his muse.
Sorry, no deal.
You live here too?
Yes.
Ever think about moving?
No.
Apparently,
neither do the rats.
Feeling all right?
Devora? Devora!
Come on, devora!
Oh, hi.
Ow, uh, I must have dozed off.
Is your little girlfriend gone?
Girlfriend?
Hiding behind the wall.
I don't have a girlfriend.
Whoa.
I'm all right, really.
So that girl, she
doesn't make the art?
Never lays a finger on it.
Good.
- Hermann.
- Hey.
There's something you
need to know about me.
That woman in my apartment?
- She is your girlfriend.
- No, no.
Uh, she's not even a woman.
Look, I... I can't
explain it, okay?
She... it... it was
something I found, okay?
In the apartment, in the wall.
I know... I know it's
hard to believe.
But... but when you want
something so bad your whole life
and then... and then suddenly
it just gets handed to you,
you don't ask questions, okay?
You... you... you just take it!
Look, I don't make the
art, okay? I don't.
She does.
You think I'm crazy?
Actually, I believe you.
You do?
I didn't want you
to find out that I...
that I don't have any
really talent, you know?
That... that I'm just some...
failed artist?
Yeah, yeah, but don't you see?
You and I, we belong together.
I mean, that is, if
you still want me.
Yes, yes, yes, of
course I want you.
There's something I
gotta do, okay, right now.
Come on, come on!
Joel?
Don't even think about it.
It's got to be
done, Joel, okay?
You have no idea what
you're getting involved in.
You had your chance.
Turn around and walk away.
No, stop, don't hurt him!
You should be thanking me!
God.
Hermann, wait.
Hermann, what are you doing?
He was hurting you, I had to.
No, don't!
Can't you see she just
wants you for your art?
Can't you see that,
what she really is?
Bitch! Monster!
Don't be such a fool, Hermann.
She's using you..
We're in love.
Don't do this, I'm begging you.
Wait, remember
when we first met?
All you wanted was
to be an artist.
Remember, that was your dream.
What are you doing?
Transplanting her.
I already have the perfect
spot picked out in my gallery.
From now on, I'm
making my own art.
No!
Stop it!
Hermann.
I'm here.
It's bad, real bad.
No, it... it's fine.
It'll be fine.
I'll patch you up,
you'll get better.
Forget the mobiles.
It's not about that.
You mean so much
more to me than that.
I don't know why I
never said it before.
I need you to know that, okay?
I need you to know that.