[instrumental music]
[siren wailing]
[music continues]
[indistinct chattering on radio]
- Mostly cloudy,
with scattered showers
and thunderstorms developing..
- Big storm tonight.
Don't mean to pry,
but I can't imagine
what a girl like you
wants to do at the lots.
[intense music]
[gasps]
- Give me some money!
[indistinct mumbling]
- Animals.
[instrumental music]
[eerie music]
[cell phone keys beeping]
[phone ringing]
- Hello?
- Mom. Hi.
- You made it?
- Yup.
- Storm coming tonight.
- Yeah, I heard.
Can you put her on?
- Julia...she's asleep.
- Please, mom.
Can you please call her over
so I can tell her goodnight?
- Julia, don't think
about her tonight.
- Well, if she wakes up,
can you just please tell her
that I called?
- Okay.
- Don't forget.
- Focus on yourself.
I don't have to remind you
that this is your last chance
or they'll take Clara away.
- Yeah, I know that, mom.
- Remember your
breathing exercises.
- Yeah.
- I don't know how many more
opportunities you'll get.
- Yeah. Yeah, okay, mom.
I gotta go.
Alright, bye.
[doorbell buzzing]
- You're a student, correct?
- Yes, sir.
I'm gonna become
a nurse someday.
- Best of luck with all that.
Around here, you work
in the night shift.
2 guards man every shift.
1 guard on patrol duty,
the other on the screens.
- Wow. What is this place?
- The building was erected
during the big boom.
Assumption being
industry drives growth.
Growth brings up demand for more
affordable luxury housing.
Imagine living in a place
providing everything you need
for a comfortable life.
You'd never have to leave.
And as you know, boom became
bust, and here we are.
- What a waste.
- You have to be careful here,
Ms. Streak.
Things are starting to...
fall apart.
Ballroom, grand hall, gym
mail and storage rooms
plus a residential tower,
30 floors high.
As a patrol guard,
you make sure nobody gets in
nobody vandalizes the place,
nothing bad happens
to the structure...
and nobody steals anything.
- Does that happen?
- All the time.
Steal whatever they can
get their hands on.
We've been having issues
of vagrancy, tryin' to make
the place into a squat,
so don't let anyone in.
This job pays well for a reason.
The nights here
can be long...and dark.
Some of the lights are on timer,
so they turn off to save
on power.
The combination
can make some people...uneasy.
- I like the night.
- We've blanketed the entire
building with security cameras
so we only need two guards.
One on patrol and the other..
- In front of the screens.
Got it.
Where's the control room?
- Upstairs.
I see your partner's
already here.
This is Dennis Cooper.
He's been here since day one.
- Hi. Nice to meet you.
I'm Julia, but everybody
calls me Streak.
- That's great.
- Nice.
Cooper will take you
through the controls.
But I think you'll find
the system pretty intuitive
once you start using it.
You'll go on patrol
once every two hours.
Cooper will communicate with you
using this headset.
Packs a small camera
and a microphone.
Show us the feed, Cooper.
[keyboard keys clacking]
Simple enough?
Also, we've been having trouble
with electricity.
We lose a video feed
from time to time
so you'll have to throw
a breaker.
- Got it.
- You know what a breaker is?
- Yup.
- Don't forget the uniform.
That is the most important part
of this job.
- Have a great night.
- There is a locker room
in the back, to the right
if you wanna change there.
Unless you feel more comfortable
changing in here, which
I could probably make
an exception for that...tonight.
- I'm gonna go
to the locker room.
- Okay.
[door closes]
[instrumental music]
[thunder rumbling]
- This place is really big.
A person could spend
a lifetime in here.
- Well, most people don't last
more than a week.
- What's your story?
- What's my story?
My story. Um, let me see.
It's a very long, detailed
richly...boring tale.
However, let's start
with tonight's chapter.
I guess it starts out
that I'm sick and tired of Dixon
wheeling in some..
...local community college brat
and expecting me to entertain
them all night.
That's my story.
'Cause tomorrow or the next day
or possibly a week from now
but without question, it's going
to happen, you're gonna decide
that patrolling a big,
empty building every two hours
is not what was meant for you
and your life
and big aspirations.
You're then gonna quit.
Then Dixon's gonna bring in
someone who's just like you
and gonna sit
right in that chair
I'm gonna have
the same conversation
and be forced to babysit
that person all night.
- Really?
- No tips, either.
- This is gonna be
a long night.
- You have no idea.
Sorry, sweetheart.
Welcome to the big world
of security.
Excuse me. Time to lock up.
Lights out.
2, 3, 4. Ta-da.
[gulping]
[burps]
[clears throat]
- Gross.
- It's weird. That happens
every time I try to burp.
What are you, 24?
25? 23?
Alright, we're just
gonna stick with 24 then.
- What, are you
talking to me now?
- Tough. Right?
Bet you were a good student.
Little teacher's pet.
Am I right?
Fit. Like your arms.
You do a little
self-defense maybe?
Little karate?
Little, uh, tae kwon do?
Judo? Jiujitsu?
Jell-O wrestling?
Pillow fights?
[exhales heavily]
Kickboxing, maybe?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I do kickboxing.
Yup. You have to for this job.
- Ho-ho. Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
- Is that what Dixon told you?
I must've missed that one.
I can't kickbox.
Guess what?
You don't.
I don't think I've seen
one of these since 1982.
My grandma had one of these.
- Do not touch my stuff!
- That's quick...kickboxer.
[burps]
Where you goin'?
- Patrol.
- Not without this you're not.
Goes on like this.
[mouse clicking]
[clangs]
[beeps]
[rattling]
[clanging]
[mouse clicking]
Um..
...do you miss me yet?
- What are you doing?
- Me?
I'm not doing anything.
Just a little, uh
welcome ceremony,
a little initiation..
...to the security world.
[buttons clicking]
- Open the door, Cooper.
Cooper, this is not a game.
- Games?
I don't play games.
[breathing heavily]
[footsteps]
[indistinct whispering]
[whispering continues]
- Cooper, let me out!
Cooper, let me out
of the elevator!
Please, Cooper, let me out!
Please, Cooper!
Please open the door!
Cooper!
Open the door!
- Relax. I'm just testing
the cut-off switch.
- Please open the door! Cooper!
- Seems to be workin' fine.
[gasps]
[whirring]
[panting]
[exhales heavily]
[thunder rumbling]
[footsteps]
[instrumental music]
[music continues]
- I can see-e-e you-u-u.
- I can't believe how huge
and beautiful it is.
- That's what she said.
- This place is amazing.
- You wanna see something
even better?
- Why should I trust you
all of a sudden?
- 'Cause I'm all you got
tonight, babe.
Go over your left
and exit through there.
Then your right,
go down that corridor.
[music continues]
[dramatic music]
[panting]
[instrumental music]
[thunder rumbling]
- They really spared
no expense.
[thunder rumbling]
And nobody will live here?
- They never finished it.
- It's so dark in here.
Uh! What is that smell?
[dramatic music]
[screams]
Uh!
- First night,
you found an intruder.
Very promising, Ms. Streak.
- Jerk.
- This way.
- Hey, Cooper,
did you hear that?
- Hear what?
[intense music]
- Never mind.
[thunder rumbling]
[beeping]
Ah!
[huffs]
- Complimentary
first night meal. Enjoy.
- This looks like
hospital food.
- You know why hospital food
tastes the way it does?
- Why?
- 'Cause it makes you wanna
get out of the hospital.
Think about that.
- Uh, why are you
being so nice to me?
- I'm not being nice.
That's company policy.
In a few hours, your stomach's
gonna be grumbling
and you're gonna
wanna fall asleep.
You need that fuel.
- She's pretty.
Is that your daughter?
- Yup.
- Are you guys close?
- Hey.
Enough.
- You know,
I have a daughter, too.
- Good.
- Her name's Clara.
[keyboard keys clacking]
[computer beeps]
[beeps]
How come I can't get
441 on the screen?
- Because there is no 441.
- It says 441 right here.
- They never got around
to finishing it
before they ran out of money.
- Where's the circuit breaker
for the cameras?
- I said there's no 441.
It doesn't matter
what the blueprint says.
If anyone should know, it's me.
I've been here
since the beginning of time.
- Well, someone
should check it out.
- That's a good idea,
someone should do that.
So why don't you go down there?
Matter of fact, I'm telling you
to go down there
and don't come back
until we have 441 on the grid.
What are you waiting for?
[snapping fingers]
- Fine, I will.
- Ah-ah.
[door slams shut]
[sighs]
[eerie music]
- 4-4-1-4-3-7-8-5-2.
4-4-1-4-3-7-8-5-2. 4-4-1..
4-3-7...8-5-2.
Circuit breaker,
where are you?
4-4-1-4-3-7-8-5-2.
[Streak sighs]
4-4-1..
[clicks]
...4-3-7..
...8-5-2.
8-5-2.
[clicks]
[clangs]
- You happy now?
- Hello?
Is someone there?
Is somebody there?
- You talkin'
to the walls now?
That what you're doin'?
What are you doing?
[clanking]
- Nothing.
[pounding on door]
[indistinct whispering]
[dramatic music]
[door slams shut]
- Keeping busy?
- I heard something in there.
- Yeah, what's that?
- I don't know,
behind the door.
- There's nothing there,
I told you that.
- You knew about this,
didn't you?
Why are there cameras down there
and why were they turned off?
- Because it's
an unfinished section
and they told us
not to go down there.
- There's something there.
- Impossible.
- There.
Can you see it?
[buzzing]
Oh, God!
[panting]
I told you
something's not right.
[doorbell buzzing]
- No, we have company.
- What does he want?
- Probably wants shelter
for the night.
[sighs]
- What are we gonna
do about it?
- Well, one of us is gonna
have to go down there
and tell him to scram
before he breaks that window.
[no audio]
And I guess
that person will be me.
- I didn't realize.
- Save it.
- I'm coming with you.
- Oh, really? Now?
[pounding on door]
Sorry, buddy,
you gotta turn around.
- Please, man,
it's so cold out there.
I have no place to go.
- Can't do it.
- Come on, you have
all that space in there
and it just stands empty.
I just need one night inside!
- You gotta move on.
I told you.
The storm's gonna get worse.
Find some place.
- Please, I'm begging you, man!
I'm begging ya!
I.. Honest, I mean no harm.
I -- I -- I.. Honest to God.
I just, just need
one more night inside.
I'll be gone before sunrise.
No one will know.
Please, man, I'm begging ya!
I'm begging ya!
- It's not my call. Sorry.
Move. Streak, shut the door.
Now! Shut it, Streak!
- Come on!
Come on.
Hey, don't leave me here!
Come on, have some compassion,
man! Have a heart!
I'm gonna die out here tonight.
I'm gonna die out here
while you're inside!
And I hope you remember my face!
And I hope you think of me
before you go to bed at night!
- What's he gonna do?
He's an old man.
We can't leave him like this.
Have a heart, Cooper.
- I said no.
[intense music]
- Please!
- I'm letting him in.
- No, you're not.
- It's freezing out there.
- I'm not losing
my job for him.
- You don't have to worry.
- Thank you. Thank you so much.
Thank you.
[door slams shut]
Nice doggie.
It's good now.
Yeah.
I gotta..
...thank you.
- You can stay here.
- Oh, wow, yeah..
- But you have to leave
before sunrise.
- Okay.
- And don't go walking about.
The entire building's wired
with cameras.
We won't hesitate
to throw you out.
What's your name?
- Jim.
- Look, Jim, I don't know you
but I just put myself
out on a limb for you
and I need to know
you're not gonna screw me over.
- Cross my heart.
What's your name?
- Julia.
- I'm sorry about
earlier today, Julia.
I'm a good person, really.
I'm not a bad person.
- Prove it.
- Okay.
What's up, boy?
What are you thinkin'?
Huh?
[intense music]
[music on player]
[clanging]
[metal clanging]
[country music on speakers]
[clangs]
[grunting]
[sighs]
[clangs]
[door creaking]
[whooshing]
[instrumental music]
¶ But it's all in vain ¶
[whirring]
¶ What can I do.. ¶¶
[thuds]
[indistinct whispering]
- Hello?
[buzzing]
Is anyone there?
- What are you thinking, boy?
Is it time? Hmm?
Oh, yeah.
I think..
...it is-s-s.
Yeah.
[rustling]
Let's see. One, two, three.
And dump it back in there.
Let's see if we can do this.
One, two..
Oh, the hell with it.
Mmm.
[breathing heavily]
- Cooper, are you seeing this?
Cooper, are you there?
Hello, Cooper?
[water running]
- What are you saying, boy?
Oh, you wanna go out for a walk.
[barking]
You heard the nice lady
they'll throw us
back out into the storm!
[dog panting]
Dumb dog.
[dog barking]
Oh, we don't wanna do that.
Do we?
[breathing heavily]
[clanging]
[thud]
- Hello?
Is anyone there?
[rattling]
[clanging]
[eerie music]
Cooper, are you there?
[buzzing]
- I hear your plan, boy.
Yeah.
[dog barking]
[barking continues]
[music continues]
What is this place?
[dog barking]
[breathing heavily]
[dramatic music]
[indistinct whispering]
- Hello?
- This way.
[breathing heavily]
[yells]
[Streak gasping]
[intense music]
[breathing heavily]
[music continues]
[screams]
[doll laughing]
[Streak breathing heavily]
- Streak, you okay?
- Where the hell were you?
- I was, uh,
taking care of some, uh..
...some manly duties.
Where the hell
are you right now?
- I'm in a shelter downstairs!
Have you seen this place?
- It doesn't look like
anything to me.
- There's like
all these drawings!
It's like a dormitory
or something!
Did you know about this place?
- I was told not to go
in there, so were you.
Get back up here.
- There's something
still living here, I know it.
- Streak, did you shut
the shelter door behind you?
- No. Why?
- Because somebody did.
I told you not to let
that piece of shit in here.
- Oh, no, no!
Oh, no, no, no!
[breathing heavily]
[indistinct whispering]
It's not him.
- Oh, it's not? Really?
Who locked the door, the wind?
- Please just help me
find the exit.
[breathing heavily]
- Can you remember
how you came in?
- You can't tell me?
- There are no cameras there.
I told you that, remember?
I've no idea to know
where you are.
- It's too dark in here to see!
- Hold still for a minute.
And just relax.
Can you see anything?
[breathing heavily]
A light, an arch, a chair
something familiar
you remember on the way in.
- Everything looks the same.
- What was that?
- What?
Cooper, what?
- Nothing.
I -- I thought
that I saw something.
- Stop messing with me.
- I'm not messing with you.
Must have been
video interference here.
It went black.
- I'm in control of myself
and I won't have my mind
play tricks on me.
I'm in control of myself
and I won't have
my mind play tricks on me.
I'm in control of myself
and I won't have
my mind play tricks on me..
- Stop. Look. Go towards
the back and to the left.
I think if you go that --
- You're wrong.
I know where to go.
- What do you mean?
- I know where I am.
[keyboard keys clacking]
- Streak..
Streak, listen to me.
I -- I can't see you.
If you can hear me,
don't move
stay right where you are.
Do not move. I'm coming down.
- This way.
[dramatic music]
[screaming]
[music continues]
[gasping]
[panting]
- What happened?
You okay? You see?
That homeless piece of shit
that you let in locked you in.
- It wasn't him.
- Right.
We're gonna find him right now.
We're gonna escort his ass out.
He's gonna sleep tonight
in a puddle.
- There's something else
in there. It was not him.
- Something? What?
Hundred bucks says
he left his room.
Come on, let's go find out.
- Jim?
[thunder rumbling]
- He's not here.
And that's why you keep
this scum outside, understand?
- Where you going?
- I'm gonna try to catch him,
save our jobs.
[clicks]
- Come on, boy. Come on, boy.
Come on.
Take it easy, boy.
Come on, boy. Come on up.
Come on, boy. Come on, boy.
[whooshes]
Come on.
[clicking]
[whooshing]
[electrical buzzing]
[buzzing continues]
Boy?
Is that you?
Oh.. Boy?
What the hell?
[creaking]
What do you know? Yeah.
Yeah!
[dramatic music]
What the..
[screams]
[screaming]
[screeching]
[dramatic music]
[rustling]
[thunder rumbling]
- I can't breathe in this.
[keyboard keys clacking]
I'm locking this place up.
- Well, I can't find
this scumbag anywhere
and that's unacceptable.
Shit.
- Found it.
- Wellville, a center
for physically deformed
and mentally challenged
children.
Last week,
I received a phone call
from an anonymous source
complaining about
the treatment of the children
hospitalized here.
So I decided
to show up unannounced.
And what you're about to see..
...are some of the most
disturbing images...
...this reporter
has ever witnessed.
We were told to go
straight down to the basement
where the institute holds
some of its youngest patients
many of them orphans.
And what we found
was horrifying.
[shuddering]
[groaning]
[instrumental music]
Kids, some as young
as five years of age
left unattended for hours
in this grizzly basement.
We found one child
covered in his own feces
sitting alone
on the bathroom floor.
[child panting]
- We don't need to watch this.
- Wait.
- The man at the helm of this
institute, Dr. Thorndike
points a finger at the county.
- You have to understand
nobody else
wants these children.
- Well, it doesn't seem
that you want them either.
- We're low on staff.
We're low on budget.
- Then how do you respond
to the allegations
of malpractice?
- It's preposterous.
We have some of the best
and most qualified physicians
in the country.
- Dr. Thorndike, is it true
that some of your patients
have been victims of abuse
and neglect at this institute?
- Alright, that's it.
We're done here.
- So we leave today..
...but the children
stay behind
unable to cry for help
so we must cry for them.
I'm Warren Rawlings.
Back to you, Bob.
[instrumental music]
- These poor kids.
They probably
spent their life in there.
I could sense it,
they're still there.
- He's the one
who locked you in.
You got confused and scared.
You're a very confused girl.
- I'm telling you what I saw.
- Enough already. Enough!
I know your problem.
- What are you talking about?
[rattling]
You went through my stuff?
- Yeah, I did.
Because somehow something
wasn't just quite right tonight.
Something didn't smell right.
Because in all my years here,
one night shift with you
has created more havoc
than anything I've ever seen.
Did you not take your
three anti-psychotic pills
this evening?
- That's none of your business.
- Oh, it is now.
- Look, I'm not crazy.
My whole life
I've been able to sense things
that I can't describe.
And when I told
the doctor about it
he put me on these pills.
And if I don't take these pills
then they're gonna
take Clara away.
- Your daughter Clara?
You can't do this.
This job is not for you.
This is not right for you.
This building at night --
- I'm not crazy.
I am not crazy, Cooper.
I know what I saw.
Please, I am not crazy!
Look.
We gotta call him out of there
and then we've gotta
shut the door.
We can't let those kids out.
We've gotta
shut the door, Cooper.
Cooper, please, I'm begging you.
Please, we gotta shut the door.
- Because spirits can't travel
through doors?
Is that why?
- You don't understand.
I have seen some things
down there, Cooper.
I have seen things down there.
- You're gonna sit down.
You're not going anywhere.
- Why not?
- Because you're delusional,
that's why.
You've done enough tonight.
- Cooper, I --
- I'm not letting you
out of here.
- Why?
- Because you're not
thinking right.
Because you put me in jeopardy.
Because I need this job.
I don't have anywhere else
to go!
You can take your pill
and go fool someone else
like you fooled me!
I can't.
No pill...changes this.
Do you understand?
- I'm so sorry.
- Don't be.
I don't need your pity.
Are you fucking kidding me?
- They won't leave us alone
unless we shut the door, Cooper.
- Or what,
you're gonna stun me?
- I'm gonna do it.
- Put it down.
You're not gonna do it.
No, you're not,
because it's just gonna prove
that you're crazy and you're
gonna lose everything.
- Please, Cooper,
I'm begging you. Please.
- I'll go down.
I'll go down
and I'll shut the door.
Okay?
See? That's better.
- What are you doing? Cooper?
Cooper, no! Don't leave me
like this, please!
- I'm not taking any chances.
Can't trust you anymore.
- Please hurry, Cooper!
Please I..
Don't leave me alone!
Cooper.
- What?
- Don't take the elevator.
- Seriously?
[intense music]
[keyboard clacking]
[elevator whirring]
Oh, come on.
Streak, did you
touch anything up there?
- I'm not doing anything.
[clangs]
[elevator thuds]
[sighs]
- Goddamn generator.
- It's not the generator.
Maybe we should call someone.
- That's a good idea.
That way we can both be fired
and thrown out in the storm
with the homeless piece of shit
that you let in here.
Maybe you can tell 'em
your ghost stories
that'll amuse 'em.
I'm gonna try
to pry this thing open
and get to the breaker.
[grunting]
- Don't do it. It's not safe.
[intense music]
[whirring]
Cooper, it's closing.
Watch out!
[whirring]
- Uh!
- Cooper!
[whirring continues]
[clangs]
[intense music]
[panting]
[music continues]
[huffs]
Cooper, are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm alright.
You know, there's only one thing
I wanna know
that I don't understand.
- What's that?
When you were down
in that shelter
how did you know
where the entrance was?
How did you know
which way to go?
- I don't know.
[indistinct whispering]
- Did you hear that?
- Hear what?
Oh, my God.
Cooper, you gotta
get out of there.
[dramatic music]
- Well, can you see something?
[intense music]
What did you see?
- The kids.
They're out.
[indistinct whispering]
Cooper, can you hear me?
- There's no such thing
as ghosts.
Or your mumbo-jumbo
getting in my head.
Just had a few drinks.
[indistinct whispering]
Wait.
Yeah.
Well, let's get this over with.
- In here.
[dog panting]
- I can hear the dog.
Hey, boy.
[whistling]
Come on out now.
Come on, boy. Come here now.
Goddammit.
[whistles]
I'm not going in there.
Hey!
If you're in there..
...it's your last chance.
I'm shutting this door.
[wheelchair rattles]
[wheelchair rattling]
[grunts]
- Close the door!
- What's going on?
What's going on?
[wheelchair rattling]
Ow!
- What are you doing?
Don't go in there!
[indistinct whispering]
- I can't control it.
- Cooper, no!
- I can't stop!
- No!
Cooper, can you hear me?
[panting]
No, no, no.
Oh..
Please.
[grunts]
Come on!
[dramatic music]
Come on! Please, please.
Uh..
Open. Please open.
Please, please, please.
[music continues]
[grunts]
[panting]
[indistinct whispering]
[flashlight clicks]
[wheel rattles]
[footsteps thumping]
[breathing heavily]
[dramatic music]
[computer beeping]
[music continues]
[static]
[thud]
- Who's that?
Hello?
- Are you one
of the grown-ups?
[footsteps thumping]
[panting]
[instrumental music]
[footsteps thumping]
[panting]
[chair screeching]
[intense music]
What are you doing here?
[indistinct whispering]
[chairs screeching]
[intense music]
[screaming]
- Cooper, can you hear me?
[panting]
Hi, boy! You're a good boy!
You're gonna help me!
You're gonna tell me
where he is, right?
[intense music]
Come on, come on.
Go! Go!
Come on, let's go!
[panting]
[breathing heavily]
[dog panting]
Cooper, are you there?
Cooper.
Cooper?
Cooper, can you hear me? Cooper?
[dramatic music]
[crying]
[screaming]
No!
[music continues]
Oh, please!
Please don't do this to me!
Please!
[crying]
- Julia?
[intense music]
They're never gonna
let you leave.
- Who are they?
- My friends.
- Why? Why would they
do this to me?
- They don't like grown-ups.
- Is it because of this place?
- Do you want me to show you?
[dramatic music]
[boy groaning]
[music continues]
[girl crying]
[shuddering]
[child screaming]
[groaning]
[indistinct shouting]
[screaming]
[instrumental music]
Some of us tried to run away.
[siren wailing]
[music continues]
- Where are they taking them?
[water running]
[instrumental music]
[music continues]
- The grown-ups lock them
in here to keep them quiet.
They drank the bad water.
When the grown-ups arrived,
it was too late.
- They all died?
- Except for one.
- Mama! Mama!
Mama!
- No! Clara!
- No!
- No! No!
No, my baby!
- Don't do it!
It's not her.
No!
[instrumental music]
[dramatic music]
[Cooper grunts]
[Streak gasping]
We gotta get outta here!
- Let's go, Cooper!
- Ah!
- No! Cooper!
Cooper, no! No! No!
No, Cooper!
Don't let go! No! No!
- Go!
- Cooper! Cooper!
- Don't let go!
- Go! Get..
- Cooper! No!
Cooper!
No!
No! No!
[crying]
[dramatic music]
[panting]
[rattling]
[music continues]
[rattling continues]
[whooshing]
[crying]
[screaming]
[dramatic music]
[rattling]
[whooshing]
[rattling continues]
[grunts]
[intense music]
[thud]
[screaming]
[crying]
[thud]
No! Please, let me out! Please!
Please let me out!
Please! Please!
Please, let me out.
Let me out! Please!
Please let me out.
Please. Please.
[instrumental music]
What, what do you,
what do you want?
[crying]
Let me see.
It's not your fault.
[music continues]
[crying]
It's not your fault.
I love you
just the way you are.
[music continues]
I'm gonna go now, okay?
Okay?
Okay.
[music continues]
[door creaking]
[monitor beeping]
[instrumental music]
[beeping continues]
[beeping intensifies]
[flatlines]
- This patient's been with us
since she was a child.
Stuck in a coma.
Time of death, 8:34.
I'm sorry for your loss,
Mr. Streak.
[music continues]
- I'd like a moment
with my daughter.
- Of course.
Take all the time you need.
Follow me, please.
[music continues]
[intense music]
[panting]
[crying]
[gasping]
[instrumental music]
[music continues]
[eerie music]