Everyone, please.
Please.
It's my unfortunate responsibility
to share with you some terrible news.
It seems that over the weekend,
your fellow student, Marina Mills,
committed suicide.
Is it true that she filmed it
on her webcam?
One of your classmates died and all you
care about is whether you can see it?
Apparently there was a video uploaded
to the university website this morning.
Some of you were crafty enough
to grab it before we could take it down.
I urge you not to... To watch it.
Anyone caught sharing it
will be suspended.
Period. No discussion.
Were any of you friends with Marina?
Or have any info
that can shed light on this tragedy?
Well, if so, see me after class.
Liv, this video's so cute!
- So not scared.
- Yeah, right.
So good.
- Hey.
- Hey. Hey.
- Hello.
- Someone didn't come home last night.
- Yeah, again.
So are you guys, like,
monogamous now or what?
- Liv, it's not a dirty word. Jesus.
- I know.
Clearly, I'm just jealous,
you know, being dumped.
You were not dumped.
You knew him for one day.
It was an amazing day.
Mmm, yeah. Yeah, I like that. Yeah.
- Eww!
- Oh, my God.
- It's disgusting...
- Oh, no.
So you're in a... In a relationship?
Oh, here we go.
No, it's super cool, it really is.
I just, you know,
love all these precious little updates
about you and Doctor Surfboard.
- Good for you.
- Oh, shut up.
What do I look like?
I'm a sophisticated lady.
Wine and dine me.
Another argument
that Internet Addiction Disorder
doesn't belong in the DSM
is that it's frequently
symptomatic of other disorders,
depression, anxiety, trauma.
Often, it's an escape from things
we don't wanna deal with,
from our everyday lives...
...to things far, far worse.
Though the most common disorder
might just be
that we have too much time on our hands...
Play it cool.
- Wait a few days.
- He already knows I'm not cool.
I think we might have an excellent example
of Internet Addiction Disorder
right here in class.
Aside from Miss Woodson and Miss Mathison,
does anyone else here experience symptoms?
- Look at that. That's a nice one.
- I love it.
Oh, I really like that filter.
- I can show you how to do it.
- Look at Kobe.
Jesus. When's he gonna get over you?
Such a creeper.
- He is not a creeper.
- Ooh.
Who's that?
A girl in my class.
Zero friends.
How is that not, like, super weird?
Maybe she just started
her profile or something.
Is she, like, 12-years-old?
Huh.
I think she's really talented.
I like it.
You like it when she rips
her hair out during class?
Oh, come on.
Dude, I literally saw her
pull an eyelash out today.
No. It's a condition.
It's called trichotillomania.
You would know all about it if you cracked
open a textbook every once in a while.
- Owned!
- Oh, whatever.
I'm actually changing majors next year.
Oh, yeah? And the year after that?
- Owned!
- Come on.
- Twofer.
- Whatever.
What you making? Is that seafood curry?
- That looks good.
- What? Seafood curry?
No, this is paella...
Well, my dad was a psychiatrist,
so I guess I, you know,
- wanna follow in his footsteps.
- That's nice.
Mmm.
Are you doing it for credit or are
you just... You really wanna do it?
I'm not sure.
I just transferred.
- I... I don't know anyone yet.
- Well, now you know me.
Are you in the dorms?
My friends and I,
we just got an apartment.
It's amazing, but we're definitely
not getting any work done.
- Too many friends.
- Exactly.
I'll see you around campus.
Bye, Laura.
Hmm.
I thought med students had homework.
You're one to talk.
What? I'm studying.
Internet Addiction Disorder.
- And you're your own case study.
- Exactly.
What's the deal with this girl?
I don't know. I think she's lonely.
She gonna be your friend
or your first mental patient?
She'd be my second mental patient.
She's going through every post
I've ever made in my life.
Oh, whoa. She's crazy.
Look what she just sent me.
Wait, I wanna see.
Oh.
Really, you guys are gonna
live happily ever after together.
- Oh, my God.
- Nice.
Who is this person?
I don't know.
Dude, scroll down.
I wanna see her timeline.
Further.
Whoa.
Jesus.
No wonder this girl's
giving you nightmares.
Jesus.
- OK.
- Oh, my God.
Laura, this girl isn't right.
Why are you hanging out with her?
I was just trying to be nice.
God, I can't believe
you invited her to your birthday.
No, no, no, no, I didn't invite her.
She invited herself.
What was I supposed to say?
Erm, how about something like "Fuck, no"?
- Yeah, that sounds about right to me.
- You can't say that to someone.
- Oh, yeah, it goes like this.
- Yes, you can.
It goes like this. "Hey, Laura,
can I come to your birthday?"
"Fuck, no." There you go.
Laura, finally.
Happy birthday.
You look so pretty.
- Thanks, Marina.
- You get my messages?
Yeah. How can I miss them?
Are you mad at me?
Did I do something wrong?
No, I'm not mad at you. I'm just...
- I'll see you in class tomorrow, OK?
- But what about tonight?
Aren't you celebrating with your friends?
Er... It's just Tyler and I tonight.
We're going out to dinner,
so just the two of us.
But you barely know her.
Isn't tonight just you and your friends?
I know, I know.
I just feel, you know, icky lying about it.
Well, you don't look very icky to me.
Mmm!
All right, go ahead.
Hi. Hey.
Hi, Mom.
- Hey, happy birthday.
- Hey.
I've been trying to get
your mom as drunk as possible.
You, beautiful guy,
you need to get drunk immediately
so we know what you're made of.
Happy birthday!
This is gonna be... A good time...
Yeah!
Yeah, it's literally her!
That was our inspiration.
And the last reason, no matter what,
that you always find
some crazy way to make me feel better.
Aww.
Wait, wait, wait, to my little green bean
who makes me so proud every day,
and who made her father so proud
every single second.
Oh, Mom.
All right, I'm gettin' in,
I'm jumping in this little love boat.
- No, I'm going, I'm going, OK?
- Oh, no.
Er... This is... This is to us.
A wonderful evening.
To the future, to success.
And you shut up, you drunk floozy.
And then, this is also to, just to you,
to happy birthday.
- Thanks, guys.
- Cheers.
- Hey, Laura. How are you doing?
- Hey. How are you?
- Good. Good.
- That's good.
I thought we were friends.
Marina, what are you,
what are you talking about?
I saw you with everyone.
Your birthday dinner. I saw it.
Marina, I'm sorry.
I... I didn't mean to hurt your feelings.
Can we talk about this later? OK?
I had a present for you.
I worked on it for two weeks.
Two weeks?
You've barely known me for two weeks.
You're a fucking liar
just like everyone else!
Why did you accept my friendship?
You didn't have to do that!
Get off me.
You have any idea how it feels
to be alone?
Completely alone?
Get off me, you freak!
Oh, God.
Laura, you didn't do anything wrong.
This chick is just damaged.
You weren't there, Tyler.
It's not your fault.
Baby, I'm really sorry, I gotta get back
to cutting up dead people.
OK.
She's trying to face-chat me.
What do I do?
Don't take the call.
- Seriously.
- Fine, all right.
I'll talk to you later.
OK. Bye.
Liv?
Hmm.
Are you OK?
Go to bed.
Remind me after class to tell you a story.
Please. Everyone, please.
It's my unfortunate responsibility
to share with you some terrible news.
It seems that over the weekend,
your fellow student, Marina Mills,
committed suicide.
How'd it go?
Fine.
I just told them she was
stalking me and kind of went crazy.
Hey, don't beat yourself up about it.
- That girl was completely nuts.
- She needed help, though.
Yeah, like, serious help.
Not from a sophomore in Psych 201.
Look on the bright side. Might be able
to get out of class for the funeral.
God.
No, no, no. There's not gonna be
a funeral, there's no body.
What do you mean?
Cops were at my dorm this morning and...
They don't know where she did it,
but it wasn't there.
I heard she hasn't swiped her key card
since last weekend.
And that's not what freaks me out.
What freaks me out,
is that they don't know
who this girl even was.
Her, uh, contact info,
her social security,
it's all been deleted
from the school database.
They don't even think
that Marina Mills was her real name.
- Are you serious?
- You all right?
That's weird.
You're killing my cheeseburger vibe.
- Oh, my God.
- What's going on?
Why are you watching this?
- Who sent you this crap?
- She did.
- She's dead.
- I know.
Again, you'll have 60 minutes.
This is an actual case study,
a very challenging one.
Oh, my God.
God.
Is that the video? I thought you said
it was in your messages.
You posted it?
No, no. Someone did. I didn't.
And they tagged all my friends.
Laptops away, Miss Woodson.
Why would they think I did that?
I would, I would never do that.
- Did you try changing your password?
- Yes, yes. I tried everything.
- She's even back in my friends list.
- Unfriend that dead bitch.
I can't.
So, according to you, Miss Woodson,
this video just magically appeared
on your timeline this morning?
- Do I have that right?
- Why would I do this?
There must be some reason
this girl burned that picture of you.
Look, Laura, we know
that you're a great student,
but multiple students
reported you harassing Marina.
No. She was the one harassing me.
She was obsessed with me.
Laura, no one's saying it's your fault
that Marina took her life.
We're looking into everything.
But in the meantime, Laura,
if you can't delete that video,
you're gonna have to delete your profile.
Hey, one more thing. Any idea where
this girl might have torched herself?
No.
No, you're not listening to me.
I can't delete this video.
I can't even delete my account.
Like I said, this isn't a call centre.
OK, well, what about the dead girl
I can't unfriend?
Can you do something about that?
- Ma'am, I'm not seeing this profile.
- What? I just saw it.
Is there anyone else I can speak to?
I'm afraid they'll just tell you
the same thing.
What's next?
Kobe, I know you're in there.
I can hear your stupid game.
That was a nice video you posted.
Yeah, that's what I'm here about.
Wow.
You're her only friend.
- How special is that?
- Shut up.
Christ, someone's still uploading things.
That... That's intense.
I fucking love it.
All right. OK, let's take
a little peek behind the curtain.
What?
You have no idea how crazy that is,
do you?
OK.
Look at that. Oh, that...
That is what code normally looks like.
Not this.
I can't even copy this.
This isn't, this isn't code.
Well, what is it?
I don't know.
Wait, wait. Can you go back?
Just stop looking at that girl's profile.
Just stop thinking about her.
She killed herself. End of story.
She burned and hung herself
in front of her laptop.
Who does that?
Is this gonna be a thing now,
you and Kobe hanging out in his dorm room?
Is that really
what you're thinking about right now?
Yeah. I'm thinking about us.
What's wrong with that?
He's just a friend. You know that.
Does he?
It's called cyber stalking for a reason.
They can't bother you
if you're not online.
Uh, yeah.
Get me some of those, uh,
chocolate macadamia crisp thingies.
No, they're not, uh...
Chocolate potato chips.
They're like cookies.
Like, uh, crackers, kind of.
Just ask the guy there.
I go there all the time. The white
chubby kid who loves chocolate.
Babe, you're not chubby.
But you're very fussy. My God.
I'm not being fussy. I'm on my period
and chocolate makes me feel better.
Isabel?
Hello?
Shit.
Jenn?
Hello?
Kobe?
Hey, guys, this isn't funny.
Seriously.
Guys?
Koobes, come on, man.
What the hell?
What...
What the f...
No. No, no, no. No.
Ugh.
No!
OK, so she's barely talking right now.
They're gonna keep her overnight,
maybe longer.
You can see her if you want.
Listen...
I didn't know Gustavo that well.
Was he on something?
No.
I saw the medical report.
It is insane.
Please, just leave.
Sweetheart.
This is all her fault.
She's not herself, Laura.
No. Gus wasn't himself.
He was having nightmares.
So am I.
You're scaring us, Izz.
What are you talking about?
Laura knows.
She knows.
It doesn't feel real.
Promise me you won't look
at that girl's profile today.
You're driving yourself crazy.
Delete your account.
Seriously.
You want Isabel to see that?
- Liv, you know I can't.
- I don't care how.
Just do it.
Fuck.
Even if it's not you behind these posts,
I'm getting a lot of pressure
from the students.
As long as the posts are up,
I have no choice but to suspend you
for the rest of the semester.
Mom, you don't always have
to call me on FaceTime, you know.
- Why didn't you call me?
- I'm sorry.
I... I didn't want you to worry, OK?
I'm coming to pick you up.
I want you home.
No, look... Look, I'll call you later.
I promise, OK?
Look at that.
What the hell?
Yeah. She friended him
right before he died.
And there's something else.
- Jesus, Kobe...
- I don't want you to watch it.
I want you to listen.
What is that?
I don't know, I think it's wasps.
She's got black wasps
all over her profile.
I did some research, and, um,
some people associated them with evil.
They say they appeared
wherever witches lived.
That they'd, like, follow them around
and protect them.
Jesus.
Who was this girl?
Do you think you could
get us into her room?
Come on.
Not much into fashion, was she?
Do you even know what you're looking for?
Well, just anything.
Oh, hey, hey. Look, look, look.
- That's her.
- Yeah, and who are these two?
Can you find what school this is?
If it's ever been online, yeah.
Are you the young lady who called?
Marina's friend?
Yes.
How close did you say you were again?
I was just getting to know her when she...
I didn't even know her real name.
Nedifar.
Marina Nedifar.
Do you know what happened to her parents?
I wouldn't know anything about that.
She came to us as a ward of the state.
Poor girl. She had such
a rough go of things here.
She was always very sensitive,
always alone,
fleeing into her little fantasy worlds.
And she found some dark corners online,
things no child should see.
Sometimes she would just stare
at the computer for hours.
Nothing on the screen at all.
Just her own reflection in the darkness.
The kids became terrified of her.
They said she gave them nightmares.
Get off me! Don't touch me!
Get off me! Get off me!
Fuck!
Jesus!
The two boys in the photo,
they were found dead near Saddle Mills
with their faces mutilated.
- They were swarmed by black wasps.
- What?
Tyler, I know you could get in trouble
for this, but, please, can you...
Can you access her records somehow,
like a family contact or a last address?
Something?
- We don't even know her last name.
- Nedifar.
Marina Nedifar.
Laura?
Hello?
Is anybody here?
Hello!
This is not real. This is not real.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
This is not real.
This is not real! No!
Miss Woodson?
Hello?
She rips out her own hair
before she slits her throat.
Now, I've been on this job 25 years,
and that's a first for me.
There some shitty new drug
we don't know about?
They never took anything.
What I want to know is, where you got
the elevator footage that you posted.
For the last time,
I'm not posting any of this.
Well, the good news for you is
we can't link your IP address
to any of these videos.
We couldn't find any address at all,
which doesn't make any sense,
unless you're familiar
with our IT department.
It all has to do with this girl.
You really know a lot of dead people,
Miss Woodson.
This is not real!
I don't think this was a suicide, Laura.
I think it was a ritual.
Erm, that, what you're looking at here,
these are, these are black mirrors.
They've been used in the occult
for thousands of years.
And they say that if you,
if you stare into it,
you can communicate with some other side.
It's called scrying.
But sometimes these witches,
if they were being hunted,
if they didn't have any other...
Any other way out,
they would hang and burn themselves
in front of a black mirror
and become something else.
You call it whatever you want,
an evil spirit...
Erm, a, a demon.
Point is, it's how
they got revenge on people.
Possessing them and, and
haunting them and killing them.
How'd they ever stop it?
It says they had to find
the original mirror,
the one they burnt themself in front of,
and destroy it.
You mean... Her laptop.
It was her black mirror.
We need to find out
where she killed herself.
What?
I mean, there...
There has to be something here.
You know, something that can help us.
I think I'm going home.
I can't handle this.
I'm so sorry for everything.
Please don't go.
I'm sorry.
I can't.
- Way to pay your respects!
- Seriously. You're disgusting.
You're late.
Why is everyone talking about you?
What have you done to this girl?
I haven't done anything to her!
She just...
Attached herself to me.
Now everyone thinks that...
Please, I want you home, baby.
You're coming home with me.
Well, I can't, I can't.
I have to stay and figure it out.
Figure what out?
...others suffered serious injuries.
Police have a suspect in custody,
but are not releasing any information
until they complete their investigation.
Moore's Grove.
It's a deserted farm town
about two hours away.
There was a fire there 20 years ago.
It's some weird commune.
Marina's mother, Ada Nedifar, lived there,
until somebody burned
the whole place down.
What?
They kept some...
Husk of her body alive
until Marina was delivered.
She was alone in the womb for months.
Jesus. She was always alone.
Do you think this is where
she went to kill herself?
I mean, it's the only lead we have.
What's going on with her profile?
What's that on there?
Hey, it's Olivia. Leave me a thing.
Something's wrong. Something's wrong.
Stop right here.
Stop right here and let me out.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God.
Olivia! Olivia!
Olivia!
Get out, get out. Help her!
- Help her!
- Help me.
She's stable. That's what matters.
Thank you so much, Doctor.
I appreciate it.
She's stable.
She might actually make it through this.
Even if she does...
Marina's never gonna stop.
Shit.
Just... Just stay here.
Stay with Liv. Please.
Don't let her be alone.
Where are you going?
Whoa.
Someone had a rough day.
What happens if there are still
people living there?
I mean, what is this place now?
I don't know.
No matter what, I'm finding that laptop,
I'm gonna fucking smash it.
- Kobe...
- Yeah?
- Thanks for coming with me.
- Who says I'm doing it for you?
Where the hell are you?
The cops are asking me
a million questions.
I'm... I'm going to Moore's Grove,
I'm sorry.
Don't go there alone.
I... I'm not alone. I'm...
I'm with Kobe.
I'm coming to meet you.
So, where is she?
I don't know, man. Bad reception.
- Yeah.
- All right.
Keep trying.
Shit.
- Charming.
- Yeah.
Thanks.
Shit. There's no service.
What are you so fucking
nervous about? You're gonna be fine.
What are you talking about?
You said she wants to make you lonely.
If that's true, then you are
the only one that's safe.
Oh, hey, sweetheart.
I said no.
No Chinese food.
Mmm-mmm, no.
No, no, no. I said no Chinese.
No Chinese. I said n...
Sure, yeah. No, I mean, we...
We could have Chinese. I...
From down...
No, down... The one by the...
Yeah, I'll call you back.
Please, please, please.
No, I don't want to die.
Please.
Oh, my God.
Really?
Laura?
- Kobe?
- What?
She's not here.
Did you check the basement?
What basement?
Kobe?
Kobe.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
She can't make you lonely if you're dead.
Laura!
Laura?
Hey, it's Laura. Leave a message.
What do you mean,
you don't know where she is?
What happened back there?
Hey, dum-dum, I'm fucking talking to you!
What happened?
Listen to me. If you touched her,
I'll fucking kill you.
Now where the hell is she?
She's absolutely fine!
We are completely fucked.
She's just peachy.
Tyler.
Laura, thank God.
I thought something happened to you.
I... I just texted you an address.
Laura...
- The factory at Saddle Mills.
- I can't hear you. You're breaking up.
Tyler?
Are you sure you don't want me
to take you to a hospital?
Take me to the factory.
Still think we can beat this, don't you?
Shut up, man.
Seriously.
You got no idea what we're dealing with.
I do. I saw where we're headed.
- Shut up, man!
- I fucking saw it!
- Shut up!
- You tell me you're going to die for her!
Cos we've all been dying for her!
Stay in the car, man.
Mom?
Laura, where have you been?
I can't reach you.
Mom, are you OK?
I'm seeing things, Laura.
I keep seeing that girl.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
What's happening to us?
Listen to me. I'm not going to let
anything happen to you.
I'm going to sort this out somehow.
I'm going to stop this somehow.
Mom?
- Mom? Mom!
- I want to protect you.
Mom!
Laura?
Laura!
Tyler.
I was so worried about you.
Laura? Hey.
Laura.
Look at me.
My mom, she's...
Jesus.
What happened to you?
Hi.
What do you want from me?
What else do you want from me?
I just want to be friends, Laura.
Best friends.
Forever.
Laura.
Come to me.