Subtitles by explosiveskull
Are you okay?
What do you think it's
gonna be like out there?
It'll get back to normal.
You'll see.
How long
were you infected?
Four years.
Did you have to be
potty-trained again?
Are you having
any violent impulses?
No.
Any nightmares?
Good.
They're there to remind
you what you did.
The suffering you caused.
The nightmares mean there might
be something human left.
Makes you wonder about those
that don't have them, huh?
You'll report to me
every week.
Lateness will not
be tolerated.
Skipping work
will not be tolerated.
Anti-social behavior
Basically you do
what I say
and your life will be..
...better.
Your sister-in-law,
Abigail Reynolds
has agreed
to take you in.
I didn't put
in a request.
Charlie Three Three Bravo,
this is..
Not everyone gets
to go home, Senan.
You should be grateful.
Bus ready to depart. Out.
Close the gate.
Delta Echo One Zero.
Bus passes,
checkpoint four. Over.
Charlie Three Three Bravo
this is Charlie
Two One Alpha.
- The last bus is loading.
- Get on the bus quickly.
- Ready the gate. Over.
- Single file.
Take your seats.
Charlie Three Three Alpha.
Transport departing
in two minutes. Out.
The cure was supposed to
be some sort of great hope
but things are
just gettin' worse.
That's not fair.
My daughter was released.
Whatever she did she can't
hurt anyone anymore.
People need to give
them a second chance.
We've given them
every chance.
They're not integrating. No
wonder crime's on the rise.
They're not
like us anymore.
They would if they were
given some choices
instead of being treated like
they were still infected.
Have you seen the news?
The violence?
The vandalism? There's
something wrong with them.
They're not human.
They don't, they don't
have a worry.
They're just scum.
Scumbags! Murderers!
Scum! Scum! Scum!
Welcome to the
accommodation center.
For those of
you going home
please make your way
to the left.
Which is my right.
Make your way
to my right.
Which is your left.
Left is home.
Senan.
You're not human!
Don't tell her.
We need to look out for
each other out here, okay?
Keep it moving, people.
Thank you.
Through that door,
please.
Don't stop. Keep going,
please. Through the door.
What are your thoughts on the
release of the Third Wave?
I think we can't
take any more.
I think the First Wave
and the Second Wave
have been
a fucking disaster.
No one wants them here.
Not much against them.
Just... just no craic.
- Yeah.
- You know what I mean?
They just mope around.
Bit of a hum
off them, to be honest.
Oh, shit!
My uncle came back
in the First Wave.
And how is he now?
He killed himself
last year.
UN's pullin' out. Who the
fuck is gonna stay put?
They're out there,
right now.
Infected, Cured,
they're all the same.
Wipe the fuckin' lot of them
out, that's what I say.
The government now face
a very difficult dilemma
of what to do with
the 25% of infected
who remain resistant
to the cure.
I mean, what they did..
I mean..
How do you get over that?
Repent!
Hop on.
Ready, activate. Go!
Whoosh!
Is this it? Is this
all your homework?
Hmm. Great job.
You don't even need me.
Hi.
I don't have to stay.
It's what.. It's what
Luke would have wanted.
Besides... technically
it's your house.
It hasn't changed at all.
I was... gonna hire
an interior designer,
but, um..
They all got eaten.
Sorry.
I thought that maybe if you made
it you would have gone home.
Cillian was born here.
And only uninfected US
nationals are considered.
I guess we're a risk.
Did they give you a job?
There was a..
...an opening
at the treatment center.
Why would you
wanna stay there?
It's just being
a porter again.
Luke always said you were
wasting your time with that.
Were you with him?
At the end?
We got separated.
You wanna go say hi?
Hey.
Are you one
of the Cured?
Yeah.
Will you be sick again?
I don't think so.
Is it nice to be back?
Yeah. It is.
Make your way to the
nearest evacuation point.
- Abbie! Abbie!
- Even if a loved one.
Make your way to the nearest
evacuation point.
Luke.
Luke!
We have to go.
Abbie knows what to do.
No!
Senan!
Run!
Do you have
what it takes to join
the Irish Defense
Volunteers?
Well, call..
Hi, Dad.
They have me working
as a cleaner.
It's ridiculous.
I thought maybe..
...you could put in a good
word at some firms you know.
Get me back
in the courtroom.
Please, Dad.
Mum wouldn't want this.
Don't you dare
mention her.
I saw what you did to her.
You're a monster.
Dad..
This is Foxtrot
Sierra Nine Two.
There's been another
attack on a Cured. Over.
November Oscar 64
this is
Papa Golf Twenty-Two.
Perimeter is secure. Out.
Twenty-six, seven..
Sierra Two One,
UN withdrawal
commencing at
1400 hours.
You're over there.
You must be the help.
She one of the Resistant?
What do you think?
Do you have any
medical training?
I was a porter.
Jesus Christ!
They take away
my staff and give me
a fucking trolley pusher.
Hold her arm.
Are you here to help me or not?
Hold her fucking arm!
Good girl.
She's not attackin' me.
It's the same reason you
can't get chicken pox twice.
Once infected, your cells retain
a trace of the Maze virus.
She thinks
you're one of them.
- Where are the others?
- I don't have access any more.
They've allowed me to
continue caring for her.
She's all that matters.
We have to cure her.
How could you
take one in? Huh?
Please, this
isn't the place.
They're murderers,
the lot of them.
Come on, love,
now's not the time.
Back off.
Murderers!
Can I make Senan
lunch tomorrow?
What do you
wanna make him?
If it's peanut butter
and chocolate chip..
...and I'm gonna
cut it in half.
Despite condemnation
from around the world
the Irish government
will commence
the humane elimination
of the resistant 25%.
The Taoiseach has called
it an act of mercy
insisting the hope
of refining the cure
is no longer a reality.
You.
- Hmm?
- You.
- He's the king.
- Gosh.
Can't we work
together, maybe?
Okay.
Cool.
I was in prison.
This is worse.
We're treated
like lepers.
It's right that
they're scared, though.
I mean.. What we did..
Why?
Why is it right
that they're scared?
They're not
the ones living here
having their every
move monitored.
We need to march.
We need to stand up
and say..
You didn't tell her.
You were right to lie.
They're all the same when
they know the truth.
They just want us
to continue
killing ourselves,
and solve the problem..
Did you see them?
The Resistant
don't attack us.
They think
we're still infected.
What does that mean?
Means we're safer
with them than the rest.
Move.
You've been
skippin' work.
I'm not a cleaner.
You know..
...I knew people
like you..
...before the outbreak.
They thought the world
was theirs on a platter.
Lookin' down on
the rest of us.
But here... now..
...I'm in charge.
I decide whether your life
is happy or miserable.
You just have to
learn to obey.
- Is that it?
- No.
Stop harassing
your family.
They don't want you back.
Get the fuck back.
It's not your world
any more.
He's awake!
It's just kids.
We've been through worse.
They suit you.
His clothes.
Where were you
last night?
I had to go see
a friend.
I have to go.
Smile, Cillian.
- We love you, ma.
- Smile!
- Hi.
- Hm.
He suits you, yeah?
- Yeah!
- Cute.
Oh, my God, that
toy is gonna be
the death of me.
- It's trippy, isn't it?
- It is a bit, yeah.
Abbie. How's it going?
Did you get my footage?
The withdrawal's
started already
whatever talks they're
having are bullshit.
Yeah, yeah, I got it,
but look, um..
It's just not a story of
interest for us right now.
No, it's too soon,
I'm telling you
the country isn't ready.
The Resistant
are still alive
it's not safe yet.
Tell that to
the families here.
Look, I... I do have
something for you to cover.
The first McDonalds
is reopening.
I need some coverage.
If it's beneath you,
I can..
Despite protests,
the humane elimination
of the resistant 25%
is now under way
with the military
estimating it will be
completed by the end
of the week.
Abbie.
Sorry, I'm a friend
of Senan's.
From quarantine?
What gave it away?
I was working
and I just saw you.
Anyway, it's nice
to finally meet you.
Was Senan with
you last night?
It must have been tough.
Raising a child alone
through the outbreak.
I managed.
Of course.
I didn't mean
anything by it.
I'm sorry.
It's just force of habit.
I guess being a cleaner wasn't
your top career choice, huh?
No.
I'm a barrister.
I was actually running for
election before all this.
Well, maybe you can
run again.
No, I doubt it.
It's nice
to have your vote.
How did you get that?
This?
Um, I was late for work.
You have to complain.
The guy we complain to has a
pretty decent right hook.
What was it like?
Quarantine?
No, before that.
Why don't you ask Senan?
I can't.
Everyone says it's hell.
It's like being trapped
inside your body.
Fighting to stop yourself.
But what they
don't talk about..
...is the moment
when you stop fighting.
When you start to
just go with it.
Gosh, I have to
get back to work.
Thank you.
For what?
For not treating me
like an animal.
Senan's very lucky
to have you.
Nerve degradation
remains the same.
Subject 301 shows
no sign of change.
Recommend
upping the percentage
of Bendamustine
in the formula.
Sometimes I feel it.
Screaming to get out.
The cure prevents
reinfection
or transmission.
You're one of
the lucky ones.
They were never gonna
keep the Resistant alive
with the
withdrawal happening.
We have to do something
to stop them.
- Now.
- We need to target the IDV.
Fuckin' screamers.
Hey, what the fuck
are you doing?
- Prick.
- Nick, I need help here!
- You're one of them.
- Aah!
Shit!
Squadron Eight.
Perimeter clear.
They're gonna die anyway.
Cured rights now!
The truth is
that every day
that the Resistant
remain alive
is a day that we risk
another outbreak.
But I can find a cure.
I just need time
and resources.
We have a stretched
medical system.
We have to redirect
our efforts
back to the populace.
You're talking
about killing
almost 5000 people.
Joan... I fear
your personal loss
has clouded your judgment.
But I would ask you,
and indeed all those
with loved ones
amongst the Resistant
do you really want them
to live
as these monsters
forever?
They won't stop
with the Resistant.
They want us all dead.
We have to stop them.
Senan. Senan.
They're all empty targets.
I promise you no one
will get hurt.
- Hello.
- Hey, there's been a series of bombings.
- How many?
- They're reporting five.
Okay. Okay, just, uh..
I have to drop off my son.
Give me 30 minutes.
Cillian?
Cillian, let's go.
Senan?
Cured en route.
Understood.
There have been several
injured and one dead.
The targets were the homes
of Irish Defense Volunteers.
The Cured Alliance have claimed
responsibility for the attacks.
The government have
insisted that they are
a terrorist
organization.
It's several weeks now
since the..
Squadron Eight.
Perimeter clear.
Cured rights now!
Calm down, will you?
Get in the car!
Get in the fuckin' car!
Calm down! Get in the car.
Cured rights now!
Senan.
Senan, it's me. Please.
Senan, please.
Senan..
Senan, please!
Please, Senan!
No! Stop!
Please!
I know it's been hard
for you all
being beaten and bullied
and forgotten.
There's no one
looking out for us
but I promise
that ends now.
Today will be
the first day
on the road
to our freedom.
Whoo! Yeah!
- Yes!
- Whoo!
You know we found
the cure together?
You can't imagine
the excitement.
Later we realized that..
...the subject remembered
what they did
when infected.
Was it worth it?
After everything
we've done?
You weren't in control,
you were just sick.
We cured you.
You get to choose
who you want to be.
Does puppy's baby
have a name?
Uh... Andrew.
- Andrew?
- Yeah.
I'm just making up..
I'm just making up
normal names.
Mm.
Are you involved
with the Cured Alliance?
No.
So where do you go
at night?
I don't want to
get in your way.
There was so much chaos
after the Outbreak.
It was two years before we could
begin to re-enter the city.
We started to hear
a rumor of a cure.
I actually convinced myself
that Luke was infected.
Just... waiting
to be rescued.
And then I came home.
I thought they'd cleared
the entire city.
The smell hit me first.
Luke's gone.
We're your family.
Abbie..
Mom?
Hey, sweetie.
How far outside the city
can we go?
Me and your dad used to come
here when we were kids.
It's as if
nothing happened.
Liar, liar,
pants on fire.
- What's her name?
- What?
What's her name?
Beatrice.
Don't get me started
on this.
Yeah.
Then what we doing
with them?
I'll get it.
What's that?
We were just
having dinner.
I won't stay long.
Take a seat.
Hello.
Hi.
I'm Conor.
I'm a friend
of your uncle's.
Cillian, bedtime.
Now, please.
He's a good-looking boy.
I can see
the resemblance.
I called earlier,
but you weren't in.
Where did you go?
Killiney Hill.
Oh. Nice.
It's good to
see you bonding.
It must be tough at the accommodation
center after the bombing.
At least they
arrested someone.
She didn't act alone.
Well, there's a lot of
anger out there, you know?
Particularly
with the Elimination.
Maybe it's for the best.
Dr. Lyons will
find a cure.
- And what if she can't?
- She needs time.
And one of them gets out, and...
and we're right back there.
We're all in danger.
Not all of us.
It's late.
You need to go.
Can I ask you something?
Do you think
we deserve forgiveness?
Yes.
And if you were faced with the
man that killed your husband..
...would you forgive him?
They weren't in control.
I'd better check
on Cillian.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to
upset you.
You didn't.
She takes you in and suddenly
you forget about us?
You told me
they were empty targets.
There's always
casualties, Senan.
We're dying every day
because of them.
I'm not gonna be
a part of this anymore.
I have to look after them.
You think you can
just shut the door
and pretend it's all okay?
You're the reason...
they're not safe.
They'll find out
eventually.
Sweetheart, can you go
and brush your teeth?
I'm gonna be late.
Cillian, now!
I can take him to school.
Uh, you don't know
where it is.
I can show him.
Okay.
Okay, but straight
to school, okay?
- Aah..
- Fall off.
I'd never fall off.
- Aah..
- Yeah.
I just wanted to check to make
sure that he wasn't late.
Yes, thank you. Bye.
What's this about?
It's customary to check in
with families
to see
how everything's going.
So, how is Senan
settling back in?
Well.
It's natural for there
to be problems at first.
Everything's fine.
You know, I have to say..
...I think it's brave
of you
to take one back in.
Especially with a young
boy in the house.
They can be aggressive.
And it probably
doesn't help that their
rehab officer kicks
the shit out of them.
You've met Conor.
The alpha of the pack.
They're friends.
From quarantine.
Is that
what they told you?
We try to make ourselves
feel better
feel safe, by saying
it wasn't their fault.
They're just
mindless monsters.
But the Infected
aren't mindless.
They hunt together.
They communicate
with each other.
They decide who to kill..
...and who to infect.
They're connected in a way
that we will never understand.
What do you want from me?
I want you to contact me.
If you think there's
anything I should know.
They're killing
the Resistant
because they think
they're a threat.
But they're not
a threat to us.
They're the key
to our freedom.
Now, we're not gonna change
anything by simply crying
and breaking windows
like petulant teenagers.
We need something that
will make them listen.
Something they're truly
scared of.
- Yes! Yes!
- This is our country too.
- Yes. Yes.
- Yes!
Katie.
What are you doing here?
I wanted to see it
for myself.
I thought you might've
come to see me.
Do you want to
ask me something?
You were involved
in the bombings.
You can't link me
to any violence.
So you're denying it?
All I've done is
tried to help people.
It's not just
for the power then?
Now, look at
how they treat us.
Look at how we're
forced to live
what choice do we have?
You have the choice
not to eat people.
Well, there's the thing.
We're not
the only killers.
We're just the ones
being reminded of it.
I want you to stay away
from me.
And stay away from Senan.
Senan... is my family...
Why? Because
you killed together?
'Cause you're a pack?
That's not a family,
it's a sickness.
He wouldn't have
told you that.
Stay away from us.
Elimination of
level one complete.
Moving all remaining Resistant
to the holding area.
Jo?
My love?
It's me.
No!
What are you doing?
She's being brought to the
rest for euthanization.
I can save her!
Please, no!
- Done.
- What am I?
A dog.
You're gonna love this.
I look a bit more
like a gerbil.
- No, you look like a dog.
- I look like a hamster.
- And it's all your fault.
- You look like a dog.
It's all your fault.
...windows like
petulant teenagers.
We need something that
will make them listen.
We need to make ourselves
heard properly.
- Yes!
- This is our country too.
Yes!
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Sorry, just on edge.
You look ridiculous.
Yeah.
I'll go wash it off.
I'm so used to doing this
on my own.
It's so weird
having someone here.
Yeah.
When Cillian was born,
Luke was petrified.
Well, it wasn't
exactly planned, so..
Hmm.
He said it was like somebody put
his heart inside somebody else.
Christ.
He could be
so pretentious.
He'd be happy
you're here.
Cured scum!
Luke..
Was there any
distinctive features?
No. Just the anti-Cured
symbol.
Did they say anythin'?
No.
We'll do everything
we can to catch them
but, uh,
this sort of thing
it's not uncommon
in homes with..
Eh..
- You can say Cured.
- E... exactly. Yes.
You were right.
I can't keep them safe.
I need your help.
They'll never
leave us alone.
We need something that
will make them listen.
Sergeant Cantor.
It's about Conor.
I think he's planning
something.
Dr. Lyons?
What's goin' on?
I asked her to come.
Sit down.
They took Jo.
We're gonna save her,
Senan.
If we have
one of the Resistant
they'll have to
take us seriously.
No more bombings,
no more violence.
What about the military?
Mm?
People could get killed.
It's mainly
defense volunteers left.
Scouts have
better trainin'.
You don't know what the
fuck you're talkin' about.
Joan, you can't agree
with this.
I have to save her,
Senan.
They're the same as us.
We can't stand by
and do nothing.
Get off, get off!
Run! Run, run, run, run!
Move, move, move!
Senan, come on!
Where are they?
Down. Get down.
- Get down. I said stay down.
- And the rest of them.
Get up against the wall!
Go look in the basement,
there are more in there.
Where are they off to?
Where are they going?
Where?
I told you
to stay away from us.
Senan told me
about the break-in.
I wanted to make sure
you were okay.
I know it was you.
You know,
for a while there
I thought you and I,
that we had something.
But it turns out you're
just like everybody else.
Scared.
And the truth is,
you're right to be scared.
No matter how much
we pretend..
...we're not
the same people anymore.
All because daddy
wouldn't get you a job.
You know,
I met your husband once.
Bless him,
he tried his best.
You're lying.
You should ask
Senan about him.
It's all very
Cain and Abel.
No!
Senan?
Where's Conor?
What's he planning?
Senan?
He doesn't care
about you.
- He looked after me.
- He infected you!
You have to give me
something.
Before it's too late.
Before the withdrawal
is over.
Time's up.
I can help.
I can help your family.
Isn't that what
Luke would want?
Conor needs to see ya.
Hey.
12 o'clock.
The baths.
Hey.
I'm sorry
I didn't come home.
What's wrong?
What happened to Luke?
How did he die?
- Abbie..
- Tell me.
I thought it would be better
if you didn't know the truth.
What happened?
- What good will it do?
- Tell me!
We were here.
We..
Luke thought that..
...maybe you'd been
trapped here.
But you'd already gone
by the time we got here.
Then there was
an Infected.
And he attacked me.
Conor.
Yeah.
Luke tried
to fight him off.
But it was too late.
And then he barricaded
himself in the bedroom.
I wasn't in control.
Believe me,
I... I didn't know
what I was doing, and...
How could you not tell me?
How could you sleep here?
- I'm so sorry...
- Get out!
Get the fuck out!
I had to show you.
They're all the same
when they know the truth.
I'm your real family,
Senan.
You never had
any nightmares, did you?
Why should I?
This is Sergeant Cantor.
I need back-up
at the baths.
On your knees,
hands on your head.
Understood.
We're on our way.
We will be
with you shortly.
Get down.
Now.
I'm arresting you
for the murder
of Cadet Jack Dermody.
I did tell you, Conor.
It's not your world
any more.
Cuff yourself.
Conor!
Conor! Stop! Stop!
Why?
I can't let you
go through with it.
People will get hurt.
I told you..
...there's always
casualties.
What're you planning?
Conor.
What're you
really planning?
It's already done.
The Cured on route.
Understood.
Copy that.
Where's the control room?
Come on.
There she is.
Come on, hurry up,
will you?
What are you doing?
This isn't the plan,
please.
Yes, it is.
- Look, this is madness.
- I told you to shut up.
Oh, God!
They're through,
they're through.
They're pouring through!
The fence is down!
The perimeter
has been breached!
The fence is down. I need
some back-up over here!
Welcome home, my love.
No! No!
Get in. Get in.
- Okay, everyone..
- Get on the truck.
Start making your way
onto the truck. Go.
What's going on
with the schools?
The schools
are being evacuated.
No, no, I have to get
to my son. Please.
All the kids
will be at the stadium.
- I have to get to my son...
- Ma'am, you need..
Get on the truck!
We've got to move!
Get on the truck now!
Get on, quick!
I've got to find my son!
Get Cillian!
Get out!
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Let's go, let's go!
Let's go, come on!
Cillian!
Senan!
- Senan!
- Hey, hey.
Come here. Come here.
Come on, I've got you.
I've got you.
I've got you, come on.
It's okay. It's okay.
Please keep calm.
If you are cured,
stay outside
the perimeter fence.
You are safe.
There is no room...
Please let me in. How
do you know we're safe?
Have the schools come yet?
Walk through.
He's just a boy.
Run!
Did you really think
you could betray me
like that?
Did you?
Check your right.
Move, move, move.
Let's go!
Get out! Come on!
I was the only one
who really cared
about you.
I took care of you.
Senan!
Hey.
You okay?
Check the east side.
Kill on sight.
Containment is priority.
Guard down!
Clear!
Listen, there's
nothing wrong with her.
- Look at her..
- He's my husband, he's..
You can't treat
people like this.
Why are they being
separated?
Just let her through!
I'm not infected.
Why are they separated?
Get out of my way!
You have no right
to separate them
they're not infected.
Madam, calm down.
Now everybody
needs to calm down!
Come on, come on. Move.
Move it! Move it!
Cillian?
Cillian.
Mum!
Oh, my.. Oh!
I love you!
Oh!
You're gonna be okay.
I love you!
Abbie.
I love you.
Stop! It's okay.
There's a cure.
He doesn't have to be
like me.
Lyons found a cure.
I can save him.
Abbie.
I love you.
I love you, little..
I love you. No..
He's gonna be okay,
I promise.
Following the recent
outbreak of the Maze
virus in Ireland,
the country is beginning
to regain control
once again.
People are desperately
trying to track down
loved ones, suspected
to be amongst the 8000
newly Infected cases..
Outcry against the humane
elimination is growing
with families joining
the Cured Alliance who
are leading the protests
against the government.
The government
have agreed that
continuing
the humane elimination
is the only option
available
if we are going to
stamp out this infection
once and for all.
..the government
are preparing to declare
Ireland Infection free.
We've obtained evidence
that a cure
for the resistant strain
was perfected
by Doctor Joan Lyons.
Now, either
the government knew this
and covered it up,
or they rushed
into the
clean-up missions
without considering
any options.
The people of Ireland
deserve better
they deserve
true leadership
that is there
for the many and not...
Sorry, we have
to interrupt here.
We're receiving
breaking news.
Despite reports,
camera traps
have discovered pockets
of Infected still
remaining in the west
of the country.
The footage shows
at least 20 infected
but the exact figures
have yet
to be determined.
The government has just
released a statement
assuring those in
the area that a military
platoon will be
dispatched
to evacuate them.
Now this begs
the question
if the military failed
to detect these Infected
how many more of them..
Subtitles by explosiveskull