Yeah, that's, yeah, that's really good.
And you... you like being a hockey coach?
Yes.
The girls love to play,
and if they're happy, I'm happy.
Mm.
Can be tricky, though.
I pity the boys trying to date them.
But on the pitch they're actually great.
Getting out all their frustrations...
I suppose.
Something like that.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
It's so good to see you.
I'm gonna go.
Ah!
I reject the good. I reject the light.
I embrace the dark. I embrace the night.
Beneath this magic tree
given to the first witches
by the Prince of the Underworld...
we will bleed this body of its life.
We reach out to his realm
with this special gift.
Enchant this fruit
and grant us your familiars.
They will be our bond
with the world beneath.
Give us that power.
Give us your favor.
Death is the beginning of everything.
Death is the beginning.
Orchard got its name because
it's located in a fruit farming area.
The town is also founded by a Utopian cult
which was later linked to witchcraft.
The most famous witch was Eleanor Young.
She was said to have been given
an enchanted Cherry Tree
as a gift from the underworld.
The roots of the tree were nourished
by the blood of human sacrifice
which, in turn gave her
the power to use its magic.
She also used its wood and fruit
to perform her spells and glamours.
The story goes that she was arrested
and convicted of witchcraft but...
when they tried to burn her
at the stake the fire wouldn't light.
- Ooh, nice block.
- All in a day's work.
Eventually she was banished from the town.
Hold it, Brian.
Is there something going on?
I asked a question.
Okay, carry on, Brian.
- He's not bad, is he?
- Thank you, Miss.
Shame about the hair, though.
Eleanor Young's legend features
strongly in local folklore but
there are, in fact, no records that exist
to prove she ever lived and, well,
no one's ever found the magic tree.
But many people in the 16th century
were accused of witchcraft
and communing with evil spirits.
They were often burned at the stake
with little proof of guilt.
Communing? Isn't that like an orgy?
You know, I think that
does mean 'orgy', yeah.
People, please.
Can we just concentrate on folklore.
Fuck-lore.
Faith. Amy.
I'll see you both after class.
Okay, girls, line up!
My name is Sissy Young
and I'm your new coach.
Now I know the loss of Miss Hunt last year
must have been very difficult for all of
you and things will never be the same.
But I know that she wouldn't
want you to live in past.
She would want you to train hard
and play to the best of your abilities.
So, let's honor her memory
and play every game this year to win.
I have two places available on
the senior team for the match on Friday.
Let's see you play.
- Ah.
- Sorry.
Hey, comedians, cut it out.
- What's your name?
- Faith Maguire.
Okay.
Let's go!
That's not where your
sani-pad goes, Faith.
Can I have your attention, please?
I've made my decision for the senior
team line-up for the game on Friday.
Caroline St John and Jennifer Engels,
you will captain the team as usual.
What a shame, the fifteen
year old virgin didn't make it.
Shut up, Caroline.
I'm not finished, ladies.
I like to reward talent,
so I'm pleased to announce
the first place on the subs
bench will go to Faith Maguire.
You know Brian has a huge crush on you.
Brian Kelly?
He's cute.
Well, you go out with him then.
That's my plan.
Are you gonna help me or what?
Because I'm a mechanic now?
Oh, fucking whatever.
Just come and help me.
Lift that up.
Well done, Faith.
Best hockey player to never get a match.
Oh, just piss off, will you?
Congratulations on not making the team.
Virgins and retards tend not to fit in.
- Hey, no, no, no.
- Alright, girls, that's enough.
Save it for the hockey field.
Shake hands.
Jennifer, Caroline, I'm sure
you've got somewhere to be.
Come on, let's go.
We have another senior match on Friday.
Will you play?
Love to.
Come on.
- Hey.
- Hey, Faith.
- Where's dad?
- He's just...
Dad?
Have you taken your meds
since this morning?
Thank you.
I'm fine.
I'm fine, come on.
Well we've got a hearse
waiting outside, if you need it.
Very funny, smartass.
Shouldn't you be learning stuff
or something?
- I have news.
- Yeah?
Got put on the senior hockey team today.
That's amazing.
No fags.
Come on, Dad, at least try and look
after yourself, I'm worried about you.
Don't be, don't think about it.
Think about your birthday.
Let's have a party.
- Bye.
- See you.
She's always going on at me.
Hey, Faith.
Faith!
Hey.
Hey, Brian. What's up?
- I was looking for you after class.
- You were?
Yeah, um, I was just wondering
like, if you've got time or whatever,
d'you wanna go see a film
or get a pizza or something?
I just don't think Amy
would be very happy with that.
So?
She's not... my girlfriend.
Yeah, but she's my friend
and she likes you so, sorry.
Cool, yeah.
Sorry.
No.
That's my dad.
That's our house.
Okay, cool.
I am very flattered.
Well, look, if you change your mind
I'll be standing right here.
Dad?
- You alright?
- Dad, are you okay?
Dad, can you hear me?
Thanks, Brian.
Alright.
See you.
He is going to need a lot of care
over the coming days.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
Took a bit of a dive there, didn't I?
Hey, Dad.
How are you feeling?
Yeah, fine.
Doctor Slater.
Faith called me.
You're going to need to take
some rest for the next few days.
I'll see you soon.
- Faith.
- Mm.
They're calling me.
What?
I have to go.
Dad?
Save me.
Remember you have a doctor's
appointment this morning.
- I know.
- You are going?
- Yeah.
- Good.
- Wish me luck for my big match.
- Break a leg.
Preferably not one of yours.
Bye.
This leukemia therapy
was a long shot, Sean.
It was working.
The balance between the red
and white cells had been restored.
But not any more.
I'm sorry.
How long?
Three months.
Probably less.
I can arrange counseling.
Sean.
- Good luck, Faith.
Jennifer. Faith! Come here.
You're on the same team today, okay?
Alright, let's go.
Kill, kill, kill...
Orchard, Orchard, Orchard...
Faith?
- Dad?
- Hey.
Dad, why are you here?
I just thought I'd come and see you play.
I am the boss, I can do that, you know.
What did Doctor Slater say?
You know, the usual stuff.
Faith.
Look, let's talk after. Okay?
- It's fine.
- Come on, Faith.
Go on, you're holding the game up.
Talk to you after. Okay?
Ah.
Hey, Ref, come on!
Faith?
What the fuck, Faith?
Claire, it's me.
Is everything okay there?
Yeah, I'm on my way.
I've just got a bit of a thing with Faith.
I'll see you soon.
Sorry.
What did she say?
Okay.
- We're gonna fight it all the way.
- Mm.
Faith.
Coach?
Are you okay?
It's, er, my dad.
I thought he was better.
I'd like to show you something.
It might help.
Come.
This is quite a house.
Hmm.
It's been in the family a long time.
This way.
My great aunt.
We were very close.
Do you believe in magic, Faith?
I don't know.
That's a very strange question.
It's a very strange world.
Not all of it benign.
Beautiful in its own way.
I can't believe this is under your house.
Hmm, I knew you'd like it.
I don't like it.
What's it for?
It's a haven for people like me.
At its heart is a Chamber
where we're safe to practice our craft.
Nothing can enter from heaven
or hell unless we allow it.
This place is a gift from
the Lord of the Underworld.
Here we serve him
and we celebrate his glorious reign.
And in return
he rewards us with his dark powers.
But he demands complete devotion,
and if you defy that...
he draws down his terrible rage.
We're nearly here.
There are forces in nature
that people rarely see.
Some call it magic.
It is sacred and righteous.
Fuck.
These are nature's familiars.
They help us to reach
from this realm to the other
and use the power that lies there.
Watch.
You see?
Death is the beginning of everything.
You can cure him?
That's why I showed you.
Will you?
Power comes from desire.
How strong is your desire
to save your father?
He's all I have.
Will you help me?
I'd like something in return.
I want you to have a baby for me.
What?
I'm fifteen. I...
Well, think about it.
What if I have this baby?
I'll cure your father.
And the baby? What will happen to it?
It'll be mine.
And my dad, he'll be cured?
Everything is connected.
Everything has to be tallied and paid for.
If you give, you will be given to.
Your father's going to die, and if you
want to change the course of nature...
you have to honor that cycle.
It's your choice.
I have no choice.
I've never done it.
Who would I do it with?
Oh, come on,
there's nice young men everywhere.
You're young and beautiful.
What's wrong with that?
Your birthday's coming.
That's the time.
- Hi.
- Happy birthday.
- Thank you.
- It's good to see you.
- Jeremy.
- Happy birthday, Faith.
- Thank you.
- Many happy returns.
- How are you?
- Good.
- Very well.
- I'll see you in there, okay?
- Okay, darling, see you in there.
- Jeremy, how are you?
- Hello, how are you?
Hi, sweetheart. Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Champagne?
Er, Sicilian lemonade. Nice try.
There you go.
Oh, thank you.
Hello.
Jennifer mentioned it was your birthday.
I wanted to give you this.
Oh.
Thanks.
Save them for later.
- I'm Sissy, by the way.
- Sean. Nice to meet you properly.
- Small world.
- Yes, it is.
Ah, this is Jeremy.
- Jeremy, hello.
- Sissy, nice to meet you.
Excuse me.
- So are you having fun?
- Mm. Yep.
You are a terrible liar. Terrible.
Well, you'll be glad to know
this isn't your real party.
- Really?
- Really. Amy's gonna take it from here.
- And Brian.
It's all been arranged.
Go out and have a good night.
- Love you.
- And I'll see you later.
- I love you.
- Mm, yes.
- Alright, happy birthday, sweetheart.
- Bye.
- See you.
- Alright, bye.
- Thank you.
- Take care.
Oh, cheeky.
Where are we going?
Okay, watch your step, watch your step.
Alright, alright, just through here.
Two seconds.
Okay. Are you ready?
- Okay, are you ready?
- Yes, yes, yes.
- Are you ready? Are you sure?
- Yes.
Happy birthday!
My humble abode.
Hey.
Hi.
Are you alright?
Yeah.
It's nice out here, isn't it?
Sorry, I'm way too good at
ruining special moments.
Unless, you know, you
want me to keep talking.
I can also do that
'cause I got plenty to say.
If that works for you,
I don't know, maybe.
Maybe not.
Hi, Brian.
Having a good time?
Uh...
You bitch.
Amy.
Sorry, I...
It's fine.
Walk me home?
Yeah.
Shh.
Quietly.
It's nice.
Faith.
Oh, God, Mrs. Fincher.
Sissy is here.
I reject the good.
I reject the light.
I embrace the dark. I embrace the night.
Come amongst us now.
Take our brother's hand.
Though today he falls,
tomorrow he will stand.
- Faith!
- Dad.
No, no, no!
I reject the good. I reject the light.
I embrace the dark. I embrace the night.
- Dad.
- Hey.
That's a lot of food.
Yeah.
Feel a bit hung-over after the party.
It's good I've got an appetite, though.
You have fun?
Yeah, it was great.
Faith.
You're sick.
Yeah.
That's good.
Take this, pee on it.
Tell me what it says.
Sean.
What d'you think you're doing?
Changing a bulb. What's it look like?
Sean?
Sean!
You're both part of this.
That's fucked up.
If you say so.
Well, you can give her this.
Tell her I'm pregnant.
You should be happy, your dad is cured.
Listen.
How can I be pregnant so soon?
I know, right?
Where's the fun in that?
Amy.
Amy. Amy, please, come on.
I suppose you're looking for Brian?
I haven't seen him, so
you should go fuck yourself.
Hey, Claire. What's up?
What?
You tricked me.
My dad is still sick.
He was taken to hospital today.
- Come in, Faith.
- I'm pregnant!
Your father is cured, I promise you.
You have to trust me.
I need the bathroom.
It'll be over in six weeks.
And then another seven months of...
No, you're going to
give birth soon, Faith.
How is that possible?
You'll see.
What am I gonna tell my dad?
Nothing.
For now.
Understand?
He better be cured.
- Excuse me, can I just...
- Just one second, please.
Faith.
- Dad.
- I'm alright.
I'm alright, really.
It's just some sort of dizzy spell.
I did some blood tests and it's alright.
Come on, let's get out of here.
You alright?
Faith, listen.
There have been reports of a
madman escaped from an asylum.
He was last seen driving up
the Orchard Road in an old red car.
You're a dick.
I've got news.
The hospital just called.
My last blood test shows
no sign of leukemia.
I'm in remission.
Hey, Faith, great news about your dad.
Yeah, it's incredible.
- Are you joining us?
- No rest for the wicked.
Faith. Look who I bumped into.
Hey, Faith.
I'd like to make a toast.
To life.
It never fails to surprise us.
Cheers.
Sean.
Faith.
I'm sorry.
Sit down.
I don't know what to say.
I'm... I'm just feeling so good lately.
I'm pregnant, Dad.
Is this a joke?
You wanna tell me about it?
There's nothing to say.
I'm pregnant, I just
thought you should know.
You're sixteen, Faith.
Who's the boy?
- Are you gonna tell him?
- No.
I'm recovering from
a serious illness, Faith.
What if it comes back? What if I die?
- That won't happen.
- You don't know that.
I do.
I need to think about this.
You shouldn't have told him.
You shouldn't have fucked him.
You know, Sean is a...
he's a wonderful man.
Be heartbreaking if he were
to get ill again, wouldn't it?
And what d'you think would
happen to the baby then?
I'll do what I want.
Alright, Faith.
Have a look at this.
- It's Brian.
- Mm-hmm.
You did this?
When you two were together
he was possessed by another being.
Tends to be an overwhelming experience.
The thing is he's gone. Sean was dead.
For him to be alive again someone else
had to die. It's the way it works.
- You said if I had a baby...
- I did, didn't I?
But before you get too upset about it,
remember this is what you wanted.
Let's stick to the plan
from now on, shall we?
Hey, Faith. Is everything okay?
Well, no, not exactly.
Can I help?
Um, could you come over tonight?
I need to talk to you about something.
Okay, great. Thanks.
He should be back soon.
Never strays too far from
home on his day off.
D'you want some tea?
Thanks for coming over.
I wanted to ask you
if dad and I went away,
would you look after the restaurant?
Probably heard I'm...
Yeah.
None of my business.
She's an obstetrician.
Thanks.
Is there someone...
It's time to go now.
I'm staying here, thanks.
Are you threatening her?
You've no right to be here.
It's unfortunate that you're here, Claire.
I want you to know that I'm truly sorry.
No. No, no!
No, no, no, no!
No!
Get off me!
You're halfway through your term, Faith.
You need to sleep now.
Dad. Dad, wake up.
Dad.
Dad, please. Please, wake up, please.
Dad, I have to go for help.
Okay?
I'll come back for you, I swear.
Jeremy, downstairs.
That's not what I asked.
Jeremy, everything is ready.
I mean, every single thing is ready.
No, no. That's not good enough.
You go back, you check
everything and you come back
and you tell me that
everything is in place.
Six weeks, six days, six hours.
We have to be ready.
She is very close
and she is going to wake soon.
Mrs. Fincher, can I go
to the bathroom, please?
Two minutes.
Where the fuck have you
been for three weeks?
And how come you're pregnant?
- Three weeks?
- How come you're pregnant?
And where's Brian?
Amy, I'm in trouble.
No kidding.
Please.
Faith, you're my friend.
Here, put this on.
How d'you know I was gonna be in detention?
Smart guess.
Shit.
Fuck.
Amy.
Amy!
Come on. Go, go, go.
Amy, Amy, Amy.
Get off the bike.
No, get off!
Go!
Fuck!
Fuck! Fuck.
Oh, Amy, the baby's coming.
The baby's coming.
I have to push. I have to push.
Okay. Lay down.
Are you okay?
Water. Get me some water.
- Water.
Damn.
Get me up, get me up, get me up.
Okay.
It's alright.
Give me your weight.
- I need to push, I need to push.
- Okay, okay, okay.
- Take my pants off, take my pants off.
- Okay, okay.
Good girl, okay.
I'm here. I'm here for you.
I'm here, Faith. I'm here, Faith.
Again, again, again.
Oh, my God.
Just keep pushing.
- Keep pushing, Faith.
- I can't.
Come on, keep pushing. Come on.
Hang on.
I need to get some stuff
to look after you.
If I go to the shop, will you be okay?
Thank you.
It's nothing.
Be back soon.
Faith?
Faith!
We had an agreement, Faith.
I cured your father,
now you have to give me the baby.
If I kill him, it's for good.
Have it your way.
Stop!
Good girl.
Oh, Faith.
Dad.
Dad, are you okay? Did they hurt you?
Dad? Dad, it's gonna be okay.
It's gonna be okay.
Here is our future.
- Our key to the dark life.
- Get off.
Dad. Dad. Get up.
His blood will set us free
and bring the Underworld to our service.
Our time has almost come.
Dad, are you okay? Dad!
We must make the final sacrifice.
Jeremy, no! Jeremy!
Jeremy, what are you doing?
Jeremy, no!
Oh, fuck!
Get out.
Dad... Dad...
Faith.
She cheated us, Faith.
She cheated you and me.
And now she plans to kill the child.
Don't let her do it.
I can enter the realm but not
the Chamber. You can.
You can save him.
You must save him.
Brothers and sisters,
tonight we end the journey.
When I came back among you,
you reached down to the world
beneath and drew up its power,
its familiars.
They served us and we served their master.
I reject the good. I reject the light.
I embrace the dark. I embrace the night.
I bleed this body to free ourselves
No more mortals, weak and cowed.
We will walk the night, strong and proud.
Death is the beginning of everything.
I embrace the dark. I embrace the night.
I reject the good. I reject the light.
We're gonna bleed you and your baby.
You fucking bitch.
We gave him his child
and now I sell myself.
I will drink his child's blood
and I will transform.
I will become Queen of the Underworld.
Join me, and let our bodies rot and die.
And in the first rays of the coming day
our new skin will change forever.
I reject the good. I reject the light.
I embrace the dark. I embrace the night.
I bleed this body of its life
to free us of what we used to be.
No more mortals, weak and cowed.
We will walk the night, strong and proud.
- Death...
- ...is the beginning
- ...is the beginning.
- Death...
...of everything.
Bleed, bleed, bleed, bleed...
No! No!
No!
Why aren't you dead?
Are you stealing my property?
How could you kill a baby?
The child's blood is imbued
with the power of the Underworld.
When the sun rises,
the process will be complete.
We will renew, and the day
and the night will be ours.
We will be the greatest of witches.
Unrivaled.
Immortal.
The child's remains must stay
inside the Cherry Tree.
Give it... back!
Stop her!
Faith.
You have to return to the Chamber.
You can save him.
Faith.
You cannot save the child
without the fruit of the Cherry Tree.
You have to return to the Chamber
and face the witch.
Faith.
I knew you'd come back to me.
You can't leave here, Sissy.
He's out there...
waiting.
I know you're afraid, Faith,
but we did this together.
You asked me to cure
your father and I did.
If you had obeyed me,
things would be so much better for you.
They still can be.
Talk to him.
Why would I do that?
You have everything to gain.
I admit I...
misjudged things.
But I've come to...
I've come to truly admire you.
Together... we could do anything.
We could have everything.
He's withdrawing the gift of my familiars.
You can stop him.
You've taken away
everything I've ever loved.
I'm just taking it back.
Enjoy Hell.
Come on, let's call here.
But it's haunted, remember?
That's why we've got to, right?
Come on, it'll be cool.
Trick or treat.
Wow. Don't you all look so scary.
Would anybody like a carrot?
No? Well, maybe I have
something else inside.
I'll have a look.
Who's that?
That's Sally.
She's too scared to come in.
Well, that's a shame, Sally,
'cause I'm all out of carrots
but I do have some chocolate.
Here, try some.
It's homemade.
Cherry flavor.
Are you a witch?
No.
But my son is the Devil.