Ma.
That's it.
Mama.
Kay?
Hey!
Hello!
Hey.
So we have three meals.
Four at a stretch.
Okay.
So that means
we're down to quarter rations.
Okay.
Is there a plan I'm not aware of?
Want to fill me in on it?
- No, I like your plan.
- Which is?
That we eat the pens.
Look, there's a town here.
Can't be more than
30 or 40 km from where we are.
Right? It's rural.
There's not a lot of people.
I say we get a car, fill it with supplies,
we just see what's out there.
- We've seen what's out there.
- We've seen what's back there. Weeks ago.
- It's quiet on the banks...
- We talked about this.
- What if we've outrun it?
- What if we haven't?
Where we need to be, actually, is here.
The river has got us this far.
If we play it smart, it'll get us there,
but we have to stick to what we know.
What we know? You had barely set foot
on a boat before we found this thing.
I mean,
it's older than both of us put together.
What if the engine goes?
What happens then?
We have to think about Rosie.
Do we? I hadn't thought of that.
What the fuck do you think I'm doing?
Look, we can't set foot on the shore
until it is our last and only option.
That's just the way it is, I'm sorry.
So is that going to be before or after
our daughter starves to death?
Shh.
Jesus Christ.
My God.
Wow.
- Any bites?
- Um-mm. Not yet.
- Oh, hang on a second.
- Quick. Hook him with the thing.
- What, with the hook? Whoa.
- Yeah, bring him in, quick!
- What?
- What's that?
- Where did you get this from?
- From the wrecked yacht.
Say thank you. Look at this.
There's enough there
for three months, at least.
- Hey, this is good news, Blue.
- It's great news.
You're not worried. It was a one-man job.
In and out. Easy. Safe.
Come on, this is a win, Blue.
This is a win.
We must celebrate those
- when they come along, just a little bit.
- No, okay.
- You sure it was safe?
- Safe.
Is there a razor in that stash of yours?
Why? I'll have you know, this is rugged.
- I think it's a bit ragged.
- Rugged.
Rugged.
How is she? How is little monkey?
She's been down a while.
Maybe you should go say hello.
I'm not sure she'd like that much.
Hey, go and have a lie down.
- Yeah?
- Yeah. Go.
Man.
- You are.
- Woman.
Good girl, Rosie. Yes.
Yes.
Okay.
Oh!
Hey.
- Mama.
- Hey, darling. Okay, all right.
Ohh!
Mommy.
Where's Mommy then?
Where is she?
Kay?
Are you in there?
Kay! Come on, let me in, babe.
Let me in.
Shit, Kay, what...
What have you done?
- No, don't...
- Let me see.
- No.
- Well, keep pressure on it.
- Mama.
- It's all right. It's okay.
Oh, shit.
Come on, let me see.
Oh, fuck.
Right, Kay, just...
Oh, what have you done?
- I'm sorry, sweetheart.
- It's all right. It's okay.
All right, keep that pressure on it.
Keep pressure on.
Shit.
- Okay. All right? You okay?
- Yeah.
All right? Look at me.
- It's okay.
- It's going to be okay.
Hey.
- So talk to me. What are you thinking?
- Well, we can't stay here.
But it's only been an hour.
Symptoms take at least three hours to...
Yeah, I know how it works.
We might not have that time.
- We can't take the risk.
- Oh, so today it's a risk.
Out there, with this?
Yes, it's a risk.
Let's not put Rosie in danger
till we know what we're dealing with.
There are dozens of things
that live and eat in this river.
- We have no idea what bit you.
- It had fingers, Andy.
Fuck!
Look, if you are sick,
then you've got 48 hours,
and we'll deal with that.
But if you're wrong, right,
and you're not infected,
then at the rate you're bleeding,
you've got two hours, three, tops.
That's a risk I'm not gonna take.
We need to get to the hospital,
where you said.
Someone will patch you up
and we'll hedge our bets.
What if we lose?
It's gonna be my call.
Yeah.
Come on.
Don't look.
Come on, little darling.
Okay.
Oh, good girl. Come here.
Put you in here for a minute. There we go.
Come on.
Oh, you beauty.
Right.
Just like that.
- Come here.
- Thanks, sweetheart.
Come here.
I just need you in the car, all right?
Impossible.
I'll get in. Have a fiddle around with it.
Okay, I'll be two secs.
Right.
There you are, poppet.
There, the new mobile's sorted for you.
Mama's here.
Good girl.
Go!
How're you feeling?
Like me.
Good.
Hey, monkey, what is it, darling?
She needs a change.
- I'll do it.
- No, it's fine.
She'll make less fuss.
- 'Course she will.
- Come on, stinky trunks.
Let's get you cleaned up.
There we go.
Hey!
Eww!
Hey, Rosie posie.
Kay!
Hey, Rosie.
Kay, give me your head.
All right. Shh...
Shh.
- Kay? Just breathe.
- Stop the car.
- Look at me now.
- Stop the car!
- We need to keep calm...
- Let me out now!
Jesus! Wait!
Christ!
Kay.
Hey, listen. Will you just...
Fuckin' don't touch me!
Andy, you can't control this.
You don't fucking keep this from me!
How long were you going to play along for?
What, until I turn on you?
- On her?
- No.
- You must take her.
- What?
- What are you talking about? Leaving you?
- You must take her.
Stop. Just stop.
Come on.
I'm here, all right?
It'll be all right.
Come on, let's get you up.
We're not going to the hospital.
We are so close.
It puts you and Rosie
further from the river.
There's nothing there for us now.
Yeah there is. Time is there. See this?
That's yours. All of it, every second,
and we're gonna make it count.
But if you bleed out, you'll turn sooner.
It's my call, remember?
So I get no say in that?
I don't have a choice?
No, sweetheart, you don't.
Kay.
I can't do that.
Watch the leg.
Shit!
Kay?
Rosie?
Hey, how're we doing?
Rosie? Rose.
Kay.
Hey.
Blue?
Rosie!
Fuck!
Oh, fuck!
They're coming.
I need you to be a very good girl.
Stay here.
Nice and calm for Daddy.
And he'll be right back.
Hey, Rosie? Be right back.
Oh.
No. No.
Mmm? It's all right.
I know what you like.
Umm.
Hey, Rosie.
It's Mommy.
I can smell Mommy.
I can smell Mommy too.
Hey.
Hey!
Do you know what you just did?
You stay away. Stay back.
Leave my dad alone!
What's the count left on that business?
Uh...
It's 46 hours, give or take.
Sit.
Give us your arm.
Won't do much, I'm afraid.
But it might help you hide it.
Best to do that around these parts.
It's all right, darling.
Who's this then?
It's Rosie.
- Mama.
- Little flower.
Folks call me Etta.
Andy.
This place looked bigger on the map.
- We never fail to disappoint.
- The hospital, is it...
That's a generous description.
It's the next building over.
There's not much left.
They cut our funding years back.
Are you a teacher?
I was.
Where are they now, your students?
Gone.
I'm sorry.
No, not dead. Gone.
Living in the old ways.
Nothing to be sorry about.
They're doing better than the rest of us.
Mobs from all over the country
coming together.
They sensed it,
those who stayed connected.
The whole community
up and left back to their country.
There's a spare bed if you want one.
What do you think, Rosie?
Do we like her?
I think we might like her.
Okay.
Thoomi!
Come home!
Shh.
- what are we gonna do with this?
- Make spears?
Bit like Mom's spaghetti, eh?
Dad!
Back in the old days,
we used to take this from an animal.
Mr. Clever Man!
They're poisoning this land,
you know?
This country, changing.
It's sick.
We all get sick.
You get sick too.
Yeah.
Hey, Etta.
You can't do that. You can't lose hope.
This is Willie Bell.
He's a good man. A friend.
His daughter Thoomi was one of mine.
Smart as a whip.
- Her daddy's shadow.
- Yeah, I've seen them.
Well, you just head right back
and tell Willie that Etta sent you.
If you want to give this baby
a second chance,
that's where you go.
Yeah?
Thanks.
- Have you seen the fires?
- Yeah.
Hunting parties are cleansing the land
of the sick ones. You just stay away.
Hey, Rosie.
Bye bye, darling. Bye bye.
Bye bye.
Now you take care.
Hello, what's here?
Let's give you some water, darling.
That's mine.
Fuck.
Army base is overrun.
There'll be more.
They would have heard that shot for miles.
Better keep that baby quiet too.
Listen, how about you get me out of here
and then I'll get you out of here?
To where?
A place you could hole up for a bit.
The little one, be real nice
for the wife to have that around.
You better think fast. Tow it off me.
Shit.
- Come on.
- Got the keys?
Don't you fuck me.
Good man. Take this.
Come on. Let's go.
Flagged me down on the highway,
this bloke.
Put himself in a spot with some diggers.
Hello.
Attagirl. Close your eyes.
It's nice.
No, it's beautiful.
Rainey'll get you settled.
Do you mind if I put her down?
He doesn't bring people back.
Well, we're very glad
he made an exception, aren't we?
Thanks.
- That's why we're here.
- What, the gas?
Vic has plans
for when things get back to normal.
It's not going to happen. Is it?
I don't think normal is on the horizon.
You worked on the lines?
In the canteen.
I cooked.
Right, well,
that's the most important job of all.
Men must have loved you.
One did.
You're the first people I've seen.
The first people who are still people.
Yeah.
All right, mate, let's go.
They've only just arrived, Vic.
Well, if he's in, he's all the way in.
Rainey'll look after her.
Take her up there, cuddle her.
Won't even notice you're gone.
I'll keep her safe.
Great.
Please look after her.
Okay.
Come on, Rosie. This is...
- You okay?
- Mama!
Yes.
Hey.
This calms her down.
Okay.
- All right...
- See you soon.
Yeah.
Vic.
What's this?
Ever used one of these?
No.
Move forward.
Stand forty-five.
Forty-five degrees to the target.
Now move the stock into your shoulder...
We're going to shoot them?
Yeah.
You're not gonna kiss 'em, are ya?
Now cheek to the cheek plate.
If the target's blurry,
you're doing it right.
- Yeah?
- You got it?
- Uh, I'm not sure. I think so.
- Squeeze the trigger but don't pull it.
- Really?
- Yeah.
If you pull it, then you throw
your sights out. So back up.
Now squeeze.
Feel the resistance. Squeeze...
All right.
Now keep shooting till you drop him...
and don't stop till we got 'em all.
Come on, I can't carry you, mate.
I thought we were here for gas.
- Call it a side earner.
- What's that got to do with her?
Can't catch a fish without bait.
When this country gets back on track,
people are gonna want things.
Whoever controls the market, power, gas...
all the shiny shit...
will be sitting pretty.
I'm just making hay while the sun shines.
The sun's not shining, Vic.
What's it worth to ya?
A safe place for you and your kid?
Only girl you need to be worried about
is your own.
Fill it up.
Hey, it's okay.
No, just low on gas, that's all.
Just low on gas.
Shh.
Hey, Rosie.
I told you mob.
The wells are mine
along with what's in 'em.
Fuck with me...
...and I'll fuck with you.
You look lonely in there.
See if we can drum you up some company.
She's sleeping.
You did well today.
Maybe we can talk about
you staying on permanent.
I cleaned her up.
Oop.
Come on. You're all right. Come on.
Oh.
Hey, Rosie.
I love you.
Come on, you fucker.
Please don't.
Lorraine.
You shouldn't be here.
I know what you're doing, and I know why.
Please, just look after her for me.
I will.
But not here.
- Lorraine, this is as safe as it gets.
- Not from him.
- What's your count?
- It's around 20.
- Take us somewhere else.
- He is not perfect, but here it's secure.
- Your husband...
- He's not my husband.
That man left my husband to die
at the gas plant with everyone else.
Locked them in to save his own skin.
I could protect this little girl
more than he ever will.
But not here.
There is a family by the river.
I don't know if they're still alive.
- I don't know if we can make it in time.
- This looks cozy.
If I didn't know better, I'd think
you were trying to steal my girl, Andy.
You do know better.
Rosie!
Vic!
Come on, let me out, you fuck!
I'm not going to hurt you.
I'm not going to hurt you, okay?
Okay, come with me.
I need to have a look at this.
God, look, I'm not going to hurt you,
I promise you.
When I saw you...
when I saw you yesterday...
I'm sorry about that.
You can be mad at me.
If you want out, I'm your ticket.
Let's play ball.
Do you want to see your friend?
He's not my friend.
I just want my daughter back.
- I want something too.
- What do you want?
His keys to the Clever Man's cage.
Whatever that is, you can have 'em.
- They're coming.
- Huh?
The ghosts. They smell it.
Come on.
Shit.
When this lifts up,
you gotta slide out straight away.
Come on. That's it.
Come on! That's it! Let's go!
Go!
Here, Lorraine, give her to me.
Fucking thief!
Get back here!
- Andy!
- No!
Vic, no!
Rainey!
He's gone.
Come on, let's go.
Wait.
I can smell your rot, you weasly cunt!
- What you took didn't belong to you!
- Shit.
You give me back the fucking black bitch!
She's mine!
If you give her to me, then maybe
there'll be a happy ending for your kid!
But if I have to fucking come looking,
then it'll be bad for you
and worse for them.
Shh.
Maybe I'll just wait
a couple of days, huh?
Until you're not you anymore.
And I'll just watch...
while you eat their fucking faces off.
Good girl.
Thoomi, I need to get back to the river.
Can you show me the way?
I've gotta find the Clever Man.
Oh, look, I don't have time for...
What is a Clever Man, anyway?
Is he just a smart guy, or what?
He's a magic man.
If you're sick,
he can give you good medicine.
And if someone steals your spirit away,
he can put it back again.
Hey, you think your dad is acting
the way he is because he lost his soul?
There are lots of people
walking around like your dad.
- My dad's different.
- I don't think that's true.
There's no fixing
what your father and I have.
Lots of other smart guys have tried.
Where are you going?
I've gotta check something.
Check what?
Thoomi, check what?
For fuck's sake.
Jesus, Thoomi.
Hey, stop!
Go away!
This is sorry business.
You're just a stupid gubba.
You don't know anything.
That's my dad.
We get buried in the trees
so the ghosts can't wake us.
His spirit's still loose.
It's my fault.
I took too long.
No you didn't.
No you didn't. This isn't your fault.
I tied him here till I could bring
the Clever Man back.
They weren't supposed to find him.
They thought
they were doing the right thing.
They did.
That wasn't your dad anymore.
I'm sorry, but it wasn't.
I should have been here,
with him, not you.
Thoomi, I have to go. I'm sorry.
I think Rosie would like it
if you came with us.
I'd be happier if you did.
I don't care about you or your baby.
I don't think you mean that.
She'll be okay.
She'll be okay. Shit.
Shit.
Rosie?
River's this way.
What's with the leaves?
They hide my footprints.
From who? The ghosts?
No, my mom.
Hello?
Hungry?
Yes.
Bingo.
This might sting a little bit.
Where is it?
There? Ready?
Why'd you do that?
It's from the old ways.
But not our ways anymore.
Then why?
'Cause it hurts.
When this hurt heals,
maybe this hurt heals too.
Where did all the people go?
Not far.
The food's still fresh.
Why do you want 'em?
'Cause I want to ask them a favor.
About bub? Are they gonna keep her?
We should think about
what we're gonna do with you.
Maybe they won't come back.
I think they will.
What if they don't?
Then you're all I've got.
Hello?
The caravan's yours.
Car too, if you can start it.
It's not the car I need.
Look.
I've got six, okay?
The last two are yours,
if you go that way.
- Please, don't do that.
- I can't leave them.
I said I wouldn't and I won't, so...
Hey.
Look, Daddy, that man has a baby!
Yes, he does.
Should we say goodbye to the baby?
Yeah.
They're leaving now.
Bye bye, baby!
Hey, mate.
Just take the two.
For her sake.
Where's my pirate, ey?
We gonna come
and find this treasure?
Hey? Come on.
Dad.
Daddy.
Come here, Rosie.
Hey, Thoomi.
Hey.
What's happened to your leaves?
I wanna go home now.
Really?
You want my people?
Yeah.
Yeah, I do.
Thoomi, if I don't make
it to the hills, you...
- You don't have to. See?
- Hmm?
They're close.
Atla.
Fire.
Say atla.
Okay.
- What's that?
- Makes it so the ghosts can't track us.
Really?
- I'd better put some on.
- You don't need any.
You smell like them already.
Proper creepy in there.
Proper creepy out there too.
They're hibernating.
They need the dark.
Vic!
You fuck!
Get the fuck outta there.
Get out!
Don't! Stop!
Shh.
Thoomi! You all right?
Oh, God. Where's Rosie?
Where's Rosie?
It's all right.
Rosie.
Shh.
Give her to me, Vic.
Come on, mate.
We're both fucked.
Vic, I swear to Christ.
If you hurt her...
You took mine, now, I take yours.
Lorraine wasn't yours though, Vic.
Vic, don't...
Don't you dare.
Listen to me, Vic.
It's done.
All right. All right, darling.
All right, darling.
Thoomi?
I know you're hurt, darling.
Stay with me.
Thoomi.
Thoomi, please.
We can't go any further
if you don't walk, okay?
Do you understand me?
Thoomi, wake up. Wake up, darling.
Are you gonna help me?
Let's help each other, yeah?
- Yeah.
- Good girl.
Teach me some of those words, mate.
Teach me how to say, "sun".
Hmm?
Teach me how to say "sky", then.
Christ, teach me something.
Teach me how to say "daddy".
How do you say that?
- Vapi.
- Vapi. Great.
How do you say "daughter"?
- Vapalu.
- Yeah!
How do you say...
What's that word you called me?
Gubba. What was that? What does that mean?
- White fella.
White fella.
Well, how do you say "friend"?
- Mita.
Yeah, mita.
I prefer that one.
Stop.
Come here.
Okay.
Let go.
Come. Help me.
Help me.
Hold onto her.
- Oh, shit.
- Stay close or they'll smell us.
See?
My paint's coming off.
Take it.
Take it away.
Okay.
Now don't worry about this.
You just treat this
like it's mom's spaghetti, okay?
All right.
Look after her for me, okay?
'Cause I'm going now.
Look after her.
Will you do that for me, mita?
- I will.
- All right, mate.
- I promise.
- Thank you.
Hey.
Hey, Rosie, you're in good hands.
You're in good hands.
She's gonna look after you, mate.
I love you.
Love you.
Thoomi. Thoomi, now.
Now.