No!
My purge playlist. I'm having a lot of fun to it.
Especially this final tune.
As it is, it will be the last song you ever hear.
Tough choice.
Then I thought of George Clinton,
the King of Interplanetary Funklinship.
George is psychedelic rock if you're
feeling a little funky obviously.
And soulful, which is the least that I can do.
Now, I played a lot of purge games tonight.
We've just one more. It's simple and effective.
It's called "Mummy's Choice".
Mummy, which one of you will survive this year's purge?
This is just one of a dozen protests around our capital
after reports emerged caliming
that the new founding fathers
have been using the Purge to
help their own economic agenda
in a recent statement by the incendiary purge detractor,
Bishop Dante.
For the past 20 years, the NFFA has taken to legalize
murder to decrease the poor population
which, in turn, keeps the government spending down.
Less welfare, less healthcare and less housing.
Recent polling suggested that
growing of anti-purge sentiments
may have a monumental effect on
the upcoming presidential election.
Establishment NFFA candidate, Minister Edwidge Owens
has been losing ground to wildcard
independent candidate, Senator Charley Roan.
Eighteen years ago, Roan was forced to watch the
brutal execution of her entire family on purge night.
And entered the political arena soon after
with one goal in mind;
to put an end to the annual holiday.
I have no doubt that the soul of our country is at stake.
The Purge has to come to an end.
Senator Roan is proving to be the
greatest threat to the NFFA regime
since they first took office 25 years ago.
Is the cunt that close?
All the polls have her a point behind.
I'm sorry, Caleb. I ..
No need to be sorry, Minister.
You are doing a great job.
Let us put you where you need to be.
Thomas.
We have our people out there
countering all these entire NFFA bullshit.
What else can we do?
We do whatever it fucking takes!
I've had it with all these idealistic pigs.
They want the impossible.
Everyone to have.
Some cannot have. Not enough to go around.
It's time to do something about all these
cocksuckers like that rat, Bishop,
and the cunt Senator.
Trying to dismantle everything we built.
We are going to use this year's purge to
do some spring-cleaning, gentlemen.
And where will you be spending tonight, Minister?
I will once again be presiding over
my party's midnight purge Mass
because I still believe in them.
The midnight purge Mass
where our great NFFA leaders gather
together and slaughter innocents.
Is murder our new religion?
Senator.
Murder's our new religion? Snappy.
Now, the midnight purge Mass is where
NFFA leaders gather to celebrate
the night which saved this country from economic ruin.
We have other ways.
Now, America is built on sacrifice.
From the revolution all the way until World War II.
Our forefathers sacrificed themselves.
Everybody look alive.
Understandably, we watched them.
Must sacrifice every year in order to rid ourselves...
You know what I said. She moves, we move.
Now the stats are undeniable.
There has been far less crime...
This is crap. So I have to listen to this?
Send me to the principal's office.
I can't listen to this anymore.
Okay, we'll send you to the principal's office
if you can't keep your mouth shut.
More low-income people are killed
during the Purge than anyone else.
The money generated from the purge line the
pockets of the NRA and insurance companies.
Any government system that relies on violence
to answer its problems must be...
She's doing good, Leo.
It's time to call upon the better angels of our nature.
At least, we will keep trying.
Jesus Christ, here she goes again.
Secure the audience.
I'm on it.
I'd like to talk to you guys.
Well, at least he was doing it, boss.
She's no good to anyone dead.
You got it, Leo,
Okay, we're on the move.
Copy that.
Please sit down.
I'd like to stay here with you for the rest of the night.
Stay cool and keep it tight.
For purge and purifying.
Hi, thanks.
As she'd done many times before,
Senator Roan broke security
protocol walking off the stage...
I'll tell you this much.
She got some little tits but
she's got some big assed balls.
She ain't got no snowball chance
on steambath in winning this thing,
but she'll be taking on 'em all those white-haired
George Washington wannabe mofo's all by herself.
And to that, I say bully for her.
Oh, horse shit. She's full of it too.
Nothing'll ever change.
Hey, Laney. Laney, Laney,
I think we offend Marcos with our anti senator talk.
The senator's going to win.
It doesn't mean it'll be changes too.
You see. All she need is Florida.
She gets the 29 electoral votes from Florida,
that will take her to over 270.
She can do it.
Smartass.
All that useless shit can't buttered them bagel correctly.
I can butter your bagel, boss.
Oh, you're butter my bagel?
Well, you got a joke over there.
Yes, you just be careful, kid, with all that hope
because it can be a bad thing.
Hope can lead to a lot of letdown.
Tell him I'm Irish, huh?
Excuse me, what?
I'm not paying attention.
I'm thinking about waffle and pussy.
That's all I really think about actually.
Irish Ike, ladies and gentlemen.
What are you laughing at? I'm damn serious.
The new founding fathers believe in fairness.
And we hear what the people are saying.
That the purge benefits the rich and the powerful.
It was never the intention.
From this point on, no one is exempt.
The rules protecting Level 10 government officials
Yeah, come in.
had been revoked.
Are you seeing this?
The NFFA is revoking the purge rules
that protects government officials
of ranking 10 on purge night.
Yeah, I'll secure the safehouse and
full security detail on that night.
No, I'm staying home on purge night.
Senator, I don't think that's a good idea.
If the voters get wind that I'm hiding
in a fortress like some rich asshole,
I'll lose votes and NFFA wins.
I'll stay home like 99 % of the population.
Make it safe, whatever it takes.
Right.
Half the price on all the masks.
Come on inside.
The purge is halloween for adults!
Hordes of young adults are arriving
from Spain, Denmark, South Africa.
They're being called "murder tourists"
because they're here for one reason.
To purge.
We have to experience the purge.
To kill. Release of the anger and hate.
Like the Americans. We're very excited.
[Speaking Danish]
Foreigners coming to our capital to kill.
Murder tourism,
a new building business in our country this year.
Murder tourism.
What's happened to our country, Joe?
Mrs Sabian, I wish I knew.
You take care of yourself, Mrs S.
Next time you need something, just give us a call.
I'll have Marcos run it over, saving you a trip, okay?
I come by to flirt with you, Joe.
What?
No one can take that from me.
Ah, you better get out of here.
Get out of here. Get out of here.
Oh, yes.
Now, she's nasty.
Oh, I like you.
She's nasty. That's a nasty woman.
Joe, come here.
Sonabitch.
Where's he gone?
I've never saw him move so damn fast.
Alright, girls. Give it up.
I won't have to call the police.
Just get out of our face, old man.
Let's not do this the hard way, okay?
I'm giving you a way out.
Right?
Give up the candy or I'll have to take it away from you.
You touch me and I'll screamed rape,
you cocksucking pig.
Now, walk away.
Give it back.
Who are you, bitch?
Better get out of my way!
That's Laney Rucker, Kimmy.
Laney Rucker?
No shit.
Oh, the queen badass?
Yo, they call you the "redeemer".
"Near death".
You're my motherfucking hero.
That makes me proud.
Now give back whatever you stole.
And apologize.
Oh, my God..
Sorry Mister. I am just playing.
So, Miss Rucker...
...what happened to you?
You look all... whitish now.
Later, Miss Rucker.
Wish I'd met you back in the day.
Excuse me.
Uh, well ..
You are lot more respectful then
when you were shoplifting here.
You know,
I distinctly remember one time you call me "sir".
Oh, bullshit.
But listen, I just wanna say thank you.
You're my family, Joe.
I appreciate it.
Thank you, Laney.
I want men in there. I want men in there.
I want a lot of men back there.
She's got some security but I
moved back the entire team.
I want barricades on all the doors,
all the windows, back and front.
Looks safe.
Chief, if you tell me it's safe one more time,
I'm gonna throw you down the steps.
Please don't do that.
Men here.
We've got a security monitoring system in this room.
We've got eyes and ears on everything.
This is her saferoom. She is not to leave her saferoom.
No one is to go inside her saferoom.
Do we understand each other?
This is a mess. She's nopt gonna be happy about it.
I don't care if she's happy, Chief.
I want to go on record to say this is a bad idea.
No matter what we do here, this house
and the Senator are at risk on purge night.
You understand me?
Duly noted. Let's lock it down.
"Let's lock it down.".
It's just me and you, pal.
Tell me what you want me to do, I'm here.
Go downstairs. Make sure they take care of the doors.
Keep an eye on that guy.
Done.
The NFFA has created predatorial capitalism.
Profit is the esence of democracy.
We come to DC to make some changes.
Joe's deli.
Excuse me?
Wait, wait, wait. Hold on. Wait a minute.
Why are you raising my rates now?
Today. You know what today is?
Yes but, look, I ..I can't afford that.
What do you mean you're sorry?
Yes, I'm talking to you. Let me speak to your sup...
Your sup...
Son of a bitch.
Son of a bitch!
Joe?
What the hell's going on?
Damn insurance company.
They'd just raised the premium of my purge coverage...
...by thousands.
The say before the day of purge.
If I don't pay it by tomorrow,
I have no purge coverage for this store.
They can't do that.
Yeah, but they just did.
Just lock the place down, Joe.
Yeah, but that's not enough.
If I have no insurance, I am screwed.
I just have to protect this place myself.
Are you crazy?
That's not a good idea, boss.
Listen, we love this place as you do, Joe.
I've been coming here since I was born.
But it's just stuff. It can be replaced.
You can't be.
Yeah, but what about what you
do on purge night, Laney? Huh?
Is that not the pot calling the kettle brown, no?
That's different, Joe, and you know that.
I'm protected. And you won't be.
This... This is all I've got, guys.
This is my slice of the pie.
Man, I cannot. I can't lose this place.
I just... I can't lose this place.
Come on, Joe. Let's talk about this.
Everything is in place.
The team's in position.
10 minutes to lockdown, boys.
Hey, mamma.
You ready?
Yeah.
Vaya condios.
Okay, let's go.
Okay.
This is gonna be your home for the next 12 hours.
If you need anything,
you contact me, and me only. Clear?
Clear.
Let's begin.
This is not a test.
This is your Emergency Broadcast system.
Announcing the commencement of the annual "purge"
sanctioned by the US government.
Commencing at the siren, any and all crime,
including murder, will be legal for 12 continuous hours.
Here we go.
Police, fire and emergency medical services
will be unavailable until tomorrow morning at 7.00 a.m.
And for the first time since its inception,
no one has been granted special
immunity from the purge.
No citizen or group will be exempt.
Blessed be our new founding fathers
and America, a nation reborn.
May God be with you all.
I see you, Bobby.
You know, you can relax now, right?
I'll relax in the morning.
Am I interrupting?
Senator, you should be in the den.
I want to thank you for being here tonight.
My pleasure.
Leo, have drink with me.
You don't have a choice.
Sound serious.
Don't say a word.
Or I'll stick my foot in your arse.
Sit.
It's water, Leo.
Are you scared?
I'm terrified.
What made you apply for this position?
I liked your politics.
No.
No horse-shit. I want real answer.
I lost my son some years ago.
He was killed.
I must have done something on night purge that would
have destroyed a lot of lives. I want this night gone.
I know you did too.
Especially, after what you've lost.
Yeah.
But despite all that, you...
...you're having problems with how I do things.
You take risks, senator.
My job is to eliminate risks and keep you alive.
You don't make that easy.
The soul of this country is at stake, Leo.
The only way I can win is to risk ..
...everything.
And that includes my life.
Well..
It is time to purge!
Come on!
I hope your night of fun.
Don't you see we're working?
Hey! Asshole!
Just go wait right here and see what happens.
Purge!
They probably won't bother us, okay?
Hey .. dear.
Purge..
Go, go, go, go! Let's move!
Stop! Stop! Please stop!
Please help him!
Oh, something's going down.
Hey, looks like there's somebody who
needs our services. Let's go. Let's do this.
Stop.
I shot my husband.
Calm down. Tell me what happened.
Hey, boss!
It's me. It's me.
Come on out of there, boy.
Good lord, son.
It's purge night. You gonna sneak up on black people?
Good night blue jesus! Where the hell are you going?
And why are you carrying the chair?
I like sitting.
Yeah, but you ain't gonna be staying.
You know I appreciate you coming
out here to watch my back
but I'm good. I got this.
No, I'll stay. Nothing else to do.
Please don't be a pain in the ass.
I want you to go home. You'll be safe.
I don't want you out here on purge night, son.
I got this.
Happy purge, you old fuck!
You better find some place else to go.
I have got a sweet tooth tonight.
And I want my candy bar.
And I'm gonna take it.
You don't have the balls to stop me.
I have the balls.
Now, go!
I'd already took care of my mom and dad tonight.
You're next!
I want my candy bar, cocksucker!
Come on!
What's up with that?
Everyday in Juarez I'd like to purge. 345 00:28:24,408
Son, I really wish you would stay home.
How long.
It's that time.
Erick.
"We are set."
still we're fine, you
the turn of the first floor.
- Do you mind?
- No
Yes, boss.
Chief, find the bedroom.
I got it from here.
Alright, Leo.
Boys, who don't you take a break?
Go to watch some TV, huh?
It's gonna be a long night.
Thank you, sir.
I'm coming outside, boys.
How are you doing out there, Bobby?
Sniper 1, radio check.
Bobby, radio check.
Sniper 2, radio check. Sniper 2.
Someone's coming for you.
What?
Wear it.
Leo, the house is surrounded....
Move, move.
I'm moving. What are you...?
You said you had men on the roof. You had snipers.
Not any more. Not any more.
What do you mean "not anymore"?
Someone betrayed us.
What?
I can't trust anyone. Put on that vest!
Listen to me! This isn't a drill.
Someone's coming to kill you, you understand me?
Move.
I'm moving.
Go!
Okay, what the hell is that?
This is my little secret. Move!
One two three!
Okay.
Boss.
Leo, it's me.
Fuck!
Where the hell is she?
Jesus Christ!
What the fuck is this?
I don't know what the fuck that is.
The mark may be outside. I repeat ..
The mark may be outside.
Check your perimeters.
No payment unless you find her.
Fuck!
I see her!
Stay down!
Move. Go!
Go, go, go!
Hey, guys. You up there?
That Laney?
Marcos!
Oh, my God. How are you doing tonight?
We're good. You?
Uh, I just dropped someone off at triage.
His wife shot him because she couldn't
stand looking at his face anymore.
She said purging didn't make her feel any
better like they said it would.
Stay safe, Laney.
Anything happens.
Do not hesitate to call us.
Yeah, same goes for you.
Okay?
Alright.
God, I hate that she sounds going like that.
Stop, stop!
What..? What is this? Some kind of homegrown militia?
Those are skilled mercs. A lot of money behind it.
Enough to get to some of our staff.
I'm guessing it's the Minister.
Minister of the NFFA.
Fucking liar. I'm getting too close.
There's a lot of blood, Leo. We should call someone.
I don't know who to trust anymore here.
You understand me?
Okay.
Where do we go?
East. Out of the city. There are a lot of threats.
And a lot of deaths.
Purge sanitation services.
Dead collection.
Purge victims removal and disposed.
Keep watch and stay clear.
Its okay.
This sounds good to go now.
Like you said,
the fate of the country is at stake, okay?
It's my show now.
Look, I'm not an idiot.
I know what you're capable of.
I'm the one who hired you.
If I see something I don't like,
I'm not going to be quiet about it. It's not in my nature.
Senator...
I need you to follow me.
Come on.
It's Tommy, sir. He's in bad shape.
He's unconscious.
Everyone else up there is dead.
Well, get him to the ground units, get him stablised.
Then start street surveillance. I'll search from above.
I want him alive, so let's find him before the crazies do.
Sir.
They're tracking us.
Where? I don't see them, how could they see us?
Mercenaries?
No.
That's a home-made drone. Purgers.
Now what?
Run...
...fast.
Come on, come on, come on.
It's behind you, Leo. 35 yards back, 15 yards high.
Get down!
The reason why I'm so hard to you, son, like I am.
Someday, I'd like to make you a partner.
Yep, well...
coming here from another country like you did.
Having your own business.
The American dream's still alive.
Fuck you, American cocksuckers!
We love your American.
America is the greatest country in the world.
[SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
We will little purge.
We will torture you and violate your flesh.
Never!
Remove your skin and share your blood.
This is the American...
Senator.
Come with us.
Stay here.
Yes, yes.
This is my place.
You can stay all night if you want to.
Now, I gotta ask you cause I'm just a nosy old dog.
What in Mississippi fuck was you
doing outside on purge night, Senator?
Yeah. There was an assassination attempt on... me.
I can't thank you enough.
Sir, I'm sorry, I dicn't know you know me.
Dixon. You can call me Joe, senator.
Joe, I'm Charlie.
Charlie.
That's, uh, that's Marcos right there.
Marcos is a... is a fan of yours.
Hi, Marcos.
Senator.
He actually thinks you can win this thing.
Oh, yeah?
Shit. Tell her what she needs to do to win, Marcos.
Go on. It's not my business here.
You saved my life, Marcos. Can't wait to hear it, please.
Florida is the key.
You have to get the elders.
Smart. He's not wrong.
Joe, what do you think?
I don't think you got a damn chance.
Well, have a little faith.
Well, I lost my faith in the system
long time ago, Senator. Water?
Thank you.
This place is moderately secured.
Cameras. Maybe we should stay here.
'Maybe we stay here"?
What... you going... you going out back there yourself?
Joe.
You have a first-aid kit? Leo, my security was shot.
I'm fine.
You're not fine.
You're not. Sit!
You want me to take it off?
It's okay. It's nothing.
Yeah? Don't look like nothing.
Let me see.
I know a little about first aid. I can help you.
The bullet's deep. You need stitches.
Yeah.
We can do it here.
Right. Clean it up, patch it. Go on.
Quick, come on.
What about you guys? Who are you?
Is this necessary?
It's very necesary.
You. What's your name? Where are you from?
Marcos Perez, Mexico City.
But I've been American citizen for 2 years.
You got a record?
Not here.
What did you do in Mexico?
I try to survive.
What're you doing out on purge night?
Protecting the deli against looters because
my boss lost his purge insurance yesterday.
Yeah, that's something you can look into, Senator.
Insurance company screwing the working man.
Yeah?
What's your name, pal?
You know what, Mr Secret Service man.
You should be thanking my black ass
for helping you instead of interrogating me.
His name is Joe Dixon.
Joe Dixon, did I offended you?
Yeah, friend. Just a little bit.
Your feeling is not a concern of mine.
Everyone. Shut up, please!
Look!
Come out, you bitch!
Sound the alert and start the fire!
Oh hell.
Who the hell is that?
The looters I was telling you about.
It's purge night, senator. What so you expect?
Hey, you fuck!
I'm back!
And I brought some friends.
And I'm gonna get that candy bar.
They have chainsaws and they're coming inside.
All right, I gotta get you out of here.
Yeah, but they're at both entrances.
Then I'm gonna purge and kill you
and burn this bitch to the ground.
I gotta call her.
Who?
We have a friend out there with a triage van.
You trust this friend?
And you're still questioning my integrity.
Boy, you are a piece of mark, man.
Come on, come on. Pick up.
This bastard, bastard in this place, I had to go back.
No, no, you're not going anywhere.
I already told your mom, I'll take care of you.
Hurry, quick, and perbanlah so I could go out again ..
Promise me you'll be home tonight.
I wanna purge tonight. I wanna...
Laney! What? Laney!
Really?
Yeah, for real.
You heard me right. Senator Roan.
Call me back, Laney. We need you bad.
She'll call back.
We can't count on your friend.
These kids will be here soon.
What do we do?
Okay, we will work as a team to protect these woman.
You all understand what's at stake here, yes?
Yes?!
Yes.
Alright.
We are gonna purge today.
We are gonna purge today. Burn this bitch down.
Fuck!
Okay, you take the back. I'll take the front.
I'll take the front with you.
No. You're not gonna be in the front line.
Are you crazy? Leo, give me a gun.
I will give you a gun but you're not on the front line.
Over my dead body.
You better drop dead.
I think he's right, Senator.
Thank you, deli man.
Deli man? I agree with you and you still...
Okay, enough! Executive decision.
I'm with Leo. We need as many guns as we can get.
Go, go, go!
Move, move, move!
Get down here.
Just point and shoot.
Do not shoot me.
If I want some candy, I'll take some candy.
I'll take whatever the fuck I want.
My mom's not gonna like this.
It's purge night.
Me getting mine,
you getting yours and there's nobody stopping anybody.
Bye, bye, motherfucker!
Say goodnight, cocksucker,
because here comes your candygirl!
Here they come.
Motherfuckers!
Hold on!
Wait here.
The redeemer is back, bitches.
Hey, guys.
I got your message.
Laney!
This is our girl.
Holy shit. It really is you.
Where do we go?
There.
Go.
Come on, Joe.
I'll be with you in a minute. I'll be there.
Joe, come on.
You've get out of here, kid. I'm staying.
They'll kill you.
Go now!
If you stay, I stay.
Just leave!
Joe, listen to me.
For some reason,
the Senator ended up in my neighbourhood
and your deli.
Maybe it's our duty to help protect her.
We'll rebuild the deli, whatever it takes, you and me.
I promise.
Come on, guys. Now!
Where are we headed?
Underground triage centre service in the community.
It's completely secure.
Extend our perimeter.
They're on foot. They can't be far.
Earl, spoke with the ground units.
Tommy regained consciousness.
Said he had a shot off at the senator's security.
He thinks the bullet is lodged in his shoulder.
How the hell did it get to this?
Who is he?
Why is he cuffed?
Rondo. Two bullet holes delivered by a rival gang,
but he's a good kid.
He's chained up because I didn't
want him to purge anymore.
So, Senator...
NFFA made a move on your ass.
Seems that way.
Goddamn conniving, duplicities, crooked,
cocksucking politicians.
Agree.
We're not all that bad.
From my experience, Senator,
might be better on your own.
No matter what you all say or promise ..
I'm partly confused too.
Who the hell is this lady?
You big dope.
You gave people from the neighborhood a bad name.
Oh, it's just some purgers.
It's cross fire.
Not for us.
Ah, it feels like you're close.
How do you know each other?
Joe gave me the job seven years ago
when I first came here from Mexico.
I've been working for him ever since.
And you?
Joe's been looking out for me since I was a little kid.
And he helps me get out of life.
Sounds like Joe is a saint.
Yeah. Well, I ain't no saint.
I'm just doing my part.
Driving round in a van,
on the purge night, helping people?
It's pretty dangerous.
I'm working for a triage unit alone.
It's true, for most part.
Seriously, Laney. Who the hell are these people?
Down! Everyone down!
Anybody hit?
I'm okay, I'm okay.
You sure?
Yeah.
Laney.
I'm okay.
Jesus Christ! Rondo's dead.
What the fuck was that?
They've found the senator.
I want you to turn left!
Go on to the freeway. Move! Move!
Tonight!
The gates of hell will always be in a fight to the end.
The survival of the fucking fittest.
Who's the fittest?!
I'm the fittest of them all!
Ow, fuck.
Don't lose them under there.
Ground Unit.
Get your asses moving and get here now.
We've got them cornered.
Turn here and stop.
So we just wait here?
No. They'll have units on the ground.
They'll gonna be all over us.
Yeah, but we all better figure out
fast cause I don't like it here.
It doesn't make sense.
There was no way they could have
known that we have this van.
It doesn't matter.
They did.
You son of a bitch.
Leo?
Move over.
Oh.
Leo, what the hell are you doing?
Leo, you...
Tracer bullet.
That's how you notice.
Just leave it here and drive away.
They'll never know we left it.
Yeah, well, I wish it was that simple.
You all need to see this.
There's a whole bunch of negroes coming right this way.
And we're sitting here like a
bucket of motherfucking chicken.
What's your ETA?
2 minutes, Earl.
Open the motherfucking door!
What are we gonna do?
They'll start blasting if we move.
They'll start blasting if we don't.
Hey, now what are we going to do?
What's the plan?
No, no, no. Calm down. Calm down.
What the hell is that?
I know what I heard, I know what I heard.
I told you I ain't no saint.
Everybody's got a past.
That was a Crip's whistle. They just threw it back.
If this is what I said, we should be good.
I know, I know what I heard.
Alright.
We're not going to hurt you. Just help my fucking boy.
He's gonna die.
We help you.
Can you do something for us?
They're still under the overpass but they're on the move.
Get your asses in there.
They've stopped.
Stop the truck.
We're going on foot.
Clear!
Earl, we found a tracer bullet.
But there was no sign of the target.
Yeah, we're heading back.
Rondi, come in.
Come in. I need a fucking sitrep.
Fuck you, motherfuckers!
No one following.
We're clear.
We are a few blocks away.
I'm gonna call in and tell them we have a special guest.
Where are we?
You're safe.
What is this place?
We call this the safe zone.
Senator. Dante Bishop.
Mr. Bishop.
This is Angel.
Dawn call and told me you guys are coming through.
So NFFA came messing tonight.
Can't say I'm surprised.
Let me show you around. Get yourself a den.
You set all this up, Mr. Bishop?
Yes, this is my organization.
We have doctors, nurses, EMTs and paramedics.
This is their way of protesting this day and night.
How many people know about this place?
Just the volunteers.
And all those that we invite in.
Look, these are the real victims of the Purge.
The people that the NFFA are trying to eliminate.
So that they don't have to take care of them anymore.
These men. They're armed.
Are they guarding all the entrances and the rooftop?
Yes. My people will keep you safe.
Or as safe as you can be on purge night.
I appreciate it.
Mr. Bishop.
Yeah.
Thank you for all of this. I am... impressed.
Well, don't thank me. Thank the volunteers.
Mr. Bishop.
I've heard stories...
of tactics that you will employ on the purge night.
I can't say that I agree with any of it.
Tell you what.
You get elected. You stop this night...
...and I don't have to do what I do anymore.
Let's go, Angel.
Fair enough.
Get down to Fourth street. Keep an eye out.
Keep watch and be quiet.
All right, let's go! Come on.
I want access to the surveillance cameras in the city.
Do a grid search for the fucking triage van.
It's out there somewhere. Find it.
Boss.
You're doing the right thing.
Yeah?
But it's time to go.
And get back to the deli.
What? No. Are you fucking crazy?
We're safe here.
Laney, you know I'll walk back if I have to.
Fine. I'll drive you.
But if we ran into any problems,
we're coming right back here.
Deal.
Is it true? You can do that?
We'll see her again, Marcos.
Well, she's safe here.
Let's hit it.
I don't know if you find it amazing but I think it's cool.
Hey. You okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
I'm gonna go take a look around.
Okay.
Stay here.
Okay, boss.
What are you doing here?
Hand.
Why are you here?
What the hell going on here?
He slipped in here.
Hey, hey. Okay, okay.
Hey! Hey!
It's alright. It's alright.
Rev, back up.
It's okay.
Just put the gun down, alright?
Everybody's okay. Backup.
We're okay.
Alright?
Alright? You're good.
It's all good, okay?
I'll just get my weapon.
What's going on?
Just doing my job.
Senator, this is just a misunderstanding.
Why don't we go back outside?
Come on.
You seeing this, Leo?
Yes, ma'am.
Senator, why don't we go outside?
Stop.
Those are the Minister's biggest financial supporters.
The NFFA.
Our Lady Of Sorrow.
Senator, why...
Is... Is that where the Minister going to be tonight?
For the purge mass?
We believe so.
You sure...
What's is all this?
Why do you have all this?
You're going to assasinate him.
You're going to assasinate the Minister tonight,
aren't you?
You know, somebody got to say it out loud.
What in the fool happened tonight?
Nobody's gonna believe it.
No.
I wish I could be, like, bullshit.
Now, where can my waffle and... pussy...
He had a one track mind. That boy had lost his head.
Shit.
I hope he's okay tonight.
Yeah.
Hold on, guys. Look.
Those are government trucks.
I saw them on Youtube from last year's purge.
They're going straight back to the safe zone.
You cannot do this.
I want to win fair and fucking straight.
They're not playing fair and fucking straight
and neither should we.
His church will be locked up like Fort Knox.
You'll never get through. You'll be slaughtered.
Fourth Church will be on that side.
The original bio by George Washington,
more than 200 years ago.
The man likes to have escape tunnels attached
to all his churches. They're all over DC.
The tunnel of the original church
have been closed up since the 50s.
But we re-open it.
We'll gonna walk right through there and
into the church without anybody even knowing.
The original founding fathers are about
to fuck over the new founding fathers.
Now, how do you like that for irony?
How do you know where this mass is gonna be?
Because we do whatever it takes.
We did this for you, Senator.
No, it's not for me.
Get your boss on the phone. I need to talk to him.
He is not here.
Angel, listen to me. You call him!
You tell him.
He does this and the Minister becomes a martyr.
I cannot have my presidency built on murder.
Do you see that?
You can't just leave it to the voters.
He does not believe in the American system.
Angel, believe in me.
We do. That's why we are trying to pave a way
for you to the White House. So you can make changes.
You're going to get people killed!
You are right!
It's Laney. She said there's trucks approaching us.
What?
Who is that?
Government soldiers.
It's the NFFA eliminating all the enemies for sure.
They're after Bishop but they will kill you.
We need to evacuate your people.
I can't leave the engine.
I need to get her out of here now.
There is a way out in the back.
Where does it come out?
Out all the way to 3rd and Thomson.
3rd and Thomson. Give me the phone.
Laney, I'll meet you at 3rd and Thompson, now!
Yeah, we'll meet you there.
So, we're driving all the way back to the war zone?
Stupid!
Oh, these people.
We will protect them.
Please, stop the assasination.
It's too late. Now go!
Go
Stay safe.
So what we supposed to be like?
Some sort of superhero or something?
It ain't what I do.
Super hero? I hate this night!
Oh, shit!
Hell's waiting. Come on.
Let's do it. Let's go get them.
I can't believe we're outside again.
We'll get you through this.
Oh, god! Got it so close!
Damn!
Are you fucking kidding me?
Ready?
Yeah.
One, two...
Go!
Good luck out there.
# Let me hear your whisper.
# That you love me too
Let's go! Let's go! Come on, I've got you.
You guys okay?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Again.
Where are we? headed
Drive.
Out of this city. Get us out of here.
You're okay, senator?
No, Marcos. I'm not.
It's a nightmare for everyone.
Senator.
I can't win like this.
It goes against everything I believe in.
We need to focus on one thing right now,
and that's survival.
I need to make sure you get through this tonight.
I have to stop them from killing a minister?
What?
If they assasinate Edwidge, he becomes a martyr.
We lose.
Yeah, and how do we do that?
I don't know. We have to do something.
Do what?
You want to risk your life saving the guy's hide...
Everybody alright?
Leo, you okay?
He's okay.
Damn!
Oh, my God!
I know where they're taking her.
I know why she's still alive.
Where?
You find a safe place to hide. You stay there.
No. No way.
Whatever it is you plan on doing, we're coming with you.
Let's go.
No!
Help! Help!
Let me go!
No! No!
Come on, guys. It is enough.
Get paid to deliver the package. Not gift wrap.
Come on. Let's go find a place to
wait out the rest of this fucking night.
Please!
As we always do.
Blessed be the new founding fathers.
Let us purge and cleanse our souls.
Blessed be America.
A nation reborn.
It's been a long journey...
...to get away from the lies and self-deception.
To this place of knowledge and
awareness of who we really are.
People flesh immensely deformed.
Oh, it's hard to see the ugly truth,
but change can only come from acceptance
And change we must as it is our
godly duty to get rid of the fury
and the hatred that poisons our souls, makes us sick!
Make us ugly!
Tonight, we the leaders of this great country
will sin, scour, sanitize and sterilize our souls
until we are free again,
and this country will be better purged.
We are not hypocrites!
We practice what we preach.
Purge and purify, say it with me.
Purge and purify. Purge and purify. Purge and purify.
Let's us begin.
Now, look. It's after midnight.
We need a pool. I need a 4-men team in there.
I need three with me. Got it?
Go!
Bishop!
I'm unarmed.
How well do you know this Dante?
Not well. So, keep your eye on Leo.
Our boy's gonna get himself killed.
I'm unarmed.
You know this lunatic, Dante?
Yeah, I do.
Guns down!
What the hell are you doing here?
Trying to get yourself killed?
That's the tunnel to the cathedral?
How the fuck do you know about the tunnel?
I asked you a question.
This is no longer assasination.
It's a rescue mission.
Jesus died for their sins!
Do not try you dare touch me!
And now our modern day martyrs,
would die for our pleasure.
Do not disturb him!
Our martyr's name is Lawrence.
A life-long drug addict.
He wants to make amends.
He wants to serve his god...
...and his government.
Let's thank Lawrence for his gift.
Thank you, Lawrence! I love you!
Thank you very much.
We love Lawrence.
These weapons have been cleansed with holy water.
And now there are now instruments of destruction.
No!
Fuck! No!
You all know the lawyer, Harmon James?
Working with the NFFA tirelessly for many years.
Harmon will be the first purger of the evening.
Oh, God, please, do not, do not!
Please .. please .. please .. please ..
Please .. please .. please .. please, please ..
Do not, please! Please do not .. do not!
Let me go! No!
Do not let go!
Release her, Harmon.
No!
Remove the violence from your darkened heart.
Purge your soul. Let the light in!
You are baptized with the light! Gone!
Disappear!
His light entered your heart, Harmon.
Yes!
The power of purging!
Purge and purify!
Purge and purify! Purge and purify! Purge and purify!
Purge and purify! Purge and purify!
Listen. No matter what happens, we stay together.
Okay, this will take us to the mechanical room.
From there we can access the cathedral.
Stay there. Where do we go?
The church is above us.
So, our pretty Secret Service agent,
you'll gonna take the staircase to the balcony.
Me and my guys will enter from behind the altar,
on this side.
Okay, good. Let's go get our girl, yeah?
Before we get to our communal purge.
A holy war for many martyrs.
I'd like to introduce a guest.
He's going to be the centerpiece of a...
very special purge ceremony tonight.
This person...
...has threatened to dismantle everything
that we, the new founding fathers, had done.
We must rid ourselves...
...of the negative emotions.
But she had stood in silence.
We must stop her from poisoning our great country.
Taking away our freedom!
Yes.
I would like all the founding fathers to come to the altar.
Join me, purgers.
As we eliminate evil...
...and purge as one.
We ask You to receive this child into your loving arms.
We are sinners. Let us release.
Caleb, our leader. I invite you, sir,
to lead us in this purge.
As you have and as you will.
Blessed be our new founding fathers.
Let us purge.
No!
And blessed be America, a nation reborn.
Rifle!
Run!
She's alive!
Get down!
Briole?
What are you all doing up there?
Bring your ass down here.
My negro.
Let's go!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Thank you... again.
What was that?
My men taking care of business.
Go, go!
We're headed out. Back there.
You have him?
We have him.
Move!
Hey!
Listen to me!
You listen to me!
Look, you're not supposed to, please!
About what?
Josh, hold a minute!
Move!
And listen to me!
I thought I'd wait it out.
I can win without it! Please!
I will be back!
You will win. I'm gonna make sure that happens.
Open up!
Stop.
This is a murder.
If you do this, you will not be different than them.
Get her.
Move! Move!
Listen to her!
She knows what she's doing.
We don't need to do this.
Hang on, Dante.
You get out of my way!
Uh, please! Oh, God!
Don't do this!
If you do this, you will be no different from them.
We need to can't be like them.
Look at me.
Purge, my son.
Purge...
It's your right as American.
Kill me. Kill me.
Your son is gone.
God won't...
Shut up the fuck up!
Coward.
Purge!
Do it, do it! Yes! Yes! Kill me!
Let me tell you right now. I like black people.
But, I will not let you all shoot these white folks.
These are our white people, okay?
So, let's put them down.
You better fucking win.
Go! Go!
Move!
Oh, my God!
You murderous pig!
I am going to beat the shit out of you on election day.
I'm not as thrilled to be correct as the senator.
Goodnight, blue jeans.
Well played, Leo.
Thanks, Joe.
Get going, man! Fucking pig!
I'm not gonna... I'm not gonna hurt you.
I'll get you out of here!
Stay here! We'll find a vehicle.
What about these people?
Back, back, back! Get back!
You got this.
You know I got this.
How bad is it?
Not good.
I've got one more move in me. Cover me!
Go!
Shit! Keep him quiet!
Shut him up before he draws all kind of attention.
Shut up! Shut up!
You motherfucker!
Get up!
Motherfucker.
You know, this is great! You're safe!
Get me out of here!
Let me out! Okay! Let me out!
Stop him!
Hang on, Joe.
Come on! Don't! Let me help!
Don't. Okay. We gotta get you somewhere.
Okay, you're gonna be okay.
Well, there's no way to take me.
You'll gonna be fine. That's what important.
She's gonna make sure, right, senator?
Yeah.
You got this.
I got this.
Uh, Marcos.
Uncle Joe, Joe, Joe.
Joe, it's me.
No!
Wake up, Joe!
Wake up! Joe!
That was Senator Roan this morning
casting the first vote of the day.
It's been a great day for the senator so far
having already won New York, California,
and... wait, hold on, I am getting word right now.
That the senator has also taken Florida
which puts her well over the
270 electoral votes for the win.
So, that is it. It is now official. The next president
of the United States will be Charlie Roan.
And president-elect Roan already
stated that her first order of business
will be taking executive action
to put an end to the Purge.
Updates?
With a landslide.
Alright, I'll come by tomorrow.
We can get started on the ceiling.
Sounds good.
The place is really coming along, Marcos.
Joe will be really happy.
I'll catch you later, kid.
We're just now hearing reports about a
few scattered incidents around the country
where NFFA supporters are
reacting violently to this defeat.
They are burning cars, breaking windows, riot,
attacking police officers...