[eerie music]
[♪♪]
[radio static]
[screams]
[dramatic music]
[♪♪]
[panting]
[screams]
[gunshot]
[screaming]
[dramatic music]
[♪♪]
[softly sobbing]
[door closes]
[dramatic music]
[♪♪]
[crying]
[dramatic music]
[♪♪]
He won't get far.
Help.
[crying]
[screams]
[car engine turns over]
[suspenseful music]
[♪♪]
[eerie guitar music]
[dramatic music]
[♪♪]
[radio static]
[muffled chatter]
You still awake?
[groans]
In the middle of a
high speed chase.
This better be important.
I just feel so good
knowing you're out there
keeping us safe.
[laughs]
And yours on your end?
There's a mess of chatter
from state police, but it
sounds like they got
it under control.
Anyway, you're about up so
we'll see you when you get in.
[yawns]
Okay.
Hold on.
Looks like I got
some kind of a...
drunk teenager.
I don't know.
Hey!
Hey, buddy, you know
it's a little cold to be
crawling all the way home.
Stand by.
[exhales]
Big night, huh?
[laughs]
Holy shit.
Dispatch, where am
I taking this guy?
Closest emergency services
is still Marsh County.
Not sure what's left
of it after the fire.
I think they're moving, but
they're still listed on duty.
Okay, uh, how about Lakeland?
It's another twenty
minutes at least.
It's your call.
Okay, you call ahead to Marsh.
Let them know it's me
that's bringing him in.
You call ahead.
[sirens blaring]
[eerie music]
[♪♪]
Can I get some help here?
Uh, Bev, I need hands up front.
Bring a stretcher.
Dispatch not call ahead?
What?
We didn't get a call.
Bev!
Uh, wanna get his feet?
Yup, I'll get him.
- Okay. One, two, three.
- One, two, three.
[grunts]
Alright.
[moans]
Are you okay?
Can you hear me?
What's his story, Danny?
Uh, he's bleeding, Bev.
We're gonna take care of you.
Beverly, we gotta get him on a
monitor and into Dr. Powell.
Let's go.
[clatter]
Oh.
Hi.
[groans]
Coming back on the air after an
interruption due to
technical problems.
What's that about?
Who knows.
They won't let me do
anything around here.
Oh, here's a good one.
De-gloving.
There's a picture.
Ugh, Jesus.
You know, statistically,
you're more likely to die
in a hospital than
anywhere else.
Cool.
Well, I could give
you a catheter.
That could be fun.
Are you even a nurse?
[sighs]
I am in training.
That's so cool.
How about I'm just gonna
go to sleep, okay?
I should go anyway.
I guess you won't
be needing this.
Goodnight.
All messed up.
Well, uh, in time, would
you say you ought to be
able to wrap this up...
[static]
Well, you sure know how to
make an entrance, Danny boy.
Yup.
How you feeling, Maggie?
I've been having some pains.
Dr. Powell says the baby
might be on it's way.
Yup, she's kicking up a storm
in there that's for sure.
[laughs]
Anyhow.
I'm just glad the
doc stuck around.
That fire really did a
number on this place.
And I can't afford to be
driving her into the city
every time that
kid gets fidgety.
Give it a rest, grandad.
[laughs]
[indistinct chatter]
Let go of me!
- Stop!
- Calm down.
Calm down.
- One more second.
- Let go of me!
- Stop!
- Just one more second.
Easy. Breathe.
Okay.
I'm not gonna miss this.
You gonna be able to
handle him, Richard?
Your friend here's
had quite a trauma.
Well, not that we have any
ID bracelets left, but for
the record his name is James.
How bad is he?
Well, he's not been
very cooperative.
The sedative will help us
determine exactly what his
condition is, but our
resources are limited here.
Everything's been
packed up for the move.
Looks like James here isn't
any stranger to needles.
Where'd you find this guy?
He fucking bled on me.
Kim, I know getting
transferred over here
wasn't your first choice,
but you're supposed to be
boxing up files.
No, there are things
called computers now.
[scoffs]
Can computers put
files in boxes?
Thank you!
[sighs]
So old school.
[groans]
You might need something
a little stronger
if you're gonna get
that stain out.
[mumbles]
Whatever, fuck.
I can do my own laundry.
Well! Look at you.
Brought you uh, coffee.
Nice.
I was looking for that.
It's mine now so don't
you get any ideas.
Right.
[laughs]
You're being friendly.
It's good to see you.
Uh... I'm sorry.
Am I interrupting something?
- No, no.
- No. No, no, no.
I'm just gonna go make sure Bev
hasn't murdered my intern.
I'll see you.
[sighs]
Our guest is out for now.
He's not badly hurt, but
it will be a while before
you can talk to him.
Fuck.
You should be
gentle with Alison.
She's still coming to
terms with what happened.
Yeah, okay.
As you know Daniel,
there's nothing worse than
losing a child.
When we lost Sarah,
I was a mess.
It took a long time to
come back from that.
You just have to keep going.
Yeah.
[footsteps]
[crying]
Beverly.
Are you okay?
What?
Jesus Christ.
[dramatic music]
[♪♪]
What the fuck are
you doing, Bev?
Beverly?
This isn't my face.
What, Bev?
No, no, don't do that.
Bev!
Put the scissors down.
Look at me!
Bev, okay, stop!
It's not me.
No, no, no, don't do that.
Bev.
Can you help me?
Bev, Bev, stop!
No, no, no!
Beverly, stop!
[gunshot]
Oh, fuck.
[eerie music]
[♪♪]
Daniel!
Daniel, what?
- What did you do?
- What the fuck?
Kim. Kim, get out of here.
[indistinct chatter]
Kim, you don't need to see this.
She killed him.
I, uh...
She came at me.
She came at me. Okay.
Alright.
Was that a gunshot?
Uh...
My god, what happened?
Beverly, she attacked
Daniel and the Robinson kid.
Okay, I gotta call
this in. I gotta call...
Give yourself a second, okay?
- Just calm, calm down.
- Tell them. I gotta...
- Just give me a second.
- Can you just call
- from the office?
- Give me a second.
[puking]
[water running]
[eerie music]
[♪♪]
[echoing groans]
[groans]
How are you feeling?
What?
I'm fine.
Shh.
I'm okay.
Take it easy, Daniel.
It looks like you might
have had a seizure.
No, no, no, no.
If you're feeling dizzy, Daniel,
you shouldn't try to get up.
Okay.
Just sit down, okay?
Come on.
I gotta call it in.
No, you need to take it easy.
There's a state
trooper already here.
What?
Oh god, how long was I out for?
Not long.
Apparently, he was
already on his way.
Something to do with
that kid you brought in.
Look, it's not
important right now.
This trooper's probably
gonna wanna talk to you.
We should see about
moving you to a room.
No, no, no.
You just experienced an
extremely traumatic event.
Okay.
Okay, look.
You are stubborn like
your father was now.
You should take
this very seriously.
I-I am, I am.
I'm good.
Alright.
Daniel.
Mitchell.
There you are.
So what happened?
They told me you found
the two of them together.
Uh, yeah.
He was dead when I arrived
and she came at me with a
pair of scissors.
How did you get here so fast?
Your guy in the other room.
What about him?
We got a major bloodbath about
twenty miles north of here.
Looks like he tore the
place up like a butcher shop.
Uh, yeah.
We looked him over and
most of the blood on his
body was not his.
Well he has a long list
of drug related priors.
So I think he gave
your nurse something.
I've got him cuffed to the
bed for the time being.
He's been out cold.
Well I'm here now.
I'll sort it out.
I need to take your firearm.
Yeah.
You know, Carter, your
dad was a stand up cop.
I wonder what he'd think
if he saw this shit show.
Okay, we need to make sure
everybody's accounted for.
Who else is here?
Dr. Powell and Kim.
Oh, and um, Ben and Maggie.
She's pregnant.
Christ, what a mess.
Hey, uh, do you mind
if I call it in?
Alright.
Thanks.
[radio static]
I'm not getting through in here.
Are you copying, Mitchell?
I'm gonna try the car.
Copy.
[keys jingling]
Dispatch, this is
Carter at Marsh County.
Do you copy?
[radio static]
Dispatch, this is
Carter at Marsh County.
Do you copy?
I have a code three
and I need assist.
[radio static]
Fuck!
[suspenseful music]
[♪♪]
Hi!
What the fuck are you doing?
[eerie music]
[♪♪]
Shit, shit!
[groaning]
[dramatic music]
[♪♪]
Help me!
Daniel, Daniel, Daniel!
Richard!
He's losing a lot of blood.
Keep pressure over the wound.
Daniel, it's fine.
Look at me.
Kim, I need you to bring me a
Sutra kit and 8mg of morphine.
Keep your eyes on
me, you hear me?
Did you hear what I said?
Kim?
Kim, what are you doing?
Kim, did you hear me?
For fuck's sake, come here.
You'll be alright, Daniel,
you'll be alright.
Keep breathing.
Put both your hands here.
Firm pressure.
- Okay.
- Don't stop.
You keep him awake.
Keep your eyes on him.
- Keep his eyes on you.
- Good boy, Daniel.
- Good boy.
- Kim!
Don't let him close his eyes.
- Hey! Stay awake.
- Stay awake, Daniel, stay awake.
Hey!
[eerie music]
[♪♪]
[heart beating]
Daniel.
Daniel?
I've stopped the
bleeding for now.
Oh, thank god.
[mumbling]
We know.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey.
Okay, maybe don't try
to get up just yet.
What happened out there?
Just give him a second.
It looks like they've got
the place surrounded.
They're not trying to get in.
Who are they?
I don't know.
I wasn't able to
get through. You?
No.
We should move
everyone back inside.
Who knows what they want.
No, maybe we can barricade
the doors or uh, you know,
get out some other way.
[screaming]
Shit.
I forgot about him.
[screaming]
Do something!
[yelling]
Fucking shoot it!
Oh my god, please!
Do something!
[deep groans]
Help me!
[gunfire]
Oh my god, fucking
help me, god damnit!
Help me, help me!
[dramatic music]
[♪♪]
[deep groans]
[suspenseful music]
[♪♪]
[shrieking]
What is that?
I think that was Beverly.
[shrieking]
Jesus, what the hell was that?
We're leaving.
Now, now, now, now.
[glass breaks]
Hey, that's not a
good idea, Daniel.
Wait, wait, wait.
What about those fucking
lunatics out there?
We got other things to
worry about, believe me.
Mitchell, Mitchell!
You and I, let's go
get the cars, okay?
Are you with me?
[banging at door]
[screams]
What the hell was that?
Make safe, back up.
Stay away from the doors!
- He's got a gun.
- Back, back, back.
Okay, make safe.
Make safe.
[screaming]
Okay, okay, drop it!
Whoa!
Okay, drop it! Drop it!
Fuck you.
Get the fuck back.
Okay, put it down.
Stay calm, stay calm.
Whoa, everybody, just stay calm!
Stay the fuck away from me.
[heavy breathing]
Calm down!
[clattering]
Okay! Put down the
gun, it's okay.
Everybody just calm down.
- Calm down, you said?
- Richard, Richard, Richard.
No, no, no.
[indistinct mumbling]
There's no reason to
involve her in this.
Richard.
It's not gonna help you.
Listen.
Just give me the knife and
this will all be over.
It isn't gonna help you.
Richard, I don't know
what to fucking do!
Don't worry, Maggie.
He's not going to hurt you.
Just let me have it.
[chaotic yelling]
[screams]
- No!
- Richard!
Kim, Kim!
I got him, I got him.
[suspenseful music]
[♪♪]
Kim.
[nervous crying]
Look at me, look at me.
We are not gonna die
in this fucking place!
Nobody wants to be in here
any longer than we have to.
Believe me.
No, he's not going anywhere.
[suspenseful music]
[♪♪]
[indistinct yelling]
Fucking idiot!
[chaotic yelling]
[suspenseful music]
[♪♪]
[gunshot]
[slithering]
Alright.
What the fuck was that?
Sweetheart, you're
gonna be fine.
You're gonna be fine.
Fuck's sake, he stinks.
[gurgled yelling]
Mitchell!
[groaning]
[muffled screams]
[screams]
Stay back!
[dramatic music]
[♪♪]
[bullet shell drops]
[gunshot]
[yelling]
[suspenseful music]
[♪♪]
[panting]
Oh, fuck.
[door opens]
Get in the office.
Get in the office now.
Now, now!
Get in the office.
Okay, go to the office!
What the fuck was that?
I'm not gonna argue
with you. Go, go!
You need to tell
me what's in there.
I don't know what's in there.
- But please, just go.
- Lock the door.
Okay. You hold on.
Who are you?
Get the fuck away from me.
Whoa, whoa, just slow down.
Who are you?
Just tell us that.
I want him.
Okay, look.
- Alright?
- Alright.
I think we all agreed that we
need to get the hell out
of this building, right? These
personal differences, they're...
[thud]
Oh, Daniel!
Stop.
No one is going anywhere.
Okay, alright.
Okay.
We don't know anything
about this place.
If you let us here,
we can trust them.
You don't need to do this.
Stop!
He can't answer you.
Shaun!
See?
That's what the last
people he trusted did.
No, you're making a mistake. You
can trust us, you can trust us.
I don't think so.
[chaotic yelling]
Wait, wait!
Please, please!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Get your hands off me.
[panting]
Are you okay?
You calm down.
Okay, we're good.
You wanna go through
all this again?
I know you believe me when
I tell you we don't know
what the fuck is going on, okay?
I...
There were things
growing out of her.
You saw it, you saw it.
What was that?
We could uh, burn what's
left of the place.
Take them all with it.
Okay, listen to me.
We didn't do anything to you.
I have a girl back there
who's about to give birth
and I need to get
her some place safe.
Are you fucking kidding?
Have you had a
look outside lady?
There's nowhere to go.
You can hear those
horns for miles.
There is something
calling them all here.
Okay, what is that?
Who are they? What just...
How the fuck should I know?
- Go ask them!
- It's okay, it's okay.
All I know is that that
thing woke up once already
and I don't wanna be around
when it happens again.
[door opens]
Oh, there's a problem.
Maggie.
I didn't know what to do.
Okay.
Hey, sweetie.
Are we leaving?
No, not just yet.
Would you put that out?
Al.
- What, this?
- Yeah.
Put it out.
Okay.
I think we all should
just remain calm.
Bullshit.
We should've been
out of here already.
You people need to wake up.
Or what?
You think you'll stand a
chance if there's another
one of those things out there?
- Okay.
- Will you, huh?
- Okay, okay.
- Who's gonna stop it? Grandpa?
The teenage fucking slut.
Oh! Come on now!
Whoa, whoa!
Come on.
We're gonna die.
[crying]
No, we're not gonna die.
You're gonna die.
I'm not gonna let that happen.
Okay.
I don't know what the fuck
you think you're trying to do.
Okay? Just calm down.
He's upsetting her
and that is not good.
- I need you to stay calm.
- Okay.
Can you please tell me
what is going on over there?
Her contractions are still
spread out, but she's
having abdominal pain
which is a bad sign.
Okay, I don't know
what that means.
What does that mean?
That means that
we can't move her.
It can make things much worse.
Also the last thing I need
is to be performing a
cesarean in the middle of
this, but I have nothing
here to help her and if I don't
do anything the baby could die.
I need to go to the
med supply room.
So I'll go.
Alone? No, no, no,
that's out of the question.
I'm not asking.
We need to handle this now.
Alright.
Okay, look.
We have no idea
what is out there.
We have no way of
defending ourselves.
Plus these two fucking
psychos now think that
we're hostage.
I'm doing this.
You're not. You're not.
You're not even...
If this is because of the
baby then you need to get
a fucking mental check.
Jesus Christ, this
is not about us.
That girl, if she
suffers an abruption
then her baby will die.
If I try to take it out
of her, and I don't use
anesthetic then she
could die of shock.
Daniel, look at me.
Okay, fine.
Fuck it, fuck it.
Uh...
Okay, but you're
not going alone.
You have to promise and wait
for me, okay? You promise?
- Okay.
- Alright.
May I approach?
The girl's not doing well
and neither is the baby so
we need to go and get
some things to help her.
What do you want from us?
Well I have a shotgun
in my cruiser.
I have ammunition.
[laughs]
We just fought our way in here.
I'm not gonna just
stroll back out again.
Okay, but as far as I can
tell we're all the same boat.
You've got a rifle without
any bullets and a couple
of fucking fire axes.
I just...
it's close and we
can do it fast.
[sighs]
Alright, but we're not
risking our lives for you.
We get that gun, it's ours.
Oh, absolutely.
Abso-fucking-lutley.
Okay.
I thought you said it was close.
What the hell?
It's still out there.
Yeah, but what are
they waiting for?
Let's just make this quick.
Shotgun's locked
on the front seat.
I gotta release it, but...
you get all the ammo
out of the trunk.
Don't get any bright ideas.
Hey, hold up.
God damnit.
What if they don't come back?
Daniel knows what he's doing.
It's alright.
I shouldn't even
be here right now.
I should be at Lakeland
turning over patients.
Fuck this place.
Well, you're stuck with us
now, Kim, so deal with it.
[soft sobs]
How you doing, honey?
It hurts.
What's gonna happen to my baby?
Listen to me.
You and your baby are
going to be fine.
You have my word.
[suspenseful music]
[♪♪]
Shit.
Fuck.
What the fuck are
you doing in there?
[suspenseful music]
[♪♪]
[screeching sound]
What the fuck's
going on in there?
Ah, shit.
K, time's up.
That's our cue to leave.
[eerie music]
[♪♪]
Come on, god damnit!
Fuck's sake!
Fucking hurry up!
Look out!
[gunshot]
I'm keeping the fucking gun.
This place isn't gonna
keep anything out.
Oh my god.
Hey.
Fuck.
What happened?
Here, here.
Where's Allie?
Well she went to get some
medicine for Maggie.
Where?
The med room.
Jesus Christ.
She said there wasn't
anything to worry about inside.
Are you guys in the
same fucking building?
Would you please wait
here, look after them?
Excuse me, sir, would
you mind following me?
Thank you.
That kid will be fine.
He's been through a lot worse.
Those people killed his family.
I barely got him
out of there alive.
Yeah, what about
you, man of mystery?
Mind your own business.
And by the way, pretty
stupid to go running off
by herself.
Okay, I'm pretty certain
you can beat the shit out
of me, but I consider it
my special privilege to
hate my wife right now so
if you could kindly shut
the fuck up.
This is Mitchell's gun.
Look.
What?
[phone ringing]
Hello, Daniel.
Who is this?
You saw...
something.
I felt it when you woke up.
But what was it?
I can show you
more if you'd like.
Hi, Richard.
I'm sure it's hard
for you to understand.
Beverly found it difficult
as well, but I assure you
my intentions are altruistic.
Please tell me what you've done.
Richard.
Richard, tell me.
Tell me!
You're trying so hard to
follow in your father's
footsteps, Daniel.
Do you really wanna follow
him where he's gone?
I understand how desperate
loss can make you.
The night you brought
Allison to me, the life
inside her desperately
clawing to get out.
Losing my daughter changed
me, but I'm doing what I
have to to make it right.
You'll understand soon enough.
Just please, can you please
tell me where Allison is?
Just...
You tell me, god damnit.
You tell me where she is.
Don't worry, Daniel.
I'm gonna help her.
I'm gonna help all of you.
[suspenseful music]
[♪♪]
This is crazy! I don't
know what I'm doing.
You can't just leave us.
Kim, Kim, Kim.
We don't have a choice.
Allison's the only one who
knows how to look after Maggie.
Please, look.
Just...
these still seem to work inside.
No.
We'll keep in
touch just in case.
We're not gonna be gone
long, we're not going far.
- Look.
- It hurts.
It hurts so bad.
I don't know what
half this stuff is!
Please, please don't...
Listen to me.
Listen to me, please.
We're just gonna down
there, I'm gonna bring
back Allison, and I need you to
hold out until then, alright?
What if something happens? What
if those people get in here?
What are we supposed to do?
Those people are not
trying to get in here.
Those people are trying to
keep us from getting out.
Okay, that's the
best that I can do.
I hope you know how to use it.
And uh...
that's there just in case.
You better know
what you're doing.
[suspenseful music]
Okay, let's go.
You think were just gonna go
down there and that'll be that?
If you have something to say
than say it, you smug fuck.
Do you know what's down there?
Nope.
But I know someone who might.
Hey.
Hey, meth boy.
Oh shit.
Oh, good, you remember us.
It's not my fault, okay?
You gotta believe me.
I didn't fucking do anything.
- Just save it. Save it!
- Please help me!
- These guys are gonna kill me!
- Hey!
You're gonna wanna pay
attention to my questions.
Please.
No, wait, wait, wait!
Oh god, please don't!
- Alright, pick a finger.
- Don't do this.
No, no, you didn't
ask me anything yet!
I wanna make sure
you know I'm serious.
I believe you, okay?
- I fucking believe you.
- Okay, okay, hey!
Do you know anything that
will help keep us safe?
Anything at all.
Anything that will
help us survive.
It's the fucking doctor.
It's that fucking doctor.
Okay, fine, we
know that already.
We don't have time for this.
Alright, you know what?
Make it clean.
No, no, please.
It is him.
It's him and I killed him.
I swear to god I did
you a fucking favor.
Yeah, well he's
not dead anymore.
How is that possible?
What?
Oh god.
Oh, no, no!
[distant screaming]
Look at me, look at me!
Oh god!
Stop!
Listen to me.
How is he alive?
What is he?
I don't fucking know.
Okay, take his hand off.
No, no, please, please!
I don't know, I'm serious.
I met a girl on the road.
Fucking please, please, please.
I met a girl on the road
and she told me she could
help me score crystal so
I followed her to this
fucking pill house.
Except it wasn't a pill house.
What was it?
It was an old farm house
in the middle of nowhere.
All of these fucking junkies.
It was a mess.
It looked like they'd been
killing people for a while.
He gave us drugs.
He watched us have sex.
And he called the
place a church.
Okay, what you're telling
me that Richard was some
kind of sex fiend,
religious thing?
My dad knew him for
years, we all did.
That's bullshit.
They were dressed
just like this.
There's a bunch of people
dressed like this, okay?
And they did killings
and sacrifices
and they made us watch.
You're talking devil worshiping?
No.
No, I don't believe
in the devil.
Okay, but I believe in this.
They made people change.
I saw it.
Thank you.
You're coming with us.
There's no reason to thank us.
What?
Yeah.
You know what? We're gonna visit
your friend in the basement.
No!
- Mhm.
- Are you nuts?
No, you've seen he can do.
Let's just get
out of here, okay?
Fuck this place.
Yeah? Have a look.
Go on.
Be my guest.
No, this is suicide.
Oh my god.
No, you're as crazy as they are.
Yeah, maybe.
[door opens]
Down here.
Looks like this place
is gonna collapse.
Can you hear me okay?
Loud and clear.
The stairwell to the basement
is at the back of the building.
Roger that.
Got it.
[eerie music]
[♪♪]
Look.
Someone's been here.
[eerie music]
[♪♪]
Kim!
Where are we going?
The door to the morgue
should be right there in
front of you.
[radio static]
I don't see any door.
Just a bunch of corridors.
You sure this is
the right place?
He went down the wrong stairs.
There's only one set of stairs.
I know where they're going.
Hello?
Carter!
Better not be leading
us into a trap.
[radio static]
[muffled chatter]
What's going on?
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
Did you find it?
Is there some kind of
sub-basement or...
No, no, no, what are
you talking about?
- A staircase going down.
- What?
[radio static]
Carter, can you hear me?
[eerie winds]
We gotta go back.
I can't ask you to
follow me down here.
You understand?
Guys, what's happening?
Nothing. We're...
We're gonna go down the stairs.
Hey, leading in with him.
Hey, you get to go first.
Yeah, right.
I'm not asking.
Be quiet.
[mumbles]
[eerie music]
[♪♪]
Don't bother.
You won't be able to move.
What? Richard?
Be patient.
I'm almost ready.
What-what-what is this?
I saw you die.
I had no idea that it
would feel like this.
The years I spent
operating on people.
Opening them up and
stitching them back
together again.
It's remarkable, the
sensation it's...
not pain, more a
sense of release.
Why, why are you...
Be quiet, please.
This is uncharted territory.
The chance to study
my own transformation.
I understand your
hesitation, Allison, but
let me ask you, all these
years, haven't you ever
wished to save someone
beyond saving?
No matter what the costs?
Well, losing Sarah destroyed me.
But it also compelled
me to find a solution.
You'd be surprised at the
things you find when you
go looking.
[footsteps]
[eerie music]
[♪♪]
It smells like a grave.
[emergency flare sparks]
I've seen this place before.
This was all over the
house we cleaned out.
He made us look at things.
The worst things I've ever seen.
We found rooms full of bodies in
the basement of that place.
They had someone on a
table like they were doing
surgery down there.
Half turned into
one of those things.
No!
No, worse than that.
Like a nightmare.
[panting]
It isn't real.
It's not real.
[dramatic music]
[♪♪]
It's a rat's maze.
Carter!
[radio static]
Is he here?
Hey!
Yeah.
He has took me here to... baby.
I'm right here, kiddo.
It's okay, it's alright.
You're gonna be fine.
You're lucky your grandpa
cares about you so much.
My grandpa just yells
at his TV and smokes.
[screams]
Shit!
- Help her, help her.
- Shit, okay, okay! Wait, wait.
Help her, please.
- The paradigm, I think.
- Alright.
Okay, Maggie, hold
still for one second.
I got this. Okay.
I'm gonna give you
something that's really
gonna help you.
It's gonna feel really good.
- You're doing real good.
- It's alright, it's alright.
- Okay.
- It's gonna be real painless.
It's gonna be okay in a second.
- Okay, okay.
- Just give me a second.
Okay, okay.
Okay, you gotta hold her still.
You gotta hold her still.
[crying]
Easy, once I get this in.
Okay, ready?
There you go.
Yeah, yeah.
It's okay.
There's no problem.
No problem.
[eerie music]
[♪♪]
Great.
I'm not going in there.
Fucking shoot me.
Hey.
This is it.
This is what?
I appreciate your enthusiasm but
we need to think this through.
[door creaking]
This is a mistake.
Come here, you little fuck.
Do you know where
you go when you die?
I do.
You travel on, reborn into
something else, like a
caterpillar becoming a moth.
Until now I've only been able to
track the moth in its cocoon.
The body has to
adjust, of course.
It adapts.
We weren't built for
this kind of thing.
I admit, early on
I made mistakes.
Some of those earliest mistakes
are still down here with us.
[echoing shouts]
In fact, they caused the fire
that destroyed this hospital.
You see, they want to die,
but I won't let them.
[sobs]
Don't cry, Allison.
I am going to help you.
This is an end to the
cycle of life and death.
Do you really want this world?
This world that took
your son from you?
Do you know what happened
that night to your unborn child?
No, please.
Umbilical cord became entangled.
Simple as that.
Strange, isn't it?
The very lifeline between
you and your child,
constricting like a noose
around his neck as he
struggled to get out.
Tighter and tighter until
finally it couldn't
struggle anymore.
Nature's futility.
I can stop it.
This is the first real step.
The true resurrection.
I lost my daughter to the
abyss, but tonight, I am
calling her back.
Richard.
Please.
Don't do this.
But it's already done.
[suspenseful music]
[panting]
You are so beautiful, Allison.
You will become something
truly remarkable.
[suspenseful music]
[♪♪]
This is a slaughter house.
[gagging]
Get this off of me!
Shut the fuck up!
I should've killed you
back at the house.
Get a hold of yourself.
[baby crying]
[growling]
Is she alright?
She feels hot.
Oh god.
[screams]
- Lord! Do something!
- Oh god, okay!
Okay!
[mumbling]
Uh...
Get a hold of yourself.
Fuck you.
Look around us, huh?
I told you.
This was a mistake.
He knows something.
[grunts]
[baby crying]
We need you with us.
[high-pitched ringing]
He's in his head!
[mumbling]
[punching]
Stop it!
[grunts]
[whispering]
[suspenseful music]
[♪♪]
[growling]
We're in hell.
[dramatic music]
[♪♪]
[gunshot]
[screams]
You've got to hold her still!
It's gonna be okay!
[sobbing]
[glass breaks]
That's the front entrance!
[screams]
[dramatic music]
[♪♪]
[gunshot]
Where are you going?
Wake up, damnit!
[crying]
I can't do it!
- I can't do it!
- You have to!
[dramatic music]
[♪♪]
[inaudible yelling]
[dramatic music]
[♪♪]
[screaming]
No! No! No! No! No!
[dramatic music]
[♪♪]
[growling]
You do what you have to do!
I'll keep those bastards out.
I can't kill her.
You have to do this.
You are the only chance she has.
No.
Please!
Sorry, I can't.
Please do this!
[suspenseful music]
[screams]
Oh my god!
Why did you do that?
It's finally time.
How could you?
Your baby.
Doctor Paul is a great man.
I'm lucky to carry his child.
Nothing else matters now.
[screams]
[dramatic music]
[screaming]
Don't worry.
Everything is about to change.
Get the fuck away from me!
[crying]
[panting]
[screams]
[suspenseful music]
[♪♪]
[creaking]
[whispering]
Just wait.
What do we have to do?
This is your fault.
This is your fault!
[grunts]
I wasn't there.
You should've protected them!
Mother wants us to stay.
I told you, look after them.
But you stayed here.
You should have protected them!
Stay here, stay here.
[screams]
[groans]
[panting]
I'm sorry.
What is this?
[panting]
Carter, Carter, Carter!
[speaker echoing]
Carter, where are you?
Shut the fuck up, shut the
fuck up, shut the fuck up.
Shut up.
Fuck!
[suspenseful music]
[♪♪]
Daniel?
Allison.
Where are you?
I'm scared.
No, no, no, no.
Allison, I'm right here.
I'm right here.
Look at me, it's okay.
Oh, I can feel it coming.
Oh, wow.
Hold my hand.
I need you.
I'm not gonna leave.
Daniel.
I know your secret.
I saw it in your face.
The night Allison
lost your child.
I saw relief.
What have you done?
I've given her what she wanted.
She's a mother.
Isn't she beautiful?
[suspenseful music]
[♪♪]
Daniel.
Stay.
[suspenseful music]
[♪♪]
Do you see, Daniel?
Tell me what you see.
I see...
a monster that thinks he's god.
I'm disappointed.
Of all the things I've shown you
and you still don't understand.
No.
No, you're right, I don't.
I refuse to let
death be the end.
I defy god.
There are things much older.
Older than time and
they blessed me.
Well, congratulations.
I spent my life resisting death,
but now I understand.
I must embrace it.
I'll have my beautiful
daughter back.
I just need one final thing.
[suspenseful music]
[♪♪]
Come, join me.
[suspenseful music]
[♪♪]
The others have all gathered to
witness my daughter's rebirth.
My disciples ready for
their own transformation.
You'll experience it
yourself, but first,
you have to die for me...
like your father
and son before you.
You've done
wonderfully, my dear.
Now watch.
You will be my audience.
Watch the abyss
open itself to me.
[chanting]
[cracking]
[dramatic music]
[♪♪]
Calvin, bless my baby.
Place my daughter
into this vessel.
[screeching]
[screams]
Yes.
Give yourself to her.
[panting]
Let her come to be.
[screams]
[baby crying]
It's her.
You see?
[growling]
[dramatic music]
[♪♪]
Hey!
[gunshot]
[dramatic music]
[♪♪]
[gunshot]
[dramatic music]
[♪♪]
[screams]
Look out!
[dramatic music]
[♪♪]
[gunshot]
[groans]
Do it!
Do it.
[screams]
[screaming]
We will all be saved.
Everything has led to this.
[inaudible muttering]
[crash]
[muffled groans]
I can see it all before me.
The infinite astro workings.
It's beautiful.
[dramatic music]
[♪♪]
Don't fight it, Daniel.
I can give Allison to you.
That's what you want, isn't it?
She's waiting for you.
All you have to do is let
go and you can be together.
That's a good boy.
This isn't the end.
[suspenseful music]
[♪♪]
Yes.
[suspenseful music]
[♪♪]
[creaking]
[groaning]
[dramatic music]
[♪♪]
[growling]
[suspenseful music]
[♪♪]
[panting]
[suspenseful music]
[♪♪]
[hysterical breathing]
[screams]
[crying]
Is it over?
[dramatic music]
[♪♪]
[thunder cracking]
[radio static]
[folk music]
[♪♪]