Say hello to Idiosa Dartellum 7...
...or the ID-7 virus.
Nasty-looking little fucker?
For the uninitiated, the ID-7 strain
makes stress hormone levels rise...
...blocks neural paths,
essentially attacking our id...
...and throwing off a very
important balance in our brains...
...the balance between emotions and reason
that keep us from doing stupid shit...
...things like punching your boss
in the face when angry...
...or fucking your date in public when horny.
That balance is temporarily severed,
causing inhibitions to drop...
...and basic instincts
to rise to the surface...
...as the infected fall victim to
what experts call emotional hijacking.
Social media has tagged it the red-eye virus
...for obvious reasons.
So in a nutshell...
...basic human dignity takes a sick leave.
The first reported case of the red-eye
virus occurred 18 months ago...
...in Des Moines, Iowa,
and quickly spread around the world.
Since then, there have been over 1,000
confirmed outbreaks reported globally...
...over half of which
are in the United States alone.
The CDC is optimistic they can
contain the virus immediately...
...through mandated quarantines,
and the nation will be virus-free...
...by the end of the year as antibodies
are being aggressively tested.
They also state the virus isn't lethal,
which is technically true.
But while the virus can't kill,
the infected, or redders, can.
Introducing Mr. Nevil Reed...
...the first redder to be officially
cleared for murder.
His legal defense alleged that those
infected with the ID-7 strain...
...can't control their emotions and therefore
are not liable for the resulting actions.
And thanks to a loophole,
the case was dismissed.
So Nevil lost his shit, stabbed a co-worker
repeatedly in the face till dead...
...and walked thanks a doctor's note.
God bless the justice system.
Welcome to the home of
Towers & Smythe Consulting...
...the corporate scumbags hired
by the bigger corporate scumbags...
...in the landmark Nevil Reed case.
TSC is a firm fueled by greed,
duplicity, and moral decay...
...a place that ironically screens
their job applicants for honesty...
...loyalty, and integrity.
Qualities I had in spades
when I was fresh-faced...
...and ready to take on the world
my first day here.
And here's me six months later...
...late nights, no respect, the bad coffee...
all the shit that comes
with paying your dues.
But none of it could slow me down.
I was striving for the success
my family never had...
...a seat at the big kids' table
with all the fixings...
...all while paying back
those goddamn student loans.
But the higher I rose, the more I felt
like I was losing myself in the process.
And after discovering that loophole
that won the Reed case...
...the requisite promotion quickly followed.
But by then, it didn't matter
that I thought he was guilty as fuck.
I just wanted the corner office.
And for my sins, they gave me one.
What a dick.
Towers and Smythe.
- I mean, how fucking stupid can you get?
- I'm sorry. I...
You're sorry? I don't fucking pay you
to be fucking sorry, Jenny.
Hey. Morning. Dude, you gotta see this.
You gotta see this. Come over here.
- What's up?
- I just got this today.
Oh, man, last year's Christmas party.
That looks like you.
Yeah. That's you.
Where'd you get that?
I googled "a small-dick douche
makes assistant work hard...
...for fake promise of a raise,"
and it was just, like, top search result...
...like, number one.
Listen, leave her alone...
...or I'll sell this to your wife for half
of the half she'll get from your divorce.
It's a good talk, bro.
Thank you.
- May not be much...
- Morning, Miles.
...but I'll take whatever goodwill
I can pillage to sleep better at night.
Thank God for coffee, right?
- Your 9:00 a.m. is in meeting room three.
- Where is my coffee cup?
- Don't know. Also, I...
- Do you know who took it?
- No. But I can get you another one.
- I don't want another mug. I want my mug.
Yep, David from Vanda Corp.
- Derek. Derek.
- What?
- David, line one.
- Okay. Put him on.
David, I was just about to call you.
David? Who the hell's David? It's Lucy.
Miles, this is my sister.
- I'm sorry.
- It is so hard to get you on the phone.
I just wanted to see if you were
coming up for my birthday next month.
Yeah. No, actually.
I'm so sorry. I will not be able
to make it to your birthday.
But I will totally make it up to you.
Well, if you're not gonna show up,
at least paint me something cool.
- How do you know I started painting?
- Miles said you're pretty good.
Did he?
Yeah. You should sign up
for art classes or something.
I don't have time for art classes.
Yeah. You don't have time for anything.
Yes. You are correct.
I do not have time for anything.
I don't have time for this conversation.
- But I love you very much.
- Wait, Derek...
Thank you so much for calling.
I gotta go. I love you. Bye.
What's my 9:00?
Good morning. Pat Sorenson's office.
Right this way, sir.
How can I help you?
My client wants to pay this overdue
debt to reverse the foreclosure.
We just need TSC to tell
the bank to allow more time.
I'm sorry to inform you, but our client
has a strong no-refinance policy.
Then what do I tell mine?
Would you be open to discussing
the possibility of a deed in lieu?
You don't know
what I'm talking about, do you?
- You should see a lawyer.
- I am a lawyer.
If you were a lawyer,
you would know what a deed in lieu is.
You're one of the borrowers, aren't you?
So what's a deed in lieu?
It doesn't matter.
Bank wouldn't agree to it anyway.
Look, you're not the first borrower
to try to pull this kind of scam.
Miss, this is a non-smoking room.
So come stop me, suit.
Wait.
We just need two more months.
Families are involved here, but nobody
listens, not the banks, not the lawyers.
I can't get past their damn secretaries.
Look, I am very sorry
this is happening to you.
- Then don't kick me out.
- The bank is kicking you out.
- The bank is your client.
- It's the firm's client.
The firm's partners call the shots.
No one raindrop thinks it caused the flood.
My mother used to say that.
Now I understand what it means.
Is there anything else I can do to help?
You can start by telling me the partner
calling the shots on the case.
Sure. That would be...
Oh, shit.
Irene Smythe.
Well, I want a word with this
Irene Smythe or whoever right now.
Sure. Let me get her on the phone.
- This way, ma'am.
- Get off me!
We're not done here!
I'm gonna sue you! I'm gonna sue all of you!
Fuckers!
You're in deep shit, too!
You're in deep shit.
Brenda wasn't feeling well,
so I had to go out to the penthouse...
...to cover for her for a bit.
Turns out The Boss is meeting
with Kara and I'm pretty sure...
...they were talking about you fucking
up a Vanda Corp case or something.
Wait, what? Are you...
I don't work Vanda Corp.
That's Kara's client.
I know, right?
Oh, no.
- How can I help you?
- Derek Cho.
- Need an access code to the eighth floor.
- To see whom?
Kara Powell, director of operations,
not effective for client matters...
...but with all things related to navigating
internal company politics...
...she's fuckin' Mussolini.
We call her The Siren.
She's got The Boss's ear.
And her songs are sweet poison.
Mr. Cho.
To see... Kara Powell.
One moment, please.
Your pass code is 7-8-5-star-9-5.
You expected me to create
a dedicated office mobile app
- ...with servers that run on hamster wheels.
- Ray, stop talking.
If I hear another whining excuse from you...
...I'll make sure you're back to building
porn-site banner ads by lunch.
- Do you understand me?
- Yes, fine.
So stop playing video games
in your troll cave...
...and get the interoffice apps
updated ASAP, okay, sweetie?
Okay. Thank you so much. Bye-bye. Asshole.
- What I can do for you?
- That's a nice mug.
- Where'd you get it?
- I told my assistant to get me one.
- And where did she get it?
- Meg!
Derek here wants to know
where you got the mug.
From a kitchen downstairs.
- Okay. And why did you choose that one?
- Because the other ones were filthy.
- And why do you think this one wasn't?
- Because the maid cleaned it.
Incorrect. I cleaned this mug
because this mug is mine.
And what's mine is mine.
And what's yours is yours.
- You're getting to a point.
- Vanda Corp is your client.
That blood's on your hands.
- So now you wanna share.
- I can't share what isn't mine.
Vanda Corp has filed more than 100 account
cases through us in the last two years.
Well, then I hope they have
a good case manager.
You mean managers. No one can work
a client that big without delegating.
And according to the annual
work distribution sheet...
That hasn't been updated in years.
...one of Vanda Corp's
complaint cases was assigned...
...to you.
File 45A.
I'm being set up.
Wow. Heads will roll.
- This will cost Vanda...
- Give me this.
- This was planted.
- I'll cut you a deal. Plead guilty.
- Not guilty.
- The corpse was found inside your office.
You knew exactly where to find it.
- Do you wanna take this upstairs?
- Great idea.
Take your file.
Wanna swipe your key card,
or should I swipe mine?
Oh, I'm sorry. I forgot.
You don't have clearance.
My bad.
Don't you worry, little one.
Daddy will pay for abandoning you
and leaving you to die...
...in that cold, dirty dumpster.
No, no. You died when you drowned
because Mommy left you in the bathtub...
...while she went shopping for shoes.
But don't worry. Daddy will make her pay.
Too bad Mommy outranks Daddy.
- Mommy's a backstabbing bitch.
- That's why Mommy outranks Daddy.
- Brenda, what's his mood?
- He's drawing.
Oh, shit.
John Towers, capital "T" in TSC...
...king of the castle, top of the food
chain, and total fucking maniac...
...you know, your typical
American success story.
Did I mention that he also
dabbles in the fine arts?
Tell me what you see here.
I see that those soldiers' lives
are in danger, sir.
Do you think they'll make it?
No, sir. The fuse is too short.
It's too late to run.
And what do you think
they should be doing instead?
May I, sir?
So simple and yet so effective.
Can you see it, Derek?
Can you see the solution to our problem here?
I think you mean her problem
because she was the one that...
Give me the file. This is our bomb.
The fuse is already burning.
So should we run like cowards and die?
We are brave, sir.
I'm so glad you said that...
...because any second now, Vanda Corp
is gonna find out about this mess...
...and I'm gonna need some scalps.
So, who dropped the ball?
I hate pointing fingers, but may I suggest...
...you check the annual work
distribution sheet?
Someone cooked the fucking worksheet.
Sir.
Go on.
Have you noticed that whenever
there's a problem like this...
...it's almost always
the same soldier involved?
Because down in the trenches,
we have all noticed.
And we wonder if discharging this problem
soldier might be the solution...
...to preventing this kind of mess
from ever happening again.
- And who would that be?
- May I?
Thank you, Derek. You can leave.
- Let's discuss.
- Yes, sir.
- I...
- Leave.
You got a sec?
Nothing like a little power meditation.
This one's new.
- Declan's walking already?
- Wobbling, actually...
...like you were last Friday night.
- Thanks for the ride, by the way.
- Thanks for puking in my car.
That's what friends are for.
So debrief me. What happened?
Just found someone else's shit
swept under my carpet.
What kind of shit?
Vanda Corp shit.
It's a seven-figure mistake.
I didn't even touch the file.
Don't sweat it.
Those clowns working Vanda Corp
are a bunch of a serial screw-ups.
Look, I realize you might
not wanna divulge...
The Siren.
All right. Let's take a beat to strategize.
Since the promotion, you could possibly
be in charge of a case that big...
...but not big enough to be untouchable.
That's why she chose you.
You're the perfect fall guy.
So before even taking this upstairs...
...you already took this upstairs
and made a mess of things.
Fuck.
Say I punch a rhino in the face.
Would you call that brave or stupid?
Brave...
...and stupid.
See how bravery and stupidity can overlap?
Now that you understand that, let me give her
a call and see if I can't find a way...
- ...to cut you a deal.
- She already offered me a deal.
I told her to suck it and that this is war.
- War is over, moron.
- Come on in, Kara.
- How so?
- Natural selection happened.
Pack your shit.
Boxes are on the second floor.
- You're fucking kidding me?
- Derek, calm down.
You blew him, didn't you?
Like I need to stoop to that level.
Now...
...get the fuck out of my face.
I'm taking this to The Nine.
Sure. Good luck with that.
And I want my mug back.
The Nine, the company's board of directors.
Good morning, everybody.
This is the Vanda Corp file.
No one here goes up or down
without their vote.
Rumor has it that they're actually
cybernetic organisms...
...but that hasn't been
officially confirmed yet.
Now, there's a common misconception about
the death gesture during gladiatorial combat.
The actual phrase used in Roman texts
doesn't translate as thumbs down...
...but rather thumbs turned.
Personally, I think we should hang,
draw and quarter the little fucker.
But... you know, that's just me.
- So let's vote.
- That's because the victors...
...finished off their opponents
with a sword thrust across the throat.
So it's unanimous. Call Lester.
Enter Lester McGill, head of human resources.
No, not her. That guy.
He takes care of the firm's layoffs.
He's as cold as his methods
are efficient, a perfect fit here.
Naturally, we call him the reaper...
...and he's the last person you want
to see standing at your doorway.
Mind if I come in... Derek?
If I said no?
Thank you.
Do you even know what happened?
I don't care what happened.
You must be good friends with Kara, then.
I hope she dies promptly.
Glad we're on the same page.
The Nine listen to you,
and I have proof that...
- Sign here...
- ...this was not my mist...
...and here.
What the hell are you doing?
My job.
So you are on her side.
I'm on the right side. Always am.
That's why it's me firing you.
Fuck you.
Sign these documents from upstairs
so I can clear accounting...
...to transfer your severance pay
into your account.
Do you know what this is?
This is a statement...
...saying that I take full responsibility
over the Vanda Corp mess.
I'll have to file that
under "N" for "not my problem."
I could be disbarred.
I could face legal action from the client.
I'm just the messenger, Derek.
Yelling at me is like yelling
at your watch because you're late.
Why would I sign this crap?
To get rich.
Wow.
Glad to see we're now on the same page.
Glad to see I'm not.
You want to do this the hard way?
I wanna do this the right way.
I wanna speak with him and The Nine.
Executive decisions
are not subject to appeal.
This one fucking better be...
...because I'm not leaving this
building until I plead my case.
Understood.
This building is under quarantine.
Get back inside.
What's going on here? You can't tell me...
- What the...
- ...hell is going on?
One of our pathogen sniffers
in the building's ventilation system...
...picked up traces of the ID-7 virus.
And who authorized you to install
a sniffer in my building anyway?
Since the outbreak in Des Moines,
detection devices are now legally required...
- ...in public places.
- Des Moines. Fuck.
According to our projections,
those infected in the building...
...will begin to display symptoms
soon, if not already.
Our experts have already released
a neutralizer into your ventilation system.
All traces of the virus should be
eliminated in approximately eight hours.
Until then, this building
is officially under quarantine.
So what are we supposed to do
for the next eight hours?
Try to remain calm.
So there I was getting the shit kicked out
of me on the lobby floor by this asshole.
And then... something...
...happened!
I don't wanna remain calm! I want this fixed.
Hey. It's me. It's me. You all right?
I think I just... I think I just
punched a rhino in the face.
- What?
- He attacked me.
And then I just kicked his ass.
- I'm going to go talk to The Nine.
- No. Fuck this place!
This mess is a blessing in disguise,
trust me. You don't wanna end up like me.
What are you talking about?
You have everything figured out!
No, Derek. This meditation
and this incense, it's all bullshit.
You think I like the taste of cale?
Come on! I'm fuckin' dead inside.
But they have me wrong. I have to tell them.
Do you have any idea what they're capable of?
Just hide out in your office
until the virus subsides...
...then walk out those doors
and don't look back.
Free as a bird. All right?
- Okay.
- Now come on.
Put some peanut butter in your
wheatgrass shot. What do you say?
- Motherfucker!
- Until the quarantine is over...
...we'll need your cooperation
to keep the situation under control.
We know better than anyone else
that this virus...
...turns people into maniacs
or blathering idiots.
As you may know, the virus triggers
a breakdown of moral barriers...
...unleashing repressed emotions
in the infected, including anger...
- ...depression, fear, lust.
- Like cocaine?
An infected individual would make
a coke addict look like a model citizen...
- ...by comparison.
- But we still feel normal.
The virus can cause drastic mood swings...
...with potentially violent
and severe consequences.
It would be best if stressful
work-related situations were avoided.
Yeah. I'm going to come to your house,
and I'm going to fucking kill you!
- Bye, Mom.
- Antidepressants, stimulants...
...even caffeine can accelerate
the virus's effect.
Meg, make more fucking coffee!
So, what happens when 287 employees...
...with average billing rates
of $200 an hour...
...stop working for eight hours?
You don't know?
I lose half a million dollars!
Now, crack your whips.
Everybody goes back to work.
And if they don't like it,
they are terminated immediately...
...and no severance packages.
Put the fear of me in them.
- What now?
- Derek Cho wants clearance to come up.
- What for?
- He said he reconsidered...
...but he wants to have a word
with you and The Nine first.
Your pass code is 8-star-1-9-9, fuck-head.
Fuck you!
No, no. No, up.
Up. Up. Let me the fuck up!
Colton Snyder...
...aka The Bull...
...The Boss' unofficial left hook.
Nobody knows his exact job description.
But whenever there's a hint
of something dirty going on...
- Take his phone.
- ...there he is.
Hello, Derek.
Look, I am so sorry we didn't get
a chance to meet again.
Things came up. You know how it is.
Now, I know what you're thinking...
"Nevil Reed, he got away with murder.
Maybe I can have a little fun here."
Did you really think
that I didn't see that coming?
Actually, I was just gonna
ask for my job back.
But I like your idea, too.
Well, I'm going to beat you to the punch.
Now, that sounds like it hurt. Is he hurt?
- Yes, sir.
- Is he crying?
- No, sir.
- Well, why isn't he fucking crying?
He is now, sir.
Now, I wanna hear a bone break.
They say the femur is the most difficult
bone in the body to break...
...but I'll settle for a pinkie.
I'm coming, Derek.
- What's happening?
- Motherfuckers!
Can someone tell me
what the fuck is going on in there?
Ewan?
I... smell...
...toast.
Ewan.
- Ewan! Ewan!
- Ewan?
Ewan!
- You killed Ewan?
- There's been an accident.
Do you have any idea how many billable hours
I'm gonna lose until I find a replacement?
I'm worried about the body
right now. I killed him.
You didn't kill him.
The virus killed him. You're infected.
You have impunity!
We have a precedent in Nevil Reed.
- You can thank Derek for that.
- Motherfucker.
Thank you for that, Derek.
Lock him up with the other one
and then get back up here.
- What are you doing here?
- They fired me.
That's nice. Justice is served for once.
What are you doing here?
Security called the cops, but this place was
quarantined before they could show up...
...so they threw me in this hellhole.
I'm suing everyone and their grandmother
when I get out of here, I swear to God.
Good luck. It's ID-7!
No one's liable for anything that they do.
- Just like any other day for you.
- Yeah.
We're not liable for what
we do in here, either.
Nice, then I'll have your balls
for dinner for that shit you pulled!
Wait! Wait! Wait! This might sound crazy,
but I think we can help each other out here.
Okay? You remember Irene Smythe,
the woman that fucking screwed you?
She's in the building's penthouse right now.
- So what?
- You help me get to the top...
...and she's all yours.
This is our shot to hold
these assholes accountable...
...for all the fucking damage
that they've done!
And our chance goes away
as soon as this quarantine is over.
Yeah?
- Can I get up now?
- Are you gonna stop being an asshole?
That's debatable. Yes. Yes.
- What are you looking for?
- A loophole.
It's my specialty.
Yeah!
I don't think they'd lock us up
in a room with working phones.
I don't need a working phone.
Just need bit of this, a bit of that.
Build a franken-phone.
And call who? Cops can't enter the building.
I'm not calling the cops.
Sir? Derek Cho somehow managed to
set up a call with Vander Corp's CEO...
...and they wanted you to join in.
In a minute.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Frank.
I'm all ears!
Glad you could join us, John.
Well, I've been having a nice,
long chat with one of your lawyers.
- You still there, Derek?
- Yes, sir. I am still here.
Good. John, can you please remind me?
Why do I do business with TSC?
Well, because it's a jungle out there, Frank.
And not only do you need a guide, but you
also need a lion walking right by your side.
And we are your lion and your guide.
- Are you?
- Yeah.
Well, we're just a touch concerned
that you may have ulterior motives.
We would never turn
against our clients, Frank.
Well, that may be true, but Derek has
alerted me to a certain document...
...that seems to suggest otherwise.
It's a report that TSC did for Vander Corp.
It analyzes the advisability
of filing a multimillion-dollar lawsuit...
...against one of Frank's
ex-business associates.
Do you remember this report, John?
- No.
- I must say, it's well-written.
I like how it weighs the slim possibility...
...of a positive financial outcome...
...against the enormous
potential litigation costs.
Do you agree with this report, Derek?
No, sir. I do not. I believe
you could have won the suit.
Then why did your advisers
advise me against it?
Your advisers missed
the deadline to file the motion.
So you believe that TSC
dropped the ball on this one?
I believe they dropped the ball, sir.
But then they also defecated on the ball...
...and then sodomized the ball, sir.
Interesting.
Oh, and, John...
...I just happen to have
your last invoice here with me.
That went well.
I want you to rip the fucking
phone out of his hands...
...his hands off his fucking body now!
Yeah. Can I please order two
pepperoni pizzas and some hot wings?
Yeah. Why not?
Throw some garlic bread in there.
Do you guys want anything?
Brenda! This fucking phone doesn't work!
Yeah.
Christ, man! He fuck your girl, too?
Damn, suit,
you don't even respect each other.
You're right.
We don't.
Now what?
Time to go to work.
- Fuck, yeah!
- Oh, shit.
They started a countdown for the
quarantine, posted in an interoffice app.
It's enough time to get the job done.
I mean, this place isn't that big.
The Boss is a fucking raging cokehead.
There's definitely gonna be more guards.
Fine. I'll bring more nails.
The only way to the top floor is with
the key card or a one-time password.
So who do we have to fuck up to get the card?
First, there's an ass-hat on the sixth
floor who's got a level-two key card.
It can take us to the seventh floor,
giving us access to the bitch...
...who's got a level-three key card.
Hey, extreme measures, right?
- Wednesdays.
- Hey!
- Him?
- Yep.
Hey!
- Open the fucking door!
- Fuck you, motherfucker!
You open doors like my grandmother fucks!
Open the door!
Open the fucking door!
It really bothers me that women don't
get the same treatment as men...
...in the workplace.
I'm all about gender equality here.
Derek!
- Need a hand?
- I don't need your help, suit.
- But I need yours.
- Fuck you.
Fuck you, too.
- May we come in?
- And if I said no?
You'll have to confer with my associate.
And mine, gimpy.
- What do you want?
- Key card.
I'm not the only one
with a level-two key card.
But you are the one that fired me, asshole!
Wrong. The firm fired you.
Don't nail-gun the messenger.
Oh, my God.
You bring up a very good point.
I'm so sorry, Lester. We're good.
We're totally good, man.
I will take it up with the firm...
...but I would love to know
where I could find the firm...
...because I would love
to kick the firm's ass.
You can't kick a firm's ass.
That's the point.
Well, then that brings us back to you.
I was just doing my job.
No one raindrop thinks it caused the flood.
I get what that means.
You know what will happen to me
if I give you this key card?
I'm going to have to file that under "N..."
...for "not my fucking problem."
Fuck!
No! The saw!
Extreme measures!
Go!
A little help?
You ready?
It's gonna hurt a lot.
You're enjoying this, aren't you?
- You're still one of them.
- I thought we were a team.
For the time being.
All right. On the count of...
All right. Calm down.
Fuck.
At least you're not that guy.
Move aside, pussies. Come on.
Wait. Wait. I have an idea.
Fuck you! Fuck you! Fuck you!
You're cool! Fuck you!
- Are we done here yet?
- We are now.
Here, take my phone.
I need you to film something.
- Film what?
- Okay. Here we go.
Case file 32376, The People vs. Reed.
Now, you all know the court case...
...but let's discuss Mr. Nevil Reed
the man, shall we?
By all accounts, Mr. Reed was
an upstanding pillar of the community...
...earned two master's degrees
by the age of 21.
He married his college sweetheart
and is the father of beautiful twin girls.
But when Mr. Reed contracted the ID-7 virus...
...shit got real.
"Overwhelmed by pure id...
...Nevil Reed became prone to involuntary...
...aberrant, and shocking impulses.
He committed a gruesome, unspeakable act...
...in broad daylight
in a room full of witnesses."
Now, we're witnessing a model citizen here...
...transformed into a brutal...
...bloodthirsty killing machine...
...at the blink of an infected eye.
So I ask you this.
Is it his fault or is it the virus's?
Let's discuss.
See you soon, fuckers.
Shit.
Kara, he's on his way up.
He has got Lester's key card.
Oh, really? That's a shame,
a real shame, sir.
Just wondering, did they get it before or
after butchering Lester with an electric saw?
Just calm down and come up here!
They're guarding the private elevator.
I can't leave the office.
- Then destroy the card.
- It's my only leverage.
Kara, I promise you...
...I will do everything in my power
to ensure he doesn't get to you.
But if he does,
you must protect those above you.
Fuck those above me!
- I'll give you the raise you always wanted.
- Fuck your raise!
- I'll make you partner.
- Fuck your...
Deal. I'll throw it out the window.
Oh, thank you.
Meg!
Hide this somewhere safe
and don't tell me where.
And make more fucking coffee now!
Stupid bitch.
The elevator's the only way upstairs.
We can ambush her here.
Well, it's gonna be a while.
Top three bands, go.
- Only three?
- Only three, that's the rules.
All right.
Motorhead.
D.R.I. and Early Anthrax.
- Metal till I fucking puke.
- All right. Okay.
That's not what I expected, but fine choices.
What did you expect, the Dave Matthews Band?
Hey, Dave Matthews Band is actually...
Other way, asshole. Go.
Turn around. Yep. You got it.
- You fucking dick, Joe!
- What?
Dave Matthews Band is a good band.
- Oh, my God.
- You ever heard them live?
I would rather chew glass.
Are you serious?
Just because they're popular
doesn't mean that they're bad at music.
I think it's actually that people think
it's more popular to dislike them...
...so they're just trying
to be cool. It's bullshit.
All right. Fine.
I'll go see them at Burning Man.
All right, make fun all you want,
but if we ever get out of here...
...I'm gonna get us tickets, all right,
to the coliseum show in July.
I'm gonna take you there and I'm gonna
turn you on to some great musicianship.
You're gonna turn me on? Before or
after we go out to buy birkenstocks?
- Fuck off.
- Do you wear them with socks? I bet you do.
Okay. So... so just tell me again...
...why you can't send a unit in
to just stop this asshole.
A heavily armed SWAT team
in a building filled with civilians...
...infected with the virus
would be catastrophic.
...for that, we need to...
excuse me. What are you doing?
Allergies. Who are you, my fucking therapist?
Anyway, all we can do
is talk to the employee...
...in an attempt to defuse the situation.
We currently have a psychologist on-site...
...who could possibly talk
to the infected individual.
Notify the team down in accounting.
I'm offering 150 grand for Cho's head.
You're talking about murder here.
You should be offering at least 450.
Agreed.
Four hours left till the quarantine lifts.
We're running out of time.
Well, sometimes you gotta say,
"what the fuck?
- Make your move."
- "Risky business."
Yeah.
All right.
Hello, Derek? My name's Mark.
I'm a psychologist working with the CDC.
- Can you hear me?
- Yes, he can hear you, Mark.
I was just told that you were
under a bit of stress right now...
...so I wanted to check in on you.
Can we talk?
Can you tell me how you feel?
How do I feel?
I feel like taking my clothes off.
I feel like causing extraordinary amounts...
...of property damage.
I feel like I wanna scream.
I wanna fuck. I feel like
twisting limbs and breaking bones!
- I feel great, Mark.
- That's the virus talking.
I agree, Mark.
Derek isn't thinking clearly right now.
He's so consumed by his id
that he hasn't noticed that...
- ...we're just here to help him.
- You should listen to her, Derek.
Why don't you sit down,
take a breath, and talk it out?
Talk it out.
Sure.
- I'll talk it out.
- Yeah. Let's just have a conversation.
Track three.
Better not be fucking Dave Matthews Band.
Okay.
Those of you who don't wanna
be a part of this can leave now.
- Derek, please listen to me.
- But if you choose to stay...
...which it seems
like you guys are choosing...
- Derek, please.
- ...you understand and agree...
...to the following terms and conditions.
- Derek!
- One...
- Derek, this is the virus talking.
- ...you hereby waive your right...
- Derek, please.
- ...to your own personal bodily integrity.
- This is not you.
- Two...
- I'm a licensed psychologist.
- ...per the State vs. Nevil Reed...
...my colleague and I
will not be held criminally liable...
...for any felony or misdemeanor
that you may be a victim of...
...including but not limited
to aggravated assault...
...aggravated battery, disorderly conduct...
...destruction of property, mayhem,
and first-degree murder.
And, three...
...terms and conditions
may change or be updated...
...whenever the fuck I want!
Consider yourselves notified.
Hello?
Derek?
Is anyone there?
Knock, knock.
Key card, por favor.
If you want it, you'll have to negotiate.
Negotiations have ended.
Well, so will the quarantine,
and I don't know where the key card is.
- What do you want?
- A truce.
Fuck your truce.
No truce, no key card.
All right.
Tell me where it is, and I promise...
...I'll be on my way and leave you alone.
You're a man of your word, Derek.
That's why I believe you.
And that's... that's why
you never made partner.
Key card. Key card, Derek.
Don't be stupid now.
There's a good boy. Meg!
Yeah, Meg!
Take your key card, Derek, and fuck off.
What card?
All I see is a useless piece
of scorched plastic on the table.
Strange.
Me too. Is that what you see, too, Meg?
- Yep.
- So tell me, Meg, sweetie...
...why did you bring me this useless
piece of plastic instead of my key card?
Oh, that is your key card,
or it used to be...
...before I put it inside a microwave oven.
And why would you do that, I wonder?
You're exactly like
every other assistant, Meg.
You're a vapid, bottom-feeding,
parasitic shithead!
You're a pair of tits with zero talent.
So tell me, Meg, you incompetent cunt...
...what could possibly possess you
to destroy my key card?
Because everyone upstairs
knew you would betray them.
So they offered me a promotion
in exchange for destroying the card.
So...
...I guess I no longer work for you,
you fucking bitch.
In fact, I don't have to listen...
...to your hideous, shrill voice ever again!
- Fuck you!
Now it's a party! Oh, my God! Yes!
Hey, just wanted to say...
...no more lies, no more power games...
...no more bullshit...
...and...
...no more siren song.
By the way, Meg, she's a little crazy.
She's perfect here.
Dude, that freak show had
some super-good-quality shoes.
These are comfy as fuck!
I loved this mug.
I got it on the first day
that I started here.
My sister gave it to me.
Fuck this place.
Do you still have that...
...foreclosure paperwork on you?
Yeah.
- Why?
- Let me take a little look at it.
What?
You're in luck.
This mortgage is part of a bad batch.
Original paperwork was filed so many
times that it'd be tough to find.
Could even be lost.
So if I ask the bank
for the original paperwork...
You'd put them in a tough spot.
Or a signature from upstairs
could void it completely.
Really?
Hey, I'm sorry...
...for not helping you earlier.
I should've, but I didn't.
It's okay.
Just don't do it again, I guess.
You rolling?
Push back. Push back.
All right. Stop.
Can you see him?
No.
Fuck you, Derek.
Is that your friend?
Oh, God.
Hey, give that to me.
Hey. Hey, it's all right.
He has kids.
Oh, God. I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
This fucking virus, it just takes...
...just takes everything up to 11.
I've noticed.
Hey.
- I know, right?
- Yeah.
- I like this virus.
So what now?
I think we should definitely
exchange numbers...
...consider an apartment, maybe a dog.
- That'd be nice.
- No, you idiot! What now?
Let's see.
- Ray sent an update to the office staff.
- Who's Ray?
He's the IT guy.
Fuckers.
There must be another way
we can get up there.
Not without the key card.
Unless...
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah.
Unless what?
What's he want?
Ray can't fix the elevators,
but I have another idea.
- Ray!
- I'm really busy right now!
Goddamn it! Fuck you!
Why won't you fucking work?
Ray!
Hey.
- Hi.
- Hey.
We need your help.
Holy shit! How'd that happen?
Well, we asked for his help,
and then he said he was busy.
Really?
Welcome to IT.
We need you to hack into someone's computer.
And I need Interpol to get off my back,
so what else is fucking new?
- Who we talking about?
- Irene Smythe.
Oh, fuck her.
What? What the...
- IT department.
- What's wrong with my computer?
Doctor can't do much
until you tell him where it hurts.
My Internet is slower than your brain.
Well, that's a miracle considering the budget
that I have for installs and updates.
Seriously, how do you expect me to keep
running things if you have one guy...
...in one room down in the fucking
basement doing everything?
Seriously, and what do I get? I get
denial, denial, denial, denial, denial...
...on all my fucking budgets, right?
But, "oh, Ray, please give me an app!
- Make sure..."
- I am shocked!
I'm shocked and appalled, and
I'll definitely bring this up with John...
...but in the meantime,
can you do your fucking job?
Cool your bloomers. Hold on.
- Just sent you a patch.
- A patch?
It's a file that you install on that thing
in front of you called a computer.
Okay.
Look, this might get complicated
for you, but don't worry.
I'll take you through the whole
process myself. You ready?
Okay.
Click on the file that's on your desktop.
- Done.
- Now click "install."
So rude. You know...
...funny enough, I think
the virus actually made her nicer.
I could've called that file mean Trojan
destroyer, the ultimate hard drive rapist...
...and she still would have installed it.
And we're in.
Okay. So what we're looking at,
those are her files?
Every last one of them, even the porn.
Seems she's got a thing for feet.
What do you want?
I want you to pretend
that that is a peaceful village...
...inhabited by gorgeous virgin maidens.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, and you're the...
you know, smelly, aggressive viking king.
You had me at peaceful.
What... what the...
Ray, you ignoramus,
that patch thing has erased my hard drive.
Hey, Irene. I got good news,
bad news, and worse news for you.
Good news is, is we have a copy
of your hard drive on the backup server.
Bad news is that I have it.
Worse news is that, if you want it...
...you gotta come down and get it.
- What trade?
- The backup copy for my key card.
That backup is worth millions to this firm.
Are you actually listening to me?
I'm meeting him. End of story.
Oh, great. Should I just remove
my pants now...
...to make it easier for him
when he comes up here to fuck me?
I'm not going to give him my key card.
Well, he has got leverage against you.
The idiot let me decide on the meeting spot.
Where's your piece, Colton?
- All right. She's clean.
- Who is she?
She's one of the mortgage
accounts that you...
I'm Melanie Cross.
I live at 22nd and Pacific.
Not for long.
Just...
Key card.
Files.
Are you...
- ...looking for this?
- Okay.
Just a little pro tip.
Employees' IQs at this firm are inversely
proportionate to their salaries, so...
...it's probably not a good idea to try to
outsmart someone with a smaller paycheck.
Key card.
Now give me the hard drive. I've done my bit.
Not yet.
Gotta sign this first.
I could sign this, sure...
...then claim temporary insanity
and have it dismissed.
Sorry, sweetie...
...but you can always take it
to the man upstairs...
...with that card you've got if you like.
You fucking whore!
- Give us a minute.
- Yeah, totally.
Bullets are for cowards.
Oh, shit.
No, no, wait!
That card doesn't work.
It needs an access code.
I got it. No.
No! No, no! No!
I'm gonna burn your eyes out.
I am done fucking around.
Give us the code right now.
I'll give you the code,
but here's the new deal, boy.
- You give me her.
- What?
She destroyed my work. That's years of my
life. You want your revenge? Give me mine.
I just want my home back, you asshole!
The quarantine is ending soon.
- Your time is running out.
- Give me the access code!
I'll give you a pro tip.
You want to swim to the top?
Drop the dead weight.
She'll do it.
Five!
Four!
Three.
- Two!
- One.
Deal.
Fuck you, Derek, you piece-of-shit suit!
You're just like all of them!
You belong here!
Fuck!
Done?
Fuck you! Fuck you.
I'll be back shortly, sweetie.
Come on.
These things only work once.
Don't do anything stupid.
Can you see it, Derek?
Can you see the solution to our problem here?
You're infected. You have impunity!
Nevil Reed, he got away with murder.
Maybe I can have a little fun here.
Well, I'm gonna beat you to the punch.
Let's discuss.
- What's that?
- The terms of my surrender...
...partnership contract.
You're a fucking piece of shit.
Look, my guy killed your guy.
You killed my guy, so we're even.
Let's just get down to business now?
Ladies.
Monthly profit participation,
annual performance bonus...
...vehicle allowances, gas,
maintenance, insurance, chauffeur.
Expense accounts, full cellphone allowances...
...paid parking, country-club fees.
I've seen you admiring all of this, Derek.
Isn't this what you've always wanted?
Yes.
Then why don't I see
a fucking pen in your hand?
Do you really wanna spend the next 20
years of your life working your ass off...
...for what, maybe half
of what I just offered you?
Sign it, Derek.
Sign it, and I'll suck your cock.
Sign it, and I'll help.
- Be smart.
- Be rich.
No.
Mine's bigger.
Mine's always bigger.
You fucker.
That's your problem, Derek. No vision.
Fuck you.
Fuck! Iron!
No, not the 9, the 5!
Look at your partners.
Look at your partners!
You know what they're thinking right now?
They're thinking how big their piece of the
pie is gonna get once you stop taking yours.
This is where we vote, right?
Well, then let's vote. Make it quick.
Can you do it, Derek?
Can you do it?
No, because you're too much of a pussy,
which is why I'm up here...
...and you are down there.
But when this is all over...
...I will piss on your corpse, as well.
And so the king falls.
With the quarantine about to lift,
I finally gotta plead my case to The Nine...
...excuse me, Eight...
and have my own day in court.
Surprisingly, given the fact that I just
threw their former CEO off a balcony...
...they seemed pretty willing to listen.
In a calm and collected manner,
I explained to them my situation...
...my dedication to the firm,
the abuse of company resources...
...by those above my pay grade, yada yada.
I don't need to bore you
with the long-form version.
With a sound defense and in light
of the day's events, I pled that...
I think I deserve my job back.
But as they voted, it dawned on me...
...something my sister had been
trying to tell me for years...
...what my new friend reminded me today.
I didn't have a job.
The job had me.
I was just another
fucking slave to the grind.
Look, we paint our paths
with the best of intentions...
...but at the end of the day, sometimes
it takes a brushstroke of circumstance...
...or a deadly virus to set us
on the right path again.
And the incident at TSC,
as they're calling it...
...ended up being a watershed case
to finally accelerate a vaccine...
...to prevent the symptoms
of the ID-7 virus...
...pending FDA approval, of course.
You're welcome. And for the firm itself...
...well, they did what any corporate
asshole in a corner would do.
They offered me Towers' job.
Finally a seat at the big kids' table.
So I took the gig...
...just long enough to make an executive
decision and do some good in the world.
I quit.
Now, I know what you're thinking.
We wrapped this story up
in a nice little bow...
...and we pretty much just killed
a bunch of people. I live with that.
But they do say everything
happens for a reason.
I'm starting to believe it.
Here's one more pro tip.
Paint your own path to success...
...in work, love, and life...
...before it's too fucking late.