7:30, Halstead!
.
Nice a loser!
How many?
.
92 and counting.
Today, we should get out a bit.
Step nine, to compensate.
I can not wait.
Let us go.
Good morning.
Yesterday, he hit me.
(Laugh).
Nice, villain!
(Giggling).
Hey, pick that.
Hey!
Hey! .
Bring it on!
You're dead.
Okay, tough guy.
You too.
Thank you.
Where are you going.
I need you to sit down.
What are you looking for, huh?
Fuck.
Please let me leave this place.
I know this is not easy.
But such a step toward
reconciliation.
The people most hurt your
addiction.
This is the door to recovery.
Well, we have to keep working.
Now this is a mandatory policy for
all rehabilitation centers.
Each of you will participate.
One day you'll get to spend every
day this week.
So go out and make good use of your
time.
Remember, do not worry, all right?
.
Each step is a good.
(School bell).
Okay, so, I told you a proposition.
I do not think I want to hear
- I
stole them from my mother.
Now you have to put them.
Come on, I went through so much
trouble.
Ok. I do not know how -
How about you?
Yes, I take it.
So, you put it.
Hey, Charlotte.
No, hey, I do not want to talk to
you character, Kyle.
Charlotte, come on, I'm
- I'm still
your brother.
No, I do not want to talk to him.
Alright alright.
If it is not our distinguished
alumni.
If you and whatever you're selling
drugs.
School property is not off in the
next 30 seconds.
I want to call the police.
(Engine speed).
(Screeching tires).
(Monitor beeps) for all staff on the
third floor.
Nurse station.
Hey, Dad.
How are you?
.
What do you want?
They, they treat you okay?
.
(Impatiently hit) what the fuck you
want.
Your little prick?
Huh? .
(Beat glass).
I tell you, I never want to see you
again.
You get out of my sight.
Ten years, because of you.
You fuckin 'paint the devil.
You fuckin 'coward!
.
(Loud hit).
If I see you again, I fucking kill
you!
.
If you come back here, I fucking
kill you!
I swear, I'll kill you! .
Okay, let's talk about today's
adventure.
Kyle?
.
I have?
Please.
(Heavy sigh) I went to see my
sister.
Well, how to go?
Not very good.
Can you explain?
.
No.
Kyle he does not want to talk about
it.
Talking is the only way to move
forward.
Oh, fuck you, go forward!
Fuck this whole place! .
This makes no damn difference to us!
.
(Chair slamming).
Fuck, I hate Bob.
He was a rooster.
He is a fucking idiot.
It's make up day.
Very happy to see you.
I'm sorry for all the money I stole.
It's all fucking bullshit anyway.
Speaking of which.
Sonya.
Have your telephone.
My father had just died.
(Light breeze).
(Soft music).
I wish I knew.
We met the first minute.
Unpayable debts.
I owe you.
Because you refuse you will be
abused, bone.
You hired me to make up.
(Crying).
Shortly after 11:00 this morning, an
unidentified man.
Threw Mission City Dam.
Authorities believe he was dead
shock.
But the staff still dredging
reservoirs.
Find his body.
In Mission City.
(Music enhanced) (thunder rumbling).
(Bulb shattering).
Fuck.
(Flick switch).
(Crackling electricity).
(Hum).
(Bent on knocking) Come on!
.
(Hum).
(Knocks on the door) 7:30, Halls
Ted!
.
Nice a loser!
This is very strange.
What?
.
93, right?
Yes ah, it should be 93, but.
92.
Let us go.
Good morning.
Nice, villain!
.
(Giggling).
Well, funny guy, clean it up.
What?
.
At the moment.
Damn.
All.
Do you see that?
.
Fuck you, Bob.
Back here.
Dick.
Hey.
Back here!
.
That's fucking weird.
(Buzzer treble).
(School bell).
Okay, so, I told you a proposition.
I do not think I want to hear this
proposition.
I stole them from my mother, and now
you have to put them.
Come on, I went through so much
trouble.
How do you steal?
.
I took it from her purse like
everything I need, okay?
.
I do not know how
- well, he took
it.
Okay, okay, I take it.
Well, is not it?
Ok.
Now, you have to put it to your lips
like you are French.
Ok. Ok.
(Giggling) You'll never get!
.
(Monitor beeps).
All the staff nurse on the third
floor of the station.
Pick up the damn phone.
What?
(Impatiently tapping).
I tell you, I never want to see you
again!
.
Once you leave my sight!
10 years of your career!
.
You fucking dope fiend!
(Loud hit).
You fuckin 'coward!
.
I see you again, I fucking kill you!
If you come back here, I fucking
kill you!
I swear, I'll kill you! .
Alright alright.
If it is not our distinguished
alumni.
If you and any medications you sell.
School property is not off in the
next 30 seconds.
I called the police.
(Engine starting).
(Ringing security buzzer).
Okay, let's talk about today's
adventure.
Kyle?
.
Is it?
What have you done it?
.
Uh.
I went to see my sister.
(Laughs).
How for you to go?
.
(Laughs).
Can you explain, please?
.
No.
Halstead.
Kyle.
(Singing echoed dreamily): Kyle.
How the fuck are you going?
.
I, I moved the TV.
I got this shock.
This is the last thing I remember.
The same thing happens I use my
light.
Week?
Who cares how it happened? .
The real question is, then how do we
do it?
.
What are you doing last night?
What are u doing?
I was in the shower, okay? .
I was shocked, too.
And then?
.
I did not remember.
I do not have either.
The same thing happens to all of us.
Fuck, I'm gonna get the call again.
(Open).
Exactly the same.
Are you OK?
.
Should we do it?
We just went through the two on the
same day.
We just want to sit here and waste
it?
.
Last night, in the news.
There's a jumper at the dam.
Let us go.
Let us do this.
Damn, we have to stop him.
No, this is. It was too late.
(Sonia sighed.
).
(Thunder rumbling).
Can not sleep.
I do not have either.
At least, you go to see him.
I do not have.
I want you to go to the hospital.
I went to the hospital, but.
I just can not enter his room.
How you think'd happen if we just.
Night stay here?
.
The trouble is in the affirmative.
Then, I will not leave.
(Laughing).
Why do you think this is happening
to us right?
.
Sorry.
No, this is. It does not matter.
7:30, Halls Ted!
.
Bob!
What?
.
What day is today?
Last time I checked, this is
Wednesday.
You see, we came up with this.
We do not find the dog feces, okay?
.
We want to repeat again and again
the same day.
Until we complete our fucking minds
go.
Well, but, you see, we all have the
same shock power.
Or something, right?
So.
So, what is it?
So maybe this is what we do? .
Well, you go and get an electric
shock themselves, then, my sister.
But I'm going to enjoy it, and I got
it.
(Quietly): God, what is that girl's
problem?
.
You know, if you think about it, it
really does not matter what we do
today.
Right?
I mean, I can take a piss group.
Due to the fact that I could just
piss Bob.
Tomorrow, it will be like it never
happened.
Ok. I do not know, man.
I. . Just think we do not mess with
it, you know?
.
How do you think we should do
something with it?
.
I do not know.
(Laughs).
Pull it out and put it back.
(Laughs): What?
A bottle of gin.
I can see it in your pants.
Pull it out and put it back!
This is not my pants.
What is your name?
Put it back!
You know, you two.
Get out of my store!
.
Whether you, get out!
Moron! .
(Laughs).
Feel better?
Oh, begins.
What the fuck are you doing?
What the fuck are you doing? .
Oh, no, man.
We better pray repeat tomorrow.
(Engine roaring life) (laughs).
Fuck!
.
(Pertussis excited).
(Laughs).
(Tires screech).
You are sick!
Ill! .
Oh, Bobby.
Wow, Bob likes cats.
Who am I?
Who am I? .
(Hum).
Bob.
Love.
Cock old lady.
(Laughs).
What the fuck?
.
Oh, no.
Almost laws.
Almost laws. Fuck, you see.
(Laughs) Oh, fuck.
All right, freeze, kids!
Party.
Hands over your head.
Let's go, right now.
That's it.
It looks like you messed up solemn
eh, this time, weeks, right?
.
Like the old man, is not it?
Hands behind.
(Laughs).
Halstead.
Your mother posted bail.
You see this morning.
Ah.
Looks like your father did not come,
cowboy.
Breaking and entering?
Vandalism? .
Your first day of pain that you do
with it, right?
.
Ah, you have to really proud of
yourself.
You have any idea that little
movement just took me?
.
Kyle.
Shortly after 11:00 this morning, an
unidentified man threw himself.
Close Mission City Dam -
(Heavy sigh).
This is very strange.
I was scared.
But.
At the same time, I think really
still alive.
If it does not repeat it?
.
You're going to have a top criminal
record of drug history.
It's quite scary, Halstead.
(Knocks on the door) 7:30, Halls
Ted!
.
Hey, Bob?
Bob.
I had heard.
Some broke into the house in the
vicinity of it?
.
What are you talking about in the
end?
.
Nothing.
Well, come on, let's go.
Get your ass in gear.
Hello there.
Ah hello.
(Laughing).
Once again.
Every time.
Let us go.
Bob, looking smooth.
(Clumsy): Good morning.
(Laughs).
(Quietly): Nice, villain.
(Sound pallet).
(Laughs).
So, what is the procedure?
.
Clean it up.
At the moment.
You know.
I think our people, Bob, on his
downtime.
He likes to just solve a little
Victorian gin.
Victoria gin?
.
Yes ah, yes ah, a little before
lubricating, he kicked off his
shoes.
He thumbs through his favorite
magazine.
(Chanting together): Almost the law!
.
Yes, Bob?
(Laughs).
I know he was a pig.
Oh, do not worry, Logan.
I think you're a little too old for
him.
Fuck you.
(Laughs).
Well, fuck, cowpokes tourism, let us
celebrate!
.
Ok.
(Country music).
(Scream) Yeah!
.
Three!
Here!
.
Baby, baby, baby, baby.
Woo!
You want to be able to.
Pay all this?
Oh, you bet your sweet ass, girl.
Well, yes, I'll need you to solve.
I apologize to you.
He has not been laid in a bit.
A very long time.
You have to help me with that?
.
Oh.
Sorry Sorry.
How can men and women will be for me
to pay.
I do not have money.
Fuck's sake.
I'm very sorry!
.
Well, thank you, partner, this is
great!
.
Well, ah, I'll sing a little song.
To pay for some drinks.
Woo!
.
Yes ah, that's right, folks!
I know that I will dedicate it.
Two of my friends.
You all know who you are.
This is us!
We're his friends! .
Oh, my dear, oh, my dear.
Oh, my dear.
Oh, my dear Clementine.
Let him sing!
Hey, let him sing! .
(Car horn tweeter) (laugh).
Oh, my dear.
Oh, my dear Clementine.
(Laughs).
(Week stupid noise.
).
You get this from?
What is that sound? .
(Laughs).
And then?
(Oinking).
Oh, that is -
I stinks, man.
Index?
.
Oh, dog feces.
Wow. My friend.
One for you.
Oh, my g -
We're really gonna do it?
.
Tell me, do you have always wanted
to knock off a liquor store?
.
These clean thing?
What? .
Well, they jam, if?
They are dirty, right? .
(Laughs): We do not intend to shoot
anyone.
Well, you know, the only thing my
old man cares.
More than his knife collection was
his fucking gun collection.
So, yes, they are clean.
Let's do it, kid!
.
Hmm!
Hmm! .
(Rock).
Stick to your hand!
This is a stick! Come on! .
Try to touch my dick I'll blow your
fucking brains!
.
Go with!
(Laughs).
Open the fucking shit roster!
.
Ok.
Do you think this is fucking funny?
.
Faster!
I have a bag, fuck!
.
Fast!
Here's what the fuck?
.
(Laughs).
Damn, there is a car!
What?
.
Have a car, fuck!
Faster! Come on! .
Faster!
Let's go, come on! .
Come on, let's go, let's go!
.
(Laughs).
(Play songs).
(Laughs) (indistinct conversations).
Oh, my God, what the fuck?
.
(Triumph laughs).
We got how much?
I do not know, man.
Like 500 bucks here 42 pence.
(Laughs) I put it all.
I take it all.
(Pulled siren approaching).
Damn.
(Laughs).
(Knock).
(Qiaokai Men).
Yo, Adriatico, what, man?
.
Well, if it's not my favorite
clients, people.
For a long time, it did not show,
man.
Yes ah, man.
You see, ah.
Michelle?
.
Charlotte?
Adriatico, how going on, man?
Tell me you did not get my sister
fucking high.
This is not what we do, g.
Hey.
Charlotte!
Very simple! Fuck Jesus.
We good?
.
There, no one wants to talk to you.
Well, folks?
.
So just fuck.
Fuck you.
Really?
.
Ok.
Have your space.
Nice fuckin 'sweatpants.
(Laughs).
Do not worry, guys.
I know a guy that we can score.
Welcome to my drug of choice, boy.
This dog feces always fucking scared
me.
They say you addicted when you take
your first hit.
Only today.
You again unaddicted.
(Sigh).
Here it comes.
Go, go, go, go, go.
(Respiratory trembling).
(Gunfire).
Is not going to cure you.
Honey time just gonna hit you.
You have.
You have to go ahead to steal.
You have to you have to go ahead to
steal.
Fuck me.
You have to go ahead you have to
steal.
Ah.
You know, your sister's children,
her slim figure, pretty face.
Yes ah, she was 15 years old fuck,
man.
(Laughs).
Almost law!
.
(Laughs).
I mean, she is fucking hot, though.
Only time will hit you.
I said.
6 kinds of plastic.
Will not stop you.
Oh my oh.
Oh, you have to you have you have
you have.
(Bent on knocking).
Go ahead Go ahead steal steal.
(Impact).
Hold the fuck!
.
What?
(Taser crackling).
(Giggles).
He grabbed his leg.
Jesus.
Fuck, he is heavy. Fuck.
(Groaning effort).
God, Tico.
Get on your knees.
Get on your knees get his mother!
.
Okay, okay.
We just have some fun man.
I did not I did not shut up!
.
Okay, okay, okay.
(Whispering): Come on, man.
Choose it.
What?
(Shooting).
Choose it.
No, man.
Fuck you, man!
Picks, you fuck! .
Fuck.
I did not touch your fucking sister,
man!
.
Select fuck!
Do not make me fucking do this, man.
Do not make me do this, man.
Fuck.
Do not fucking cry, just fuckin
'pick it up.
(Sobbing): The first (sob).
Mm- ah.
Now bite.
(Crying).
Bite, Quantico (sob).
(Vomiting and retching).
(Sobbing) Fuck you, man!
.
I did not touch your fucking sister,
man!
.
(Sobbing).
You have to go fuck jail!
.
Fuck you!
(Sobbing).
(Giggles).
All right, kid, let's go.
It's ok.
Woo!
.
(Pertussis excited).
Time bet!
.
If you slip it?
Bang!
.
Waking up in bed, as if it were a
bad dream.
Yes ah, this is the assumption that
we have another repeat.
Ah, if we do not do.
Make sure they bury me my boots.
(Gasp).
Jesus.
(Laughs).
Hey, Mike, come on, man.
Sh Kyle.
You'll screw up my attention.
(Laughs).
(Water roaring).
Ah. Who is next?
.
Huh?
Hey.
What?
What are u doing? .
You tear your mind.
We still do not know if we're going
to repeat.
We can not fuck like this.
I'm fine.
It's ok.
Oh, who is this girl?
.
There you go, girl.
Rip that pole.
(Laughs).
Oh, one foot, one foot fuck week!
.
(Laughs).
Woo!
.
I saw a smile!
Stop! .
(Laughs).
I will not say another word of -
(Screaming) No!
.
Do not let go!
Week! Zhou, help me! .
(Laughs) No!
.
(Screaming).
(Laughs).
You fuckin 'dead!
.
(Laughs) fuck you dead, you fuck!
Fuck you!
.
See you this morning!
Fuck you!
.
(Laughs) You fucking dead!
(Knocks on the door) 7:30, Ted
Halls.
(Chatter and laughter).
You should get some hash browns
before they are gone.
(Tray crashing) Nice a loser!
.
I never realized how much I love the
hashbrowns.
Jesus.
Ok.
It took only three days rise again
from the dead.
Good morning.
(Sound pallet).
Well, you died last night.
I see you dead.
What is it?
You What else remember? .
I remember before then.
It is empty.
You know, I think about suicide,
but.
I mean, just before that moment, the
right things happen.
I. .
I can not believe how bad I wanted
to live.
We have to stop.
At the moment. What?
.
If today is not repeated
- but it
did not repeat.
It looks like he was going to
repeat.
Yes ah, we are tempting fate w-.
We just want to spit something,
okay?
.
We want to get out of this somehow.
You fucking kidding me up.
This is a fucking gift.
We want, we can do anything,
anything.
This is your fucking losses.
Do not you think this is a weird.
All this stuff happened on the same
day, your father is dead?
.
I forced myself to my dad.
And a first, i-i do not know how to
do.
I mean, I.
I do not even know what he was
doing.
I'm older.
I will fight back, but.
It never seems to stop it.
So, I mean, I, I do not know what.
What, I should give him some peace
of mind is what?
.
Here we go.
No! No, no, no! .
Do not!
Do not! No! .
Fuck!
No! .
You do not want to do this!
Who are you?
.
You do not want to do that.
Look at me.
Let me go!
.
You do not want to do that.
Please let me go, let me go.
(Sobbing): Please.
It does not matter (sobbing): Please
let me go.
News said it was a man, but.
This is a girl.
Just a girl.
I know that she is like, my age the
same.
Maybe this is what we should do.
You know, maybe we should help
others.
She continues to be there again
tomorrow.
He caught me, I tried, I said stop,
he would not, a.
Well, we'll get you a jacket.
Copy.
We will give her assessment.
Obtain all necessary tests.
This is how it happened?
.
A girl was attacked.
(Sobbing).
I need a description.
I do not know what he looks like!
.
You know who did it to you?
Do not touch me!
Can you give me a description of it?
.
That's him.
What?
.
This is him!
Hey, hey!
Just let me go.
Do not touch me, okay?
.
Matter in the end is what Kyle with
you, is not it?
.
Kyle!
Stop!
.
What the fuck?
You raped her!
You fucking raped her! .
I do not know what the fuck you're
talking about!
.
Do not fucking lie to me!
You raped a 15-year-old girl!
.
Well, first of all, she is 16 years
old, I'm sure she is to it.
You fucking raped her!
.
Tomorrow, he will be like it never
happened, Kyle!
.
It does not make better.
So, what is holding the liquor
store, is not it?
.
Okay?
What about kidnapping dealers.
Stick a gun in his face, let him eat
cow shit it?
.
You are so close to blowing his damn
mind, Kyle!
.
Now you have some fucking guilt
trip.
You want to tell me how I can act?
.
I do not know why this is
happening.
However, because it is, I want to
use it, okay?
.
You two better stay the fuck my way.
(Screeching tires).
That is why it happened to us?
.
(Knocks on the door) 7:30, Halls
Ted!
.
Bob!
What do you want, Halstead?
.
It was Wednesday, is not it?
Last time I checked, yes.
(Sound of chair legs).
Nice a loser!
.
I can not believe that Charlotte
hang out with Quantico.
No, I.
I just never thought that she is
what she is?
.
Like you?
I do not know.
(School bell).
Okay, so, I told you a proposition.
I do not think I want to hear.
This proposition.
I stole them from my mother.
Now you have to put them.
Come on, I went through so much
trouble.
How do you steal?
.
I took them from her purse like I
take everything.
Hey, Charlotte.
Hey, uh.
You see, you think, uh
- But, ah.
I do not want to talk to you.
Charlotte!
.
Hey.
Hi. My name is Sonia.
Ah.
You see, I know you think your
brother is a jerk.
But, if you want to just let him
talk to you a minute.
You would do me a favor, will you?
.
Because I was too tired to hear him
bitch.
How poor, he has been to you.
How you'll never forgive him.
Look, we are going to get some
Chinese food.
Why do not you come?
.
Ok.
We can meet in the truck, right?
.
Er, yes ah.
Ok.
Come in.
What Colour?
.
Blonde.
Are you going blond?
Ok.
Article
- I do not know.
I mean, I like blonde, but your
hair.
I mean, your eyes so well.
This is quite.
Yes ah, we have bought a package,
and we're doing this weekend, so.
It should be fun.
(Door bells jingling).
Oh, ho, ho!
Good, good, good.
If this is just too cute not prime
time.
You girls want to get more fucked.
I have been smaller than your life
in your squeaky?
.
Put it aside and weeks.
What, it does not matter, you smoke
meth, but it limits.
The rest of the family, is not it?
.
If it is not the good-neighborly and
friendly guy!
.
Besides, weeks.
How they make like you a gutless
Cuozi.
Become a cop anyway?
.
Just keep talking.
Come on, week, continue talking.
Well, you know, this is not even
remotely funny.
You see, you want to think of what
you are now doing.
Oh, I think, I think.
All my thunk.
Mike
- Shut up, Kyle.
I'm going to give you three seconds.
Let your ugly fat ass out of here.
A.
Pistol, Gerald.
Pushed from the gun hand.
You go there, you go there.
Two (door bells jingling).
(Gunfire).
(People screaming).
Fucking mess with me!
.
Yes ah, no father come to you!
Fuck!
.
You do not know what you're missing.
You okay?
.
Hey
- Are you okay?
.
Charlotte, are you okay?
Are you OK?
Are you ok? .
(Sob sob shock people).
(Knocks on the door) 7:30, Halls
Ted!
.
What the fuck are you doing?
Hey, you're doing everything.
It is to leave you!
It will remain in all of us! .
Kyle!
.
You do not want to do, Kyle!
(Muffled cries).
(Garbled): Kyle!
.
(Screaming in frustration).
You have to do this.
It does not make any difference.
Nothing.
You must try.
You know, it's amazing.
This is something I just can not
justify the score, you know?
.
Yes, I would like to take this from
my mother, she'll never know it's
gone, or.
Steal my sister atm card.
Siphon off some cash here and there.
What a child needs all the money,
right?
.
Then, they.
They destroyed my house.
Because I owe money.
And.
Beat my little sister dog feces.
Five feet away, and I am.
Fuck blow my mind.
I can not let anyone touch me the
longest time.
Come on, Mike Have you ever had to
eat or drink all day.
Sonia and I worry about your man.
Oh, you is not it?
.
You two, thoughtful couple.
How good.
God, she finally got you, huh?
.
She fed you line.
What is it?
.
Uh. I can not let anyone touch me
the longest time?
.
Before that, she grabbed your cock,
it is correct?
.
How she do?
You know, I is not no impression,
myself.
The biggest challenge is to find a
nice place, where the fuck.
Do you do from here?
.
You did not do it, is not it?
What happened, man?
!
.
Look!
Mike!
.
Just.
Stop, will you?
.
Stop.
Just let us forget this, okay?
Let's forget all this dog feces.
Just try again.
Let's try to find that.
There is some deeper meaning.
Here.
(Laughs).
I. .
I just put my pants pee.
There are some deeper meaning that.
Do not you think?
.
(Laughs).
See, look for?
.
(Laughs).
I'll see you this morning!
.
You still drunk?
Maybe.
(Girls giggle).
You should not be locked in place?
.
Charlotte, I need to talk to you.
I do not want to talk to you.
Charlotte.
Fuck off.
I was just wondering if I could talk
to her.
If I can explain.
Maybe just no point in me trying to
explain what I do dog feces.
Kyle, she will come back to you.
I do not know.
You, uh.
About the earlier you okay?
.
Ok.
I am very okay.
Is not that part of you do not know
maybe he was right?
.
I mean, if we do every good thing
erased.
We were erased every bad thing.
What's really important, what do we
do?
.
I guess.
I just need for him it does not
matter.
(Knocks on the door) 7:30 Halls Ted!
.
(Sound pallet) Nice a loser!
Hey.
Bob, Mike, where?
.
What?
Sonya? Do you know where they are? .
I do not know, Halstead and smoke
it?
I do not know.
(Sob fear).
Remove the club.
Come on, Kyle, this is a fucking
club.
Give it up.
You think you can decide how I spend
my repeat?
.
It is only fair that I return the
favor.
Take the knife.
(Crying).
Knife on the table, put it.
What?
.
Come on, Kyle.
Great.
Standing there.
Mike, what.
Now.
Cut his throat.
(Sobbing and crying).
Mike, please do not.
Cut his throat.
I will a bullet in her lap.
I do not lie to you, Kyle.
I will a hole, her legs.
Fuck grapefruit size.
(Gunshot) (screaming).
To do this, or I'll put her mind
bullets!
.
You fucked!
That's right, get angry!
.
Get the fuck wild!
Cut his fucking throat!
.
(Muffled crying).
(Strangled choke).
Welcome to the club, Kyle.
Are you all.
(Moaning).
Come on, come on.
(Sob).
All rights.
We will be very happy I'm fine.
Come on, what's wrong?
Come.
No, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
Fuck!
.
Get up, you fuck a dog feces.
I know you have your.
I'm going to give you three seconds
to get lost.
Fuck you.
(Gunshot, screaming girls).
Voice echoed: see you this morning,
Kyle.
(Knocks on the door) 7:30, Halls
Ted!
.
(Panting terror).
You want me to come?
.
No.
I'm fine.
Tonight you will die.
Do not ask me how I know, but it is
true.
I thought about what I wanted to say
to you so many times.
I do not hate you.
I do not know, but I have to move
from this.
I have nothing else to change.
For any of us.
(Doorbell rings).
What do you want?
.
Trouble?
No, I.
They let us out for a few hours.
Can I, can I come in?
.
I really need to talk to Charlotte.
I, I really do not think this is a
good idea.
Mom, I really need to talk to her.
You clean?
.
Yes ah, my mother.
Please let me talk to her.
Ok.
Residents reeling tonight.
Death two local police.
In what is shaping.
Double homicide.
The suspect was described.
As a white male in his early 20s.
Charlotte?
.
What are you doing here?
I need to talk to you.
Get out of my room.
No.
Charlotte, no, I'm not going
anywhere until you and I have talked
about, okay?
.
We have nothing to talk about the.
Whose car?
.
Your addict friend?
Her name is Sonia.
Yes ah, I met her recovery.
I've been thinking a lot lately.
Just.
About what I've done to you and
mother.
I do not want to hear this news,
Kyle.
I can not let another day pass
without telling you.
I do not tell you how sorry I am.
Fine.
Now we?
.
The thing is.
Charlotte, I see you go down the
same path, I did not.
You think I like you fuck?
.
Article No, it's not what I mean.
You do not have to watch me.
But I.
I did it.
Charlotte.
Charlotte, I do, because this is
what big brothers do.
Their little sisters.
I know you may not care now, but.
However, from now on, I will be
there waiting for you.
I'll be there for you when the
number.
Because.
I love you.
And.
I'll be your big brother.
(Knocks on the door) 7:30, Halls
Ted!
.
Sonia!
Kyle?
.
To give him.
Great.
(Sob).
Now, I can meet you all day, Kyle.
Lets you indulge in your urine.
But this is not very interesting.
So we have to do is to play a little
game of hide and seek.
With a twist.
If I find you.
I want to spend my life hurt your
day.
(Crying).
(Whispering): You have one minute?
.
One minute.
Are you ok?
.
(Gun cocking).
Other door.
A Come on!
.
-. Two three.
Four V.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
10.
(Panting) Come on, come.
One minute!
.
(Engine speed).
Have!
Have! .
This way!
Ya! .
Bring it on.
Come.
Come out, boy, I is not got all day?
.
Come out!
(Gunshot) (gunshot ricocheted).
Bring it on.
Bring it on!
.
Come.
Come on, come.
Go with!
Bring it on! .
.
Are you having fun yet?
(Gun cocking) You know, the last
place I went to the rehabilitation
of.
They move from the terrible events
of our past.
I can play my father!
.
Or, maybe Kyle can play father
because he can not stop you fuck!
.
What the fuck are you doing?
(Gunshot, men groan).
Go with.
Go with!
.
(Gunfire).
(Screaming).
Go with!
.
(Panting).
(Beep forklifts).
Hey Hey, kid!
.
(Gun cocking).
Hey, are you okay?
(Gunshot, men groan).
No snow.
What day is today?
I said, what day? .
(Groaning).
(Heavy breathing).
Oh, fuck.
How are you?
.
I'm fine.
I just got a tetanus shot.
Some needles.
Where is he?
.
No one has seen him.
We need you to come with us.
(Siren wailing).
You fucking head down on the floor!
.
If the two of you fucking move.
I'll be the fucking bullet in your
head, you hear me?
.
I'll fucking kill you.
Mom?
.
I am sorry.
Lieutenant, this is Kyle Halstead
and Sonia Logan.
So, I know you've grown up speed?
.
Ok.
The most important is that you let
him calm.
(Speed Dial).
(Phone ringing) Give me the phone,
come on.
Faster!
.
Hey?
I have your friends here.
Mike?
.
Kyle.
Mike, man, y, you do not know.
You think that day was, I repeat,
please?
.
You think you have a clean slate.
You do not know.
Do you think the jury to go fuck
believe?
.
(Charlotte sob).
Mike.
We can solve this problem.
We got together, right?
.
So we can solve it together.
You opened my people.
You should have let go.
You should let it run its course.
You should have had my back, Kyle!
.
Mike.
Please.
People do not do.
Do not take it out on them.
Please people, do not do in
Charlotte.
(Scream and sob).
Mike?
.
Mike!
Well, we went to go inside.
No, no, let me try again, I can -
Listen, this guy killed two people.
Follow me.
Hey, hey, hey!
.
No, no, Kyle, no!
Step down! .
Everyone away!
.
Mike?
Kyle, you're dead.
You died to keep.
Mike, I'm coming, man.
(Hostage crying).
Mike, you gotta let them go.
(Crying).
Nobody move.
Nobody fucking move!
.
Still stuck shut up!
Mike!
.
This is my sister.
This is my little sister I will not
let you hurt her, okay?
.
(Crying).
I warn you, Kyle.
To keep you where you are.
Mike.
It's over.
Stop.
Just give me the gun.
(Gunshot, groan Kyle).
(Crying).
I'm never gonna make up my old man.
I never, I never will.
It does not matter how many days
repeat!
.
That's the difference between me and
you, right?
.
Mike!
(Gunshot, screaming girls).
(Sobbing).
Hush, Hush.
It does not matter, it does not
matter.
Hush, Hush.
Sh.
Hush, it's okay.
Are you ok?
.
Ok.
Where doors are moaning.
Day.
Leaning stairs.
From Dusk Till Dawn.
Where windows.
In light breathing.
Room.
Set our lives.
Where the door.
Is groaning all day long.
Leaning stairs.
From Dusk Till Dawn.
Where windows.
In light breathing.
Room.
Set our lives.
(Siren wailing).
This is a place.
I do not feel lonely.
I call my home.
(Knocks on the door).
Get up, weeks.
In another day in paradise.
At breakneck speed.
Occupy your hands.
Because you landed on your feet.
You know what I mean.
Vowel change.
I remember when our voices sound the
same.
Now we just translate.
Because I'm still surprised you out
alive.
What did you do after.
Born at your feet run.
Under your bed forest fires.
But it is a good back.
Good come back good back.
Spell it out.
I always skip the word.
Because all pictures are so bright
and loud.
Now better off than.
Because I'm still surprised you out
alive.
What did you do after.
Born at your feet run.
Under your bed forest fires.
Because this is a very good back.
Good come back.
Super fun.
In drunk, young film.
Double knot to undo.
But the bad years are gone.
Yeah big bad completed.
And disappear.
I remember when our voices sounded
exactly.
Now we just translate.
Because I'm still surprised you out
alive.
What did you do after.
Born at your feet run.
Under your bed forest fires.
But it is a good back.
Good come back.