I don't know, he just seems to be
working us a lot harder lately.
Practices are getting a lot rougher
and a lot of exercise and a lot of running.
You know how I love running. I don't know.
Yeah, I heard there was a party going on
tonight, I don't know if I want to go.
I don't know if I want to sit
around Robbie's basement
while you guys make out
in the laundry room.
Which Mark, Mark Mendola?
It doesn't matter.
I'm babysitting. Yes, again.
I don't know maybe. How late
are you gonna be hanging out?
- Hi, sorry.
- I gotta go.
Do you know where the post office is?
The post office?
I'm not real good with directions.
Oh, hey. Can you help this lady
get to the post office?
- Are you Anna?
- Yeah!
Jacob, can you come down here?
Your dad should be home
any minute with a new sitter.
Get down here and help me
with your brother.
Bye, Mom!
Hi.
- You must be Anna.
- And you're Mr. Thompson?
- Yeah, yeah, call me Dan though.
- It's so nice to meet you.
Yeah, Maggie has been a lot less reliable
since she got her braces off.
I don't know what's going on with that.
It's me and my wife's anniversary tonight,
so you're really saving our butts here.
- Happy anniversary.
- Thank you. Thank you.
So, the kids have had play dates
with the Abbott girls.
Ashley and... what's the little
quiet one's name?
- I forget.
- I just call them sleepy and grumpy.
Sleepy and grumpy, that's good.
Yeah, well, our kids,
they tend to be more energetic.
They're good kids, great kids.
They're just...
And then there's...
then there's our oldest.
He's 11, he just started
middle school and...
you know... stones are dropping.
- You know what I mean?
- It's okay, I can handle an 11 year old.
Yeah, Maggie said you were
quite the... child herder.
You got a Facebook page and everything.
- Did you see my page?
- No, no. I don't...
I barely go on the computer.
Yeah, I don't have one of those.
It's a little too much sharing.
But Joyce might've.
And what age are the other two?
Sally just turned 9,
she just had her birthday.
And Christopher is 4.
He's a... he's a cute little guy.
He won't give you much of a problem.
They're good ages.
- Give it back, Christopher!
- Boys, slow it down.
Mama?
- Is the new babysitter a girl?
- Yes, she's a girl.
Because I like it when I'm not
the only one all the time.
- You can't catch me!
- Guys!
You guys. No, no, no. No jumping.
Come on, keep it downstairs.
Jacob! Hey!
- Jacob!
- I'm okay, Mommy.
- Little idiot!
- Jacob.
- You know what?
- What?
Hand it over.
Jacob!
- Hand it over!
- He won't leave me alone!
The kid won't leave me alone,
it's not my fault.
Give me the game.
- Till the weekend.
- For what?
I can't keep doing this with you.
You want me to keep paying
for babysitters till you're in college?
Yes.
Like it or not, you're the big brother,
and I need you step up.
You're not a little anymore.
- Jakey's gotta take care of us.
- Shut it, meat bag.
Hey!
Hey, Jake. Jake, you there?
- Pick up!
- Hey. Yeah. Howie. What do you want?
Wanna come watch me play
The New Dark Realm?
No, no, I can't. Getting babysat tonight.
Maggie's coming over?
She so fine now she got her braces off.
No, not Maggie. Someone new.
Her best friend or something.
My mom let's me watch my sister
after school till she gets home from work
- and I'm born three months after you.
- Good for you.
Hey, so, remember how my cousins
went on vacation to Nevada?
Well, they brought me back something
that's gonna blow your hole.
- What is it?
- I stashed it in your tree house.
- Meet me there after bedtime.
- Alright.
I'll think about it.
Over and out.
Hon?
Hon, how we doing?
Hon? Okay.
Hi, I'm Joyce.
Hi. It's so nice to meet you.
Your house is beautiful.
Sorry it's kind of a mess.
- I'll be right down.
- Okay.
- Can I get a hug before we go?
- Daddy!
Thank you. Thank you. I'll miss you, too.
- You smell funny, Dad.
- It's Cologne. Your mom got it for me.
- What's cologne?
- It's like perfume for Daddies.
Okay, guys. This is Anna,
she's your babysitter for tonight.
- Anna!
- Hi.
- I'm Sally.
- And I'm Christopher!
- That's my brother Christopher.
- Hey, Christopher.
- Oh, who's that guy?
- That's Glow Nose.
Glow Nose. Okay.
- He was my... No, he was Jake's...
- He was my...
...when he was a little kid, and then
he was Sally's, and now he's mine.
- He looks like he's had a lot of love.
- Yes, he does.
Chris and Sal are babies.
I don't need her here.
You know, this a really special night
for your mom and me.
When are you gonna be back?
You'll be asleep.
Get downstairs and meet the new sitter.
They already ate dinner but if they
get hungry they can have a snack.
There's cookies, crackers,
gummies are in the cupboard.
There should be some baby carrots
in the crisper. Yes, there are.
- I left the number for the restaurant...
- I have a pet hamster.
- And the number for my cell phone.
- His name's Admiral Wubbles.
Yeah? You'll have to introduce me.
- Do the kids have their own phones?
- "No cell phones till high school."
That's right, family rule. But feel free to
call my cell anytime, with any questions.
- Okay.
- He's coming down.
What else does she need to know?
Let's see.
They will probably try to convince you
to let them play in the garage.
- Do not let them.
- What's in the garage?
A '73 Corvette Stingray Coupe
that I restored myself.
- So...
- Nice.
Yeah. Yeah, I had it bored
and stroked to a 383.
- Got about 400 horsepower in that...
- I thought we were in a rush?
Yeah, yeah, we are.
And we're taking the minivan.
So, bedtime is nine o'clock.
Jacob can stay up till 9:30
but only to read.
They so should go down easy
because we had soccer practice today.
This one had ballet.
Any allergies or medications
I should know about?
- No, nothing like that.
- Nope, good genes.
You have to watch Christopher
brush his teeth.
Otherwise he just eats the toothpaste.
There he is. This is Jake, our oldest.
- Jake, this is Anna, the new sitter.
- Hi, Jake.
Say hello.
- Hey.
- A wealth of conversation.
He's mad at me because I took away his...
what is it called, hand-held DX thing.
Where is my good coat?
Is it upstairs or where is it?
Right in front of you.
Alright, kids, gather around.
Where's Christopher?
- Christopher!
- It's your anniversary!
- Say goodnight.
- Goodnight.
- Nighty night!
- Alright, listen up, you three.
Anna here is in charge, okay?
You be good and do what she says. Capiche?
- Ka-peach.
- Ka-peach, ka-peach, ka-peach!
- Good night, guys.
- Good night.
- Home by eleven.
- Enjoy your meal. Happy anniversary!
- Thank you. Bye guys, I love you!
- Love you.
Love you, too!
What shall we play?
- Do you want to draw?
- No.
What do you want to do?
We could play board games?
- We could do make-up.
- No! I'm a boy!
Can we get ice cream?
Oh, let's play dress-up!
Yes, let's play dress-up!
You coming, Jacob?
Don't bother.
Jacob never plays with us anymore.
Dress-up's for girls, Chris.
Okay, what dress should I wear?
- This one, this one, or this one?
- That one!
- Which?
- This one.
- Right?
- That's awesome!
That's the best darn dress
that I ever saw!
And then she becomes queen.
And so then they can't decide
who's gonna be queen again...
So why don't they play 'rock
paper scissors says shoot?'
- They can't play rock paper scissors.
- Oh, yeah.
And so then they decide
that they're both gonna rule together.
Hey, guys.
What if I told you...
that you don't have to be a boy,
or a girl, or a human,
or really anything?
You can be whatever you wanted.
And all you had to do was pretend.
Because pretending is this...
super power we all have.
When we pretend,
we can be anyone we want to be.
When you get really good at it...
people won't even know
you're pretending anymore.
- I wanna play pretend!
- Good.
Cool room.
It's alright.
Lemur-boy?
You ever read Death Vice?
No. Mom and Dad say it's too violent.
Well, your parents aren't here
right now, are they?
See ya later?
I never feel great leaving them
with someone we don't know.
I thought Anna seemed
like a very nice girl.
Yeah, I noticed.
The kids are gonna be fine, okay?
Jan Abbott said that Anna
is great with her girls
and we both know that they're nightmares.
Tonight's about us.
Thirteen years.
Our marriage is a teenager.
I think we deserve a night off.
I agree.
- New dress?
- Yes. Now you notice.
I... I noticed before.
It just took a little while
for the Polaroid to develop.
Thank you.
I am Princess Petalsong.
My leaves are vibrant, my fruit is tart,
and my roots run deep.
She's from enchanted forest. On toon tube?
Mommy bought it for me.
It's my favorite show.
What a big scary Bronto!
- Look how the floor shakes when he moves.
- What the heck?
Were those mommy's good pillows?
- What'd you stuff it with?
- Sweatshirts.
Now this is pretending.
Not some out-of-a-bag get-up
your mom bought you.
He ruined Mommy's good pillows!
Sometimes it's okay
to destroy things for fun.
Good job, Christosaurus.
Jacob!
Daddy's old uniform!
- Jacob's gonna do pretend with us!
- Leave me alone.
Just get off of me.
Anna, we're not allowed
to play with this stuff.
Well, Sal...
Mom and Dad aren't here, are they?
That's right.
No fair.
Hey, you were supposed to be
pretending to be something, too!
I already am.
What do you mean?
I'm a photographer.
Yeah, I travel around the world
taking photos of amazing creatures.
- Hey, Christopher, what do dinosaurs do?
- Sit down and eat meat!
That's right.
Smile.
Alright, give us a twirl, Princess.
Beautiful.
Stand up. Come on, big boy.
Alright, stand together.
Raise that trophy over your head.
But not like you're victorious, like you're
going to smash it on top of her.
Sally, stop smiling.
Stop smiling.
Good.
- Did you do this?
- Yeah, I did that.
When did you have time to do that?
I had enough time on my lunch break
to run them here from Vinnie's.
- Vinnie!
- Remember Vinnie? Yeah.
- Vinnie.
- Vinnie was 75 when we first met him.
- How old is he?
- Vinnie was 75. So he's a 104 now.
Remember what he said?
- I don't remember what he said.
- "Red is for the passion.
White is for the longevity."
That's right.
- We got that.
- We got them both.
- I don't want to play this anymore.
- Yeah, let's play a different game.
Alright. How about hide & seek? Not it!
- Not it!
- Not it! Jake's it!
No. No, no, I'm not playing.
I'm not... I'm not playing.
I don't want to play.
Come on, Jake. Don't you want to find me?
One hundred... ninety-nine...
Ninety-eight... ninety-seven...
No peeking.
Ninety-eight,
ninety-seven,
ninety-six,
ninety-five...
seventy, sixty-nine,
sixty-eight...
fifty-four, fifty-three,
fifty-two, fifty-one,
fifty...
thirty-six, thirty-five,
thirty-four, thirty-three...
Ten, nine,
eight, seven, six, five,
four, three, two, one!
Ready or not, here I come!
Now where could they be?
You found me.
Jake?
Jacob?
Hey.
Hey, will you find me a new tampon?
A what?
I have my period.
You know what that is, right?
Yeah.
So, where does your mom keep her stuff?
This?
No, that's for when your mom
has an infection.
Look for Pamtax.
Which color?
Green.
Can you open it for me?
Okay.
Thank you.
Oh, man!
Jake. Come in, Jake.
Jake!
Jake. Come in, bro.
Dude, you gotta come see this stuff.
Howie...
Yo.
I think I just saw my first China hole.
You know eventually we're going
to have to have 'the talk' with him.
What talk?
'The talk'.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- No. I don't want to think about that.
I don't even like picturing him
with armpit hair.
You know the little Stevie
kid down the street,
he's got the little starter mustache
going on. Yeah.
It's just a weird time, especially
if you're the last one to sprout.
You think they're making fun of him?
They better not be. I will punch them in
the face if they're making fun of my baby.
- Joyce...
- He's my baby!
Well, your baby has a pretty
interesting browsing history.
Hey! Give it back!
I already dipped the feet!
Anna! Tell him to give it back!
- Don't be a drama queen, Sally.
- Yeah, Sal. Really?
- Christopher!
- Just get a different cookie.
- Chill out, okay?
- But I had a whole cookie family
and then the papa was about
to take them to the pond,
- and now no one else can drive stick!
- Anyone can drive stick.
There's a whole package
of cookies here, so...
- pick a different papa.
- Yeah, pick a different one.
Yeah, Sal,
there's a whole pack of cookies.
Yep, look at all of these...
Jacob!
- So many cookies.
- Anna! Do something!
Lots of options.
Can I have one? Please.
I want juice.
- You have juice.
- I want that juice.
- Go get it yourself.
- Okay.
You know now that your DNA
is all over those cookies...
- you're gonna have to eat all of them.
- No fair!
Really?
I mean it. Eat them all.
- Go.
- What?
They yummy?
This is a loada B!
Can I have some milk?
Not till you finish those cookies.
Best babysitter...
Hey, what's your favorite color?
Black.
- Black?
- Yeah.
That's my favorite color, too.
Hey, how about we go cheer up your sister?
Yeah.
Man, which of you guys put
the wrong cap on the marker?
- How's that masterpiece coming?
- Good.
It's the right one.
See there's blue under the green cap.
And now I've got a blue flower stem.
Hey, Jacob.
- If you open your mind I'll tell you...
- Fascinating.
So, this the flower queen.
- Queen!
- And then this is the princess.
- Who is the king?
- There isn't a king.
- The royal family.
- It's a queendom.
Hey, Anna, check this out.
Yeah.
- Christopher, what's this?
- Attack of the killer olives!
What happened to that guy?
You mean this guy? He got
stepped on by the monster's toe claw.
That's the toe claw and this where
he chewed off his legs and arms.
Hey, Anna, wanna help me feed my python?
- Can we come, too?
- I don't wanna go.
No, you guys know the rules.
Just me and Anna.
- Please?
- Yeah, he's right. We're too little.
- You know, that's just rude.
- Fine.
- I don't wanna go. I don't wanna go.
- We'll all go. Come on.
No. I'm not going.
I don't wanna see the python! Please!
- Can I hold the mouse?
- No.
- Please.
- Nope.
- Can I feed the snake?
- Why not?
- Because you suck.
Hey. Jake.
In the wild, these animals are hunters.
They always devour their prey alive.
Warm.
This is cold.
But this...
- is warm.
- Admiral Wubbles?
What's he doing here?
Tonight I think Drake
deserves a special treat.
- Cool!
- No. No, no.
- Drake's gonna eat Sally's hamster?
- No, he is not!
You know, I've never seen Drake
eat anything that big, Sal.
- That's not funny!
- Let's see.
- No!
- Hey!
- Yeah, yeah, you wanna get him?
- Get out the way! Move it, Jacob!
Nope. No. Can't get pass me.
- Christopher, what are you...
- No, no, no! Christopher, no!
Get him out! Stop! Stop!
Get him outta there, Jake!
- Yeah, we should get him out...
- Wait. Just watch.
He's scared.
No!
Get him out!
Let go!
Get off of me!
Do something, Jake! Please!
Let go!
No!
I'm sorry, Sal.
Don't be sorry.
Everyone dies at some point.
Okay, I'm really bad
at keeping this secret.
I was gonna wait till dessert but...
since you busted out the champagne...
Happy anniversary.
Alright. Coupons for those mittens
that I wanted to get, right?
- Slippers?
- Open it.
The Nascar Sprint Cup?
Two seats. 'Pit terrace,'
the guy aid those were the best.
Yeah. Yeah. They are the best.
- How did you... How did you even...
- Don't worry about it.
I've been putting away for this
for a while. I got hooked up.
And you deserve it.
You deserve it.
You're the best.
You know who's gonna
freak out about this? Pete.
He's gonna flip his lid
when he hears about this.
He's been talking about this
for three or four months now.
I was kinda thinking you might take, Jake.
Yeah.
- Of course... it's stupid of me...
- I mean... it's not stupid.
...not think about taking Jake. I just...
You just haven't had a lot
of time together lately.
I think he needs it.
And I thought that would be
a fun way to spend time together.
Screw Pete.
Hey. Come on, look who's here.
Look who's here.
You want him?
It's okay.
We'll get more Wubbles.
Wipe away the tears.
Wipe away them!
Come on, wipe away those tears.
Where's the big Sally I know?
Where is she?
Where is the old Sal?
Soaked.
Where is the old Sally I know?
Where is she? Is she still here?
Kids, movie time.
Come on. It's movie time!
It's movie time.
- Come on.
- What are we watching?
I hate movies.
I don't know what's wrong,
it won't turn off...
No, you're with me.
- Jake, where are you going?
- Bathroom.
- It's Mommy.
- That's not Mommy.
What are you doing to me?
Oh, my God.
Just trying out the camera.
Get over here.
I want to take your pants off.
Daddy's naked!
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, you're so hard right now.
Jacob!
Howie?
- Go to bed, Jacob.
- Mrs. Parker?
Howie's had his walkie taken away.
Supposed to be doing his homework
and he's out doing God-knows-what.
Go to bed, Jacob.
Mrs. Parker, there's something wrong
with the new babysitter.
Mrs. Parker?
Crap.
That's private!
Alright.
Well, I think it's time for bed.
Come on, babe.
"Once upon a time...
in a faraway land lived a mama bear
and her little cubbie.
They lived in a cave in a snowy forest.
Mama bear loved her cubbie so much.
He made her smile in a way
mama bear never thought she could.
- Mama bear worked very..."
- This book is strange.
You're strange, Sally.
"Mama bear worked very hard to pay..."
- It's my night to pick the story!
- Then shut up and listen!
- Is that my mom's bracelet?
- Get out! Get out!
You get out!
"Mama bear worked real hard
to pay for food, and the cave.
When she came home at night
and saw her cubbie's chubby little face,
it just made it all worth it.
And then one day mama bear
made a mistake...
and her cubbie died.
This made mama bear very sad.
She missed her cubbie so much...
that her mind cracked.
It didn't break, it didn't break.
It just cracked.
And then mama met a skinny hyena.
His mind was cracked
worse than mama bear's
but he liked her a real lot
and said he'd help her
make a new cubbie...
but it didn't work.
Mama bear's insides were twisted shut...
and the rulers of the kingdom
wouldn't give mama bear a new cubbie,
even when she asked nice."
That's mean.
I think so, too.
"Mama bear and the skinny hyena were angry
and they got into some trouble,
so they decided to escape to a new land
and become new animals.
And began their search for a new cubbie.
But it couldn't just be any cubbie.
It had to be her cubbie.
And then they searched..."
What happens next?
I don't know.
What do you think should happen?
I want mama bear to find a new cubbie
so that she can smile like that again.
She's trying.
Jacob, Sally, time for bed!
Hey, Sal.
Sal, what are you doing?
Get into your pj's.
It's Daddy's gun.
Don't.
The babysitter left it out.
She's no babysitter.
No real babysitter
would give us a gun to play with.
Or show us private movies.
Her name's not even Anna.
What?
It's Emelie.
Who's Emelie?
You're a liar...
and I know it.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Are you gonna shoot me?
Shoot me.
Shoot me!
What you guys doing?
Nothing.
Give me the gun.
- Can't you just leave us alone?
- I'm not gonna say it twice.
- Christopher.
- Christopher!
- Hey. Hey.
- It's not a toy, Christopher!
Hey, give me the gun.
No escape from Chase Hunter.
Give Mommy the gun.
I knew it was you.
No! Hey! No, no, no, no. Stop. Stop!
Stop. Okay?
Inside. Christopher? Christopher!
I do not know who that is
but I do not want to hear one word
about all the games we've been playing.
- I've been nice to you guys so far.
- You haven't been nice at all.
That is what happens when you misbehave.
Now I want you to stay here and be quiet
until I come back, do you understand?
Do you understand!
Who are you?
I'm the babysitter.
No, you're not.
Of course I am. Who are you?
I'm Maggie. You know,
the Thompson's usual sitter?
See, I was supposed
to watch the kids tonight but...
this guy I know that goes to college
asked if I wanted to hang out
and I've been wanting to hang out
with him so I couldn't say no.
I called my friend Anna to see
if she could babysit for me
and she said she would and I've been
texting to see how it's been going
but Anna hasn't gotten back to me which
is weird 'cause she's like the most...
- It's Maggie!
- Maggie.
...the last thing she posted
was that she was coming here
and since then she hasn't posted anything
so I thought I'd come by on my way back
to make sure everything's okay
but then like, you're here
and she's not and I'm kinda like,
WTF is going on.
Right, Maggie.
Yeah.
So you're a friend of Anna?
Yeah. She got sick. Food poisoning.
And the Thompson's called me.
They're a family friend.
Well, do you think I could
just say hi for a second?
No! No. You know what, they're asleep.
Come on. They never go down on time.
I won't tell Dan and Joyce, I promise.
No. You know what?
Stay there. I'll get them.
Sally, Jake, Christopher!
Is that Maggie?
Yeah. And you like Maggie.
You wouldn't want anything bad
to happen to her, right?
Okay, stand up. Stand up.
Okay. Go. Come on.
We're friends, right?
Come on. Come on.
Hey, doodies!
Hi, Maggie.
- You guys having fun with the new sitter?
- Yes.
What have you guys been doing?
Playing.
Pythons prefer live prey.
Kids.
Anna literally like, just texted me.
She is sick. And she called and canceled.
Well... I guess I better
get going, okay, guys?
- No, Maggie, don't go!
- Yeah, please stay and play with us!
I have a life of my own, ya know!
But I see you guys in like,
two days so we'll play then.
- No, wait!
- Hey...
Hi! What's this?
I just... love you, that's all.
- Bye, Maggie!
- Okay. Bye, guys.
Get in.
Go over there. Sit down.
No, no, no, where I can see you.
- Drink.
- Why is the juice dark blue?
It's gonna give you good dreams. So drink.
Stop it! Please.
Good. Come on. Come on!
Hey. Hey! No, you already
had... get outta here!
What are you doing? Don't you dare.
- Don't you dare.
- That's my bite!
- You've had more than your half, sir.
- Your half is in your stomach already.
Wait. Wait.
- What's the matter?
- I never called Anna.
I never called Anna.
I told her I'd call her.
Yeah, it's bed time, too. You better
call her. I'm worried about her.
- Will you get me...
- With those kids.
Will you get the bill?
I'm going to just give her a call.
Hey, you ready to go to sleep?
Where's Jake? Where's Jake?
He's upstairs in bed.
Hello?
Hey, Joyce.
Yeah, they went out like a light.
- I hope they didn't give you too much trouble.
- No problem at all.
- That's good. I'm proud of them.
- Oh, they're so good.
- Well behaved.
- Thanks. Did they need to eat anything?
Well, they did, they ate...
they ate some snacks.
- Oh, good. Not too much sugar.
- Nothing... nothing too big.
- It sounds like you guys enjoyed your meal.
- Yes, it was delicious.
I can't believe I've never been here.
- It's a terrific place.
- Good.
Great. Well, that's good.
I meant to ask you, can you make sure you
leave the hall light on for Christopher?
Yeah, I will do... I will do that,
but no worries at all.
We're just getting the bill right now
so we'll be home in about twenty minutes.
Okay.
- Yeah. Sorry. Wait, say that again?
- I don't know what we'd do without you.
- You saved out night.
- Great. Absolutely.
Yeah. That's great.
- Okay.
- Okay, bye.
Mom? Mom? Mom?
Time to go, little cubbie.
Howie! Howie, thank gosh!
Dude, check it out.
Fourth of July up in here!
Howie, do you have your cell phone?
Hey, I thought we might stick them
in Becky's mom's...
Howie, shut up!
There's something wrong
with the new sitter.
We need more time.
You're not listening, Howie!
She hurt Maggie really bad.
And she's got this weird obsession
over Christopher.
She has my dad's gun, okay?
I think she's trying to kill us!
You gotta help...
And you left...
Chris and Sally alone with her?
I don't think I should drive.
Can you drive? No?
Let's see if there's a taxi.
Taxi!
There you go.
Get off me, Maggie!
No! No! No, no, no!
- You okay? Are you okay?
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
- Dan, what are you doing?
- Stay in the car. Stay in the car.
Dan, be careful!
Dan!
Fuck. Fuck.
Sal?
Sally?
Maggie?
Maggie.
Wake up! Maggie.
I told you what would happen
if you misbehaved.
Where's my sister.
I have her, but she's not the one I want.
Where is my little cubbie?
He's not your cubbie!
He's not your fucking cubbie!
He's my brother!
Do you want your sister
to end up like your friend?
Backyard. Five minutes.
I'll trade you Sally for Christopher.
Is he dead?
- He died on impact.
- Oh, my God.
- You know who he was?
- We still don't know.
The vehicle was reported stolen
and he didn't have any ID on him.
Oh, my... Oh, God.
He was alone.
Thank God. I wanna go home.
I wanna go home.
Officer? Do you know how much longer
you need us here?
We... our kids are at home and we told
the babysitter we'd be back 15 minutes ago.
Can we...
- Okay, let's get you guys outta here.
- Thanks.
Thank you.
Jacob?
Jacob!
Christopher?
Dan, something is wrong.
Something is wrong. She's not picking up
and our machine's not picking up.
I'm sure she just fell asleep.
Yo!
I don't... I just have our home number
I don't her cell number.
- Car 82110?
- Go ahead.
- Report back to Pearl and Court.
- The accident site?
Affirmative. The body of a young girl
was found in the trunk.
Jesus Christ, did you hear that?
ID says victim's name
is Anna Coleman of Amherst.
We're sending a cruiser
to her family home now.
- That's... that can't be. That's our sitter?
- Anna Coleman is our sitter?
I'm sorry, can you please hit the gas.
Hit the lights. It's an emergency.
We need to get home. Go, go, go!
Jacob, get out of the car!
Jacob!
This is it, we're pulling
onto our street right now.
Goddamn it! Can we go faster, please, sir?
There's a car. There's a car.
Hit the brakes! Hit the brakes!
Sally!
Christopher?
Sally? Sally?
Sally?
Dan.