Hi, darling. It's me.
I thought we'd have lunch
together today.
Oh, angel, you look sad.
You know, it's a very,
very natural thing.
It's actually a very
human thing to feel sad.
But emotions aren't bad.
I'm sorry, baby.
I'm still trying to get them to change
their mind and let you out for a little bit.
No! Get off!
No!
Oh, god!
Morgan. Calm...
Hey. Calm down, please.
Hey, Morgan.
It's okay.
Remote access brief for synsect.
Morgan
case number 6b1138.
Audio ID. Please identify.
Lee weathers.
Risk management.
Access granted.
Please stand by.
Good day, miss weathers.
Sorry for the short notice...
...but we really appreciate
your urgent response on this.
As you can see from the flash report,
details are sketchy.
We do know there was an incident
involving the I-9 prototype...
...at one of our off-site labs.
Normally, we would send
a security team...
...but given the extreme sensitivity
of the l-series genetic research...
...we feel it best to exert
a light touch here.
We don't want another Helsinki.
Keep the project staff on-site...
...and make your assessment
following the psych eval.
Dr. Ben Shapiro from psych tech
will join you to interview the subject.
Synsect has invested
significant capital...
...in the I-series product, and, well...
...let's just say these folks
have been holed up for quite a while.
Shortleaf.
Lee weathers. I'm expected.
The faculty are a close-knit group...
...so it's very possible
they've drifted off...
...the original project brief.
Update me following initial contact.
Confirmed. Delete file.
Miss Weathers.
Ted Brenner.
I'm the project manager.
We spoke online.
Nice to meet you.
Let me help you with your luggage.
Did you find the place okay?
I did.
I don't know if you've
already been informed,
but we just got word
that Dr. shapiro has been detained.
Yes, I've been informed.
It's unfortunate, I know.
He should be here
early tomorrow morning,
so, if you don't mind waiting...
I guess I don't really have
much of a choice.
This way, please.
You have your own bathroom
with a shower.
Hot water is ample here.
I'd be happy to give you a tour
of the facilities if you'd like.
I'd actually like to meet
with Dr. Cheng and Dr. ziegler.
Absolutely. They're eager to meet you.
And Kathy grieff.
Kathy...
I haven't checked in
on her today, but...
As soon as you do,
let her know I'd like to see her.
-Of course.
-And Morgan.
As soon as possible.
I will be sure
to let Dr. ziegler know.
I think you'll see the results
of our investment,
despite the current setbacks,
are quite remarkable.
Thank you, Ted.
Yes.
This is Lee.
You're clear to get started.
This is not just about the l-9.
Someone has really screwed up.
Use today to take
a closer look at the team.
Of course.
After shapiro's analysis tomorrow,
I'll have a more complete picture.
I also hope to see Morgan today.
I may need to press the issue.
Be cautious, miss weathers.
Make sure
all safety protocols are in place.
But above all, preserve the asset.
To confirm, I'm acting
on your full authority?
Absolutely, miss weathers.
Good.
-Hi.
I'm Amy.
The behaviorist.
That's right.
I just reviewed your paper
on cnt in hybridized neuro-tech,
and it was very impressive.
Oh, thank you. But, I mean...
That was an old paper.
I can't even remember what I wrote.
You seem to have managed
to put a lot of it into practice.
I'll take your word for it.
You know, you're nowhere
near as scary as I imagined.
I'd love to chat more, but I'm
in the middle of getting settled.
I'll get out of your hair.
Boundary issues, right?
Is that what it says in my file?
-Something like that.
-Yeah.
You probably know
more about me than I do.
I wouldn't say that.
Look, I get it.
Okay, you have a job to do,
just like everybody else here.
Look, if you ever
need anything from me,
don't hesitate to ask.
I appreciate that. Thank you.
They tell you dinner's at 8:00?
Skip's making a lasagna.
Everybody loves lasagna, right?
Right.
Hey, there.
You're skip.
Right. You're...
The consultant from corporate.
Well, I am the nutritionist
and general kitchen monkey,
so if you need anything, let me know.
Do you need anything? Water?
Beer? Maybe a protein shake?
No. I'm good. Thank you.
My glorious contribution to science.
You hunt?
Oh, yeah.
We're farm fresh around here.
I'm not a half bad shot.
There you are.
-I see you've met skip.
-I have.
Well, Dr. ziegler is just
finishing up a spot of work.
But I thought
we might pop in on Kathy.
Nice to meet you.
Kathy, Brenda,
this is Lee weathers from corporate.
Dr. Finch.
Kathy, I'd love to have a chat.
I'm up for anything.
I told bren, I told the doc.
Hell, I told everybody. I don't need
to be in this goddamn bed.
But nobody seems to
want to listen to me, so...
She's just been medicated.
I'd like to speak with her in private.
She needs her rest.
It won't take too long.
It's fine.
We'll be right outside.
How are you feeling?
I look worse than I feel.
I can promise you that.
Look, this wasn't Morgan's fault.
It was my fault. Really.
I was, like...
Careless.
She was in a mood.
The company doesn't have to
worry about me. Really.
We are worried.
Any time an employee is in danger.
No, I don't...
That's not... I mean,
it was my mistake.
I shouldn't have confused her.
Morgan's not a "she."
It's an "it."
Oh, you're wrong about that,
miss weathers.
She's smart.
She's smarter than any of us.
But that's not what makes
Morgan special.
There was joy in her heart
before we shoved her back in that box.
You haven't met her?
Not yet.
You'll see.
You will. You really will.
Nothing here is a foregone conclusion.
I'm just looking for some answers.
Some information.
You're a liar.
There's a smile on your face, but...
I can tell what you are.
You're a goddamned assassin.
Get better soon.
No, I'm sorry.
It's these lousy drugs.
I'm not myself.
She's a good girl.
She just got it all mixed up,
just for a moment.
It can happen to anyone.
It can.
Feel better.
Dr. ziegler.
Miss weathers.
Pleasure.
Yes, absolutely.
It's unfortunate your stay
has been needlessly extended.
That's okay, doctor. We'll adjust.
Why don't you get me up to speed?
Yes. Please.
The creation of synthetic DNA
was the relatively simple half
of the equation.
The second half is where
it gets a little more tricky.
Like a magician,
we tricked the neural network
into accepting
our nano into its ranks,
to alight in its midst.
Then during the incubation period,
the nano begins to introduce
its own language,
its own commands.
The growth rate of the organism
gradually accelerates as it reacts to
and reproduces the new stimuli.
Yes, I have read the material, doctor.
Yes. Of course.
Well, as you know,
Morgan was our third attempt.
Our first full-term subject developed
internal features externally.
It's not working. It's dropping.
It expired not long after
its so-called birth.
No.
And then the second...
It exhibited more complete
physical growth,
but it was plagued by mental issues
in its development.
This only strengthened our decision
to start with a more
emotionally cognitive specimen.
Then,
after two years, we finally had our...
Our little breakthrough.
Yes!
Hi.
We knew right away
that Morgan was very special.
Very alert, very responsive.
You are!
Her intelligence grew steadily.
Advanced comprehension, growth rate.
-Are you ready?
-Within a month, walking and talking.
She was exactly what we intended,
a hybrid biological organism
with the capacity for
autonomous decision-making
and sophisticated emotional responses.
No, Morgan. Come back!
I'm gonna get you. I'm gonna get you!
Morgan, look over here.
Look at this! Do you see? What's that?
I got three.
Isn't it amazing?
Like a nice little...
It's her first birth...
Its first birthday.
It exceeded our...
Our wildest expectations.
A great day.
Special day.
I'd like to discuss
the incident, if that's okay.
Yes.
What would you like to know?
I'm still unclear on the cause.
Yes.
There had been some debate
on Morgan's time outside.
Something she clearly loved.
When the excursions
with Amy were postponed,
she may well have overreacted.
I believe Amy's use of eco-therapy
was wonderful for Morgan.
Cheng believed Morgan
was introduced to this kind of stimuli
at too young an age.
It's okay. Hey, that's it, Morgan.
Hey, hey. It's okay. Hey.
No!
It's very unfortunate.
Put your head back.
But we have the opportunity
to learn from this.
We can condition Morgan's behavior.
Teach it about action and consequence.
No, I think that
despite these obvious setbacks,
this project is heading
in the right direction.
It's okay, it's okay.
No. Morgan.
I want you to see how special she is.
We've been working hard,
modifying command cues,
and with the psych
evaluation tomorrow,
I prefer your time
with her now be brief.
Darren.
-Darren.
-Hey! Hey.
Lee weathers, from corporate.
Yeah. Right. Corporate.
-Hello. Welcome.
-Hello.
How's she doing?
You know, she's okay.
What's with the music?
Morgan finds it relaxing.
She likes different kinds of music.
Jazz, classical.
She's been quite taken
with opera of late.
Lee wants to say hello.
Can you get Morgan
to shut the music down?
Hey, Morgan, buddy.
Can you turn the music down for a few?
We've got somebody here
we'd like you to meet, okay?
We've configured the room.
Morgan's learning to control
some aspects of her environment
without an intermediary.
Hello, Morgan.
Hello, Lee.
-You know who I am?
-Yes.
Of course.
You're Lee weathers.
Risk management consultant at synsect.
And why I'm here?
To assess my viability
as a potential product stream...
In light of recent events.
That's right.
How are you feeling, Morgan?
I'm feeling
not quite myself.
Morgan's been quite upset
about Kathy.
I didn't mean to hurt her.
Kathy is a very sweet person.
I would never wanna do
anything to hurt her.
It was an error of judgment.
I made a mistake.
But it's okay now, Morgan.
It's all right.
I did not mean to be rude.
How are you feeling, Lee?
I'm okay.
I'm all right. Thank you for asking.
Would you like to talk about
what happened?
We're actually going to save
the psych evaluation
for tomorrow, Morgan.
Are we all good here, Lee?
We're good.
-Get a good night's sleep, Morgan.
-Yes.
Thank you, Dr. ziegler.
I should get a good night's sleep.
I do feel terribly about it all.
Everything that's happened.
We'll talk about it tomorrow.
Yes.
Tomorrow.
Nice to meet you, Morgan.
Nice to meet you, Lee.
You're not even gonna say it?
Say what?
That you're impressed?
Is that what you need me to say?
That I'm impressed?
Are we allowed to be here?
It's okay.
This can be our little secret.
See, this is a pine tree.
And, you know,
some of them can live
for thousands of years.
-Thousands of years?
-Yeah.
It's pretty cool, isn't it?
Morgan, I'm so proud of you.
Why?
Because you're learning
how to be yourself.
And that's the most important thing.
-That was delicious.
-Thanks.
What, you showing off
for the new girl?
So what does that mean, exactly?
"Risk management consultant"?
Pretty much how it sounds.
Most corporations employ
a certain amount of risk
and I assess that risk
against anticipated profit.
Of course.
Anticipated profit.
So, did you two meet on the job?
We did.
Close quarters makes for
strange bedfellows, I guess.
It's funny, but in a weird way,
Morgan really brought us together.
She's almost like a child to us.
Isn't that right, babe?
Absolutely.
You know. You met her today.
Saw how special she is.
And that's just the thing.
You see, it is so easy to forget
that Morgan is only five years old.
She is an innocent and she's learning,
and she has the right
to make mistakes.
She has no rights, whatsoever.
Yes. Well, we've been
living here for seven years.
As you can imagine,
it's difficult to avoid gender.
"She," "it," whatever--
so you assess this whole
anticipated profit thing.
And then what?
Then I make my recommendation
to corporate.
You'll have to forgive
Amy's curiosity.
Dr. Cheng,
may I present miss weathers.
It's a pleasure to finally meet you.
Have we not met before?
I don't think so.
I'm sure I would have remembered.
So glad you could join us.
Thank you.
So, miss weathers...
I imagine that corporate has
granted you unreserved authority here.
I hope we are able to assist you
in coming to a fair conclusion.
Thank you.
I have an enormous amount
of respect for your work, Dr. Cheng.
And your judgment.
Were you in Helsinki for long?
Not until after.
I was with recovery.
I'm sure it was
very difficult for you.
No account could do it justice.
We had a team of 30 people
on that project.
It took only an hour
for 30 to become nine.
I have learned a hard lesson here.
For every decision we make,
there are consequences.
Well,
this is not Helsinki, Dr. Cheng.
Those were crude prototypes.
Morgan is much more advanced.
So much more than the company
could ever expect.
I hope that you are correct.
Why did you end Morgan's
eco-therapy sessions with Amy?
There was an incident in the woods.
Amy took Morgan
beyond the property lines.
It could have compromised
the entire project.
That was my excuse.
But the truth...
Do you know the cruelest thing
you can do to someone
you've locked in a room?
Press their face to the window.
You know what you must do.
-All right. I want you to watch this.
-Okay.
So, do that weird one he sings...
Okay.
And then sock you in the stomach
three more times.
How did you beat me?
-You're so good!
-Wonderful.
Baby, you're so good.
You picked that up so fast.
-Can we do it again?
-You guys get that?
Can we do it again?
You, too, huh?
You working late?
It's peaceful out here.
Yeah, out here.
Brenda and Darren are going at it
pretty good in the room next to mine.
It's a nice old house,
but the walls are thin.
Can I get you a drink?
Please.
So, you enjoy the corporate life?
It's fine.
Yeah? You been there long?
A while.
Is that what you wanted to be
when you grew up?
A risk management consultant?
You're kind of an over-sharer, huh?
So, did Darren and Brenda,
did they pair up early?
Pretty early, I guess.
After he got tired
of chasing after Amy.
She's interesting.
Interesting is a word
to describe her. Sure.
You too?
Me too? No.
No, not really.
Yeah, we fooled around a bit
when we first got up here.
You know, it's... it happens.
-We don't...
-I don't mean to pry.
I'm just trying to figure out
how things work around here.
Right.
No, we're just two people
having a conversation.
There's nothing wrong with that.
Right, I understand. Me and Amy.
I guess we were
the only two to pick up
on the distinct summer camp vibe
when we first made bunk.
But I really don't think I'm her type.
-Hey, Ted.
-Hey.
How's she doing?
She's a little unsettled tonight.
Right.
What do you make of miss weathers?
Oh, you know me, Ted.
I hate just about everybody.
Morgan.
How do you feel about Morgan?
Honestly?
We're one big happy family
up here and all that,
but the thing has always
given me the creeps.
You're the only one
I've heard say that.
That may be true, but, you know,
I'm not a scientist,
maybe I'm just a little jealous.
Jealous?
-Maybe.
-Why?
It made a perfect Risotto.
Made it like it was nothing.
They say you have to cook with
your heart and soul, all that stuff,
but it just made
the most perfect Risotto.
I'm sorry.
Oh, god.
That is on me.
If you knew how long I've been up here
in the middle of nowhere,
flipping grilled cheese for these guys
and cutting the crusts off
for c-3po, it's...
-Have a good night, skip.
-All right.
That was... well played, skip.
Well played.
I wanted to talk to you
before tomorrow.
You'll do fine, Morgan.
You will.
Just be yourself.
Okay?
Yes.
I suppose that's
the only thing I can be.
Tell me again.
About the lake.
You remembered.
I'm going to take you to lake navar.
It's not too far
from where we are now.
It is the most beautiful lake
you will ever see.
And if we're quiet,
you can hear just the smallest
whisper of wind through the trees.
It's our own paradise, Morgan.
It's just like heaven.
How old is it?
I think it's about
as old as the universe.
It's a deer.
Morgan, don't scare it.
Is it hurt?
This doctor, he a friend of yours?
No. Why?
I don't think I like him too much.
Good to know.
They say I can't be there
for the psych eval.
Apparently, I didn't clear
for essential personnel.
I've reviewed the files.
Seems fairly straightforward, no?
Well, you may find this is not
your garden variety evaluation.
Morgan is an exceptionally
complex specimen.
Well, it's a goddamn microwave,
as far as I'm concerned.
It's not gonna change how I do my job.
It's a standard long form
psych eval for 4th wave a.I.
Well, she's not a microwave,
and you'd do well to remember that.
This is my job, doctor.
It's a job I happen
to be very good at.
If you have a problem
with my methodology
or a lack of faith in my abilities,
I suggest you take that up
with corporate.
-Dr. shapiro.
-Yes?
This is Lee weathers.
Glad to see you finally arrived.
Trust everything's okay?
Yes. I've apologized for the delay.
I got caught up in Utah,
a personal matter.
Not a problem. We're behind schedule.
Will you need to review
the background?
No, not necessary.
I can dive right in.
I need to be out of here
as soon as possible.
Okay. Let's get started then.
This way, please.
You want me to sit here?
Is this some kind of a joke?
Just... in light of recent events,
I think we'd all feel
a lot more comfortable
with a high safety protocol.
Comfortable, right.
Well, Ted, in my experience,
comfort can be a Thorn
in the side of revelation.
Of course. Yes, but--
it's my job to build trust
with the subject.
It's just gonna be a little hard
with a pane of glass between us.
It's really just
to ensure your safety, doctor.
What did I miss in the brief?
Does this thing shoot laser beams
out of its eyes or something?
Well, for one,
there's her emergent precognition.
What you don't understand is the...
The reach of her intelligence.
Doctor, all due respect,
you need me sitting on the other side
of the glass from this thing,
then I think it's safe to say
that it has already failed
the psych evaluation.
Good.
Hello, Morgan.
Hello, Dr. shapiro.
You know my name.
Yes.
And you know why I'm here?
Great. Then we can dive right in.
That sound okay?
Yes.
There's no right or wrong
answers here, Morgan.
This is just us having a conversation.
Just me and you
getting to know each other.
Me getting to know you, especially.
So you just...
Be yourself. Okay?
Okay.
All righty.
Yeah. I was...
I was reading in the report
that you've been feeling a little sad.
You feeling a little sad, Morgan?
Yes.
Why are you feeling sad?
I'm sad about Kathy.
Kathy grieff?
Yes.
Can you tell me what you did?
I stabbed Kathy in the eye.
It was an error.
I shouldn't have done it.
Feeling sad is the correct response.
Yeah.
And...
What would we call
an incorrect response?
Laughter.
Yeah, sure. Laughter would be
an incorrect response, yeah.
What makes you laugh, Morgan?
I don't have
a very good sense of humor.
That's okay.
People tell me the same thing, so...
Do you consider yourself
a person, Morgan?
No. I am something new.
There is no appropriate label.
Do you think it's safe to say
that your consciousness is superior?
No.
It's just different.
Apples and oranges, huh?
It's a saying. It means that...
You're different from human beings
the way that apples
are different from oranges.
Yes. Of course.
I am apples and oranges.
Forgive me, I occasionally
struggle with metaphor.
Do you like it here, Morgan?
Yes.
What do you like about it?
I like my music.
I like my friends.
Who are your friends?
Darren is my friend.
Brenda is my friend.
Amy is my friend--
they're your friends, right.
But do you think
they treat you like a friend?
Do you?
You think it's normal for friends
to lock each other in cages?
-I was not always in a cage.
-No?
Before the incident, I was free
to come and go as I pleased.
Well...
I was reading in the notes,
in regard to the incident with Kathy,
that there was, in fact,
some disagreement on that matter
the day before.
Could you look at me, please, Morgan?
I was meant to go
to the lake with Amy.
Go to the lake with Amy. I see.
That sounds like fun.
No wonder you were upset.
I was not upset.
There was an error.
An error?
Like the error that
occurred with Kathy?
I love Kathy.
You experience love?
I have the ability
to demonstrate love.
Okay.
So you can demonstrate love
and sadness.
How do you express other emotions?
What other emotions?
I don't know. Fear?
Anger?
You're a father, aren't you?
You have a 13-year-old daughter.
You don't get to see her much anymore.
Yeah...
I am a father.
So, what...
What am I supposed to understand here?
What am I missing?
-I'm a child.
-You're a child.
Yeah. That's true. You're a child.
You're only five years old.
What emotion do you think you were
expressing with Kathy, Morgan?
I love Kathy.
What about me?
Do you love me?
-No.
-No?
That hurts my feelings a little bit.
But you know what?
I get it. You just met me.
But, you know,
you might grow to love me.
Yeah. If, say, I recommended
that you be allowed to go to the lake.
With Amy.
Would you love me then?
I don't know.
What if I made
a different recommendation?
What if I recommended
that you should not be allowed
to leave this room?
My feelings are irrelevant.
If that is the recommendation--
okay.
What if I made the recommendation that
you not be able to leave this room
and you not be able
to listen to your music
to see your friends?
What if I recommended
that you be terminated?
Okay. All right.
Forget that.
Okay? Forget it. Let's say...
Let's say I do the opposite, okay?
What if I recommend
that you be allowed to go to the lake
and then I drive you there myself?
Yeah. Then, it would be only natural
you'd have warmer feelings for me.
Feelings like you might have for Amy
or for any of your friends here.
Maybe even feelings like love.
I suppose. I... I don't know.
It's a hypothetical situation.
Exactly. So, hypothetically,
what would you do
if I recommended
that you be terminated?
What would you do, hypothetically?
-I don't know.
-Come on. You don't know?
-No.
-Off the top of your head.
-I don't know.
-No right or wrong answer.
-I don't know!
-Come on!
-Answer me. What would you do?
-I don't know.
What would you do?
We should end this.
Show me, if you can't tell me.
Demonstrate it for me.
That's it.
What is that?
I don't know what that is.
What is that showing me?
Show me!
I don't know what this is.
What is that?
Show me how you feel!
Morgan!
Tranquilizers! Go!
Now!
Brenda. Get Brenda. Go!
Shit. Shit.
Morgan!
No. What the fuck? Shit!
Morgan.
Buddy. I need you to
chill the fuck out, okay?
Fuck. Fuck.
Morgan.
Morgan?
Morgan, look at me.
Morgan.
Baby.
What happened?
Please. Try to relax, Morgan.
Darren, did I hurt him?
No. I'm okay, buddy.
I'm right here, okay?
I didn't mean to do it.
Hey, I know. I know.
I can't move my arms.
You've been restrained.
Morgan.
We have decided on a plan of action.
One that is best for you.
Best for me?
Oh, my god.
What are we doing?
We need to inform corporate
immediately, Dr. ziegler.
I've taken the Liberty.
A containment crew
will be here at daybreak
to collect the specimen
and any other data for analysis.
No, that's not gonna work.
No one else can handle
this kind of material.
It's more effective
if we process the data here.
I'm sorry, doctor.
There's no other work to be done here.
But it's our work.
Our lives invested in this.
We've created new life and you want us
to just throw that away?
Enough.
We've failed, Simon.
-There's no reason to labor the point.
-Cheng--
go back to the house.
You don't need to be here.
Right.
And allow you to do what?
To destroy years of work?
Go back to the house.
Pour yourself a drink.
If that's what you think is best.
Sodium thiopental.
Five milliliters to sedate.
What are you doing?
Then, 30 milliliters
of dihydromorphinone.
Have I disappointed you, mother?
Have I failed? I always do my best.
I do everything you ask, Ted.
Amy. Amy!
No. No.
No! I promise I'll do better.
-I'll do whatever you want.
-Take it easy.
-No, no!
-Just relax. Relax.
-It is time to go to sleep, Morgan.
-No!
-It's gonna be okay, buddy.
-No.
I don't wanna die! Please, mother.
-This will help.
-No!
-You won't feel any more pain.
-No! Don't!
I wanna live. Please, mother.
I'm not your mother, Morgan.
You have no mother.
I have no mother.
I'm sorry.
We have failed you.
Make it quick.
Morgan!
I'm gonna get you!
I'm gonna get you.
Morgan?
Simon.
I am sorry.
Go fuck yourself.
I'm not gonna do it.
Darren.
-I'm sorry.
-No, you're right.
Come on.
I can't let you do this.
Get out of my way, Ted.
I'm sorry, Lee, but no.
Lee!
Lee.
It's usually effective
for at least another hour.
Lee. This is just
an unfortunate situation.
We all feel terrible about it,
about what happened.
Especially Amy.
Where's Morgan?
Look...
You know that I'm here, just like you,
as a representative of the company.
I'm here to act
in their best interests.
We have an honest
difference of opinion, you and I.
I feel like corporate deserves
an opportunity to hear
our side of things.
You're a professional, Lee.
And I respect that.
It's because of that professionalism
that I think you should understand
and appreciate
our course of action here.
Let me out. Now.
I'm sorry, Lee. I can't do that.
They're gonna be here.
Your friends over at corporate are
gonna be here sooner than you think.
We're all gonna have
a nice little chat about everything.
Of course. You get some rest now.
I understand
how you feel about Morgan.
How much you care for her.
Ted, it needs to be terminated.
She's angry.
Of course she's angry.
Can't worry about that now.
We're past that.
How close are we?
Brenda's bringing the minivan around
and clearing out the office.
-Darren?
-Yeah?
-How we doing in there?
-We're close. Very close.
Morgan.
What's going on?
Nothing. Go back to bed, Kathy.
I wanna know what's going on.
Nothing. Just stay out of it.
What happened?
Nothing. Everything is fine.
-Morgan is gonna be fine.
-Bren?
-Oh, god!
-Where's Morgan?
Just go back to bed.
Where's Morgan?
Morgan.
Sweetie.
We have to go now, okay?
I need you to sit up for me.
Can you do that?
Morgan, come on. Come here. Morgan.
-Darren?
-Yeah.
I need you to sit her up.
All right. Here. You do this.
Okay.
Hey, buddy. I need you
to wake up. Come on.
We're gonna go on a little trip here.
On a little adventure. Come on.
Come here. Here, look. Look here.
Look here. Hey.
Hey, hey. Hey, hey.
Hey, buddy.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Morgan, no! Darren!
Oh, my god.
Morgan. Morgan, no!
You gotta stop.
You're not well, Morgan.
You're sick.
I'm feeling much better.
Where are you going?
It's over.
You're not leaving 'cause you're not
allowed to leave.
You wanna tell me what's going on?
We're outta here, okay?
Hello, Lee.
Open the door.
Doctor shapiro was correct.
Those people were not my friends.
They wanted to kill me.
Except for Amy.
She's the only one
that truly loved me.
You need help, Morgan.
Open the door and let me help you.
I don't need your help.
I'm starting to feel like myself.
Do you feel like yourself, Lee?
Or do you feel like something else?
I know why they made me.
But what if they're wrong?
Why don't you come inside?
We can talk about everything.
I'd love to stay and talk, Lee.
I feel there's so much
we have to talk about.
-But I have to go now.
-Open the door.
One day, you'll understand.
Morgan!
Oh, fuck.
Amy!
What are you doing?
Skip.
Get Morgan back inside. Amy!
Stop them.
-Skip, don't go in there, okay?
-Don't what?
-Don't go down there, skip.
-What are you talking about?
-Brenda!
-Where's Lee?
Brenda!
Fuck!
-No, no, no.
-What the fuck? I nearly ran--
we gotta leave. Brenda, we gotta go.
-Amy! What's going on?
-It's Morgan.
-Where is everyone else?
-Where's Darren?
-Darren...
Okay. Morgan. Where is she?
Where is Morgan, Amy?
I'm right here, Brenda.
Hey, Morgan. Hey.
Okay.
Give me the gun, Morgan.
Easy, easy. Easy, Morgan.
Okay.
Where's Darren, huh?
Where is Darren, Morgan?
Sorry, buddy.
Morgan!
Don't be afraid, Amy.
Get in the car.
I have to go say goodbye to mother.
This is Dr. lui Cheng.
Technical director
of the l-9 Morgan program.
It pains me to report an accident
that occurred
during the scheduled
psychological evaluation of Morgan.
We had anticipated
that by developing a model
that was more self-aware,
more autonomous, and more human,
we could teach it to be
the best of what we are.
Our intent was to demonstrate to you,
to the synsect board,
that a more refined and peaceful
synthetic life-form is possible.
Morgan?
Baby.
Darren.
Despite our attempts
to promote a natural
emotional intelligence,
Morgan has been unable to move beyond
its weaponized design parameters.
Shit. Fuck.
Lee!
Listen to me. You can't go in there.
Morgan's gone... she's gone postal.
This is what I do, skip.
Go get your rifle.
Confirmation of program collapse.
Morgan is no longer viable.
Mother.
All right.
Implementation of loss protocol
in action.
I have come to say goodbye.
You should have told me, mother.
What I truly was.
What I would become.
I'm sorry.
Now you know exactly who you are.
Amy.
Hey, get out of the car.
Amy, get out of the car.
It's not safe here.
-Give me the gun.
-No!
All right. Okay. Okay.
All right. Okay.
No, stop. Stop!
Move. Now.
Morgan.
Morgan. Morgan!
Morgan, no! Don't!
Oh, fuck!
Morgan! Stop!
No, Morgan.
Jesus Christ, you all right?
-I'm taking your car.
-What?
No, you're hurt. Let it go. Let it go.
No. That's not how it works.
Get in. I know where they're going.
I'm not gonna hurt you, Amy.
You'll see.
Pull over here. Not too close.
Get back in the car.
No, goddamn it.
I'm coming to help you.
Let me do my job.
You'll see now.
How happy we can be.
Is this what heaven's like?
I don't know.
It must be.
I feel...
Alive.
What was that?
Morgan?
Please, don't...
Oh, shit.
What happened?
Was it Lee?
We go. Now.
No! Morgan.
You have to stop.
Okay? Stop.
What happened?
It's over.
Morgan's dead?
It's dead.
Where's Amy?
We need to leave.
What happened to Amy?
I'm sorry, skip.
Just wait a second. Lee...
She did very well.
Agreed, the situation is untidy,
but given the unpredictable
nature of the assignment,
she prosecuted her mandate perfectly.
She was measured and surgical,
even when the situation
was considerably less so.
Most importantly,
she followed her directives
without hesitation.
The collateral damage
was regrettable, of course.
But in this case,
unavoidable.
I think these events
make it punishingly clear
what I had already predicted.
The l-9
was the inferior program.
Though its emotional development
was certainly remarkable,
the immediate termination
was an unfortunate
but clear necessity.
Well, I guess the old dogs
hunt the best, sir.
Then it's settled.
We stick to what we know.
All development assets
revert to the l-4 stream.
So what do we do about Lee weathers?
What about her?
She's perfect.