RESTORATION
Subrip: Pix
I've spoken with your family
and they're on their way.
They'll be here soon, John.
You're doing great.
Now let's talk about where
you're gonna vacation
after this?
What's your favorite place?
Are you a mountain man?
You like to go
camping and fishing?
Maybe a little cabin
with your girlfriend?
Because you're doing great.
Now where do you wanna go
when you get out of here?
How about New York City?
It's so magical there.
The Statue of Liberty,
Times Square, Broadway.
I'm a water baby myself.
Love the ocean.
You ever been to the Bahamas?
You'd love it, John.
Just love it.
Warm sun, the coronas
are cold and cheap.
Come on, John.
Just hold on, okay?
Your parents are coming,
they're so close, I promise.
Just hang on.
John, just stay with me, okay?
Stay with me.
John, just stay with me.
You're gonna make it, John.
You are, I promise you.
You can do this, please, John.
Please.
John?
Jonathan.
Dr. Jordan?
You need to call it.
Time of death, 3:15AM.
You can keep it if
you've lost yours.
I know how hard moving can be.
It wasn't for me, it was for
the patient, nurse Smything.
Great, honey.
Hey.
Hi.
You're home.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Baby, these are our neighbors.
Harold and Francine Stone.
-Hi, I'm Rebecca.
-Nice to meet you.
-Hi.
And they
brought homemade cookies.
Not right now, thanks.
Homemade, that's
so kind of you.
Well, we're foodies so any
excuse to get in the kitchen
is a good one for Harold.
Hey, I earned that.
Actually, Francine and I were
just talking the other day
about how we needed some new
blood in the neighborhood
so we'd love to have you
guys over for dinner.
Yeah, as soon as
the hospital gives her
some time to breathe,
we'd love that.
That's right.
Congratulations
on the residency.
It's a fantastic hospital.
Yeah, I feel pretty
lucky about it.
So, how does that work?
I mean, they just choose
where you go and you pack up
your life and move
there for four years?
'Cause that just sounds rough.
Um, well actually...
Just Google it, Harold.
The poor woman just
got off work, okay?
Let's just let her relax.
Sorry.
And we love your plans
for the house, by the way.
Very impressive.
Yeah, we're pretty
excited about it too.
It's a lot of work but
I think it'll be worth it.
And then we still have to
sort through all the belongings
from Mr. Vanderhorst.
My goodness, he had such an
odd assortment of things.
So he just walked away?
Did you know him?
-No.
I mean, I waved at him a
few times from the mail box
but that's it.
Well the brokers said that
his wife passed away recently?
And he just wanted to put
this house and his whole life
behind him, I guess.
So sad.
Not unusual, though.
I mean, statistically speaking,
men who outlive their wives
don't live very long.
And that's why you
have to live forever.
-Forever?
-Forever and ever.
Well, okay then.
Let's go, old man.
Yes, ma'am.
A hug. Okay, thank you.
Thanks so much for the
cookies and the teddy bear.
Teddy bear?
Nope, that's a actually
a gift from the house.
Yeah, I found it in the wall.
I thought it was a possum,
it scared the shit out of me.
Well, there's one more
for the collection then.
You collect teddy bears?
No.
But Mr. Vanderhorst
certainly did.
Yeah, a lot of 'em.
400 of them.
-Really?
-No shit.
You know, I've heard
that old teddy bears
can be worth a lot of money,
like there was one guy
on Craigslist who was...
Honey.
I'll Google it,
I'll Google it.
See you guys.
-Bye.
Bye.
Hi.
Internal damage.
The brain haemorrhage
was just too much.
I was really hoping that
he could see his family
before he passed.
They were 10 minutes out, Todd.
They were so close.
You know, maybe it's
a good thing that
they didn't make it.
That they didn't
see him that way.
You know?
Yeah.
I wanna be there for you,
and you for me in our
last moment of life.
I want it to just be us.
The last thing we see and know.
If you're last
thing that I see,
when I die,
then I'll be happy,
'cause then I know I'll
already be in heaven.
My god.
That is the best and worst
thing I've ever heard.
I hate you so much.
I love you so much.
God, you're so sweet.
You're so sweet, thank you.
The candles are so beautiful.
Just wait until I get
that gas line installed
for the fireplace.
Then whoosh.
As you wish, my lady.
God, you know
how I love it when you
spoil me with technology.
And fine cuisine.
Don't forget the hours I've
spent slaving over a hot phone.
Perish the
thought, master chef.
You belittle
me with your giggles.
You see, this is man's work.
You couldn't
possibly understand.
Really?
Me thinks you doth
protest too much.
-Is that right?
-Yeah.
Pardon me, ma'am,
but I think, I think
you've got some dry rot
in your timbers and
your transom.
Really?
Is that how you see me,
as this old house guy?
If the
shoe fits, partner.
Is that right?
Okay.
Well you know what
this calls for.
What?
Bear fight.
Come on!
Ho!
Yeah, butt first!
God!
Okay!
In the face!
Come on! Come on!
Don't be a
feared little fella!
I ain't gonna hurts ya!
I'm gonna get you!
Todd?
God, you dick!
Baby, I'm
sorry, are you okay?
-Yes, I'm okay!
-I was just playing.
Well that bear isn't,
that shit is hard!
There's something
inside this.
Easy...
My god, Todd, there's
definitely something in here.
Todd, it's a book.
It's a diary.
No no, you do the
honors, doctor.
Me?
Okay.
How do I...
Okay seriously, I mean...
Okay baby, I don't know how
you're ever gonna make surgeon
with a grip like that.
You are so fucking...
My god!
Hey, I got it.
No, it's small,
really it's nothing.
No, my kit's upstairs.
It just scared me.
No, I don't care.
These hands are worth
millions so we're gonna
get you upstairs, we're
gonna get you cleaned up.
And then you're going
to bed, young lady.
Yeah.
My big strong man.
I love it when you take
charge, you know that?
As you wish?
My
God, that's so bad.
Todd!
Todd, you let me
sleep in too late.
You looked too cute,
I didn't wanna wake you.
Really, you are
sch a sweet-talker.
True.
I'm seriously late.
Okay.
Coffee.
Coffee?
I only have time for one sip.
All right.
Yeah, that's good.
I gotta run.
Made you breakfast.
Really?
You are the best husband
ever, you know that?
I love you.
Go save lives!
Howdy, neighbor.
Hi, Harold!
What's up, doc?
You tell me.
Damnit.
Really?
At least
the breakers work.
God, Todd, fix it.
I got a better idea.
Sweety I had
the strangest...
Hey there, sleepy head.
Harold.
Francine.
Morning.
Hello.
Morning, gorgeous.
-Morning.
-Sleep okay?
Think so.
So you always make breakfast
for your neighbors?
Just the ones we like.
The others we burn at the stake.
You are horrible.
We were just on our
way home from the store
and we saw your big strong
man without his coffee mug.
So we thought we would
do our civil duty.
And make him fat, like me.
Seduced
by the dark side.
Honestly, I'm just
trying to bribe him
into giving me some free advice.
Francine's just my
coworker in crime.
Well, you
paid your dues.
Take your pound of flesh.
All right, our
plan worked, honey.
We are off to landscape town.
Love you, baby.
I love you.
I am sorry if we set you off.
No you've
been so welcoming.
Thank you.
You're sweet.
I'm not sure how I'd react to
another woman in my kitchen.
Especially so early in the
morning, but you are a dear.
We will get out of
your way, right away.
No need.
Okay then.
Well I promise to rein Harold in
and you just enjoy
your breakfast.
I said it was too early, but
when he saw Todd out there...
Harold just loves to
think he knows everything
about everything.
He will not call a plumber until
we're practically drowning.
Or an exterminator unless
we're overwhelmed by rats.
Rebecca?
My god.
Are you okay?
Yeah,
I'm...
I'm okay, I'm just tired,
and the hours at the
hospital wear me out.
And my
cooking doesn't help.
I'm sorry.
No, no no.
It's not you,
really, it's just...
I'm stressed from work and the
house and the new hospital.
I understand,
more than you know.
What you need is a night out.
A girls' night.
Get your glow on.
World's biggest bird cage.
Glad I'm not cleaning it.
Right.
It seemed kind of odd it just
standing there all broken.
It'd make a great
park or something.
You'd have to talk
to the city about that.
They haven't been listening
for about 70 years.
I think they're waiting
on some big company
to make a bid and make
it worth their while.
Then all our property
values go up.
Anyway, there's this
pond I'm gonna rehab.
Based on the foliage it
looks like they set up
some sort of English garden.
What?
English garden?
No, that was their burn barrel.
They got rid of their
garbage in that hole.
Really?
Like, what, leaves?
Trash and plastic, whatever
they want to get rid of.
There were no recycling
bins back then, just,
fire and smoke.
You scratch the surface
we're all just an inch
above the dark ages.
Yeah, I guess I'm
romanticizing it a bit?
You should.
It's your house.
Your home.
Fall in love.
No no, I'm good.
Those will kill you.
Truth, but if you're
already in the train,
you might as well
enjoy the ride.
What does that mean?
Lung cancer.
Got the eviction
notice four months ago.
Shit, I'm sorry.
Harold, I didn't mean
to make a joke about it.
Don't apologize.
Nobody lives forever.
God, longest seconds ever.
Okay.
What the hell does this mean?
Come on.
Hey, baby?
I got the washer nuts
for the tub faucet.
Can I get in there?
Yeah, okay.
Um...
Okay.
Give me a second.
I really gotta pee.
All right, just
give me a minute.
I'll be right out.
All right, hang on!
I really gotta pee!
Yeah, one minute,
I know, I know.
I'll be right out.
You scared me.
The shank came
off, and the knob.
Yeah.
You all right?
Okay, just give me
a few minutes, all right?
Okay, yeah yeah.
Get out.
See you in a few, thanks baby.
-Okay.
Hey hey.
Hey, how's the faucet?
It's perfect. Easy fix.
Good.
How you feelin'?
Good. I'm just
tired, you know?
You seemed a
little sick after breakfast.
Yeah, too
much greasy bacon.
Maybe you just got the
flu from work or something.
Um, no it's not the flu.
Is there anything else
that you think it might be?
I dropped my wrench
in the trash.
Todd, I was just gonna...
I was gonna tell you.
I just needed to figure
out how to tell you.
How to tell me.
Baby, we're a team.
I just wasn't thinking.
You hid this in the garbage.
I mean, I'm sorry but
that is fucked up, honey.
Okay, you know what?
I don't wanna get into
an argument about this.
So let's just talk
about this later.
We're gonna talk
about this right now.
How long have you known?
I just told you!
I found out just now!
Rebecca, you are a doctor!
Of medicine!
How long have you known?
I didn't wanna say anything
until I was sure, okay?
Okay, I appreciate
that. Thank you.
I really do, I understand that,
but don't fuckin' protect
me from our lives.
God, why are you
getting so angry?
I'm not angry,
I'm intense, okay?
Intense.
Involved.
This is supposed
to be our decision.
What is that supposed to mean?
I wanted to have
a kid with you.
When we are ready.
So you're not ready now?
Don't play that game with me.
You know that I wanna
have kids with you.
I just also wanna
have you with you.
And the last five
years have been...
Past five years, Todd?
What, what?
Tell me about the
past five years, what?
The last five years have
been about supporting you.
School, studying, the residency.
It's all been about you
becoming the doctor you wanna be
and that's okay,
I understand that!
Well I'm so
sorry that you were
really fucking supportive, okay?
-Don't!
-God!
Hey, this is us!
All right?
Us.
And I just wanted to have
some time being together.
Creating a life together.
Spoiling you with no
fucking responsibilities.
Just us, all right?
I wanted to have
a fucking choice.
I didn't plan this.
And you know what?
I'm not sorry.
But I am sorry that
you're not happy.
I'm fucking ecstatic!
I fucking love you!
And I wanna have kids with
you, it's just this is...
Fuck this is a lot!
You know? It's a fucking lot!
Fuck!
Cheers to you, buddy.
There you go.
I'm gonna be daddy.
Becca?
Dear diary.
Today is my 11th birthday.
I wanted a doggy so we
could adventure together,
but Daddy said I wasn't
responsible enough.
So, instead I got
you, Dear Diary,
and a rad new bike.
So I guess you could say
that I'm a pretty lucky girl.
Dear diary.
Today new people moved
in down the street.
A family with a boy
and girl my age.
The girl's named Delia
and the boy is Robert.
He says they're adopted, but,
they don't look adopted to me.
He says that he's gonna be
a New York Yankee one day.
I think I like him.
I gave Delia Mr. Tickles
'cause she likes him so much
and maybe Daddy will think
I'm responsible enough
to have a puppy for
my next birthday,
if I don't have little kid toys.
But, I miss him already.
Dear diary.
Robbie's mom got super-mad
that we were playing
explorers in the
meadow and said that
I could have gotten them
hurt with my stupidity.
I'm not stupid.
They are stupid.
They don't even let Delia
and Robbie go to school
like me.
It's not fair.
I hope their butts fall off.
Dear diary.
A girl from my school
got disappeared,
and nobody found her.
Her mom came into the school.
She doesn't have a dad
'cause she's a latchkey kid.
Principle Clark talked
to us in the gym
about stranger danger.
Back in class, Miss
B. told us to go home
holding hands with
our safety partners.
I feel sad, even though
I didn't know her.
Dear diary.
Robbie told me his new mom
and dad keep secret stuff
down in the basement.
So we're gonna investigate
like Nancy Drew.
We looked into the basement.
It was all dark, but
then I saw something move
and I heard a song.
I can't remember what I saw.
It's like my head
doesn't want to.
But the song, I kept
on hearing the song.
It was like a church
song, but mad.
It was so mad.
You okay?
Why do you have a weapon?
I heard something and...
So you brought that?
Yeah.
There was a shadow and then
there's a noise so I...
Yeah.
Todd.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I should have told you when
I even first suspected.
I just couldn't bear
to get my hopes up.
Todd, I love you so much.
We're having a baby.
Go save lives.
-Love you.
-I know.
Son of a bitch.
That's it.
All right.
It's a brownout?
We paid the bills
so why is this...
Come on.
Okay.
I got this.
Let's see.
That's the wall.
That's the front yard.
That's the...
Water heater.
All right.
Shit.
Come on!
Hello?
What are you doing down here?
It burns.
It's okay.
I didn't mean to scare you.
What's your name?
It's okay.
Why don't we find your parents?
It burns.
Okay, he's stable
but he can't sleep
for another four hours,
so make sure you keep
him in your line of sight.
Get him food, walk him around.
Yes, exactly.
Compound fracture in 1A?
X-ray is done, no
internal lacerations,
bleeding's stopped, ready
for reset within the hour.
Good.
Thank you.
Okay, what's next?
Grab a Red Bull.
You've got a long night.
Dr. Jordan, we have a
second-degree-burn victim.
Just came in. Might
be self-inflicted.
Okay, who's doing
triage? What room is he in?
1C, he's prepped and stable.
Sedatives? Painkillers?
Morphine and narcex.
Just give me a moment,
okay? I need to check...
No, Dr. Jordan.
It's your husband.
My god.
Todd, what happened?
How did you...
A girl, she...
She was on fire.
And grabbed me.
She grabbed me.
What?
What, Todd? Look
at me, sweetheart.
Okay? Focus, and I
need you to tell me.
What happened?
She was on fire.
From the inside.
Okay.
Okay, all right.
I'm gonna look at this, okay?
How is he?
-Harold?
-I called 911.
I heard him screaming when I
was outside having a smoke.
I thought your house
was gonna burn down.
What?
Harold, what happened to him?
He came stumbling
down the stairs,
holding his arms
out in front of him.
I tried to help but
he was so out of it,
so I called and came over
with the ambulance and...
Sir, this is for family only.
You need to be in the lobby.
No no, he's fine.
It's okay.
You stay here.
I'll take care of the
paperwork, you take care of him.
Thank you.
Okay, let's lay you down here.
Okay, sweetheart?
There you go.
Just like that.
-The girl.
-Todd.
It's okay.
She was...
From the inside.
Okay.
It's okay.
Dear diary.
Susie Mortez is missing.
She went to a different
school than me.
Now I have to stay in the yard.
No more adventures
with Robbie and Delia.
They waved at me
from their yard,
but their mom called
them back inside
like I did something bad.
Dear diary.
The police took
Robbie's dad today.
He had blood on him and
yelled at the policemen.
Robbie and Delia
wouldn't talk to me.
Their mom was crying.
I've never seen a mom cry.
She ran up to me and
gave me Mr. Tickles,
then Robbie and Delia took her
inside, like she was a kid.
Dear Diary.
Dad said he took the
disappeared girls.
That's why the policemen
took Robbie's dad away.
Dear diary.
I saw Robbie and Delia.
They were outside my room.
Dad said no one was there,
but they were.
They were there.
I don't wanna get disappeared.
Dear diary.
Mom and Dad won't listen.
Maybe it's better.
I don't want Robbie and Delia
to hurt them 'cause of me.
I'm scared.
I don't wanna get disappeared.
But if I do, I know
you won't forget me.
You can remember me if I'm gone.
I think that the last
time that I saw you I
said some things that
seemed a little crazy
but it's not me.
It's not me.
Look, I know that you're a
doctor and people come in
and say crazy shit all the time.
I believe you.
What?
I believe you about the girl.
She was on fire.
Yeah, she was on fire.
Where did you...
I saw her in the house.
I think I know who she is, Todd.
How?
How could you?
She's that girl
from the diary.
Something happened to her.
Todd, something really bad
happened to that little girl.
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah?
Yeah.
We have dinner tonight
with Harold and Francine.
It's like a welcome
home dinner, okay?
Yeah.
That sounds good.
I don't know what I would
have done without him.
So what are we gonna do,
about this fire child?
I got this
from nurse Smything.
I'm gonna check the hospital
records later tonight
when it's just
the skeleton crew.
What?
How?
Her name is on the front
cover of the journal.
That was delicious.
-Yes.
-Thank you.
Only the best for us.
We have an organic
butcher in Valley Village.
Local-grown.
I'll have to borrow him.
Do you want me to put
the salad in the fridge?
Relax.
You open another bottle of wine.
We've got this.
Okay.
Women.
The more the world changes,
the more they stay the same.
Yeah, don't let Rebecca
hear you say that.
I think the spirits
have made me fearless.
I thought we were gonna
light it up together.
Get my Frenchy going.
One's my limit.
You mean, half.
I'm watching my figure.
For the both of you?
Really?
How did you know?
My cooking's not that bad.
That's quite
the bottle opener.
Our illustrious patron.
Allow me to introduce you
to Lieutenant Colonel James
Smyth Burget.
First Baronet of
Easton and the director
of the East India
Trading Company.
The spring from whence all
our riches bubble forth.
Really?
Grandpa?
Um, many greats, but yes.
Sounds great.
Actually, he didn't
start that way.
He was volunteered into
the East India Army's
foreign cavalry where
apparently he was rather adept
at um, "converting the savages."
New world term for
old world massacre.
Promoted to Lieutenant
Colonel, given a directorship
in the company with shares.
Kinda like buying a stock
in Apple Computers in 1976.
Exactly.
So you're a baron.
No.
The title died with him,
but the shares gave birth
to a family of ne'-do-wells
that continue to this day.
And of course the
nouveau riche always settle
in the suburban neighborhoods.
We prefer to call it "mingling
with the lower classes"
purely subterfuge for
our nefarious plots.
It's not the golden
ticket people imagine,
but it does allow us to travel
and pursue alternative
cancer treatments
whilst keeping a roof over
our heads and for that
I'll always be eternally
grateful to the old man.
Sounds like a hell of a guy.
The Maharaj called
him Burget, "the beast."
So you've got the
location right.
More ancestors?
August and Drusilla.
Apples from the poison tree.
Great year.
Yeah?
You sure?
Definitely.
You and Harold have children?
Didn't stick.
You two are just
great together.
A lot of people your age
don't have kids nowadays.
My age?
You have no idea.
I just meant that you both
seem really happy together.
Every day, it's like
I won the lottery.
Every day.
Um, Francine
your blouse is wet.
Might wanna...
Let it dry.
Lighten up, doc.
You've got plenty of wardrobe
malfunctions coming your way.
What do you mean?
A breast-feeding mother
will lactate at the
sound of a baby.
Just the sound.
Even if you're not aware
of it, your body is.
And it behaves as if it
doesn't even belong to you.
Thank you.
Any time.
I hope not.
You don't have to thank me.
Yes we do.
He only did what any
good neighbor would do.
Yes but it was you.
Do you remember much?
No, not really.
I remember being in
the basement and,
then I remember your face as
I went into the ambulance.
"She's on fire."
That's what you kept on saying.
I, um...
I saw something when
I went down there.
And it burnt me.
Old wires.
No.
It was a girl.
It was a little girl
screaming, on fire.
We've both seen her.
You got off lucky.
I'm not sure.
We found a diary in the walls.
It's a little girl's diary.
Yeah, Rebecca thinks
that the little girl...
Katie, her name's Katie.
Katie is the little
girl in the diary.
Rebecca thinks that
she's the one that...
Set you on fire.
Yeah.
I've seen her myself.
In dreams and in waking life.
This is something that I
never imagined believing
from somebody else but,
it's true.
I've felt it.
I've felt her.
Do you know the history
of this neighborhood?
Anything that would make
this crazy shit make sense.
Well.
The average house
price is going up 12.7%
but that's what my real
estate agent told me
when we bought the place so,
flaming girls weren't really
a sell point.
I'm sorry, guys.
No, I guess so.
Who
wants creme brulee?
You gotta be kidding.
My god.
Okay.
Get it together, Becks, come on.
All right.
Vanderhorst,
Vanderhorst, Vanderhorst.
V, V, V, V, Vanderhorst.
Come on.
Really?
There we go.
V.
V for Vanderhorst.
Vanderhorst.
Okay.
All right.
V, V, V, where are you?
Vanderhorst, Vanderhorst,
Vanderhorst, Vanderhorst.
Where are you?
Vanderhorst.
Vanderhorst!
Vanderhorst, Vanderhorst.
Jesus.
Todd?
Hello?
-Sweety?
-Rebecca.
Rebecca, hello?
Todd.
Can you hear me? The
reception's kind of shaky.
I'm down in the basement.
Yeah, okay.
Listen, there's
nothing on her file.
It just stops as if she
transferred hospitals.
That's because
she went missing.
What?
Honey, look for a
file on Linda Cruthers.
Who is she?
She's her alleged kidnapper.
She was sent to a
sanitarium nearby.
She might still be alive.
Todd, what?
What?
Hello?
Honey.
Damnit.
Okay.
Cruthers.
I don't understand.
Why isn't it here?
Shit.
Linda Cruthers.
Hello?
Health Institute.
How may I help you?
Hi, this is
Rebecca Jordan from Seeders.
Isn't Linda Cruthers still
a patient at your facility?
What is this
in regards to, please?
I was
hoping to visit her.
Ask her some questions?
Are
you a family member?
No, but...
I'm sorry,
we don't allow visitors.
My residency
is in neurology.
I was hoping to do a
medical evaluation of her.
Has this been
cleared by your supervisor?
Yes. They believe
she's a perfect candidate.
Be here at 9AM.
Parking is in the
north-east corner.
Bring all necessary
paperwork and credentials.
Excuse me, can
you tell me where...
Okay?
You ready?
Help me!
May I help you?
Um yes, we're here
to see Linda Cruthers.
You called earlier?
Yes.
Credentials?
That's good, doctor.
I'm sure she'll be
real happy to see you.
Really?
Yeah.
No one's ever been to
see her but her children.
Not since I've been here.
When was the last
time they visited?
A few days ago.
Sign in, please.
You'll need these.
Thank you.
I'll take you.
I'll be right outside
if you need me.
Thank you.
Mrs. Cruthers.
We need to talk to you.
I know it's been
a very long time,
but we need you to help us
find Katherine Vanderhorst.
Or at least her remains.
Mrs. Cruthers, you were the
last person to see her alive.
She wrote about
you in her diary.
Please.
Help us.
Do the right thing
and make this right.
You destroyed lives,
families, with what you did.
Try to make it right,
before you die.
-Todd.
-No, no.
This woman is responsible
for some terrible shit.
This is her one chance.
Clinically
insane, Todd.
She's not responsible.
No.
I can't buy that, Becca.
Not with what we've seen.
This is a waste of time.
Let's go.
Mr. Tickles.
Did you say something?
I missed you so
bad, Mr. Tickles.
Did you give Katie
the teddy bear?
Katie gave him to me.
For keeps.
No escapees.
So Katie gave you the bear.
Katie did.
Katie was Nancy Drew.
Me and Robbie,
were Bess and George.
We played adventures.
Okay, Linda.
Where did you play?
Where did you go with Katie?
Jungles.
In Africa.
In France, on the Eiffel Tower.
It hummed at us.
But the grass was soft.
And Mr. Tickles
always found the best
clues for Nancy.
Linda, where is that?
Would Katie have
gone there alone?
Linda, where did Katie go?
Delia.
What?
Todd, what did she just say?
Delia, I'm Delia.
-Okay, okay.
-I'm Delia.
Okay, Delia.
Okay.
Now where did Katie go?
They took her
to France.
And they lit up the Eiffel
Tower like fireworks.
And then...
And then it all went dark.
Who is "they?"
I can't tell you.
They'd punish me.
They'd find out.
They always do.
All right she's had
enough, Bec, come on.
Let's go.
No!
You see me?
This is not my skin.
They took my skin and
put me inside this!
He sees me, he knows who I am!
This is not my skin!
No!
-Delia!
-No!
No!
No no!
This is not my skin!
-That was a dead end.
-Yeah.
What, Todd? What's wrong?
I don't...
Something isn't right.
She had a psychotic break.
No, it's not that.
She's talking gibberish, Todd.
It's something that she said.
Look out there.
What? The House?
No no, the transformer.
Okay?
What does it look like?
It looks like a
transformer, Todd.
No no, but if you
were a little girl,
what does it look like?
Imagine you're 11-years-old
on vacation in France.
The Eiffel Tower.
Yeah, exactly.
But how did you know?
We pass by it every day.
We can see it from our yard.
And you thought Eiffel Tower?
No no,
it's what she said.
-What?
-Linda.
She said that, "and
then it went dark."
There was a blackout the
day Katie went missing.
You think
she's out there, Todd?
Todd, that symbol,
I've seen it before.
Holy shit.
My god.
I'm so sorry, little one.
You deserved so much more.
So much more than this.
We need to call the police.
Forensics.
Get them out here so she
can finally be at peace.
We found you, Katie.
You can go now.
You're safe.
-Do you...
-Yes.
Dear diary.
Robbie told me his
new mom and dad
keep secret stuff
down in the basement.
So we're gonna investigate
like Nancy Drew.
Dear Diary.
The police took
Robbie's dad today.
He had blood on him and
yelled at the policemen.
Dad said he took the
disappeared girls.
That's why the policemen
took Robbie's dad away.
Everyone back!
Robbie? Delia?
What?
It's me, it's me.
It's me.
Delia, it's me.
It's not my skin.
It's me.
Dear diary.
I saw Robbie and Delia.
They were outside my room.
Dad said no one was there,
but they were.
Dear diary.
Mom and Dad won't listen.
Maybe it's better.
I don't want Robbie and Delia
to hurt them 'cause of me.
I'm scared.
I don't wanna get disappeared.
But if I do, I know
you won't forget me.
You can remember me if I'm gone.
Goodbye, Mr. Tickles.
My god,
Harold and Francine.
We've got what we
need and we're gone.
-The authorities.
-And tell them what?
Who's gonna believe us?
Honey, we're not safe here.
What about the house, Todd?
I don't give a shit
about that house.
I care about you,
and our little baby.
The rest is storage.
Come on.
You grab the cash,
I'll grab the clothes!
Becca!
No.
Please don't.
Please don't hurt,
just let her go.
Please.
Okay.
Please!
Please.
No!
Mom says hi.
Her last words.
Loved the teddy bear.
Please stop.
Whatever you need
you can have, just...
Just please stop.
Whatever I want?
What do you think that
you could give me?
Anything.
Anything, just let her go.
Take anything.
I will.
What do you want?
We're leaving, we're
not even a threat to you.
You never were.
I want you,
to cut yourself.
What?
Cut yourself across the heart.
Out of love.
No.
No?
It wasn't a request, Toddles.
But don't worry.
You're playing with a partner.
Okay.
Baby.
I'm sorry.
They're adorable.
I told you they
were a lovely couple.
Sweet as pie.
We've had our eye
on you, kitten.
You.
You're so special.
The boy's got gumption!
Tenacious!
I like it!
Very sexy.
-May I?
-Of course August.
I'll be back for you.
Run, Todd, he's coming!
Front-row seats.
Todd.
Toddy, Toddy, Toddy.
Come on!
Come on, Harold!
Come on, you motherfucker!
I love what you've
done with the place.
Strong bones.
Nice frontage.
Of course, I'll have
to change the locks
and clean the carpets.
Nice shot, Todd.
Now me.
But I just love to nest.
Especially with two
babies on board.
I like the fight in you, son,
but your round is over.
Are you the devil?
No.
For Satan is a sign of God.
The fallen Zion
must have a father,
and he is not mine.
But pray to him if you want.
It changes nothing.
It never does.
Try harder.
You took their souls.
No.
Swapped.
Traded in for an upgrade.
New chassis.
Same engine.
And now daddy wants a new ride.
Here comes the dark.
Finally.
Wouldn't be the
same without you.
That's enough, Harold.
That's not my name.
Whoever the fuck you
are, this ends now!
Not the way you think.
Todd.
Go.
Go, baby, go.
Get somewhere safe.
Todd.
Todd, look at me.
I'm okay.
I'm here.
I'm here right beside you.
Look at me.
But I'm leaving.
Please stay.
You can't leave me.
Please stay, Todd.
I never will.
Todd,
you can't leave me.
Todd, Todd.
Todd, no.
You shouldn't be up, sweety.
I won't tell.
I couldn't keep me away
if it was me either.
Do you have any names yet?
She will be Drusilla.
And he is August.
So Todd is his middle name?
No.
Why?