We still meet sometimes...
Bea, Meja and me.
But we never talk about it.
It's a solemn promise.
As by not speaking of it,
it has never happened.
But deep down, of course, we know.
Elvira, hurry up now.
We're leaving soon.
Are there pillows there
or should I bring my own?
They are there.
But what if it gets cold?
I have no wam clothes.
There are blankets as well.
You won't freeze.
I should bring some food.
What if I get hungry?
Stop worrying. It will be fun!
What if we're not allowed to share a room?
- Would that be the end of the world?
Yes. In that case, you must talk to them.
We're leaving now..
- Sibel is ill. She can't come.
But you'll have a great time,
even on your own.
- Hi.
- It's time, come on.
Sibel is ill, so we can't go.
I hope we never get there.
You'll find new friends there.
Hitta mig...
- Did you bring grandma's ring?
- It's actually not grandma's anymore.
Don't get rid of it. Promise me.
- Oh my god!
- What was that?
I don't know.
Are you coming?
My tummy hurts.
I want to go home.
Elvira, you're 12 years old.
You're too old for this.
It's only a week.
It will be over before you know it.
Come.
Here we are.
Hello, sorry we're late.
- Hi. You must be Elvira.
Hello. I'm Jennifer.
You're the last one. You can come here.
Have fun now.
You'll be roommates with... Bea.
No, I'm Meja.
- Then you must be Bea.
Come.
- Bye.
How old are you?
- I'm going to start at six.
- Me too.
- And me.
- Is this your first time?
- Yes.
So... let's see.
You'll be staying... here.
In room 217.
So...
Okay, there's blankets.
We'll get some pillows later.
Other than that, just pick one.
Damn crap.
Oh, shit!
Björn!
What happened?
- I just turned on the tap!
We'll need to let this room dry.
No one can stay here.
Isn't there any other room available?
Thay can take room 213.
But that's not in use.
The key is downstairs.
Room 13. That's scary.
- But it's 213.
- It's still a 13.
- Shocking.
Then why do all those bad things
happen on the 13th.
- Do they?
- I read it somewhere.
And my grandmother slipped in the shower
and broke her leg on Friday the 13th.
Oh, stop it.
I found it!
Let's see.
It seems to be stuck.
I'll get something to
clean this place up with.
Check.
Come back down when you're done.
Björkudden!
Okay. If you have any questions,
just ask me or Björn.
Otherwise, I'll see you at lunch.
- No, wait...
Before you go, turn on your phones.
- Check out those guys.
You can have your phones on days 2,
4 and 6, half an hour after dinner.
If at any other time you need a phone,
just use the public one.
I don't have one with me.
Okay, have fun!
Who do you think's the cutest?
Isak I think. Or Arvid.
So who will it be?
I can't choose.
They're both really cute.
I like Kevin. I like his style.
Okay, now smile. Do your thing.
What about you, Elvira?
Who do you think is the cutest?
Melker! No doubt about it.
I don't know.
But!
Tighten up. Only two sausages each!
Damn. I should have met Meja.
Here. Have mine if you want.
- Thanks..
- Can I take your picture?
- Okay.
- Say "cheese".
- Cheese.
It's not right again.
A little closer.
I didn't bring my camera.
It's broken..
There must be something wrong with the flash.
- Or it's me.
Meja, you look like a ghost.
Need help with those?
- No, the ghost is helping me..
Stop!
- What is it?
- I feel dizzy.
- Afraid of heights?
- No...
But I'll take the bottom bed
just in case.
Stop it! Stop!
Stop!
That's a nice ring you have.
- Thanks.
My grandmother gave it to me.
She's had it since she was mny age.
- Good night then.
- Good night.
My ring! I'm sure I put
it on the nightstand!
It didn't just fall onto the floor?
Someone must have taken it.
Who would do that?
No one's been here.
Or are you saying it was one of us?
I didn't say that.
I'm going to brush my teeth.
Kevin!
- He's in trouble for this!
- Can't you reach?
- Help me then.
What the hell! Stop!
Stop!
Kevin wet himself.
Cell phone time.
Yes, we had a lot of fun.
We had a water fight today.
Look at her cell phone.
I want one of those.
No, we're not doing anything crazy.
No, no one's sad.
Thought I did something bad today.
But that's a secret.
I hope she doesn't get too angry.
I know Meja took my ring.
I'll get her back for that.
I know you took Elvira's ring.
Return it immediately
or I will take something of yours.
The ghost of room 213.
So he took the spare can and went
for the gas station miles away.
The girlfriend was left alone in the car
listening to the radio.
After a while something knocked
on the roof, so she got out...
to see what it was.
And then she saw...
Revenge is sweet.
- Stop it, Kevin.
Calm down. That's enough for one night.
Thank you Arvid, for the
last story of the night.
- There's one more thing.
- Okay.
Henny can finish for tonight.
I just wanted to say my mother
has also been here at Björkudden once.
Long ago, when she was our age.
And every night, she woke up
because the door handle moved...
and the door slowly opened.
But when she went to look,
there was no one in the hallway.
One night she heard foorsteps
and she followed them.
She came to a large mirror.
But instead of seeing her own reflection...
a girl in a white dress
stood stare and stared at her.
Okay, that's enough for now.
- Henny, don't be intimidating like that.
We all know there's no such
thing as ghosts. Right, Henny?
That was scary, what Henny said.
About that girl.
Maybe Henny's ghost took your ring, Elvira.
That would seem to be a
very mischievous ghost.
Stop, it's not funny!
- There might be a ghost living in this room.
The ghost in room 213.
Meja, I'm scared.
I think I know what this ghost looks like.
- You do?
- Like a sheet.
- What?
I think I know her name as well.
- Whose name? The ghost?
Yes. What's its name then?
- It starts with an M.
- And then?
- An E.
Me?
Mebel...
Is that a name?
I don't know where it came from.
Goodnight then, ghost Mebel.
Bea, what is it?
- There was someone at the door.
Who?
You were dreaming. There's no one there.
- Someone was there!
What are you doing?
It's the middle of the night.
Have any of you seen my camera?
- No. Why?
I'm sure I put it on the night stand.
It's my brother's.
He'll kill me if I lose it.
Aren't you coming with us?
- We're going over there.
They'll run into us.
Hurry up, Elvira! Paddle!
Damn it, Kevin!
- Have you seen my cyclops?
- No.
Can you find it?
- No, it's gone.
Bea! Bea!
You nasty piece of work.
Isn't this yours?
Bea, is that not Elvira's cyclops?
- I'm just borrowing it.
I wonder what else she's 'borrowed'.
Shit, it's Bea. of course.
- What?
The one who took my camera.
And your ring.
Didn't you see how she looked at it?
- It was you who...
I don't want it to be her.
I really like Bea.
Don't you remember she didn't
bring a cell phone
I don't think she even has one.
Or a camera.
She said it was broken.
Definitely a lie.
Besides, she's the only one
who hasn't lost anything.
What are you talking about?
- Nothing.
You're talking about Melker aren't you?
- Right.
He checks on everyone
all the time.
Can I go with you tonight?
- Yes.
It could be just the two of us.
- They actually said that?
Okay, then it's fine by me.
There's 12 questions. They're all
multiplce choice. And you play in pairs.
Where's Bea?
- She's in her room, she's not feeling well.
How typical. Pretending to be sick
so she can take more stuff.
Watch where you put your feet.
It's completely dark in the forest,
What are you afraid of?
- How about you?
But you're girls. Girls are more
scared than boys, everyone knows that.
I promise. It's a scientific fact.
- We will see.
Are you ready? I can't hear you!
Are you ready? Okay, good luck!
'Scientific fact'.
He should watch himself.
Yeah, it's a lie.
Henny's scared of ghosts.
That's the question, isn't it.
What year was Björkudden opened?
1930, 1940 or 1950?
- Not a clue.
- We'll put down X.
What's the owl's name?
Cat Owl, Spectacled Owl or Ghost Owl?
Ghost Owl.
What was that?
Probably nothing.
But... we have to go see.
There's no question here.
We're going in.
- No, I want to go back.
Come on.
There's nothing here, we're leaving.
- But 'was just going to...
Are you crazy?
You nearly scared us to death!
- Who are you going with?
- Ingen.
Or, I'll just go by myself.
- What? You can't do that!
You shouldn't be here.
No, there's nothing here.
Come on.
Can I have the flashlight?
- I dropped it.
Go get it then.
Hello there!
Huh?
What was that you said?
That thing about "scientific fact"?
I was really scared.
I thought there was a maniac in there.
So not a ghost then?
- No. There's no such thing as ghosts.
You! I'm glad you think I'm cute.
You're also...
What? I never said that!
But you wrote it in your text.
I didn't send any texts
Hmm. Might be mistaken then.
I'll get you back for scaring us.
- We were really scared.
I'll scare the shit out of you.
- I'm not afraid of anything.
What about the thing Henny's mother saw?
The girls who sneaks around at night.
Let's just hope it's not
a ghost who wants to hurt us.
Stop it.
Why are all ghosts girls?
Why always in white dresses and long hair?
What? A ghost can just as well be a guy
in a white sheet and a wig.
Name a guy ghost then.
- Dracula, Freddy krueger, there's lots of them.
There's no girl ghosts.
- Samar in The Ring, Kayako in The Grudge.
Do you like those kinds of movies?
No wonder you can't sleep at night.
As long as you know
that it's not real.
It was bedtime 10 minutes ago.
To bed with you. Let's go!
Did you hear what he said?
"Melker's skin". As if...
How silly.
But then... he's so cute.
_ That's true.
Kevin then?
By the way, melker said
that I had texted him.
That's interesting.
What did you say?
That... that he was cute.
Oooh. Love is in the air!
Stop it.
Can you hand me my bracelets?
Thanks.
- What is it?
- I saw a girl!
Bea, you just dreamed again.
It wasn't a dream. I saw her!
- But there's no such thing as ghosts.
What did she look like then?
- Like you.
Like me? Maybe it was me.
What are you talking about?
_ Mom says I walk in my sleep sometimes
No, can't be. She was a redhead.
Maybe you found a wig in your sleep.
Here we go.
Has anyone seen my pen?
- We're actually singing.
Maybe we should help her?
- But... she took it herself.
She was very sad.
- Ever hear of 'crocodile tears'?
How can someone just take
someone else's stuff.
I get it when someone takes Elvira's ring or
my camera. They're actually worth something.
But what about your pen. 20 öre?
Something can be valuable
even if it doesn't cost a lot of money.
My aunt gave it to me a week
before she died, it means...
Arvid and Sara?
Maybe he didn't know you like him?
I'm not feeling well. I'm going to my room.
- I'm coming with you.
I want to be alone for awhile.
Cell phone time!
- Are you coming?
What are you doing?
Getting rid of some of the
unwanted things in my life.
There you go.
By the way, I think Isaac is the sweetest.
I thought so all along.
Where is my camera?
- Your camera?
I know you took Elvira's ring. Return it
immediately or I will take something of yours.
The ghost of room 213.
- That was just for fun!
A blast. Now get me my camera.
- I didn't take it.
I sent that text because
I thought you'd taken my ring.
Why should I take your ring?
- I thought you did it as a prank.
But that was just
to get along with Melker.
I texted him that he was cute
and write that it was from you.
How could you think
that I'd taken your ring.
What? You thought it was Bea.
- What? You thought I did it?
But... like... it's because...
You don't have your own stuff.
Cell phone, camera, and so on.
And then you're alone
in your room all the time.
That's because you make me feel left out.
That's not true!
- Is it, Elvira?
What? You think I'm being mean to Elvira?
In that case, you're just as mean.
Can we just stop with the accusations?
I didn't take anything...
and I don't think it was
any of you guys either.
Okay.
What is this?
Elvira, look.
So things went missing at night?
- Apparantly. Something different every night.
And you're absolutely sure
that they're gone?
We've searched everywhere.
What do you want me to do anout it?
- Quiet!
- Okay.
We have some obvious rules here.
No swimming by yourself.
Don't leave the camp without staff.
No drygs. No smoking.
And don't steal from the others.
Break the rules,
and we will send you home.
It could be a prank. or a ghost.
- Not a very funny prank.
If anyone knows anything,
now's the time to speak up.
Maybe it's a real thief.
Someone from the outside.
- What's happening.
- Look.
The ghost.
No, it's not a ghost.
There's problems with the generator.
If it was someone from the outside,
we would have known about it.
And the doors are locked at night.
So you mean it's someone from here?
One of us?
I'll count to 50 and then I'll come.
If you don't hide well I'll find you.
50, 49, 48...
Close your eyes!
3, 2, 1, 0. Here I come!
What are you doing here?
- Hiding.
Look over there.
Eva is my mother.
She stayed in room 213 when she was here.
This is the most haunted part.
Have you had a cut?
- I'm here. Where are you?
Anyone here?
Maybe under the bed?
- It's just me.
- Are you playing?
- No.
- Can we just say you are?
So at least I found someone.
- Okay.
Mebel and Hjördis...?
Does she really exist?
Bea, Meja.
- You can hide here if you want.
You...
It was meja who sent that text,
Yeah, - So...
Found you!
- Look, Meja. Melker and Elvira are kissing.
- Stop!
- So are you a thing now?
We were just hiding.
- Yeah right.
There's so many mosquitos here
but they didn't get me once.
Me neither,
Do you know why they bite you?
- No?
Me neither. But I feel like
they should like me.
- What was that?
- What?
Is anyone here?
Gitls are so easy to scare.
- You idiot!
What? You think it's a ghost taking stuff?
- We don't think that at all.
Yes you do. look how scared you are.
- Stop it!
It's quite clear that it's Kevin.
Right?
He's teasing because he's on love with Meja.
- Oh stop it.
But yes... that must be it.
Charlie, Charlie...
are you in the room?
We're you doing that?
- I didn't do anything.
Shh... he's coming.
We know you're here, Kevin.
What if it's not Kevin but the ghost?
- Stop it, Bea.
Bea!
I'm just kidding,
- I got really scared.
Shit, this sucks.
Shhh... that's him!
Come on.
I see him.
Kevin...
Come find me...
Elvira...
Elvira?
Why didn't you wake us?
- I just woke up.
When did you change then?
I don't know.
What's that?
It seems to be a letter.
And it's written with my pen.
- A purple pen?
What does it say?
Ask the woman in the red house.
Ask what? And what red house?
It looks like...
Look, it's a page from my diary.
Asl the woman in the red house.
What does that mean?
- There's no red house here.
- No.
How, Elvira? _ What?
There are no red houses here.
I've seen a red house.
Although it's outside the camp.
Does a woman live there?
_ I don't know.
We drove past it on the way here.
It looked deserted.
What are you waiting for then?
Come on!
I need to talk to you.
- Leave me alone.
Are you going somewhere?
Nowhere. Just going for a walk.
Yes, but... were you building a raft?
- I was.
Yes, yes. Don't leave the camp alone.
- I won't.
Isn't it illegal to go here?
There's certainly no one here.
It looks completely deserted.
I think we should go back.
- What are you doing?
- Hello!
- Hello.
- Sorry, we were just...
We were wondering if anyone lived here.
- Someone does. What do you want?
Can my friend use your bathroom?
Sure. It's right through there.
The door is open.
But I don't need to use the bathroom.
- We're looking for something suspicious.
What's your name?
- My name is Hjördis.
- You're from Björkudden?
- Yes.
Are you allowed off the camp site like this?
- Yes. Or... well, no.
No. In my time they were
very strict about those rules.
Hjördis and Mebel.
Björkudden, 1961.
Where did your friend go?
No problem. She's not feeling so well.
Yes. I should probably go and look.
No, it's alright.
Elvira, hurry up!
Elvira, we have to go now!
What are you doing up there?
- I'm sorry.
- What's that?
- Hurry up!
Run!
So there really is a Mebel?
- Yes, it said so on the card,
Mebel and Hjördis, 1961.
She was a redhead.
- Just like the girl I saw at night!
There was an abituary as well.
She's dead.
Where have you been?
Has the raft been completed?
We were just out.
- Out? Out where?
What is it?
Did something happen?
Yes. or no.
It's haunting our room.
- Haunting?
She's a redhead. The ghost.
The ghost is a redhead?
- And her name is Mebel.
How do you know that?
Did she introduce herself to you?
No, but Elvira said so.
- But I'm not sure where she heard that.
There's no such thing as ghosts.
You're 12 years old, you know that,
There they are, the smugglers.
- We built it ourselves. Where did you go?
Nowhere.
- We noticed. We were looking everywhere.
What are you doing, really?
- Nothing.
So you were doing nothing nowere?
- Right.
Come on, Isaac.
We'll name the raft.
What idiots.
What do you think?
- So it was you after all?
You're full of shit. I knew it!
- What? What have we done?
The missing stuff!
The door! The letter!
But how do you get Hjördis to do it?
Do you know her?
- Which Hjördis?
- Which letter?
Why else would you name the raft Mebel?
Come on.
Meja, come!
Calm down now.
Be nice to each other now.
Hörni, what did I say?
It's you.
Hah!
Jennifer... is it true a girl
died here at camp?
So it was you. I always thought so.
- What?
Hjördis came around and told me
some girls had come by her house.
No... or...
You know you can't leave camp grounds.
Are you going to send me home?
Here's what we do.
Don't tell anyone, but...
I'll pretend that I
don't know what you did.
Okay? But don't break the rules again.
I will have to send you home then.
When I was here,
I was also in love with a boy.
But I didn't dare say anything either.
Then camp was over and I went home.
Are you alright?
- A little to the left.
A little higher.
Down a bit now.
- Just a little more.
Get off now.
- But we're almost there.
We can't stand it.
You know what, forget about it.
Can you imagine anyone
picking it up, Elvira?
- It's in the office.
- Okay.
What are you afraid of?
- I just want to show you something.
- What?
- It's a secret.
Did you take them?
- No. I can show you if you promise...
not to tell anyone.
Not even Meja and Bea.
I promise.
Henny, how did you know
about the cuts?
My mom told me.
Close the door behind you
and stay quiet.
Here they are, sit down.
But they're kittens.
- Aren't they cute?
I hid them here so
no one would find them.
No one else knows?
- No. I'm afraid that if someone finds them...
they might get killed.
You should talk to Jennifer.
She's nice. She can help you.
Where did you go?
- Picking up this.
In the shed?
- No, I was just going to look.
Oh, come on.
Which do you think I should take?
- This one. It would fit...
- This?
- No, that one.
This one would look great.
Doesn't this feel too pink?
- Or take it here.
I think it actually gets better.
You can borrow my eye shadow.
It will match your eyes.
Thanks.
Don't they look too green now?
No, it must be the light.
You look great.
I just wanted to tell you about Mebel.
We didn't understand why you got so angry.
We didn't mean anything by it.
- Why did you do it then?
It's because...
We thought our raft was so great...
so we wanted to name it
for the prettiest girl in camp.
Then we all thought of someone else.
So we took the first latters of all
the names and we made a new name.
That's all.
Meja, Bea, Elvira.
Mebel.
How stupid of us.
- Shall we dance?
- Yes.
- What is it?
- Nothing.
Shall we go outside?
Did I look different in the mirror?
Huh? No.
You...
I was thinking of something.
I like you.
Elvira?
What is it? What are you doing?
- Look... she's sitting on Elvira's bed.
Who is that?
It's Elvira.
- But look at the hair. Don't you see it?
Do you see now that it's just Elvira?
What are you doing?
Are you writing in your diary...
in the dark?
- I don't know.
- What? You do.
You have a pen in your hand.
Isn't that Bea's pen by the way?
So it was you?
The ring and camera are in
a cigar box in the shed.
Thanks for letting me borrow them. Mebel
- I didn't write that.
If you think this is funny
then you're crazy.
I must have done it in my sleep.
Did you go to the shed in youre sleep too?
I saw you picking up the cord.
That was completely different.
- Yeah? And what was that?
I can't tell you.
- No, you'd betray yourself then.
It was Henny. She found some kittens
and she showed them to me.
Kittens?
- Yes. In a basket in the shed.
Then let's go there and see. For your
sake those kittens had better be there.
You go first.
So where are these kittens?
- They were here.
- Sure.
I swear...
Where is my camera?
- There's a box.
Thief.
Wait, don't go!
Wait!
Let me in.
- You can call Björn or Jennifer.
But then they would know it's you
running around at night, stealing stuff.
Or...
you can take my camera.
Come on.
Look, she's awake.
- I solved the mystery.
What mystery?
About the ghost and who took our stuff.
That was you.
Last chance to tell the truth.
- It wasn't me.
As you wish,.
- Here's the camera.
- Alright.
Schyst.
- What';s the matter. What happened?
Have you seen a ghost again?
- There's no ghosts, there's a thief.
There must be a ghost.
I can prove it.
You've been lying all along.
- I never lied to anyone.
You're accusing everyone all the time.
I did as you said.
I told Jennifer about the kittens...
and she found a shelter where they
won't be killed. All except one.
- I can keep it.
- How sweet.
I told you so.
Can I tell you about the ghost now?
Or maybe I should just show you...
Shit, you went there
on your own last night?
These are journals from
a hundred years ago.
This is from 1962.
The girls in room 213
report strange noises at night.
Wristwatch gone. The ceiling light came on
in the middle of the night.
And check this out.
Björkudden, 1985.
Eva woke up with
inexplicable cuts on her legs.
Do you remember Henny told me
her mother saw a ghost at camp?
Eva is her mother.
Eva and Gunnel see a red-haired girl
in the hallway in the middle of the night.
What's that?
Tragic death at Björkudden. Yesterday,
12-year-old Mebel Andersson was found dead...
at Björkudden's children's camp.
The cause of death is still unknown...
but all signs indicate it was an accident.
I'm sorry.
I think it was a ghost.
But stop it. It's all just a coincedence.
What about the other stuff?
The door that was opened? The letter?
And the strange picture of Elvira?
And the letters that wrote themselves?
Was that also a coincedence?
Check this. The picture looks normal now.
You must send those of Melker to me.
Of course.
What's that?
I didn't record any video.
Has anyone recorded with your camera?
It's me!
Thank you for staying in room 213.
It's been empty for so many years now.
When you came here
it was like I was alive again.
Thank you for giving me
my best week ever,
I hope you enjoyed it as well.
Play it again.
I can't. The video is gone.
Elvira, you're mom's here!
- Elvira!
- I'm coming!
It's been almost a year since this
happened. A completely ordinary year.
The only thing that changed is that
I'm not afraid of being alone anymore.
- Should we...
- Do you mean...?
Yes, we should.
Although maybe I should be afraid
of being alone.
I still think of Mebel sometimes.
And know Bea and Meja do as well.
We know she's there. And waiting.
Find me.