Lights out!
--struggle which followed
the death of Lenin...
...Joseph Stalin prevailed.
Stalin was the new face
of an old idea: Marxism.
While the Bolsheviks firmly established
their authority at home...
...the Comintern fomented revolution
throughout the world.
Communism was on the march.
Stalin was in the Kremlin.
But what of the common people?
What of the proletariat?
Those who fought to win a new world?
If we look at the history...
They're frying someone, Pop.
You're on the Hades Express, mister.
Quiet.
Death is nothing to celebrate.
- Don't matter who it is.
- He just died.
His name was Wayne Fisher.
He was 32 years old,
and he killed a lady with a hammer.
He had a rib eye for his last meal.
He's been on death row
at Dewbend for three years.
- And his last words were, "Go to hell."
- How do you know that?
It's just in my head.
All right.
It's past your bedtime, children.
Go brush your teeth
and go to bed, please.
And history always repeats, my friends.
The ghosts of their past
will soon become our present...
...if we do not confront them head-on.
Elise, I thought I told you
to put all these toys away.
You're not listening to me.
It wasn't me who made this mess.
Then who was it?
Christian, shut the door, please.
You can tell me.
It was the little boy.
He lived here a long time ago,
and he loves playing with our toys.
- I swear.
- I believe you.
I do.
You know,
you've been blessed with a gift.
You're special.
Some people are afraid of special people.
Your daddy, he's one of them.
He doesn't understand your gift.
You just keep it between us
from now on, okay?
Okay.
It's time for bed.
- Good night.
- Don't turn off the light, Mom.
I'm gonna be right out there, honey.
And if you ever get scared,
what do you do?
That's right.
I gave you this,
so that if you ever get scared, you can go:
Wherever I am, I'll come running.
But you gotta save it...
- ...for when you really need me, okay?
- Okay.
I love you both so much.
- Love you too, Mommy.
- Love you, Mommy.
We see an actual atomic bombing run.
Heading for the target is Backseat,
code name for the ship.
The radio navigator...
Hey.
What?
You asleep yet?
No.
Do you ever think about the people
who go to the electric chair?
Sometimes.
Do you wonder where they go
after it's done?
No.
I know where they go.
Oh, yeah?
Where?
They go into the dark.
Christian?
What are you doing?
Elise.
You made all the mess, didn't you?
Yes.
Where's my whistle?
The boy is in the closet.
It's okay.
We won't hurt you.
Come on out.
Stop it, Elise.
I'm not in the closet.
The people took their revenge.
Gerald. Gerald, no.
What have you done, Elise?
- Put your hands on the wall.
- Leave her alone.
Quiet, Audrey!
Did you see a ghost?
Gerald, stop it.
Yes.
I don't want to hurt you, girl.
Just say no. That's all you have to do.
I'm just gonna ask you again.
Did you see a ghost?
Yes, I did.
They're all around us in this house.
They're everywhere.
You don't have to do this. Please.
She's just a little girl, Gerald. Please.
No. No, Daddy.
No, no.
No, no, no. Take me. Please take me.
- Help me.
- Please, please, please. Gerald, stop!
- Please, honey, she's had enough.
- Don't. Stop.
Please don't. No.
Don't tell me how to punish her.
I punish people for a living.
Please!
Please, not in there.
No, no, no.
No, Daddy!
No. Daddy, please,
I don't wanna go in there!
No, not in there.
No, Daddy, please, not in there!
Daddy, let me out! Daddy, please!
You can either follow my rules...
...and sleep under my roof or you can
break them and sleep under my floor.
Don't put me in here, Daddy.
Daddy, please.
Daddy, come back.
I don't wanna be in here alone.
Daddy, please!
Are you scared of the dark?
Who is that? Who's there?
Don't be afraid.
I can make it light.
Who is that?
Why are you down here?
My daddy put me down here.
Your daddy doesn't treat you right.
Open this door.
There'll be lots of light.
Go on. Open it.
There's a key hanging up right there.
Take your time. I can wait.
You're the only one
that can open the door.
You are more powerful than you know.
I want you to help me open all the doors.
Don't forget what Bill the turtle just did,
everyone...
...because we might have to do
the same thing.
That's what this is all about, my friends.
Duck and cover.
This is an official civil defense film...
...produced in cooperation
with the Federal Civil...
Elise?
...for the ultimate...
Audrey?
Audrey.
Audrey!
No, no, Audrey. Audrey, no.
No. No. No.
No, Audrey!
I'm sorry.
No!
Good morning.
The dreams are coming back, Warren.
Just won't go away, will it?
How would you like breakfast in bed?
I thought so.
- You're getting old, Warren. We both are.
- I've been studying last week's footage...
...from the church. We missed something.
There is movement in the frame.
- Look.
- It's a piece of lint.
- Lint doesn't walk across the room.
- Behold.
The reason I was up all night.
The lights.
That's right, my friends.
It's voice activated.
No more dealing with pesky switches,
having to find them in the dark...
...straining fingers as you switch them.
Yeah, that was a real problem before,
you know.
Toil in the darkness of sarcasm,
my friend.
I prefer to work in the lights.
The lights?
Lights!
Bad acoustics.
Natural light's better
for the environment anyway. Voila.
I love that you boys are staying
in the house.
But please don't try to fix anything else
that isn't broken.
Spectral Sightings.
Yes, she is.
Elise!
- This is Elise.
- Hey there. My name is Ted Garza.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Garza.
Yeah. I'm having some problems.
Things are happening in my house...
...and they say
that you know about this stuff.
I know some things.
Yeah, well, I was wondering
if you could take a look.
I need... I need help is the thing, see.
May I ask where you live?
I live at 414 Appletree Road...
...Five Keys, New Mexico.
Mr. Garza...
...I wish I could help you,
but I really can't.
I'm so sorry.
I thank you very much
for thinking of me.
Sorry to drag you boys out of bed.
That man who called today about a job...
...he told me he lives in the house
that I grew up in.
I call it a house because it wasn't a...
A home.
I don't have memories from that place.
I have scars.
This gift I have
that you boys are so in awe of...
...my father tried to beat it out of me.
And...
...my mother...
...she was killed in that house.
She was murdered by something
that I brought into this world.
This demon wants to use my abilities...
...and it will hurt the ones I love
to get to me.
That's why I never want to go
into The Further...
...like I did for Quinn.
I have spent my life fighting
these things...
...because I can never forget the look
on my mother's face when she died.
So...
...I have to help this man...
...because I know what he's up against.
We'll pack up the truck tonight.
We'll get an early start tomorrow.
Not this time.
This one, I have to do...
...alone.
We have to come with you now.
This cost us 700 bucks.
Plus 200 for the logo paint job.
Before we go inside...
...I brought some clothes for you boys.
Some of it belonged to Jack,
and it's very important to me.
I bet I can guess who you are.
There's no need. I'm Elise.
- Hi.
- And this is Specs and Tucker...
...my associates.
She's psychic.
We're sidekick.
What was that?
She's psychic. We're sidekick.
- Sorry, I'm... I'm not understanding.
- Yeah, never mind.
You wanna come in? Here.
Come on. I'm supposed
to invite you in. Come on.
Hello.
--aggression.
And history always repeats, my friends.
The ghosts of their past
will soon become our present...
...if we do not confront them...
You still have so much of our old stuff.
It was all here.
Pretty good stuff, you know?
I didn't see any reason to get rid of it.
There's stories.
About your family.
I never listened to them
when they said that...
...this wasn't a place that I should live.
You know, I looked at it,
and I just saw a little house.
I said, "Screw the stories,"
and I bought it.
Now I believe the stories.
You getting anything?
There are so many spirits,
it's hard to tell the good from the evil.
A lot of people died in that prison.
When did these occurrences start?
Soon after I moved in.
First, it was...
...the little things, you know?
Things that...
You've been blessed with a gift.
You're special.
You just keep it between us
from now on, okay?
No. No!
You okay?
Yeah, I'm... I'm fine.
These experiences you're having...
...where do they mainly occur?
Mostly in one room.
I keep it locked now.
I haven't opened it in three months.
I'll take that one.
You wanna give me a hand?
That's good.
A little bit more.
Sorry.
Can't go in there.
When it first started...
...I could hear somebody
just walking back and forth.
Someone was talking to themselves.
You think you're going crazy,
and then you...
You actually hear it.
And you know you're not.
Finally, one day, I walked in...
...and I screamed at it:
"You stop."
"You stop.
Please stop."
My whole life savings is in this place.
You gotta help me.
You gotta help me, please.
That's what we do.
The camera is so we can see
what she sees from out in the truck.
We call it the "Winneba-ghost."
I think I'm gonna go there now.
You really are gonna stay here all alone?
My presence tends to draw the spirits
out of their dark, little corners.
You need to take this.
Thank you.
Good night.
Can you hear us, Elise?
Yes. Try not to drown out
the other voices.
We got you. We gone.
Here you go.
- What's this?
- Lights.
Thanks.
I thought you were gone forever.
My mother got this for my brother...
...and he lost it
when he was 6 years old.
Safe now.
- Stop.
- What?
Go back, to the left.
- Yeah, nothing.
Thought I saw some feet.
Feet?
Elise, there's someone
right in front of you.
Looks like a woman.
I don't see anything.
Elise, be careful.
I don't see what you're seeing.
You're going to touch it.
Be careful.
Help her.
Elise? Elise? What happened?
The whistle.
It took the whistle.
What were you doing in there?
Thought you were gonna stay
in the bedroom.
Something led me down there.
The spirit of a woman.
I don't know why she said, "Help her,"
but it's a ghost I have seen before...
...in this house.
When I was 16 years old.
Did you hear that?
Hear what?
There's someone in the laundry room.
No, there isn't.
I heard it.
I'm gonna go look.
No. Don't, Elise.
Hello.
I live here with my brother, Christian.
- What's your name?
- Stop it.
You're making it up.
Come out and see my brother.
He doesn't believe that you're here.
Christian!
What are you doing, girl?
There's someone in the laundry.
There's no one in here.
You're doing it again.
You can't punish me for this.
I never wanted it. I never asked for it.
If there's one thing...
...you've been doing
your whole life, Elise...
...it's ask for it.
I won't let you hurt me anymore.
Please!
Elise.
Elise!
Elise, don't go!
Leave her be. Leave her be.
She needs to learn that nobody else
can possibly love someone like her.
I haven't been back here since.
I think that's all for tonight.
We'll pick it up tomorrow.
Christian and I came here a lot as kids.
Do I look okay?
Yeah, of course.
All right.
I'm sorry. I...
You just look so much
like someone I know very well.
Oh, really?
I'm Elise.
Melissa.
Imogen.
- And you're sisters.
- Yes, we are.
Tucker.
Specs.
I'm Specs. Or Steven.
Whatever. Your choice.
She's psychic, and we're sidekick.
I'm sorry?
Forget it.
- So are you guys visiting the area?
- Tough to talk about.
Actually, it's pretty confidencial.
It's a poltergeist infestation
involving Ted Garza.
Do you know him?
He lives, like, down the road or...?
Ghosts and ghouls.
What he's trying to say
is we're ghost hunters.
The three of us.
Kind of like cops.
Only we don't arrest humans.
I'm funny too. A lot of the time.
- I can also be funny. What?
- Okay. Okay.
- I think that that's enough, boys.
- Oh, yeah?
I used to live in this town
a long time ago.
Well, good for you. You got out.
I'm really making a fool out of myself.
We're making...
No, you're not.
It's really nice to meet you.
- Ernie, how's it hanging?
- Dad, over here.
- How are you?
- Hot enough for you?
Hello, Christian.
Have I aged that much?
Well, aren't you gonna say anything?
I have nothing to say to you.
Girls, come on. Let's go.
- Come on.
- We just got here.
Hear me out.
I'm... I'm still your sister, and...
That only means something if I choose it
to mean something, and I choose it not to.
Please, Christian.
I just want you to hear my piece.
I didn't know how this was gonna go.
- I thought you could see the future.
- Is this your sister?
- No, it isn't! Come on.
- Yes, yes, I am his sister.
Listen to me. You listen.
Now, when we were children,
you terrified me.
You scared the life out of me...
...with stories about a monster
behind a red door...
...and then you opened the door
and you left.
You left me.
You abandoned me to a real monster,
our father.
Look, I wish you no harm,
but you stay away from us, Elise.
You stay away.
Christian.
Christian!
I was stupid to come back here.
No, you weren't. You're helping people.
That's what you do, remember?
Elise.
I'm sorry.
He can be unreasonable sometimes.
Knowing what he grew up with,
that's perfectly understandable.
He's never told us anything
about his childhood.
I've never even seen a picture.
He never told us anything about you.
I left him alone, and I shouldn't have.
He is a great dad, you know?
I love him a lot.
You have no idea how happy
that makes me, honey.
- Tucker?
- Share with me. Yes?
Do you have the still frames
that we printed?
- Yes, I do.
- Bring them here.
- Eaten by the female, that's why I don't...
- Tucker?
- Tucker, I need you.
- Yes.
Come on.
Here you go.
Here. You give this to your dad...
...and you tell him it was taken yesterday
in our old bedroom.
Oh, I think he will be
very surprised to see it.
I'm so happy to meet you.
Okay.
Testing. One, two.
Can you hear me, guys?
- No.
- I noticed this last night...
...but I couldn't quite place it.
Then Christian reminded me
that when I was a child...
...I saw a red door.
The entity that killed my mother
came through it.
I don't get it. A red door is a red door.
Anyone can see it.
No, it's not a literal door.
It's a metaphysical one.
Remember when I went into The Further
to find Quinn Brenner?
I came across a red door.
And I... I passed through it,
and it took me deeper into The Further.
If I can find out what it means...
...I might be able to stop the thing
that's haunting this house.
Well, this might help.
I spoke to you last night.
Are you there? Can you hear me?
You took something from me.
Why?
Why did you say, "Help her"?
Help who?
This way.
Is that you?
Whistle once for yes, twice for no.
Are you the woman I saw last night?
Is there an entity in this house...
...that is trying to hurt Ted Garza?
Are you that entity?
Is there something
you're trying to show me?
Is what you want to show me...
...behind this wall?
Keys.
Freeze, buddy. Freeze.
On.
Wait. On.
Wait.
Thank you.
What is it you wanna show me?
Help her!
Help me.
That's not a ghost.
Oh, my God.
I'll break the chain.
No, you won't.
Move.
Get away from her!
I asked you, help me get rid of the ghost.
Help me get rid of it!
Help me!
Why did you have to come down here?
- Why?!
- Your ghost led us down here.
He's in my head.
Is that your friend?
That is your friend.
You there, Specs?
Specs!
What?
Her name is Mara Jennings.
She's a nurse from a town
about 10 miles outside of here.
She's been missing
for approximately four months.
Watch your step down.
- Can you stick around for a few days?
- Yeah, we'll be here.
I'm gonna have to get statements
from all of you.
There are plenty of demons in this world
who are very much alive...
...and you stopped one of them.
Thanks, Elise.
Dad, this is crazy.
This is something I have to do.
I gotta find it.
It's a little whistle,
a little silver whistle.
Look, I deal in the spirit world...
...and spirits can make people
do bad things in the real world.
Some of these people come to me
for help.
But to you, that's weird.
To me, it's a day job.
This one was different though.
The haunted house was my house.
It's not in here.
Hey, I'm gonna check on him.
Why would Garza invite you up...
...knowing the risk
that you might discover Mara?
These hauntings can be terrifying things.
Maybe the fear of the beyond...
...overcame the fear of getting caught.
Or maybe he wanted to get caught.
What? What is it?
I'm sorry.
I'm seeing things.
The shock of the whole thing, I suppose.
Do you need me for anything else?
No.
Thank you.
Melissa?
Dad?
Down here, honey. I found the whistle.
- What are you doing here?
- You can't find her, can you?
What happened to her? Where is she?
- We've looked everywhere.
- Not everywhere.
Oh, God, no.
Imogen, call an ambulance.
Now!
How did you know where she was?
What happened to her?
There's something evil in that house...
...and I let it into this world.
I think it made Ted Garza do
what he did...
...and it's taken your sister's spirit,
and I'm gonna find it...
...and I'm gonna finish it tonight.
I can see things too.
When I was a little girl...
...I went to sleep
and floated out of my bedroom...
...all the way
to our elderly neighbor's house.
Then she told me she was leaving
this world and going on to the next.
My dad told me
she had died the night before.
I told him I already knew.
- He wasn't too happy to hear that.
- Imogen, let's go.
Come on, honey.
No, I... I'm staying.
Just trust me, okay?
Come on, boys, let's get our things
and get in the house and get started.
Son of a...
I am going to get the attention
of all the spirits in this house.
I need things
that were important to Garza.
Specs, go upstairs.
There is a Bible he held very dear to him.
It was a red King James version,
and I need you to find it.
- Take Imogen with you.
- Okay.
- Do not let her out of your sight.
- I won't.
Tucker and I are going down
to the fallout shelter.
I get the death chamber,
he gets Bible camp with a beautiful girl?
That's not a democracy.
You're the only one I trust
to go down there with me.
Don't patronize me, woman.
So why do you guys dress like that?
It was Elise's idea. She dressed us.
No, my usual style's a lot more laid back.
It's a little weird.
- What?
- Dude.
This is vintage. No, this is worth a lot.
I'm serious. We gotta find this thing.
I'm just saying.
- Gotta have hobbies.
- I'm saying.
Can't all be work. Gotta enjoy yourself,
go out on a date.
You gotta do stuff like that.
There's something here.
I can feel it.
She wants me to have it.
Oh, that should do it.
- Step aside.
- Yes, sir.
It's time to sleep.
I know this slip.
- This will help you sleep.
- Don't make me drink anymore.
Please, let me go. I beg you.
There you go.
Please, let me go.
I promise I won't tell.
Please, let me...
Did you hear that?
Hear what?
- My brother doesn't believe you're here.
- Christian!
There's someone in the laundry.
There's no one here.
You can't punish me for this.
I never wanted it.
Goodbye, Anna.
She wasn't dead.
My father did the exact same thing
that Garza did.
The woman I saw in this house
all those years ago...
...she was alive.
I could have helped her.
I let him kill her.
Take this thing off.
Okay.
Her death was my fault.
Until I free her from
wherever he put her...
...she's trapped in the dark.
Lost.
I'm going in there.
Stand back.
Go for it.
I'm good.
I'm sorry, Anna.
I failed you.
Oh, my God.
Where you going?
Elise.
You weren't the only one, Anna.
- Audrey!
- Elise?
Audrey.
Elise.
Where am I?
You're in a special place...
...where the spirits go.
Who are you?
I'm a friend.
I don't wanna be here.
I don't wanna go where the spirits go.
Elise...
...no matter what your daddy says...
...you have to go on doing what you do.
Never be afraid of your ability.
Daddy doesn't mean it
when he yells at me.
He's scared...
...of the man with the keys.
He's the one controlling it all.
He's the one who opens all the doors.
- He opens all the red doors?
- Yes.
The man with the keys said
I'm more powerful than I know.
He says he wants me
to help him open every door.
He says he'll do anything it takes
to get me.
He's standing right behind you.
No!
Leave this place!
Elise, wake up.
Elise!
Specs!
I need help!
Here, here. Careful with her head.
- She's on the other side.
- Somebody has to go in.
Yeah, who's gonna do that?
I can't do that. Can you do that?
- I didn't say...
- I can do it.
I can help her.
I've never actually hypnotized
anybody before.
I've never been hypnotized.
Well, then you won't know
what I'm doing wrong, right?
Okay.
The exercise, it's a little...
I'm gonna... I'll put my finger there.
E.T.
Imogen.
That's pretty cool.
Just look here.
And concentrate on it and just relax.
Imagine that your body is made of water
and you're in the ocean.
That doesn't make sense.
- What?
- She's made of water...
...and she's in the ocean.
Therefore, she is the ocean.
Would you like to do this?
- Thank you.
- I'll still be here.
- Don't touch the subject.
- I'm not.
Move away.
Close your eyes.
Listen to the ticking.
Focus on it.
I'm going to count back from five.
By the time I reach one,
you will be hypnotized.
Five, four...
...three, two, one.
Nod if you can hear me.
When I say "now,"
you will open your eyes...
...and you will be on the other side.
Now.
Wanna go there.
I'll help you.
Red door.
That's the red door
Elise was talking about.
This is the place.
I can't go in there.
If he finds me, he'll...
He'll take me again.
Trust me. You'll find
what you're looking for in there.
I admit it!
Shut up!
That's right!
Elise?
The key is missing.
You're all gonna get it again!
Do you ever think about the people
who go to the electric chair?
Sometimes.
Do you wonder where they go?
Your turn now.
Look out, little girl!
--always repeats, my friends.
The ghosts of their past...
--if we do not confront them head-on.
If there's one thing you've been doing
your whole life, Elise, it's ask for it.
No! No, Daddy!
They're all around us in this house.
Everywhere.
She needs to learn nobody else
can possibly love someone like her.
Stop, Daddy, stop.
- No, Daddy, please.
- Please, stop. No.
- Stop.
- No. No.
No, Daddy!
Some people are afraid
of special people.
Your daddy is one of them.
I won't let you hurt me anymore.
Did you see a ghost?
Just say no. That's all you have to do.
You can't punish me for this.
I never wanted it. I never asked for it.
You killed your mother.
Elise.
Elise!
He's in my head. He's in my head.
My father did the exact same thing
as Garza.
My father was your puppet.
I am not gonna feed you
with hatred anymore, demon.
You can fucking starve.
Elise!
No!
Leave her alone!
You wanna take somebody, take me.
Let them go.
See now?
Honey? Honey?
Nurse! Nurse, get in here!
Melissa!
It's okay, it's okay.
One, two, three, four.
I'm sorry.
No! No!
No!
Elise!
Hands off my little girl.
No, no, no.
Elise!
She's hurt
Return to your body. Go.
Baby.
Oh, Dad.
Elise, she saved me.
I don't know the words.
I already know, my love.
Keep helping people.
Go home.
Imogen, wake up!
Are you okay?
Yeah, I think so.
You can't get rid of me that easy.
The hospital.
Nurse needed in ICU stat.
- Hey, sweetheart.
- Hey.
Hi.
I'm okay.
Oh, my God.
Hi.
I believe this is yours.
You were right, Christian.
I'm cursed.
Demons follow me around.
But I don't want to give them
what they want for one second longer.
Fear and pain is what feeds them.
I'm the one that's been feeding them...
...shutting you out all these years.
You forgive me?
I never should have left you.
Thank you.
Yes.
Melissa...
...you gonna eat that?
Go for it.
You know, I always thought
that I was afraid of dying...
...but now I realize that I wasn't.
I was afraid of dying...
...before I truly had a family again.
Now I do.
Son of a...
I told you not to park there.
- Just saying, I did.
- Listen to your buddy.
He gets the girl, I get the ticket?
I'm riding shotgun.
We'll have to come back here
to deal with that ticket.
Dalton.
Today was just so horrible.
I'm scared nothing's gonna change.
It will.
I promise you.
Just gotta give it time.
Oh, Dalton.
Hello.
I'm so sorry for calling so late.
My name ls Lorraine.
You helped my family a long time ago
when my son was just a boy.
And now the same thing is happening
to my grandson.
Dalton.
How did you know his name?
It's what I do.
Tell Josh I'll be there in the morning.
Thank you.
- Good night.