Yeah, follow me through here.
I'll show you the showroom.
Cool.
Actually, um, Oz...
Oz, do you, uh, have a sec?
Can you show this
young lady around?
Uh, well never mind.
Just, uh, do your thing.
Tunnel vision.
Uh, well, I think we have, uh,
a few things from the
'90s you might be into.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, please.
Great. All right, I'll show you.
Um...
Uh, sorry.
Uh, just hold on a second.
I'm...
Where.
Never mind.
I'll find it later.
Hey, listen, did you get
that old '83 up and running?
Yeah, I think so.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
Well, I'm gonna kick your ass
in a head-to-head
here in a minute.
Yeah.
Don't you laugh at me, you
little millennial motherfucker.
I'm gonna pop you right
in the starfish.
Whoa. Okay. God.
Hey, what'd you
think of that girl?
Uh... girl? What girl?
The girl that was
in here earlier.
Oh, my God. You are hopeless.
I got her phone number.
You wanna call her?
No, that's creepy.
Come on. Oh, that's not creepy.
Call her.
How is that not creepy?
That's...
Well, fine. Suit yourself.
Um...
Listen, um...
I got some bad news.
Uh, it looks like...
we're gonna have
to close up shop.
Close up, like f...
Like, forever?
Yeah, we're just not getting
the business that
we used to get.
23 years I've been here.
I thought I'd make
it to 25, but...
You okay?
Yeah, yeah, I'm just,
uh, a little confused.
Yeah, me too.
I never understood
why arcades went outta
fashion in the first place,
so what the hell do I know?
You know a lot.
How long?
A month?
You got any savings?
Yeah, I think so.
Like a couple hundred...
Like a hun... Like
a hundred bucks.
Okay.
Well, look here.
I would not be here today
if it wasn't for you
and all the great
work that you did,
so I think it's only fair that
we split everything 50/50.
Are you serious?
Yeah, I'm serious.
You deserve it.
Thank you.
Hey, listen, I gotta go up
north for a couple weeks...
Family bullshit.
So, you're gonna have
to look after the shop,
take care of things.
All right.
All right, I tell you what,
why don't you just take
the rest of the day off
and, uh, go get drunk?
You know?
Can I give you some
old man advice?
Uh, don't just go and get
another job in a repair shop.
You're better than that.
Go and find something
that you really wanna do.
You spend enough time making
other people's games beautiful.
Do something for you, okay?
- You ready for another?
- Yeah, thanks.
- There ya go.
- Thanks.
Hey, Audrey.
Hey, Tess. Tom Cat?
Yes, please.
What's on?
What?
What are you... What
are you lookin' at?
It's pretty intense,
whatever it is.
Uh, what?
On the TV.
It's off.
Yeah, I know it's off.
Okay, okay, start over.
I'm Tess.
Oz.
Wait. Oz?
Really?
Yeah, it's short for Osgood.
I'm sorry. Have we met before?
Do you not remember
me from earlier?
Were you the girl
from the, uh...
Yep. Yep, yep, yep.
I was looking for a game for
my brother for his birthday.
Actually, that is totally a lie.
I don't know why I
just said that.
I told your boss the same thing,
but I never had any intention
of buying anything.
I just...
I just wanted to come and,
like, check out the games.
Why would you lie about that?
I don't know. 'Cause I
thought it'd be weird
if I just rolled up and said,
"Hey can I come play
some video games?"
But I-it's an arcade-game shop.
Yeah.
Yeah, when you, uh...
When you put it like
that, it makes sense.
Oh, my God.
17.
Oz?
Hey, I thought I told you to get
outta here and go get drunk.
I'm about to head
out myself, so...
Oz?
Hey. Oz.
Oz!
Where are you?
What the hell is that?
You weren't supposed to be here.
I'm so sorry, Jerry.
Have you ever tried a Tom Cat?
No. What is that?
It's a kind of gin,
but it's so good.
It's smoky like mescal. Try it.
- No, uh, I'm good.
- Try it. Come on.
- Okay.
- Don't be a baby.
Right?
That's actually...
That is really good.
Like gin and mescal had a baby.
Yeah. Exactly.
I hope this doesn't
sound too creepy.
I've totally seen
you in here before.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I don't remember you. Well, I usually
sit over there in that corner,
with my notebook, making notes.
- You're a writer?
- I'm a writer by night.
By day, I'm a receptionist.
Well, technically, I
work for a temp agency.
I'm on unemployment.
I'm unemployed.
If you ever wanna get, like, a
drink or coffee or whatever
somewhere else sometime...
you could have my number.
Well, um, act... the thing is,
I don't really have a phone.
That's, like, the lamest
excuse I've ever heard.
No, I... Really, I don't.
I don't. You can ask anyone.
Really?
Mnh-mnh.
- How do you call people?
- Pay phones.
They still make those?
I-I guess.
Wow.
You're an antique.
I've been told that
before, actually.
Okay, well, how should
we do this, Osgood?
Um...
I could send my
carrier pigeon over.
Or smoke signals. We
could do smoke signals.
Um, I'm gonna be at
the arcade all...
All day tomorrow if
you wanna come by.
Yeah. Yeah, that'd be awesome.
I'm gonna leave around
4:00, go get some dinner.
If you haven't eaten,
maybe, if you wanted,
you could come with me.
- Perfect.
- Yeah?
Yeah, that sounds great.
All right, see you
tomorrow, Osgood.
I'll see ya.
Sorry if this was weird.
No, not weird.
- It was a little weird.
- Unh-unh.
Tess.
Oh.
Oh, shit.
Hey.
- Hey.
- Hey, you showed up.
S... Uh, sorry I'm late.
Uh, come on.
So, did you, like, just
wake up or something?
- Yeah. Yeah, I did. I'm sorry.
I just... I had, like, a
really late night last night.
That's cool.
Yeah.
Is your boss gonna be mad
that you just are
opening up shop now?
No. No one ever comes by here.
Well, except for me.
Where do you find
all this stuff?
All over, really.
Um, like junkyards
and garage sales
and side of the road and stuff.
Yeah, I just... I restore
the ones that I can
and the other ones I
just sorta fix up.
I'll paint the sides.
Sometimes I'll just
build a whole new one
using an existing circuit board,
and, yeah, I like to think of it
as bringing the
dead back to life.
Very noble.
Cool!
Do you just imagine, like,
sweeping orchestral music
every time you do that?
'Cause I would.
Definitely will now.
You got any quarters?
Oh, it's all free.
What? Your boss made me pay
yesterday when I came in.
You guys are a bunch of dinguses.
You know that?
This is the one that I saw online
that made me wanna come in.
I used to play it in the
movie-theater lobby
when my parents were
seeing R-rated films.
Mm.
All right, I'm a little
out of practice.
Um, so I know that you just
woke up and everything,
but do you wanna
still get lunch?
- Totally.
- Okay, cool.
I know a really good spot.
I hope you weren't expecting
anything too fancy.
I don't really do restaurants.
Mm, no, this is perfect.
It's tacos and it's beer.
I mean, you can't do
better than that.
Right?
Sometimes I like to sit up here
and look out over the city
and pretend like this
alien invasion is coming
and they're about to
wipe out the entire town
and I'm protected and safe up
here with my tacos and my beer
just watching the
whole thing go down.
What do you do after you finish
your tacos and your beer?
Well, I go to the Sword Emporium
like 45 minutes north of here
and I grab a couple
samurai swords
and then I go hole
up in some motel
right by the vending machine
and then I wait for, like,
the army convoy to come by
and them to join forces with
Will Smith and then I team up.
Wow. You've really
thought about this.
Yep, every day.
Was that just, like,
major nerd central,
or was that a bonding moment?
- Or both?
- Both, I think.
I think it was both.
Yeah, I'm sorry. I'm not...
I'm usually just really
bad at communication,
so when, um, things are going
well, I get all in my head,
and I-I think that I'm
doing something wrong
and then it ends up being bad.
Yeah, I-I do the same thing,
except I always end
up talking a lot,
which I'm sure you've
noticed by now.
Oh, I'm sorry. I...
I really like you, Oz.
I think you're cool.
Um...
I don't know.
I-I feel like I'd be down
to hang out tomorrow,
if you are... I
mean, not tomorrow.
Like, when ever you're free.
It could be whenever.
But, like, soon.
Sorry I'm talking so much. I
do this when I get nervous.
Why are you nervous?
I'm nervous.
- Why are you nervous?
- Because...
you're definitely the prettiest
girl that's ever kissed me.
You're really sweet.
It's true.
Okay, let's go.
- Okay.
- Come on.
Tess?
Jerry?
Hey, man, look, you
can't be in here.
All right?
Don't make me call the cops.
You plugged in.
Huh?
Is it beautiful?
What the fuck are
you talkin' about?
The White Eye.
It looks at you, doesn't it?
Yeah, you gotta go, man.
Just let me touch it.
Ow!
Shit!
Don't just look into the void.
Let the void look into you.
Okay, but why haven't you yet?
I don't know. It just
takes a lot to make a game.
It's a lot of work.
Takes a lot of time.
I know that. Answer
the question.
Uh, money is a thing that
it takes that I don't have.
Well, we could raise money.
If I... If I... If I had
one chance to do it,
I would just wanna make
sure it was perfect.
You know? I wouldn't wanna...
Oz, if you tried even half
as hard as anybody else,
you could make something better
than like 80% of the shit
that comes out every year.
I don't know. I just...
I just...
I want my first thing to be
my absolute best, you know?
I don't wanna... I don't
wanna half ass anything.
You can't think
that way, though.
Miyamoto's first game
was "Donkey Kong."
- Uh, no. No.
- Yeah.
No, no, no, no, no.
Miyamoto worked on a ton of other
games before "Donkey Kong."
"Radar Scope"? Hello?
- Oh, yeah. That's true.
- Mm-hmm. Yeah.
Well, I dunno. It doesn't
really matter anyway now
'cause I'm about to
be out of a job.
What do you mean you're...
You're about to be out of a job?
They're closing this place down.
About to sell all
of our inventory.
Gonna put some shitty
mattress place in here
in like six months.
Shit.
- Yeah.
- I'm sorry.
Mm, it is what it is.
It's gonna be okay.
You know what I think?
What?
I think this is it for you.
- Thank you, I think?
- No. No. No, no, no.
Not... Not like,
this is itfor you,
but, like, thisis it for you.
It's a thing that my mom
used to say all the time.
It means that everybody
gets an "it" moment,
and it's when everything
in the universe
and all around just
aligns perfectly
so that you see exactly
what you should be doing
with the rest of your life.
Right? So for Miyamoto,
it was "Donkey Kong,"
or, like, when Doc Brown
falls on the toilet
and sli... and hits his head?
Right?
And they see it and
they follow it
and... and... and stuff changes.
Stuff happens for them, right?
This is it for you.
This is your moment.
That's just my two cents.
Can I tell you a secret?
Only if it's a good one.
I've never told a soul.
What is it?
Come here.
Okay, so, a couple of years ago,
uh, I made this kinda...
Uh, I made a thing.
I knew it. I knew it.
Well, it's called, uh,
"Lazer Balls," so...
Yeah, it's, like, the
dumbest fuckin' name
I've ever heard of in my life.
Furthermore, I-I never hired,
like, an artist to do...
- No, it's cool.
- Any renderings or anything,
so it just doesn't
look very good,
but I think, you know, the
general idea is there.
And, just, like, the
infrastructure's good.
I just need someone
to take a look at it
and make it sharp
and make it smooth
and make it, you know,
something people would see.
Tess?
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, I just zoned
out for a second.
What's that game over there?
- Aw, it's nothing.
It doesn't even work. It's...
- But what is it?
It's some piece of
shit that came in.
We don't... Doesn't work.
- Should we try it?
No, we should go get a drink.
That's what we should do.
- Oz, you're still sick.
- No.
You shouldn't be drinking.
Yeah. Yeah, you are.
And I'm taking a very big health
risk even hanging out with you.
- Uh...
- You could be Carrier X.
- I could.
- Yeah.
Hey.
What are you doing up?
I do this every night.
What?
You're crazy.
Hey, are you okay?
Just, every shitty
thought I've ever had
just comes to me at
3:00 in the morning.
And couple that with the fact
I've got this gorgeous
girl in bed next to me...
I don't know. The last few
days have been a lot.
Just kinda like my mind
is working overtime.
I read somewhere once
that when you wake up
at 3:00 in the morning,
it means that your
brain is operating
at a higher level
than most people's.
Really?
Yeah. Thomas Edison,
I think it was,
he only slept for like
45 minutes at a time.
Hmm.
It's either that, or you're
being possessed by demons.
- It's probably that.
- Yeah, probably.
Earlier when you were
in the bathroom,
I walked by your desk and I saw
something that made me think,
"I really know who this guy is."
Uh-oh.
There was this stack of old
"King's Quest" floppy disks
just sitting there on your
desk waiting to be installed.
It reminded me of this
Tamagotchi that I used to have.
I wore it on my key chain,
for, like, years after
I last used it,
just in case I ever wanted
to fire it up again.
Don't they die when you
don't take care of 'em?
Yeah, yeah, it... it was dead.
Rest in peace.
I'm just telling
you that because,
if one of the things that
you're up thinking about
is the person in bed
with you right now,
you should strike
that off your list,
'cause this is easy,
this is good.
Relax.
Tess? Tess? Tess? Tess?
What'd you think of that girl?
Tess? Tess? One, zero,
zero, zero, zero, one.
You're definitely the prettiest
girl that's ever kissed me.
Tess? Tess? Why are you nervous?
I'm nervous.
Tess? Tess?
I think this is it for you.
Who are you?
Tess? Tess?
Tess! Tess!
Relax.
Made of duct tape,
so they slashed the
tires on my car...
- I did that.
- And threw it in the snow...
I-I used to make them, too.
- You made duct-tape wallets?
- Uh-huh.
Did you sell them
for lots of money?
No, I just gave them away
for free to my friends.
- That's so generous of you.
- I know.
My friend, Michael Neukirk, he
wore a duct-tape tux to prom.
- Ooh, that's cool.
- He looked like a fuckin' idiot.
No, that's cool. I used
to, back when I...
I'm so stoned.
I know. Me too. I wanna
play video games.
- What?
- What the fuck?
Oh, did you turn it on?
No, it just keeps
turning on by itself.
Maybe it's haunted.
Probably.
Ooooh. No! No, no, no.
I wanna play it.
- No, you don't.
- Uh, yeah, yeah, I do.
I don't think you do.
It's gonna make you puke.
- What?
- I'm serious.
Do it. You can play.
It's just gonna
ruin your night...
Maybe your life, I don't know.
Oh, well, sounds like you think
maybe it's gonna ruin yournight.
- What are you talkin' about?
Like, maybe you think you're
not gonna get any action.
Well, that is something that
I had thought about before.
It did cross my mind, yeah.
My libido is perfectly
intact, mister,
so if your ego can take a
beating, we'll be just fine.
All right, which one turns it on?
This one?
Don't you dare touch that!
Shit, dude, you can't be in here. Get
outta here! Who does she think she is?!
Who the hell do you
think youare?!
Go, go, go, go, go.
Call the police.
Hey. Hey! You gotta go, man.
You forget yourself?
What the fuck?
No more distractions, all right?
You have a path.
- Get offa me.
- That is an impossibility.
- Let go of me.
- Hey!
Hey.
Are you awake?
You okay?
Yeah.
You know you were supposed to
come by last night, right?
I was?
Yeah, at 8:00.
Oh, shit, I'm sorry.
I-I totally forgot.
I spent, like, all... all
night last night at the shop.
No worries.
I was just worried, is all.
I'm fine.
Are you sure?
I threw up last night. I
ruined a bunch of stuff.
Can you please go see a doctor?
Oz?
It's just, I... There's a ton
of stuff to do here. I...
Do you want me to bring you
some soup or something?
I can come by.
No.
Okay.
Um...
Well, I still really
think you should go...
For fuck's sake, Tess, I'm fine.
Okay.
You need to trust me.
I do trust you. It's
not about that.
I just... I don't know.
There's something up
with you right now.
Maybe this is how I really am.
I don't believe that.
Listen, if you need anything
or you wanna talk, I'm here.
Otherwise I'll just... I'll
let you do your thing, okay?
Okay.
Sorry I yelled at you.
It's fine.
I'll talk to you later.
Bye, Oz.
Bye.
Ow! Fuck!
Fucking idiot.
The White Eye.
It looks at you, doesn't it?
Doesn't it?
No.
Ones and zeros.
Intelligent design.
Made from chaos to chaos.
Oh, it is so beautiful.
I will do what he cannot.
No!
God!
I know.
I must choose...
what Ichoose.
Alone.
Ugh, quit checking your phone.
Hmm?
It's amazing what you can see
in the bottom of a tumbler
if you actually look.
Been a source of inspiration for
a lot of writers before you.
Well, maybe I'll quit
checking my phone
if you guys get the TV fixed.
I'm in no hurry.
People don't talk to each
other when the TV's on.
- Sure.
- You all right?
Yeah, yeah. I'm fine
I just...
I'm confused. And annoyed.
But... I'm fine.
I am confused and
annoyed most days.
Quit thinkin' about him.
I don't know what
he said to you,
but whatever it is,
it's not nice,
and anyone who is not nice
to you does not deserve you.
Yeah, I know. I just...
I felt like I was talking
to somebody else.
Unless it was literally
a different person,
then he is exactly who
he's always been.
You just didn't know it.
Now you do.
Just quit checking your phone.
Nothing good appears on that
screen after 10:00 p.m.
Oz?
Oz, you left the door open.
Oh, my God! Tess!
Tess.
Tess!
Tess! Tess! Please,
please, please.
Do you see?
Who are you?
I didn't kill the girl.
- Yes, you did.
- No.
You have to break it.
It's unbeatable.
The game killed her?
The game did nothing.
When you play by its rules...
it'll always win.
Did you build this?
We built this.
What is it?
A door to the infinite.
What does that mean?
We're in prison.
And where there's a prison,
there are walls...
Walls that cannot be toppled,
walls that cannot be climbed.
You can't escape this prison.
On this side...
it's hell.
You dream...
but then you wake up
from these dreams.
And then you die,
and all the beautiful things
in your dreams die with you.
But on the other side, there's
time enough for it all,
because there is no time.
And in the infinite,
all things are not
just possible.
They're inevitable.
So I can save her.
No.
You have a higher purpose.
If all things are possible,
then she's still alive!
No! No!
Delete the sequence.
Un... Unset decimal,
unset decimal,
F, F-94, 15, 19...
What the fuck are
you talking about?!
You have a responsibility!
Look beyond what's
in front of you.
Delete the senses.
Break the sequence.
Be the man I could never be.
Tess: Oz...
Look between the
ones and zeroes!
Hit reset!
Get outta here before
I call the cops.
Maybe he likes arcade games.
Oz.
I'm so sorry, Jerry.
Maybe this is how I really am.
Be the man I could never be.
Did you build this?
We built this.
Oz!
Oz?!
You can have both.
Look between the
ones and zeroes, Oz.
Hit reset.
No!
Hey, Jerry.
Yeah, what's up?
Hey, is it cool if I use
the phone for a sec?
I think I finally
found an artist.
Like, this guy's incredible.
I saw his pixel art, and
it's just exactly...
Yeah, you can call
him in a minute.
Uh...
first, there's a girl coming
by to look at a game.
Would you show her around for me?
Okay.
- Thanks.
- Sure.
I'm gonna go close this deal.
It's an end of an era.
Eh, it's gonna be okay.
Yeah.