Even serial killers live
next door to somebody.
Tough pill to swallow,
I know, but it"s true.
If I"ve learned anything,
it"s that people hardly ever let
you know who they really are.
Just past the manicured
lawns and friendly waves,
inside any house, even
the one next door,
anything could be happening
and you"d never know.
And that"s the thing
about this place.
It all might seem
normal and routine,
but the truth is the suburbs are
where the craziest shit happens.
You never know what might be
coming around the corner.
Davey.
Hey bud, what"s going on?
Oh, hey Mr. Mackey.
Hey.
Oh, thank you.
What"s with all the dirt?
I"ve been doing a little
planting in the garden.
Um, there was no cash in
your mailbox yesterday
for the paper.
Has it been a month already?
Yeah.
Jeez.
Uh, ok.
Well, actually I
was going to ask
if you could help me
lift something inside
if you have a second.
I"ll get the money then.
Two birds, one stone?
Ok, sure.
Great.
After you.
I knew I had it.
There you go.
Thank you.
You got a big family, huh?
Yeah, I guess so.
Just uh, you know, make sure
you don"t live too close
to them or they"ll come knocking
on your door every day.
Alright, this is it.
Some new furniture for upstairs,
so I gotta get this hunk
of junk downstairs.
Think we can manage it?
Uh, yeah.
Sure.
Alright?
Here we go.
Ok.
It is heavy.
Yeah.
Watch your step.
Here, let me try that way.
There we go.
Woah!
Jesus.
You ok?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, shit.
Sorry.
That"s ok.
As long as it didn"t get
your foot or anything.
You alright?
Yeah.
Why don"t we just take a break?
Ok.
Sorry about that.
Damn water heater just keeps
getting louder and louder.
Gotta get a new one.
Flip side of not living
near any family is
never anyone around
to lend a hand.
Hey, I uh, I really appreciate
you helping me out.
Uh, what"s in there?
Well, that is where
we"re headed.
Think you can make it
the rest of the way?
Yeah.
Heavy son of a bitch, huh?
I am putting the finishing
touches on my dark room.
So I"m an amateur photographer.
I figured that this piece
could store some equipment.
Yeah, it"s cool.
Um, I"m sort of an amateur
videographer, so I get it.
Just like the old man.
My god, I remember when
your parents would push you
around the block
in the stroller.
Now look at you.
How old are you, anyway?
15.
That"s the perfect age.
I wish I could just
freeze it for you.
Uh, well, I gotta go.
Yeah.
Of course.
Go ahead.
Thank you for this.
I will, uh, take it from here.
Give your family my best?
I will.
Manhunt!
I am going to get you shitheads!
I'm going to find you.
Farraday?
Find your own spot.
You"re gonna get us both caught.
This is my spot.
Not anymore.
Now go!
Fine. Go.
Jesus.
Gotcha, dudes!
Christ, guys!
Hiding in Farraday"s spot, man?
Lame.
You"re better than that.
Treehouse in 15, after
we catch this bitch?
He"s close.
I can practically smell
the Noxell on him.
Vaginas are magical.
I can"t wait to get laid.
Aren"t you guys tired of
looking at those same chicks?
Shit no, man.
Or even just feel up a chick.
Second base?
That"s it?
I rounded third once.
She was hot, too.
Oh, it just so happens to
be a chick none of us know.
It was on vacation, dipshit.
I"d just be happy to get
on any base with Nikki.
In your dreams, Davey.
Yeah, wet dreams.
"How is she so frikken" hot?
Too bad she"s into my brother.
Kyle?
No way.
He"s like twenty and he
works at a hardware store.
You think Kyle"s a dick?
My asshole father wants
to tear this thing down.
What?
Ser-seriously?
No, man.
Can"t he at least wait
until we go to college?
Eats, I need this place.
Shit, I would live
up here if I could.
I mean, I don"t know how
safe that would be.
With the...
What?
Kids going missing.
Ok, here we go.
What?
Come on.
I mean, we all know
what you"re gonna say.
It"s a conspiracy.
It"s all connected.
The missing kids aren"t
random, they"re part of
some vast governmental
alien cover-up, right?
So you don"t think it's weird?
Look, last summer a kid
goes missing in Hazelton.
Now another kid
disappears in Freeport?
Uh, Davey, I love you man
but uh, you do kinda
sound like a schitzoid.
Remember when he connected a
Lite-Brite to his keyboard
to try and communicate with
the extraterrestrials?
Or when he swore there was a
demonic presence in his room
because our houses were built
on Indian burial grounds?
That was, like, three years ago.
And our houses were built
on Indian burial grounds.
Davey, there"s literally
no proof of that.
Yes, there is.
No, there"s not.
Are we done here?
I gotta beat off before
my parents get home
and W.W. III breaks out.
Good call.
I"m gonna go make a withdrawal
from the spank bank.
You guys are animals.
Yes you are.
Woah.
Wait, I thought you were sick
of looking at the same chicks.
I am.
Why do you think I stopped
banging your mom?
You are so dead.
Oh yeah?
Give me the magazine.
I"m pretty sure
this is non-lethal.
This is my magazine!
You should not read this
stuff before bedtime.
Mom, I"m fifteen.
Mmmhmm.
You don"t have to
tuck me in anymore.
Maybe you don"t need me to,
doesn"t mean I'm
ready to give it up.
You think dad"s
coming home soon?
I don"t know, hon.
You know how the news is.
Always something going
on that needs reporting.
Ok, sleep tight.
Hey guys, Ipswich
Lanes tomorrow?
Scope some cuties?
I"m in.
I hope that chick from
last week is there.
She was all over me.
You asked to touch her boobs
and she threw you
over the railing.
Bet I don"t look half
as dumb as Davey
every time he sees
Nikki in the DJ booth
and jizzes in his pants.
Oh yeah?
Well, I can see her right now.
Naked.
Bullshit.
Dude, if you"re
serious, I hate you.
Oh my god, she"s waving
for me to come over.
Ok, now I know
you"re full of shit.
Eats out.
I"d easily trade both my
nuts to have the view.
Ok, genius.
If you"ve got no balls what's
the point of the view?
You"d just be some
ball-less perv.
Can you at least
make mom double-bag
her meatloaf next time?
It smells like werewolf crap.
Well, if you would
have remembered
to put the cinder blocks
back on the garbage cans
like I told you we
wouldn"t have this mess.
I hate raccoons.
You should do an exclusive,
get pest control in here.
I could film it.
Camcorder"s off limits, pal.
Station property, you know that.
How am I supposed to
become the next Spielberg
if I don"t practice?
Nice try.
Just uh, make sure
the driveway"s clean
before you go anywhere.
Capisce, Spielberg?
Whatever.
Guys.
Dude, what?
Those are the Pacific Grove
Babes from last week.
Get off of me, you psycho!
I can"t.
I got needs, Woody.
Nikki fucking Kazsuba.
She"s, like, scientifically
the perfect woman.
If she was my babysitter I"d
have been banging her the day
my balls dropped.
Yeah, was it hard
not to get a boner
when she was giving you a bath?
Jesus, guys.
It was, like, four years ago.
Not ten.
We just played games and shit.
What kinda games?
Naughty games?
I hate you guys so much.
It is now confirmed
that 14 Eastern Bloc countries,
including the Soviet Union,
will boycott the Olympic games
in Los Angeles
later this summer.
Only Romania and Yugoslavia
will remain in attendance.
Unbelievable.
The Cold War"s never gonna end.
Your future is dim, Davey.
Ok.
John dropped these
off for you today.
It must be the fliers
for the Bay Festival.
Mmmhmm.
Oh.
Come on.
They got some crummy synth
band playing this year.
Nikki"s not DJ-ing
like last year?
She"s amazing.
Well, with her parents
getting divorced
it wasn"t really
in the cards, pal.
Nikki"s parents are
getting divorced?
Where did you hear that?
Bob Burnqvist.
He bowls with Mike Kaszuba.
Apparently it"s pretty ugly,
supposedly Mike"s not even
staying at home right now.
Let"s not gossip, Randall.
But that is awful.
I never would have thought
they were having problems.
That"s why they
invented curtains, hon.
Hey, Randall, it"s Jimmy.
Listen, uh, this is
going to sound crazy.
The Chronicle received
a letter from some guy
calling himself the
Cape May Slayer.
This guy claims he"s killed
at least 13 teenaged boys
over the last decade.
Oh my god!
Are you sure this isn"t a hoax?
No, it's... it's legit, man.
The story"s gonna
break any second.
We need you in here pronto.
I"m on my way.
Guys, something big
is going down.
Someone"s going down on who?
No, I was right.
You know those missing boys?
It"s a serial killer.
My dad just got called in.
Holy shit!
You"re not kidding.
It"s on the news right now.
This afternoon the
Cape May Chronicle
received a letter
from an individual
calling themselves
the Cape May Slayer,
claiming responsibility for
the deaths of at least
13 teenaged boys along
with two adults.
The author also provided
a list of names, dates,
and pertinent details
related to a number of
open missing persons cases.
We have confirmed the
accuracy of these statements.
I can now officially
label this person
as an active serial killer.
The sheriff"s office reports
they're likely looking for
a white male in his late
30"s to 40"s living alone.
Preferred targets appear
to be males aged 12 to 16-
I can"t believe
something like this
Could actually happen here.
It could be anyone.
This is the coolest thing
that"s ever happened to us.
Didn"t they say he
hunts guys our age?
Should we cool it with
the late night manhunt?
Why?
None of the missing kids are
from Ipswich and Cape May
"is pretty frikken" big.
It"s not that big.
What is it, nine towns?
It"s ten towns.
Guys, how are you
not freaking out
that something"s finally
happening here?
Because there"s no way
it"s gonna hit us.
Or this neighbourhood.
Dude, look at this place.
You"re desperate for
crazy shit to happen.
There"s a serial
killer on the loose.
What else could possibly
be this exciting?
Incoming titties, 12:00!
Holy shit!
Move over, Woody!
Dude.
If I was over there right
now she"d be pregnant.
Show her a little respect, ok?
Her parents are
getting divorced.
Statistically, that means
she"s, like, 78 percent
more likely to engage
in pre-marital sex.
You guys are disgusting.
Whatever, dude.
You were thinking it.
Bank it and spank it, boys.
Please turn around, please.
Shit! Get down!
Dude!
Fuck!
Oh, I"m so fucked.
Oh, Davey... you're...
you"re a really bad kisser.
What?
I"m-I'm sorry, Nikki, I-what?
Guys!
Cut the shit!
Unlike you idiots I actually
come here to study.
So don"t get me kicked out!
Check it out.
Cape May Slayer.
Fifteen confirmed victims
and still counting.
So rad.
I don"t get it.
Why would the killer
only write a letter now,
after all this time?
He"s been killing people and
getting away with it for years.
He"s bored so he's
raising the stakes.
He wasn"t counting on us.
Jesus, Farraday, it"s not
like you"re gonna break it!
Peek-a-boobs!
Get it?
What the hell are you doing?
Free porn, bro.
Is he just gonna take that?
Yo, where the hell"s Sammy?
We need him or we
don"t have numbers.
I dunno.
We haven"t heard from
him in a few days.
"The Hoffmans" car's
in the driveway.
They must be home.
Let"s go get the little shit.
Woody, stay with
these dickweeds.
This way, dickweeds.
No movement.
Or lights.
Oh well.
Oh well?
No one"s seen Sammy in days.
What if-
Don't even say it.
He"s probably up at the
lake or some shit.
Why is their car here?
Maybe they rented one?
Why would they-
Who cares?
Ok, the real issue is that
we don"t have numbers
"cause of the little prick
so now I can"t play manhunt.
Whatever, I"m out.
Yeah, sorry Davey, I got
a book to finish anyway.
Congrats.
You"re getting your calcium.
So what?
Mackey is the Cape May Slayer.
Uh... I knew we shouldn't have
taken you to the library, Davey.
I blame myself.
I also blame Farraday.
No man, look.
Who"s the missing ginger?
That"s the kid I saw in
Mackey"s dining room
a few weeks ago.
When we were playing manhunt.
Redheads all look the same.
So true.
Well, if you"re so sure
it's him why don"t you uh,
just tell your parents?
Because they"d never believe me.
Guys, I was only,
like, ten feet away.
I saw him clear as day.
That"s him.
Plus, what about the Hoffmans?
Their lake house is only
a couple hours north,
but their car"s still here?
And they"re neighbours.
So?
What if one Hoffman saw
Mackey with Dusty?
Who?
The missing ginger.
Mackey found out somehow
and killed them
to get rid of the threat.
Eats, tell them what Kyle said.
Farraday, what the fuck?
What did Kyle say?
Goddammit.
Fine.
Um, he said that Mackey goes to
the hardware store every week
and buys, like, 100
pounds of dirt,
says it"s for his garden.
Bullshit!
Who uses 100 pounds
of dirt a week
in a backyard garden?
You know, he"s also got
a room in his basement
with a padlock on the door.
Why would he need that?
Still not convinced?
"Suspect is likely
a white male,"
"late 30's to 40's,
lives alone."
Who does that remind you of?
Dude, Mackey"s a cop
with a sick reputation.
That"s why it's so genius.
He knows police tactics.
He can plant evidence
to throw them off,
or destroy it if they
ever find anything bad.
And who would suspect a cop?
It"s the perfect cover.
Guys, if Mackey is
what I think he is
then we gotta do something.
Ok, Magnum P.I.
What"s your plan?
Well, we have to find out the
truth and be able to prove it.
We need real, hard evidence.
Which means...
Stake-out?
Search and destroy.
Who"s with me?
This is bat shit crazy.
I"m in.
Operation Mack
Attack starts now.
He leaves his house every
weekday at 8:24 with a gym bag.
Contents unknown.
He gets home from work at
6:25 with that same bag.
Goes in through the garage
and closes it behind him.
He always closes it.
His weekends are all
over the place.
No patter.
Except that he gardens.
A lot.
Acidity in the soil
must be off, though,
plants look like shit.
He has dinner alone every
night at 8:30-ish,
then probably wanks it and
cries himself to sleep.
Loser.
Well, no, because most nights
he goes for a jog at 11:00
for about an hour.
Not sure where he goes
but we should
definitely find out.
Now that we know his schedule,
what do we do next?
We catch this fucker
and become heroes.
Farraday, you"re retarded.
You think a bunch of glorified
Care Bears in hoods
could take down the empire?
They are aliens and they"re
highly intelligent!
I mean, did you see how fast
that one learned to drive
a speeder bike, and then ditch
it without even being spotted?
Whatever, dude.
They"re bears.
Now, if it was Gremlins,
I"d buy it maybe.
I"ve still gotta see Gremlins.
Hey, maybe you
should take Nikki.
She can find out what happens
if she gets your Mogwai wet.
Farraday, stick to shit
that could actually happen.
Like me fathering a
sibling for Woody.
Dude, I told you to stop
talking about my mom.
Would you rather I acted it out?
No, I"d rather you just
not talk about anything-
Shit, Mackey"s back!
Let"s break into his garage.
No.
We can"t do that.
He"s a cop.
Hey guys.
Look, at 11:00 he"s
gonna go for a run.
Trust me, I"ve got a plan.
Guys.
What the hell are we doing?
His fucking trash?
Are you kidding me?
What?
Look, there could be
evidence in here.
Fingers or bloody
rags or something.
If we find anything, we got him.
Do you know me at all?
I am not digging through trash.
Yeah, we"re gonna get
in a lot of trouble
if we dig through
this on the street.
Look, I"ve had to clean up
my driveway three times
in the last two weeks
because of raccoons.
That"s all anyone's gonna think.
If I find a used
condom in there,
I'm gonna be so jealous.
You guys are crazy.
Quit crying, Farraday.
Oh my god.
You know you can get AIDS from
looking through trash, right?
The only way you"re
ever getting AIDS.
I can"t believe it.
Nothing.
Maybe he doesn"t do
the killings here.
He could have, uh, like
a lair or something.
Somewhere.
A lair?
He"s Cobra Commander now?
You know, we could always
look through his mail.
For instance...
Ask and you shall receive.
Farraday"s right.
We can check his mail every day
and he"ll never suspect a thing.
See what bills he"s getting,
people sending him stuff.
I"ll take care of
that responsibility.
Guys, look. It's after midnight.
We should get out of here
before Mackey gets back.
Try again tomorrow?
Night one, no luck.
Says you.
Hey, Davey.
Um, do you think maybe I
can sleep over tonight?
I kinda don"t wanna be at home.
Yeah, sure.
We"ll make popcorn,
watch Close Encounters.
Awesome.
I"m gonna get my stuff.
I"ll be over in a bit.
Come on.
I love you mom.
You're so good.
Dude, what took you so long?
Expecting someone so late?
Uh, no, no, just uh, Woody.
Wow.
I guess I haven"t
been here in a while.
Your mom moved everything.
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, I guess, like a year ago.
Where"d your folks
go all dressed up?
Um, date night.
Good.
Huh.
Better view of my
room than I thought.
I"ve never seen you naked.
That"s too bad.
I"ve got a great body.
Wow.
When I gave you that first
journal I did not think
it would lead to this.
God, we used to
have so much fun.
Sucks how much
things have changed.
Uh, yeah.
Yeah.
Things have changed.
You know, like good things.
I think we"re old enough
to hang out together now.
It"s too bad I'm leaving.
Davey?
We"re back.
Fuck me.
Sweet dreams.
Thanks again for everything, Mrs.
S.
Any time.
Call when you get home so
we know you"re safe, ok?
Yeah, it"s cool, I will.
See you tomorrow.
Get down, shit-for-brains!
Woody, what"re you doing?
You"re gonna lose him!
Go!
Christ, I"m freaking out, ok?
My mom catches me,
I"m dead shit!
Woody, relax.
You said she was sleeping
off a 36 hour shift.
She"s gonna be out for hours.
Yeah, and you look
like you"re 30.
It"s gonna be fine.
Now, go.
Hurry up.
Keys...
Oh my god.
Hey, Woody.
Where were you last night?
I thought you were coming over?
Yeah, um... sorry, my
mom needed my help.
Oh.
You"ll never guess who showed
up at my door instead.
Nikki.
No way.
There is a parallel universe
with butt-fucking wookies
where Nikki showed up at
your house last night.
I"m serious!
She was-she was about to kiss
me when my parents got home.
Guys.
Guys, Mackey"s coming out.
We are picking up
this convo later.
Yeah, ok.
"Is that a fuckin" pick axe?
Holy shit.
That is a lot of dirt.
Just like Kyle said.
How many bodies do you
think that would bury?
We gotta keep following him.
Go.
You drive like my grandma, dude.
We"re gonna lose him.
Shut it, Eats.
Woody, look out!
Woah!
The hell, man?!
Get off the road, you maniac!
Great, now we lost him.
Frick this, ok?
I"m never doing this again.
You guys are dicks!
Guys, relax.
Let"s just get home as
fast as we can and hope
that"s where he's going, too.
Oh, shit.
Fuck.
Fuuuuck.
It"s a cop.
Dude, is that Mackey?
Everybody just be cool.
I don"t have my license, genius.
Tell him you forgot it at home.
How am I...
What if it"s fucking Mackey?
I"m so screwed.
Oh shit, Officer Cole.
Goddammit, Dale Woodworth,
I thought that was you.
Does your mother know
you stole her car?
No.
We, uh, we were
just borrowing it.
We ran out of snacks and
she was asleep so I just-
What if it wasn"t me
that pulled you over?
You could be in
some real trouble.
I know, I"m so sorry.
I won"t do it again.
You got me in quite a bind.
I just can"t bust you
because "cause then
how am I gonna look"
your mother in the
eye at church?
I know, I understand.
Mr. Eaton.
What a surprise.
Officer Cole.
We meet again.
Look, guys.
Another kid has gone missing.
Everybody up at town
hall is in a panic.
They"ve been talking about
canceling the Bay Festival.
Get your asses home where
it"s safe and stay there.
You got it?
Yes sir.
Yes.
Straight home.
Guys, shit.
He switched cars.
Who cares?
Where"s the dirt?
That"s what I mean.
He doesn"t have it.
It must still be in his cruiser.
Unless he stashed it some place.
We"re onto you, Mackey.
I thought everything was fine.
And then they just...
sat me down and told me they
don"t love each other anymore.
They didn"t even seem upset.
So fucked up.
I just feel like my life
has been one big lie
and I can"t even talk
to anyone about it.
What about your friends?
Especially my friends.
All their parents are
still happily married.
Whatever that means.
Well, you don"t know that.
Who knows what really goes
on behind closed doors?
People will keep stuff
like that private.
Are your parents happy?
I don"t know, I guess.
Honestly, I can"t wait to get
out of this stupid town.
God, you must think
I"m such an idiot,
bringing you out here for this.
No way, never.
Can I tell you my secret?
Mmmhmm.
I think Mackey is the
Cape May Slayer.
Mr. Mackey?
Davey, he"s friends with my dad.
Yeah, that"s what he
wants you to think.
They go fishing.
Look, I know how
your brain works.
But you"re wrong.
No, look, this is different, ok?
We"ve been spying on him and-
What?
Davey, he"s a cop.
If your mom and dad found
out you were spying on him
they would flip their shit.
I know, that"s why they"re
not gonna find out.
At least not until we
have solid evidence.
Listen to me.
You gotta stop.
I"m not gonna get caught.
Davey, just let the
cops deal with this.
I don"t want anything
bad to happen to you.
You"re like the only person left
in this town I actually like.
Really?
What about Kyle?
He"s twenty and he works
at the hardware store.
Hey, uh, who wants
a freezie pop?
Nice and cold,
come and get "em!"
One for each of
you, there you go.
Enjoy.
Oh!
Snagged it from my dad"s stash.
Finally using those
brain powers for good.
About damn time.
Give it.
Oh.
It"s bad.
It"s so bad.
It tastes like my
mouth is bleeding.
Let me try it.
Oh.
Guess you dickheads
just aren"t men yet.
So, what"s the deal
with you and Nikki?
Well, we hung out
again last night.
Oooh, Davey.
No way.
We have, like-no, we have,
like, a connection.
A connection?
Any connection I want
with her is vaginal.
Oral if she"s into it.
Don"t talk about her like that.
Mackey"s still out there.
Look, Davey, we"ve
been on him for weeks.
I mean, if he was
gonna give us a clue
we"d have seen it by
now, don"t you think?
Not if they missed
it the first time.
What?
Everyone keeps their doors
unlocked around here.
Well, yeah, but this
was locked last time.
We gotta go in.
What if they"re dead in there?
You said he killed
kids, not adults.
That"s not totally true.
One of the articles at the
library said he killed
a whole family at Pacific Grove.
They said something
must have gone wrong.
And if it"s Mackey?
Fuck that.
I mean, you wanna go
in there, be my guest.
Dumbasses first.
Davey, I was kidding.
I"ve got a bad
feeling about this.
The light doesn"t work.
You guys smell that?
Yeah.
It smells like... roadkill.
If there"s dead bodies in here
I"m totally gonna
shit my Calvins.
Oh...
You guys still think I"m crazy?
Woah, dude. Check your Calvins.
Guys, shut up!
Ok?
He could still be in the house.
Hey, Woody, try the
kitchen light.
Motherfuckers!
Oh, you guys scared
the crap out of me!
We scared you?!
I nearly had a goddamn
heart attack!
What"re you doing here?
With the lights off?
I blew a fuse vacuuming
up this mess.
Stupid cats.
Why are you cleaning
up after their cats?
They rented an RV and went up to
the lake house for the summer.
They pay me to make sure
their cats don"t die.
It"s easy money, usually.
You wanna explain to me
what the hell you
guys are doing here?
Um... well, Sammy was
missing so we thought
maybe the Hoffmans were dead.
And let me guess.
You thought it was Mr. Mackey.
Seriously?
Wait, you were really
talking to her?
Ok, what"s going on here?
You guys hooking up?
Let"s just say he's more of
a man than you jerk-offs.
Oooh!
Davey, you are my God!
Oh, man.
Can I get a picture
of you for my shrine?
And don"t forget to
clean your room.
I mean it.
I know, mom.
God.
Hey guys, what time are we
playing manhunt tonight?
I got an idea.
Alright, here"s the plan.
No way, you still have those?
While you guys are
spying we"re gonna plant
one of these outside
Mackey"s bedroom window.
We can use the other
one to listen.
Audio surveillance.
Smart.
Let"s just not get caught, ok?
If Mackey spots you just act
like it"s part of the game.
Now, we probably have
like two minutes
"til those little shits are
up our asses with flashlights
so let"s be quick, ok?
Farraday, Eats, you guys
take the back yard.
Me and Woody will
plant the walkie.
Operation Manhunt starts now.
Let"s go.
Hurry up!
Come on.
Who"s got eyes on him?
I got him.
He"s in the living room.
Over.
Let"s go.
Found you, you bit
tittied butthole!
Nu-uh, we had time out.
No you don"t, I caught you.
Why don"t you shut the
fuck up and get outta here
before I pound you,
you little shit?
Whatever, pussy.
You two are out.
Ha!
"I freakin" hate that kid.
I"ve got him.
Holy fuck.
Guys, he"s wearing rubber gloves
and he"s got a bucket
of cleaning shit.
What?
Wait, what do you mean?
Farraday, he"s coming your way.
What"s in the bucket?
It looks like bleach,
a scrubbing brush,
and I can"t tell
what the rest is.
Holy shit, he"s
got blood on him!
What? Are you sure?
I- I don"t know.
It could be paint.
It"s on his shirt.
Shit.
He went into the basement.
What the hell?
All his basement windows
are painted over.
Mackey"s M.I.A.
Who"s watching the
basement door?
Hey, let me down.
Alright, stay here.
Watch ok?
Shit!
Do you think he"s onto us?
I don"t think so.
As far as he knows we were
just playing manhunt.
Stupid G.I. Joe
walkie"s not working.
Well, you taped the
button down, right?
Of course I did.
And the batteries are brand new.
It might be the distance then.
Those things were junk.
That"s why we upgraded.
Are you just gonna say frick
it and leave it up there?
No way.
I gotta make it work.
Davey.
Hey.
I gotta say, you scared the
hell out of me last night.
Uh, yeah, yeah, we were
um, sorry about that.
Just... we were just
playing manhunt
and I didn"t expect you there.
No, I get it.
There"s a lot of good
hiding spots for manhunt.
Yeah, your yard "s full of" em.
Guess you didn"t see me
coming either, though.
So what"s up?
Wait, let me guess.
I owe you money.
Uh, yeah.
I"m ready for you this time.
Come on back.
There you go.
Thanks.
Hey, you uh... you're not using
those things for manhunt,
are you?
I mean, if you want real walkies
I got a couple that are
retired from the force.
They"re inside.
They"re just gathering dust.
You can come in and take a
look at them if you want.
They pick up everything.
I- I can"t right now.
Gotta get back to my route.
Alright.
Thanks for the offer.
Yep.
Uh, sorry.
Um, I guess they are
pretty crappy, huh?
Well, the offer stands if you
ever want the real deal.
Just come on by any time.
Oh, shit!
Oh, fuck.
Fuck.
Guys, guys, come in.
I"m freaking the fuck out.
Dude, it"s 1:00 in the morning.
You"re gonna wake up my mom.
Not after the pounding
I just gave her.
I"m serious!
Emergency meeting,
treehouse, now.
"The friggen" walkie was
sitting in his window.
He wanted me to see it.
Oh my god, he"s onto us.
Oh, I should have just
gone to space camp.
There"s no way he knows
why we"re spying on him
and even if he does
he"s only onto me,
which is why I
need you guys now.
When Mackey heads out
for his 11:00 jog,
Farraday and Woody,
you"re gonna follow him.
I don"t like where
this is going.
Yesterday on my route I
saw Mackey dumping dirt
over something in his garden.
Something the size of a body.
While you two follow Mackey,
we"re gonna tear up his garden.
See if we can find that body.
What if Mackey catches us?
That"s not gonna happen.
That"s why I had you
grab Kyle"s CB's.
If Mackey starts heading back,
Woody and Farraday will
radio to let us know.
What about the garden?
He"s gonna notice his
plants are all dug up.
Raccoons.
Just like the garbage
in the street.
Just wait for him to leave.
And stay in touch with
our CB"s the whole time.
It's... it's foolproof.
Look, we need that evidence.
We gotta get closer.
How the hell are we gonna do
that without him noticing us?
We?
I"m not going by myself.
What are you, chicken?
Oh, nice try.
What if I told Eats about
that Hustler magazine
we have that you stole?
Goddammit, Farraday.
Noah?
Oh...
Hello?
Someone there?
"That was way to friggen" close.
Shit!
What if he"s going to his house?
Guys, we lost Mackey.
I repeat, we lost Mackey.
Do you copy?
Fuck, Davey.
There"s nothing here.
No, we"re just not
digging deep enough.
Maybe he"s hiding
something in there.
What?
I can"t see anything.
I got this.
What"re you doing?
How the hell"d you do that?
I"m just good at
working the hole.
Seriously, how"d you do that?
Honestly, you just jiggle
it a bunch, work it around,
and it"ll pop open
most of the time.
It"s easy.
Unless he"s killing
people with his lawnmower
we got jack shit.
Well, this whole night"s
been a waste of time.
Until now.
This is Dusty Dewitt"s shirt.
Who?
Oh, the ginger?
Shit.
That"s blood.
Hey, what"re you guys
doing in there?!
You got a death wish?
Us?
We"ve been trying to
call you on the CB
for like 10 minutes.
We lost him.
We don"t have a
clue where he went.
We need to go, now.
And Davey, you"re not gonna
believe what we found.
Neither are you guys.
Come on.
He keeps a car in
a storage unit?
And like a million
bags of dirt, too.
Plus, shovels and a pick axe.
Why would anyone need all that?
It"s the same reason he's
got Dusty Dewitt"s shirt.
He killed him and buried
the body somewhere.
And there was like a bunch of
bags of um, something else.
They had like
chemical signs on it.
It looks hazardous.
It said Noah.
Noah was on the bag.
Noah?
What the hell"s that?
How am I supposed to know?
I just know it was like
spelled kinda weird.
Here, hand me that.
Classic Woody.
What?
This look right?
Yeah, that"s the same thing.
No, what you wrote means
absolutely nothing.
What I wrote is the chemical
formula for sodium hydroxide.
Congrats, Woody.
You"re retarded.
Shove it, Eats.
Stop.
What the hell"s
sodium hydroxide?
I don"t know, but I do know
that it"s not used in gardening
"cause I"m pretty sure
it"d be toxic to plants.
Holy shit.
Guys, look at this.
Sodium hydroxide breaks
down the chemical bonds
that keep flesh intact, turning
organic tissue to liquid.
Frequently used to decompose
roadkill dumped in landfills.
This will reduce the
odour of decomposition.
This sicko"s using this
stuff to cover up the smell
from the dead bodies
he"s dumping some place.
I got good news for you, Woody.
It"s time to tell my parents.
Mackey.
He"s a cop, for Christ's sake.
He"s been our neighbour
since before you were born.
Dad, every serial killer
is somebody"s neighbour-
That milk carton.
That t-shit and
the storage unit?
That-that doesn"t
prove anything, guys.
How could you guys
go along with this?
We wouldn"t have if it
didn't make so much sense.
Yeah, and then when we
were following him-
Jesus, you have
been spying on him?
Yeah, we had to!
And the more we watched, the
more the details stack up.
He goes jogging at
11:00 at night.
He buys a ton of
dirt every week.
He keeps a spare car
in a storage unit.
Why would he do that?
There was nothing in his
garden when we dug it up
but I"m-
You dug up his garden?
Oh, goddammit, David.
You guys are in
deep, deep trouble.
I mean, it"s vandalism,
spying, stealing.
I mean, it"s unacceptable, boys.
We"re trying to save people.
Yeah, well, you"re not.
Alright, we"re gonna go
over there right now
and you"re gonna apologize
for all of this.
And you better hope he
doesn"t press charges.
Let"s go.
Randall.
Guys, what"s going on?
Hey there, Wayne.
Uh, listen, the boys have
something they need to tell you.
And I want to
apologize in advance.
Just know that Sheila
and I are as outraged
as you are about to be.
I"m sure whatever it
is we can work it out.
Um... hey, Mr. Mackey.
We just wanted to
say we"re sorry.
You probably thought it was
raccoons that dug up your garden
and your garbage.
It was us.
Tell him why.
A few weeks ago I thought I
saw this boy in your house.
We were playing manhunt and
I had this idea that...
you were maybe the
Cape May Slayer.
Oh.
Well.
Uh...
I"m sorry, it's just the
uh, guys at the station
are gonna love this.
So who was the boy
that was here?
That was my nephew, Jamie.
He was helping me to
renovate the dark room.
I thought you didn"t
have family nearby.
And we found this in your shed.
David.
You broke into my
shed, too, huh?
You don"t have to
answer any of this.
I"m sorry.
No, no, it"s fine.
We were hammering nails all
day, he probably cut himself.
Why don"t you guys come
in, we can call him,
we can clear this up right now.
That is not necessary at all.
Look, we just wanted to let
you know what happened
and uh, the boys promise to fix
anything that they damaged
no matter how long it takes.
Right?
Yes, sir.
Look, I appreciate the
apology but honestly,
no hard feelings.
I remember what it was like
to be a boy in the summer.
It"s hard to pass
up an adventure.
You are a better man than
me, Wayne, thank you.
This doesn"t change anything.
Are you high?
Your summer"s fucked.
We may get out of this
with just garden duty.
I"m not risking the little of
the good life I"ve got left.
Yeah, Davey, spying on
Mackey was fun and stuff
but this is way too heavy.
I"m out.
Guys, go home.
And I"m calling all your parents
and I will be telling them
what happened.
Go.
Not you.
You are grounded until
further notice.
I"m so disappointed
in you, David.
Just-look, just go home and
do not come out of your room
until I say so.
Hello?
Can you come over?
It"s so surreal.
It feels like I was
just a kid, you know?
Oh my god.
Look at this one.
That is definitely coming
with me to Stanford.
Oh god, really?
Can"t we just burn it?
What?
No way.
It"s a classic.
You know, I didn"t think I
was gonna miss this place
but now I can"t deal.
Everyone"s talking to me
like I"m already gone.
It"s wigging me out.
You know, it just feels
like the end, you know?
And the closer it gets
the more I feel alone.
Hey, you"re not alone.
After today I wish I could
get out of this stupid
neighbourhood with you.
I"m sorry.
You wanna leave?
Holy shit.
You got caught.
Davey!
My dad made me admit the
whole thing to Mackey.
No he didn"t.
Oh my god.
I"m so grounded.
I"m-I'm gonna be locked up
until I leave for college.
Wait, if you"re grounded how
are you here right now?
Well, my parents
are downtown so I-
I just snuck out.
Just a rebel without a cause.
You"re done now, right?
Right?
Well, the guys all bailed on me
so there"s not much I can do.
I know I"m right about him.
That"s the shittiest part.
Just let it go.
You only get a chance
to be a kid once.
Believe me, I know.
So enjoy it while you can.
But if I"m right,
who"s gonna stop him?
Davey.
How"s it going?
What"re you doing here?
Just kinda wanna make
sure that we"re good.
I feel bad about everything
that happened yesterday.
Mind if I come in for a second?
We can talk about it?
Now is not a good time.
Ok.
Hey, you know that
we"ve got everyone
that we have looking
for this sicko, right?
Why haven"t you found him yet?
Well, these things take time.
Sometimes years.
If you want I can stop
by, give you updates.
No, you don"t have to do that.
I see the paper before
anyone, remember?
You sure?
It"d be my pleasure.
I can tell you have an
interest in this stuff.
Was there anything else, Mr.
Mackey?
Wow, you uh, you really
got it in for me, huh?
Uh... Davey, I like you.
I think you"re a
good kid, alright?
The last thing I want is
for there to be bad blood
between us.
Yeah, me too.
It"s just uh, my summer's
basically destroyed
and I"m pretty sure my
parents hate me now.
You want me to talk to them?
See if I can lighten
the sentence?
I"m happy to do that.
No, it's... it's alright.
Thanks, though.
You"ve got quite
the imagination.
Yeah, I guess.
Um... my dad says it's because
I read too many mysteries
and with the killer on the
loose I got caught up in it.
I get it.
That"s the whole
reason I became a cop.
It"s exciting, the
stuff that"s going on.
And you wanna help,
and that"s great.
And I"ll admit that the stuff
that you thought was proof
looks pretty bad out of context.
You got a pretty good brain
for this kind of work.
Davey, is there anything I can
do to help smooth things over?
Um... well, yesterday you
offered to call your nephew.
Would you mind maybe
just calling him now?
Absolutely.
Just kinda gotta...
come in to do that.
Uh, no, no, actually our
cord"s really long.
Just wait here a sec.
Shit!
Shit.
Place looks great.
I haven't been in here since...
you must have been a toddler.
I helped your dad get some
stuff into the attic.
My sister"s in Seattle.
Hmm.
Not answering.
Jamie"s big into baseball.
He might be at
practice or something.
Well, maybe I"ll come back
later, we can try him again.
Uh, no.
It"s ok.
Look, I"m sorry for
being such an idiot.
I promise I"ll fix your garden
even better than it was.
No hard feelings.
Sorry again that
you"re uh, grounded.
I"m gonna see if I can get
you outta this house.
Listen, Davey.
I"m gonna do everything I
can to catch this bastard.
I promise.
Operator, how may I
direct your call?
Um, can you tell me the last
number dialed from this house?
The last number dialed from
that residence was 555-0167.
How are you guys not
freaking out right now?
He called himself.
There"s no Jamie.
This proves he"s guilty.
We gotta get into that
house to find out what"s
in the basement.
Are you crazy?
Look how much trouble we got in
just for digging up his garden.
Davey?
Come down here.
Shit.
If I think she knows
you"re up here I'll radio
so you can climb up the window.
I want you to see this.
Please stand by as we
join a press conference
underway at city hall for
an update in the case of
the Cape May Slayer.
We are happy to
report that we have
the Cape May Slayer in custody.
Thanks to the fine efforts of
the Ipswich Police Department,
we apprehended Mr. Arthur
Ray Peterson earlier today.
And I would like to bring
up the arresting officer.
No, I think it"s perfect.
Wayne Mackey.
This is what everyone needs.
I know that this is uh,
it"s been a trying time
for our community but uh, we
hope that this announcement
can bring a little peace
to those who have
been living in fear.
I"ll be there in a few. Bye.
Justice will be served.
The Bay Festival"s back on,
and all because of Mr. Mackey.
So while we"re all celebrating
I want you to think
about your actions.
It turns out the man across
the street is not a killer,
David.
He"s a hero.
A hero.
Did you guys not
hear the broadcast?
He"s clearly guilty.
And you"re clearly
fucked in the head.
Dude, he just caught the killer.
It can"t be him.
Don"t you think it's a little
coincidental that the person
we just accused of being
the killer just so happens
to then catch the killer?
Dude, you just sound
desperate now, ok?
Just admit you were wrong.
I"m not wrong.
And I know there"s something
behind that locked door
in his basement.
We have to find out what it
is before more people die.
Listen, Davey.
Even if you were to
hypothetically get
into his basement,
there"s no way you could
take anything to prove it
without him knowing
that it"s you.
I don"t have to.
I"ll use my dad's
camcorder, film it all.
No need to steal anything
if I get it on tape.
Tape doesn"t lie.
I know you guys all
think I"m crazy,
but I"m gonna prove it to you.
Look, I"ll take
all the risk, ok?
I just need you guys
to watch my back.
Make sure Mackey doesn"t
come home while I"m inside.
No.
I"m done with this shit, ok?
You"re gonna get caught, either
by Mackey or your dad or-
No.
Because everyone"s gonna be
at the Bay Festival tomorrow.
All I need you to do is
set up at the bus stop
down the street, ok?
And Farraday-
No, dude.
You know that my parents
take me every year
and there is no way
they"d let me ditch.
Which is why I need you to
keep an eye on Mackey there.
If he leaves the party early
just give me a heads up.
Woody, I need you to stay
and watch right outside
his house.
With multiple layers of
protection there"s no way
I get caught.
Are you with me?
Whatever. Fine.
But if shit goes sideways
I"m pinning it all on you.
Yeah.
This is your last shot, Davey.
I mean, if you think there"s
something down there...
I guess I"m in, too.
This is so not fair.
David.
Punishment"s a punishment, pal.
If you really cared about
going you wouldn"t have acted
like a delinquent all summer.
Hey, just let me go and I"ll
be grounded again after.
Not happening, end of story.
Alright guys, it"s go time.
I got eyes on him.
Over.
Roger that.
How"re you looking, Eats?
What? Can"t take a
little family time?
Fuck off, Kyle.
Eats.
Are you in position?
You want a lift, limp dick?
Why, you need an alibi?
Ok.
Hold this.
This, too.
Come on.
Can you hold it?
Yeah.
Here.
If you see anything,
make some noise.
Alright?
Move over.
What for?
I"m not gonna let my
best friend go in
a serial killer"s house alone.
Hold the window.
Ok.
You good?
Yeah. I think so.
Alright, let"s go.
Thanks, Woody.
I owe you one.
Let"s just make this quick, ok?
Ok.
What are you guys doing?
Why do you keep
doing that to us?
Because it"s so easy.
What"re you doing here?
I figured you"d need some help.
I thought you said I
should let it go.
Yeah, but if you"re right,
who else is gonna stop him?
Oh, come on.
Davey?
Davey, do you copy?
Is he on his way back?
Way worse.
You were wrong.
You were wrong about everything.
The dirt, the shovels,
the pick axe,
it was all for a project
Mackey was doing with
the police department.
They planted a shitload
of flowers down here.
Listen to me.
It"s over.
No, Farraday, wait.
I"m sorry, man.
But you"re on your own.
Maybe he"s right.
We should just go.
I mean, we"re already here.
We might as well
just check it out.
And if it"s not him
then we know, right?
It"s him.
Look, Eats is still in
position so we"re safe.
We have to look "cause we"re
about to find the proof.
I know it.
Please tell me somebody
brought a flashlight.
Oh, uh, there should be
one on the camcorder.
Ok, come on.
Creepiest basement ever.
Jesus fuck!
Oh, jeez.
Oh my god, calm down.
It"s just a light.
Are you ok?
Ok.
Quiet down!
Take a chill pill!
Shine the flashlight
on the lock.
What"re you doing?
Seriously, did Eats
teach you this?
It doesn"t work.
Shit.
Vagina!
Farraday, you fucking dick!
What are you even doing here?
You"re supposed to
be watching Mackey.
The whole thing"s off.
Mackey"s clean, 100 percent.
Are you fucking kidding me?
It"s a long story.
Just trust me.
It"s not him.
Fuck that.
I gotta hear this.
Maybe I could sleep at
your place tonight?
Parents again?
How bad is it this time?
Let"s just say I don't wanna
witness a murder suicide.
Yeah.
But I"m not watching
Gilligan"s Island.
What the hell is this place?
You think he... keeps his
victims here or something?
Guys.
"To Wayne. Keep it up, slugger.
1958."
Holy shit, was this his room?
When he was a kid?
That doesn"t make any sense.
I mean, these houses weren"t
even built back then.
God, suburbia is so fucked up.
Davey, you said there was
gonna be evidence here.
Where is it?
Oh my god!
No, no, no, no.
Davey, no, no.
Just make sure you"re filming.
No, Davey, wait.
Is this enough proof for you?
Davey, we need to go.
Now.
Come on.
Wait, what"s that?
Oh my god.
Oh my god!
Help...
Come on, guys.
Come on.
Are you ok?
Watch out, watch out.
Let"s go.
Come on.
Oh my god, Davey!
Davey, let"s go!
Davey, come on!
We gotta get out of here!
Davey!
What are you looking at?
Holy shit!
Davey! Davey!
Guys, the people in the
pictures aren"t his family.
They"re his victims.
What?
I"m next.
Oh my god.
Is this enough proof for you?
Davey, we need to go.
Now.
Come on.
You found all this in his house?
Yeah, and there"s
pictures of dead people
"all over the freakin" walls!
What were you even doing there?
Get out to Mackey"s.
Bring that sick son
of a bitch to me.
Let's go.
You folks should be proud.
That boy"s alive
because of your son.
He"s a hero.
You ok?
Uh, yeah.
What"re you doing
out here all alone?
My parents are giving
a report, I guess.
Hmm.
Kinda feels like none of
this is actually real.
My parents just got here and
I saw them hug each other
for the first time
in a while, so...
Well, that"s awesome, right?
I"m not gonna get my hopes
up, but it happened
because of you.
I don"t know about that.
See ya, Davey.
I love you, pal.
And I"m so sorry.
I"m proud of you.
I"m real proud.
Davey"s got the sleeping
bag all set up for you.
And when your mom gets off
her shift in the morning
she will pick you up.
Thanks, Mr. and Mrs. Armstrong.
You guys are safe now.
We"ll keep an eye out and make
sure nothing else happens.
I wonder where he is.
Well, the APB"s
been out for hours.
They"ll get him.
It"s just a matter of time.
We love you.
You boys are gonna be
the talk of the town.
How does that feel?
Nothing"s ever gonna
be the same again.
Alright, get some rest, you two.
Goodnight.
"Night."
You think they"ll catch him?
There"s nowhere left
for him to hide.
It"s over. We got him.
Woody! Woody!
Get up!
Turn around.
I"ll untie you.
It"s Mackey!
I can"t see shit!
What the fuck was that?!
We gotta get outta here!
No, no, no, no!
Yes, we have to!
Wait-he"s-he's out there.
Where is he?
Oh, my god, run!!!
I know how much you
guys like games.
So I got a surprise for you.
We"re gonna play manhunt.
Only now we are gonna
play it for real!
It"s ok. He can't catch
us if we keep moving.
Alright?
We gotta go. Let"s go.
What-what the hell?
Shit!
Come on.
Where did he take us?
It"s a tidal island.
It has to be.
Fuck.
What do we do?
If we-if we just keep
going, eventually-
We"ll find a road.
Come on.
It"s ok, it's ok.
It"s ok.
I know where you are.
I know you"re close!
We gotta get to the cruiser.
I can"t die tonight,
my mom needs me.
You"re not gonna die.
I got you into this mess, I"m
gonna get you out of it.
I"m gonna be your diversion.
No, no, no!
I"m gonna get his attention so
you can get to the cruiser, ok?
Find a way out!
No! No, I can"t-
Hey, Wayne! Fuck you!
I am over here, you
fucking loser!
Stay the fuck there.
Woody! Woody!
He"s coming!
Woody!
Run!
Davey! Davey!
No! No!
Woody! Woody!
You brought this on yourself.
All you had to do
was leave me alone.
This is your goddamn fault!
I"m sorry.
You forced me out of my home.
You stole my life!
You do not get to be sorry.
All I wanna do is kill you.
That"s not enough for you.
You have spent so much
time thinking about me.
I want you to keep
thinking about me.
I want you to imagine
what I am going to do
when I come back for you.
And I am going to
come back for you.
After you have spent your life
looking over your shoulder.
After you have wondered
every single day
if that is the day that
I"m gonna come for you.
One day... you'll be right.
You never know what might be
coming around the corner.
And that"s the thing
about this place.
It all might seem
normal and routine,
but the truth is
the suburbs are where the
craziest shit happens.
Just past the manicured
lawns and friendly waves.
Inside any house, even
the one next door,
anything could be happening
and you"d never know.
If I"ve learned anything,
it"s that people hardly ever let
you know who they really are.
Tough pill to swallow, I know.
But it"s true.
Even serial killers live
next door to somebody.