Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
♪ Here is
cruel Peter Hoffmann, see
♪ A horrid wicked boy was he
♪ He caught the flies
Poor little things
♪ And then tore off
their tiny wings
♪ And, oh!
Far worse than all beside
♪ He killed the dog
and now he'll die ♪
This girl is accusing you
of cutting her face
with a razor.
Is this true?
No, Mother.
She's a liar.
Did you hear
what Peter said, Giovanni?
Yes, milady.
- But that would...
- The girl is a liar. That'll be the end of it.
I want her off my property
by this evening.
You know I love
you, don't you?
I do.
Give me the razor, Peter.
No, Mother.
Please, do it for me.
My father gave it to me.
It's mine.
I see you found your dog
in the end.
Inside a box.
Underground.
It's your fault.
You took too long.
The garden isn't so big.
Lasciami!
Try it... peasant.
Lay one hand on me and my mother
will cast your family out.
And you... will starve.
You're even more stupid
than I thought.
Did you think I didn't
recognize you?
I didn't know you were
a poet, Alfredo.
"And Oh! Far worse
than all beside.
"You killed the dog..."
And now you will die.
Let me out!
Let me out of here,
you bastard.
I'll have you killed for this.
Your materials are here,
Professor Nash.
- From Froome? On my desk please.
- Yeah.
No, not yet.
Please tell me,
why do you have this book?
Fine.
I think I'm in for it with Liz.
Boys?
Christ, no.
She thinks I'm a total idiot.
In reality I suspect it's
something to do with her mother.
Do you think
she feels guilty?
Guilty?
Liz?
After she died, you stopped
traveling, locked yourself away.
I hate to say it,
but you're wasting your life.
Maybe Liz thinks it's...
because of her.
What person's gonna give me a
chance after messing up like that?
There's a restoration job
going in Italy.
Quite interesting,
not too demanding.
Where?
Town in Sicily.
There's even a school for Liz.
You've thought
of everything, boss.
That way you can show the
world what I already know.
That you can still
run a site.
And this is
the English cemetery.
Much of it destroyed
by the earthquake.
Along with almost 90%
of the estate's capitals.
Messina was one of
the richest cities in Sicily.
And English ancestors
did good business here.
It's probably not the most
interesting place for a young girl.
Oh, when she
was six years old,
Liz was playing in the Catacombs of
Paris amongst millions of skeletons.
She'll be fine.
The school is a two-minutes
walk from the house.
You can go straight
through the wood.
"I can walk myself."
Alone?
We'll see.
Teenagers, no?
Tell me about it.
Professor.
- Norman.
Uh, you should come for
lunch at my house sometime.
If you like.
My aunt is a great cook
and she'd love to meet you.
Liz is a vegan.
It's a touchy subject.
That's no problem for Aunt Emma.
Great.
Yes. Thank you.
Grazie. Grazie.
"Here is cruel Peter Hoffmann.
"See.
"A horrid
and wicked boy was he."
What did he say?
Um... These toys have been
put there for a little boy.
That way, he can keep
playing in the next life.
Help me.
Help.
♪ Na, na, na,
na, na, na, na, na
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na
♪ Na, na, na, na,
na, na, na, na ♪
Help me!
Are you all right?
You're scared.
Why?
What's your name?
There you are.
Hello.
I'm Harriet. I live nearby.
I have to walk
through these woods.
You're English.
Yes, Oxford.
I didn't think there were
any English people left here.
Somebody remained.
Uh...
My daughter can't hear,
but she lip reads very well.
- Her name is, uh...
- Liz, yes, as you said.
Right.
I'm Norman.
Pleased to meet you.
I hope to see you again.
Bye.
Mom!
This is
Edgar Hoffmann.
He committed suicide in 1907,
slitting his own throat.
Why did he do it?
Well, no one seems to know.
It was a big scandal
at the time.
He was one of the
wealthiest men on the island
and Peter was his son.
Now, he disappeared
on the 25th of December, 1908.
That's three days
before the earthquake,
and he was never found.
- Hmm.
- Twelve years old at the time.
Quite the mystery.
They destroyed it.
Do these cameras work?
Ah, unfortunately, they don't.
Well, make them work.
Yes, sure.
Ho una cosa per lui.
A gift for you.
What is it?
It's a piece of material that
has been bathed in holy water.
Inside it,
there's an image of Christ.
She'd never admit it,
but she has one too.
My auntie believes that the
dead can either be good or evil.
This helps keep
the evil ones away.
You used this?
Don't worry.
This...
It's only a toy.
It's not a toy?
You heard Mum?
Please.
You couldn't.
It's impossible.
"What will it take
for you to believe me?"
Liz...
Bianca.
What's missing?
Uh, in this mess
it's difficult to know.
Where is the metal box?
It was right here
and now it's gone.
I'm sorry, Bianca.
Liz and I, we got off
to a bad start this morning.
We can talk about it
if you want.
Correva l'anno 1908...
I never asked you
what brought you here.
I mean,
for someone
of your experience...
it's a little low key.
I thought
that was common knowledge.
Not for me.
Five years ago...
my wife and I were working
on a dig in Turkey.
During the excavation, we...
uncovered this
Roman sarcophagus.
Beautiful.
Totally intact.
All I had to do
was clean it up
and it would
have been perfect.
I could've waited
till the next day.
But I was so excited that I...
I couldn't leave it.
So I sent Jane home
in her car...
with Liz.
A truck...
knocked her car off a bridge.
While I...
was dusting the earth
off piece of marble.
I lost her...
and Liz lost her hearing.
The day after the accident...
I...
I returned to the site,
I grabbed a pickax,
and I smashed that
sarcophagus into pieces.
Go away.
"Tomorrow...
"school finishes early."
Shall I pick you up?
I'm sorry about earlier.
Liz.
I'm confused.
Please tell me, why?
I don't buy that.
Something is up.
I eat meat.
But with you there, never.
Please.
Can we talk
about this together?
That's enough!
I'm your father.
And I don't want
any cheeky talk from you.
I'm not the father of the year,
but... I'm trying my best
to connect with you
and you're just
driving me crazy.
Professor Nash.
Lieutenant Calarco,
the Carabiniere.
Finally.
We've been waiting for you.
We've had some
tomb damage and a theft.
Oh. What did they steal?
A, uh, a metal box
containing some toys
and, uh, a wooden tombstone.
That is not
much of a robbery.
Have you made
any enemies here?
Enemies?
Whatever for?
Maybe you did something wrong?
I'm simply trying
to protect this cemetery
against vandals
and decades of neglect.
This cemetery, not a colosseum.
No one cares about the dead.
Well, I do, for a start.
Professor, take my advice.
Go back to England.
How about
you do your job...
I'll do mine.
I am.
Hello!
Hey.
What were you thinking?
The whole place is crumbling.
All the coffins
are full of rusty nails.
Last week,
Giuseppe hurt himself the same way.
It wasn't a nail.
This wasn't there before.
Sure you wouldn't like some?
I just wanted to apologize.
For what?
I'm a complete stranger
and there I was chasing your
daughter around the woods.
You could've got the wrong idea.
I didn't get any idea.
Well, I'm the one
who should be reprimanded.
I was three hours late from
picking her up at school.
She seemed
to manage just fine.
With a father like me,
she has to.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
We do what we can
for our children.
Do you have kids?
No.
It's getting late.
I should get going.
I scared you.
I try to defend the villa...
as I can.
Questo and de Padre Nicolo.
He lost his arm...
Nel terremoto.
In the earthquake.
And who's this?
His brother. Alfredo.
He was not so lucky.
What about Peter Hoffmann?
Your father must have told you
something about him.
Well...
my father said...
in all his life...
he never met anyone
as mean as Peter.
He enjoyed hurting others,
and he did it without fearing
to be punished.
His mother
always protected him.
She also did it
when he killed his father.
Peter wanted his mother
for himself.
She silenced what happened,
claiming it was a suicide.
Everybody knew the truth
in the villa,
but they were too scared
to talk.
One day, my uncle,
tired of that cruelty,
decided to make him pay.
Peter had to be stopped.
But Alfredo
was not a murderer.
And my father convinced him
to set him free.
Unfortunately...
he chose the wrong day.
Corpses everywhere.
Tens and thousands of bodies
were thrown into mass graves.
Alfredo!
With death everywhere,
no one cared about Peter
and Alfredo's fate.
Alfredo!
It was
the 28th of December, 1908.
The city of Messina
was completely destroyed.
Mrs. Hoffmann
didn't accept the idea
of losing this boy
she loved more than anything.
And they were
not only rumors.
That woman was a witch.
Back in the villa,
my father saw her
while she performed a ritual
on the body of a housekeeper.
As soon as she was pulled
from the rubble...
Mom.
...that lifeless body
spoke with Peter's voice.
Help me.
On the same night, Mrs.
Hoffmann disappeared in the woods
and nobody saw her again.
People say
she's still looking for Peter,
and that she won't find peace
until they're back together.
Let's try to finish classifying
the monuments tomorrow.
I want to get back to
London as soon as possible.
- Why?
- It's Liz.
She's unwell,
she needs help.
That's a bishop sphere.
Yes, it is.
It's a dangerous thing.
Why is it in this house?
Liz had it. She's been
trying to contact her mother.
And what happened?
Nothing.
Nothing!
Her mother's dead!
What do you think happened?
Liz should see
Aunt Emma.
We already moved a month ago,
so this is past normal.
By using that thing,
Liz could have left a doorway open.
I'm just asking you to let
her spend a day with my aunt.
You've met her.
She's a good person.
She understands things
that others do not.
And I will be there.
They are making a cake.
What did your aunt say?
She's just trying
to get her to relax.
We'll see.
- Norman?
- Yes?
- I'd be sorry if you left.
- Me too.
But I have to look
after Liz.
Okay.
Right.
I'm gonna finish my rounds.
See you soon.
Liz!
Zia! Zia!
Zia!
Zia.
Liz.
It's a rite of purification.
Liz is possessed.
She had black magic marks
on her body.
The marks of the witch.
Hello, sweetheart.
Help you?
Yes? You wanna go home?
- No. No, don't do it.
- Norman, please.
That's enough.
She's terrified.
We are going back
to London, tomorrow.
- Out of my way. Please.
- Please.
- Out of my way.
- I beg you.
Tomorrow, you and I
will go back home.
You will feel...
much better.
I'll get it.
- Hi, Rod.
- Hi! Did you try to call me?
I did.
I need to talk to you.
It's important.
What's that?
Liz?
Liz, stay there.
Stay there, Liz.
Not Liz. Peter.
No. No!
Liz!
Liz, hey...
Liz...
Stay still.
I've to get
back to the woods.
- I have to find her.
- You'll never find the way.
Dark forces
have been unleashed.
And they will
keep you from it.
What am I supposed to do?
Just accept that
I've lost my daughter?
Diglielo.
There is a water tank
at the back.
We have to find Peter's body
and exorcise it.
But we must do it tonight.
- Or she'll be lost forever.
- But it's impossible.
It could be anywhere.
Then we must ask
someone who knows...
and this time,
you must believe.
Hm.
Alfredo, I call out to you.
Alfredo...
I call out to you.
Alfredo, are you there?
Hello, Peter.
I left you some air.
More than what
you gave my dog.
I know where he is.
I know where he is,
but he was trying to tell me something.
- Who?
- Alfredo.
It's Peter's mother.
She's the one who took
Liz through the woods.
She was here, in my house.
And my daughter said something
about speaking to Jane.
She wasn't lying.
But it wasn't
her mother she saw,
it was Peter's mother.
Liz?
Good evening, Norman.
I'm sorry to
bother you so late,
- but I'm quite sure that I saw Liz.
- Where?
In the woods.
Can I come in?
No! Don't come in, witch!
Amen.
We are safe in the house.
The witch cannot come in
until somebody invites her.
Take the car
and go to the cemetery.
Once there, you will be safe.
The witch cannot walk
on consecrated ground.
And what about you?
Don't be afraid, honey.
I'll be fine.
You know what to do.
- Thank you, Emma.
- Now go.
Giuseppe.
Giuseppe, I want you
to open the gates now.
Open it!
It is fucking locked.
It's all right, Bianca.
It's all right. Don't worry.
Shit. Don't look. Don't...
It's all right.
Don't look at him!
Come on. Come on.
Help.
In the name of the Father,
and of the Son, and of the Holy Spirit.
In the name of the God...
Go away.
We believe in you
and we pray thee,
come be with those who love
and learn to accept your will,
as it is the blessed
Virgin Mary.
Mother of Sorrows,
at the foot of the cross.
The Queen of the Martyrs,
through Christ, our Lord.
O divine light,
urge the evil spirits
to leave us forever
and accept the light.
We believe in you
and we pray thee...
and we pray thee.
Come be with those who love
and learn to accept you.
...Mother of Sorrows,
at the foot of the cross.
We believe in you
and we pray, my God...
Liz.
Liz, wake up, darling.
Please, my love.
Wake up.
Lieutenant.
Why did you not
listen to me, professor?
Why did you not leave?
What do you mean?
You can't kill the dead.
You drove her to him.
And now, they'll be
together forever.
Lieutenant, what do you mean?
Mom.
Help me.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org