Subtitles by explosiveskull
Patrick had a vague feeling,
something was about to happen.
How could he tell his parents...
that the malevolent things
were all around?
In the ether and in each
speck of dust.
Patrick had always seen these
things...
and always it had seemed that
he alone knew about them.
And so, on the evening
of the seventh day...
he could feel their imminent
arrival.
Something in the breeze
of twilight had whispered...
"It's going to happen tonight".
The following day when his
mother opened the door...
there was absolutely nothing
there.
The trail of Patrick William
Ward's urine...
led to an empty closet bathed in
the darkness of his last night.
The end.
Wow, gosh.
Here we go.
That's one of your best!
Mom, you tell her that every
single time.
Yeah, but this time I mean it.
Really?
I was fascinated, captivated,
scared.
It was like...
- Lovecraft.
- I know, too much like him, huh?
- No.
I haven't completely found
my voice yet.
Hm, yeah, that's what it is.
Vera!
Mom, my sister's a freak.
Something new, please.
No, Beth, honestly,
I can't wrap my mind around how
you spent days writing this...
piece of crap that ends
with piss on the carpet.
You wouldn't understand.
What the hell are your stories
supposed to mean?
They're supposed to be scary.
Oh, scary, what's scary
is having you as a sister...
but, good luck finding
a boyfriend.
I don't speak French!
Keep writing, Beth.
What if I'm not good enough?
You are good enough, Beth.
You're only saying that cause
you're my mom.
What's that?
What the fuck?
Okay, buddy.
No French, Mom.
It's green, everyone likes it.
No, no.
Yeah, it's no problem, yeah.
That's quite the vintage
car you got there.
Mom and I love old things.
You just passing though?
No.
I mean, we're moving here,
into Aunt Clarisse's house.
Aunt Clarisse? She live around
here?
Um, I'm not sure exactly.
I mean, she's dead.
She was my mother's cousin's
sister-in-law, or something.
Ah, Clarisse Jourdan, that
kooky, old French lady...
who had that place way up
in the prair... oh, damn it!
For Christ's sake! It's gonna
smell like nail polish...
in here for at least a week.
Watch the store for a minute,
will ya, Miss... Jourdan.
My name's Keller.
What you doing?
What is that?
A story you wouldn't like.
How would you know?
Is there nobody here?
Oh god, it stinks.
She'll be right back.
My god, I look heinous.
Okay, what's the story about?
Some guy's been breaking into
homes, murdering the parents...
and sparing the daughters,
who are always about your age.
Uh-huh... and?
He stays in the house
with her...
along with the parents' dead
bodies.
Tss, you made that up.
Girls!
Let's go?
Jesus Christ, it's Rob Zombie's
house.
She's gonna like it.
It's not bad.
Yeah, it's an extension
of your brain.
You got to be kidding me.
The bedrooms are upstairs.
Mom, it smells like old
ladies in here.
It smells like mold, Vera.
Yeah, that's what I said.
Look at all these dolls.
Clarissa never
let me play with them.
What was Aunt Clarisse's deal?
- Is it working?
- Nope!
Bingo!
When are you gonna give up this
arty writer bullshit...
and just use a laptop?
Never.
Oh god, it's like
a flea market in here.
Think she bought all these
for herself?
You know, old ladies love
that kind of crap.
- A Chinese puzzle box.
- What?
It's more than a mirror,
it's actually a box.
I've read about these.
There's gotta be a secret button
somewhere.
Jesus!
- So, you like it?
- No.
Vera, careful with that.
Who would even want to
buy something like that?
Honey?
Baby? Beth? Beth...
I'm okay.
Oh, sweetie.
Of course, you're okay.
That's why you look so pale.
- What's wrong with her?
- Nothing.
She's like you now.
Great. Well, you know you have
a great sense of timing.
Vera!
Is she alright?
Oh, so now you ask.
You could have stayed
and helped her out.
Why bother, you'd rush and
rescue her anyways.
I just, I don't get why she
would write these stories...
when she falls apart at the
first sight of blood.
Mom, she's afraid of flying,
she's afraid of boys...
she's afraid of her own
freakin' shadow.
The other day when I was
packing...
I found something you'll
never believe.
I'm not into games, Vera.
An interview with her, Mom.
Several pages, all typed up
like it was in a magazine.
She made the whole thing up.
Like, in it, she's some famous
writer and this journalist...
is asking her all these
questions about her books.
She needs a reality check, Mom!
It's nice to know you do love
your sister after all.
I know you're angry about
leaving...
your boyfriend behind, Vera,
but...
Whatever, Mom.
And quit wearing make-up.
Fuck you! Piece of shit!
I know you love her more!
Beth, Beth... fucking Beth.
Shit.
Mom!
Where does your antique lamp go?
I'm upstairs!
With you favorite writer,
I know.
Your antique lamp, where
does it go?
In your room.
Did you hear me?
Yes!
Hey, go easy on the door.
Enjoying my bed are you?
This is yours.
Oh, this is yours too.
Your Cthulhu shit is not
staying in my room, take it.
Would it kill you to be...
a little nicer to your sister?
It might.
You are unbearable!
Not mine!
It's an old house.
God, Mom, it's my room!
Go help Lovecraft Junior. Jesus!
Lower!
Shit.
Jane? What?
I can barely hear you. Hello?
Hello? Jane, I can't hear you.
Agh!
Mom? Mom!
No! No!
They just wanna play with dolls.
Don't look at me.
No!
Listen to me, Beth.
You have to go please, go run
away, baby, run away!
No!
Fucker!
Mom!
Mom! Mom! No, no!
No! No!
Beth, Beth, come here, come
here, baby, baby, come here.
Hey, hey, it's okay, Beth,
it's okay.
You're okay. You're okay, hey.
Oh, god.
I was in the basement.
I know, I know.
- With Vera.
- It's over now, okay?
It was so real.
It was a long time ago, Beth.
Hey. Oh... hey.
It's
a beautiful morning on CO1.
Sit back and enjoy Chicago's
classical music station.
Yeah?
Uh, it's Jerry.
Hey, Jerry...
No, I'm sorry, she can't come
to the phone right now.
I need to talk to her.
Yeah, I'll get her to call you
back right away.
Five times the sales.
Excuse me.
Five times, my friend,
is she writing?
Uh, yeah, no, of course,
she's writing.
We're all
gonna be there tonight.
This is it, does she get it?
I don't know, Jerry. I'll tell
her, she's right here.
I'm gonna tell her right now,
okay?
- Okay, cool.
- Okay, great, thanks.
I'm so fucking happy.
The entire publishing staff
are gonna be at the show.
Your sales are through the roof,
they adore you!
They adore the sales.
Do you want to know?
I hate numbers.
Well, but they're huge.
And they love you.
Yes, hi... no, I just told her!
Okay.
Tonight's guest has been
described as a master of horror.
Her latest book is
"INCIDENT IN A GHOST LAND".
It's only been out two weeks...
and already it's topping the
bestseller lists.
We're very lucky to have her...
as she very rarely makes
television appearances...
Elizabeth Keller!
Oh, it's such a pleasure to meet
you, Elizabeth.
It's a pleasure for me,
too, Eve.
"Incident in a Ghostland"...
is your most personal book
so far...
and a kind of tribute to your
family.
Yes, that's true.
What happened to you and your
sister when you were teenagers?
Oh, are you asking if the book
is autobiographical?
What I'm saying, Elizabeth,
is that it just seems so real.
The details are so intense that
I guess the question is...
why write this book?
To keep from going insane.
Truly?
I mean, is there a better reason
to write?
No.
She just wouldn't shut up
about Vera and I...
I got defensive, I'm sure
everyone noticed.
It's not as bad as that.
You know, in your own mysterious
way, you call the shots.
You're only saying that because
you're my biggest fan.
Shit, you're right.
I'm gonna take Harlequin
up to bed.
Are you sure you wanna watch
this all over again?
Take a note from your son,
look how much he cares.
He's not gonna go to bed
in this, is he?
Why not, he loves this costume?
I told you, they love you!
Hello? Hello?
Hello?
Beth! Please,
you have to come back.
Vera?
Come back! Please...
Is Mom there with you?
They're in the house!
Vera, listen to me.
You're not hearing me, Beth.
I hear you!
Don't leave me alone, Beth.
Is Mom there?
Vera!
Your Mom's with her obviously,
right?
She has to be.
Pick up, Mom, pick up.
It's busy.
Okay. You can just try again.
Are you sure about this?
I don't know,
it could be nothing...
just one of Vera's delusions,
but...
Mom isn't answering her
phone...
and I'm having those
dreams again.
Something's not right.
I understand, but...
They never should have
stayed in that house.
It's not helping Vera.
She should be in a hospital.
All right.
Call us when you get there.
I will.
Take care of yourself.
Here? Are you sure?
Yes.
Mom?
Mom!
Beth?
Oh, baby doll! What are you
doing here?
Why didn't you tell me
you were coming?
Vera called last night.
She was screaming in the phone
and then it got disconnected.
I tried calling back, but I
couldn't get through.
And I didn't know what
was happening.
I didn't know she used
the phone.
- Everything's okay?
- Yeah, she's resting.
I've missed you so much!
You look beautiful.
You haven't changed at all.
Oh well!
House looks exactly the same,
Mom.
After all these years...
you're still living in old
Clarisse's style.
Unfair.
I sold most of it.
Yeah?
You'd never believe what I got
for the antique toys.
Really?
And, I'm going to be able
to redo the whole house.
Mom, haven't you been getting
the money I send you?
Sure I have.
Oh, Beth, I didn't mean
it like that.
Mom, if it's not enough,
just tell me.
I don't even know why
I said that.
You're already spoiling me!
I'm your daughter, I can do it,
I'm not spoiling you, I...
Oh, sweetie.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I overreacted.
Beth...
You're not mad at me?
Why would I be mad?
Because I left you here
all alone with Vera and...
Beth, look at me.
You didn't abandon me.
You left because you had your
own life to live.
That's perfectly natural.
Understood?
Now dry those tears,
that's my girl.
Let's have a toast!
Since when did you start
drinking redneck beer?
Shit.
The key above the door.
You lock her in?
No, honey, she does.
She hides the key down there.
I made a copy.
Vera! Sweetie! Are you hiding?
Vera?
The first-aid kit, Beth, in the
wardrobe to your left.
Vera, where are you?
Honey? The first aid kit, Beth!
Help me!
Vera! Mom!
Grab her legs, hurry up!
No!
Beth! Move... grab her legs!
It's okay.
No!
Ssh, it's okay, it's okay,
get in the room.
Help me!
Calm down, Vera,
it's okay, calm down.
Help me!
Calm down. Get the key, Beth.
Look at me. It's over,
babe. It's over....
there you go, it's over.
Never again... hurt me.
No one's going to hurt you,
honey.
My sister.
Ssh...
Beth...
I'm here, Vera.
She sees you.
- Vera...
- She sees you.
Please tell me how you got the
inspiration for this book?
Sure, yeah, it all started...
when I was doing my masters
degree at the Sorbone...
and I went to galleries
in Paris...
Come here.
And I went in
and saw a bunch...
of what seemed like outsider
art, it was bizarre...
it was kind of off-kilter.
It's tough, isn't it?
I know.
How do you do it, Mom?
Last week I found her
in my room...
tied to the radiator.
She was screaming like...
I had to turn around to make
sure no one was there.
What can I do?
There's nothing you can do,
Beth.
She keeps reliving that night,
over and over.
Come here.
It's okay.
Help me!
Vera?
Are you gonna let me die alone?
No, not alone?
You're not going to die, Vera.
They're making me pay,
and you're not there.
I move, and they burn me.
I scream and they...
please, please!
I'm begging you, please tell
them...
tell them I'm not a bad girl.
Vera, Vera listen to me, okay?
And I'm sorry if I offended
them!
Tell them to stop punishing me.
You didn't do anything wrong.
- Tell them...
- It's not your fault.
It's not your fault, okay?
- They're here.
- Vera, it's just Mom, Vera...
Vera!
The truck! Oh god.
The truck.
Mom?
Get lost!
Up already, sweetie?
Yeah.
Did Eugene come?
So much crap in this house.
Did he leave you the bill?
Oh, I didn't even see him.
What a great day
for a picnic.
Mm, you still smell like Beth.
That smell drove me crazy.
What are you talking about?
I should have eaten you up,
you and Vera.
So you'd never leave me.
So no boys could ever come
near my girls.
Stop drinking, Mom.
The flesh of my daughters.
You're not making any sense.
Are you okay, Mom?
God, I look like shit.
I don't know where your talent
comes from, honey.
Your capacity to create
your own worlds.
Does it still hurt?
Nothing hurts for real anymore.
You're still pretty, Mom.
What I'm trying to say
is that...
Incident in a Ghost Land
is your best novel yet.
You read it?
Of course, I did...
and it was so good that it
completely rattled me.
I didn't send the book
because...
You're better
than Lovecraft!
Beth, I miss you.
Leave me... all alone.
Vera!
Vera, it's okay. It's okay.
Vera, it's okay.
It's okay, it's okay.
Vera, what did you do?
Vera, look at me.
Vera, nobody's here.
No one is here, Vera!
Where's the key?
No!
No, no, no, no, no...
Vera, Vera, Vera!
Listen to me, please open
the door.
Stop it!
Vera! Open the door!
Vera, please!
Vera?
Agh!
Mom!
Mom, Mom, where's the key?
Vera's having a fit!
She's locked herself in her
room! Where's the bedroom key?
The bedroom key, where
is the bedroom key?
There's no key, honey.
Stop! I hate you!
Vera?
Agh!
Get off me, you motherfucker!
Fucking asshole!
Vera? Vera?
Mom, call an ambulance!
Vera!
Vera? Wait, stay! Stay okay?
Okay! It's okay, it's okay.
Here you go, here you go.
The ambulance is on its way!
I know why you did that.
I know what you want
from your sister.
I'll wait for them on the road.
Otherwise they'll miss
the trail.
Mom?
Stay with her, and wait for me.
Mom, what did you mean
back there?
Don't listen to her, Beth.
Vera? Vera?
Vera, stay with me!
Stay with me, Vera!
Vera! Stay with me.
Vera... Vera?
I can hear you.
Oh, Vera, I can hear you.
Vera, please stay with me.
Please, Vera. Vera?
Vera?
We broke your sister...
and now, it's your turn.
Mom?
Mom! Mom?
Mom!
Vera?
What did you do to me?
Do you understand now, Beth?
Vera, what'd you do to me?
They broke me and now they're
playing with you.
Vera...
He chose you, Beth.
You psycho!
- Stop it!
- Tell me what you did!
- It's not me!
- Tell me!
Stop it, Beth! Wake up, Beth!
For once in your life,
stop running away!
Try to accept reality!
Come back!
Beth, you're still here.
Beth, listen to me...
accept what happened...
you just need to face the truth.
Mom.
There was nothing she could do.
No, no, no, no...
No!
Mom died, Beth.
- No.
- Yes, she did, she died.
They killed her, Beth.
She died.
I'm so sorry.
Mommy, Mommy, Mommy...
Ssh... she died, Beth.
You have to let her go.
Ssh, Beth...
It's just us.
It's just us, now.
Are you back?
Beth, are you back?
You were talking to them
like they were real.
And to Mom, you looked at me
like I was crazy!
You couldn't hear me.
You were gone.
I didn't know how to bring
you back.
I hate you, Vera!
I hate you!
Get up, get up, now, now!
We have to hide!
Ssh... in here!
It's a game, okay?
She wants us to hide!
Listen to me, if she takes
you upstairs, you don't move.
And you don't cry, okay?
No matter... no matter
what he does to you.
He'll go easier, okay?
Last time I hit him in the leg,
he hurt me much worse.
Don't do it.
Listen to me...
if she takes you upstairs...
no matter what he does,
you don't move, and don't cry.
You're pretty.
Will you be my friend?
Do you want to be friends?
I like you.
I like you. You're pretty.
Will you be my friend?
No!
Agh!
I love you. You're pretty.
Nobody loves you.
You're ugly.
You're a fucking pig!
I'm going to kill you.
Nobody loves you.
Agh!
No!
Vera!
Ssh!
Ssh... in here.
At that door, one two, three.
No! No! Wait!
Wait!
Hang in there, okay?
We're here to help.
- Easy, easy.
- Don't you fucking touch her!
Don't you come any closer.
Back off! Back off!
Back the fuck off!
Okay.
You're doing really good, girls.
- Don't you fucking...
- I promise.
Patrol 10 to dispatch.
I've got a situation here.
Tell me who did this to you?
A witch, and an ogre.
They came for us, at Aunt
Clarisse's.
About 14, 15, slender...
one's blonde, the other
brunette. Over.
It was two fucking men...
in a candy truck.
A candy truck?
You read me?
I read you, John.
I'm at the gas station.
Janet says she saw the girls
you described!
Are you kidding me?
I swear to God!
Hold on, can you tell me
where Aunt Clarisse lives?
Janet said they were going...
to Clarisse Jourdan's
old house...
at the corner of Holly Flowers
and Jackson.
I know the place.
They were with their mother.
Janet talked to one
of the girls.
She's sure they're the ones.
For Christ's sake, John,
send a team!
We'll stop at the hospital
and head straight over!
Copy that. Over and out.
Cooper! I got some info!
We have to go! I know where
the girls come from.
Beth! Beth! Look at me!
Come back!
Beth!
Why? No!
No!
Beth!
You look wonderful as always.
Thank you so much.
Thanks for coming.
- Thanks for the invitation.
- Of course, enjoy.
I will.
You look beautiful.
You, too. Your world is
perfect, honey.
A most beautiful dream in a most
beautiful world.
- Hi.
James, this is my mother.
Pleased to meet you.
Do you think I could steal her
away for a minute?
Yes.
Right this way.
Thank you.
See where Mom is? Wave to Mom.
It's not really your scene,
is it?
Not exactly, no.
I figured as much.
Even less so when I have
just finished reading.
Oh god.
What?
Uh, I have waited my entire life
for this moment...
and now it's finally arrived...
and I would rather die
than hear you say that...
Your novel is a masterpiece.
What?
You heard me perfectly.
If you change even one word
in that book...
I will never speak to you again.
Thank you... thank you.
I mean...
Thank you so much,
Mr. Lovecraft.
Howard.
Help me!
Vera!
Don't listen to her, Beth.
There's nothing left for you
there.
Beth!
She's my sister, Mom.
Her world is an ugly place
to be, honey.
But she's still my sister.
You sure you wanna do that?
Beth!
Yes.
Go, baby.
Go.
Agh!
Help! Help me!
No!
Don't move. Step away.
Hands up! Slow...
Do it now. Hands up!
Don't fucking move!
Don't.
I love you.
Okay, Beth, we're about 30 or 40
minutes from the hospital.
I'm afraid until then,
you're stuck with me.
You're very strong, you know?
You're very brave.
I bet you like to play sports.
Do you play sports, Beth?
No.
No? Well, I would've lost
that bet.
I like to write stories.
Subtitles by explosiveskull