Stop that humming, will you?
- Can I enter?
- No.
What did you draw again?
I don't know.
Hmm.
Is Mummy with the
visitors again?
Why can't we ever
see the visitors?
Because only Mother
talks to the visitors.
But why only visitors come
when Dad is not home?
I'll tell Dad.
No! She will punish us.
Don't you dare.
What happened to you?
- I'll tell Mother.
- No!
Mama!
Mummy!
Okay. Don't worry.
She is simply here.
It's going to be okay.
What is it?
Oh, my.
Oh, no.
No.
No! No!
No. No.
No.
Mother, have the visitors left?
Yes.
Yes. They're gone.
Now, Holly... my sweet child...
we're going to
play a game, okay?
You're going to stay here...
and shut your eyes
and count to 100.
And if you finish counting,
you're going to
start again, okay?
Now, shut your eyes.
- Okay.
- One. Two.
Eleven. Twelve.
Thirteen. Fourteen.
Fifteen. Sixteen.
Mother?
Hazel?
Holly!
Visitors, begone!
Holly?
Forgive me.
I have to do this.
I have no choice.
I'm so sorry.
Mummy!
No. Don't.
Holly!
Come back! Holly!
Come back!
Hey.
Hey, baby. Thank you.
You're welcome.
So you're still looking for
the cover of your book?
Yeah.
I mean, I did a couple
of things last night,
but... they weren't right.
You know, when I worked on your
story and wrote about you,
you know, the cover
came from the heart.
It just flowed. It was natural.
It felt right.
No advice, no
agents, no nothing.
What do you think of this one?
Um, well, it's...
it's dark and depressing.
Oh, of course.
But, I mean, it's...
it's beautiful.
Well, I'm still working.
No. It's beautiful.
I'm gonna take these with me.
Mm-hmm.
And, uh, I'll eat
them on my way.
Okay.
Thank you, sweetie.
- Good luck.
- Thank you, baby.
Dear friends...
our only friends,
thank you for being here with us
on the third anniversary
of our wedding.
What?
Holly and I...
decided to have a baby.
- Whoa!
- Yes.
- Okay. Yes. All right.
- Bring 'em home!
Yes. Cheers to that.
- Yeah.
- Well done, guys.
Congratulations.
Uh, I just wrote an...
An article
on this, uh, crazy
world-famous cult
that actually believes in
the apocalypse happening
pretty soon.
It's like Scientology
with astral travel.
ULM?
Umbrella of Love and Mind.
That's the one. Yeah.
- Do you know them, too?
- Have you heard of it?
Bruce O'Hara, I mean,
he's a rock star.
Yeah. And they're
in town, actually.
Uh, and they're having their
gathering tomorrow night.
And believe it or not, we're
gonna go check it out.
Yep.
Yeah.
Well... we actually had a
friend back in New York
who later on became
a ULM disciple.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
She was, like, Tim's special
buddy, and we became friends.
Best friends.
Come on. She was not
my best friend.
We just became friends,
and it's that in the end,
we ended up living together
in New York and...
You know, I-I sort of remember
her, like, from New York.
- The curly-haired, folksy girl.
- Yeah.
What was her name? Valerie.
Yeah, yeah. Valerie. I remember.
Yeah. Anyway, she...
Like two years ago,
she just disappeared.
I mean, we haven't
heard from her since.
- She just...
- Wait. Whoa, whoa. Hold on.
- What do you mean, disappeared?
- Well, she...
I think that she's
touring with ULM
and she's following them,
whatever they're doing.
Anyway...
But if she's part of ULM,
she might be at this
gathering tomorrow night.
We're going. Maybe
we'll meet her.
You guys should come, too.
- Why don't you? Yeah.
- I don't know, man.
Um, I don't think it's
a good idea, but...
These things are pretty fun.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Go away! Go away!
Don't worry, Holly. It's me...
Valerie.
Why did you disappear?
I mean... I know why
you disappeared,
but... why didn't
you send a message
or... even call us?
I had no other choice.
You always have a choice.
I guess it was how
it's meant to be.
And I came here for
a bigger reason.
Why are you laughing?
I missed you.
I missed you, too.
Come on.
Come on. Oh.
Look what I found.
Do you remember that day?
How can I forget?
Yeah.
I know.
And now the universe
brought us back together.
- Oh, the universe?
- The universe.
Always the universe.
Hello.
Uh, hey.
Hey, Valerie.
It's been a long time.
Uh, what are you doing here?
How did you find us?
Maybe I should have called,
but can you let me in?
Yeah, yeah. Come in.
It's been a long time.
Bring it in!
Where's Holly?
Oh, she's sleeping.
She's, uh, she's in there.
- Go on. Go ahead.
- Thank you.
Holly?
Valerie.
Where's my girl?
Whoo!
Oh.
Mm!
Oh, you smell exactly the same.
Isn't it great how the
universe brought us here,
back together again?
Universe? Is that
what you call it?
Well, I know. I'm sorry.
I should have called somehow,
and I should have let you know.
I think it was perhaps
a very abrupt way...
- Yeah, it was.
- To leave.
But, you know, I've been
completely disconnected
from everything and everyone.
I had to come here in person.
And I'm here to apologize.
Is that why you came?
To apologize?
That and ULM is in town tonight.
Yeah.
Well... I came here to take
you to tonight's seminar.
Yeah. I know this. A
friend of mine wrote it.
Oh. Well, is he coming tonight?
No idea.
Well, okay.
So... look, Holly.
I know that it's very
difficult to put into words
what I've been through
for the past two years.
But I-I need you to come
to tonight's seminar,
that if you just
give me a chance...
Just come tonight.
Please.
Okay.
Okay. Let's see what's
the big deal about ULM.
I mean, if that's what you need.
Yeah.
Oh, this is gonna be great.
Okay. It's a date.
- It's a date.
Can I have your name, please?
Yes. Uh, Valerie plus
two from family.
Oh. Of course.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
Who pays for all this, Val?
Bruce O'Hara Fund.
Come. Join me.
It's beautiful.
Yeah.
You want a drink or
anything, sweetie?
No, thank you. I'm fine.
Oh, look. They're here.
Oh! Oh, hi.
How about that? This is great.
- Hey, guys.
- Oh, you made it.
Glad to see you.
- This is Valerie.
- Oh, this is great.
Oh, hi, Valerie.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
The pleasure is ours.
Oh, my.
I can't believe I'm saying this,
but it's really an honor to
meet someone from the family.
There are gonna be other
family members here, right?
- Yes, there are.
- This is great.
Holly, why don't I show
you to the bathroom?
Yeah.
I'm gonna go get ready, and
I'll see you guys inside.
- Okay. Okay.
- All right.
- You done?
- Yeah.
- Crazy pictures...
- Yeah?
Inside this.
Is this your first time?
- Yeah.
- Ah.
- Yours?
- Yes.
You're lucky.
I came all the way
from Morocco for this,
uh, with, uh, with the wife.
- Morocco?
- Morocco.
Wow.
My wife, uh, she's gonna
be in the family soon.
Lucky you, man.
She's been, uh, dream-training
for, uh, 14 months for this.
She's becoming quite the pro.
Dream training?
Dream training. Yes.
Some mornings, she
wakes up, uh, totally,
like, all wet and
stuff down there.
Crazy.
What? Did he see you?
- I don't know.
- Okay.
You go find him and
I'll meet the family
and I'll see you inside, okay?
- Okay.
- All right.
I have a feeling that this
place is going to go crazy.
It's packed.
Yeah.
It's beautiful here.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome...
the family members!
Why do we dream?
How do we dream?
Here in Umbrella
of Love and Mind,
we believe many of those answers
lie where we may know the least.
The sacred time is near,
and here in our family,
we have found the savior
to guide us in our dreams,
to our destiny.
Maybe tonight it's your turn.
The time has come!
He's here!
He is... Bruce O'Hara!
We are trapped...
Inside our own
heads, our memories.
We're components in the system.
Here in Umbrella
of Love and Mind,
we're not supernatural,
as some claim.
No.
We're naturally super.
We're visitors, visitors
outside of our walls,
inside others' walls, past
others' minds' walls.
And beyond those walls,
we know that we are one.
Tonight I want to begin
with those who doubt us.
What does it mean
being a dream surfer?
It wasn't an easy
thing to discover,
being able to know
about people's minds,
their lives, their secrets.
You see, when I touch them...
I can see their needs... their souls...
everything.
Last night, I had a
vessel dream again.
This time, it was about
a very important woman
who's about to enter my life.
Yes.
I must see you tonight.
I can feel the
vibration in the room.
She is here.
She's the soul mate... of a
new member of our family.
So it's you.
Welcome.
May I, please?
Oh.
- No.
- I...
Don't be afraid.
Fear, my friends,
is our addiction.
It's our drug.
It enslaves us, feeds on us.
I used to be a slave
to my own fears,
but through studying my
dreams and visiting others,
I am healed now.
I'm free.
I strongly feel that...
you need healing, too.
Am I right?
It's okay. It's okay.
No. I-I'm not sure I'm the right
person to do it in front...
- Oh!
Please.
Holly... give me your hand.
It's her.
It's you.
Just breathe... and
open your mind.
Why can't we ever
see the visitors?
Because only Mother
talks to the visitors.
But why only visitors come
when Dad is not home?
What am...
Oh, my God.
How is this possible?
No.
This is Bruce
O'Hara's show, right?
You okay?
I'm fine.
He knows me.
Great.
Great. Exactly what we needed.
Dream surfer, my ass.
Let me tell you this... That
dude is a fucking con man.
He was bleeding, Tim. Come on.
So?
That was a fucking weird
hypnosis or something.
He tried to fuck
with my wife's mind.
That dude, oh, I give it to him.
But he's a con man.
I've never seen
anything like it,
and, no, he's not a con man.
Wake up. Wake up.
Akasha frequencies and
astral projections,
I know this shit.
The dude is fake.
How do you explain what
happened to her, then?
Because since you
know everything...
Are you two seriously arguing?
Actually, it's quite nostalgic
hearing you two argue
like the good old days
when we were in our
little house in New York.
How do you explain what
happened to her, then, huh?
I can't. But I'll find out.
What's happening with you two?
I'm telling you, I feel great.
I feel great.
- Sweetie...
- Hmm?
Do you want to tell me
what happened tonight?
Well, I don't know what it was,
but it's just as if he
was in my head or...
Or in my fears, maybe.
I mean, I don't know, but I
feel so much better now.
- I don't understand.
- Okay. Um...
I have to confess something.
When you told me that you
wanted to have a baby,
I said okay, but I lied.
I mean, I wasn't ready.
I was afraid of it.
Oh, Holly, come on.
Why?
I don't know.
- Oh, Holly.
- I was scared.
I'm sorry, Tim.
I'm sorry, but I am ready now,
and I think that Bruce
cured my fears,
and I'm ready to have
this baby now, tonight.
Why didn't you tell me, huh?
How long you were planning
to go along with it?
I don't know, and I'm so sorry.
I am.
I'm...
I understand, okay?
I wish you said something,
but I want to understand what's
going on with you, okay?
I want to know.
So just for one...
One small second,
if you can be, like,
normal and tell me...
Okay, no, I don't know what happened.
Why don't you tell me?
Actually, why don't you
write a book about it, huh?
- What did he do to her, Val?
- I don't think she knows either.
I don't think she experienced
something like this
with him before.
Oh, come on, sweetheart.
How would you know?
- I'm a family member.
- Tell us. Go ahead.
Okay.
Well, when you enter
his frequency,
there is complete
and utter surrender
in which fear materializes.
Are you jealous, Val?
- No!
- Okay, good.
Because that would be
completely unfair.
I mean, coming here after
two years of silence
when we shared
everything with you.
We shared our home with you.
We shared our bed with you.
- I shared my husband with you.
- Oh, come on, Holly.
Then you have the nerve
to be jealous of your
new boyfriend and me,
of your new family and me?
I said I'm not jealous, okay?
Okay. Okay.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
Look, I'm here, okay?
Here with you.
Just wanted to help you.
Then help me.
Help me.
What is it?
Go on, baby. Don't stop now.
I'm... I'm...
Oh, yeah.
Hey! Hey, who are you?
Holly!
Holly, what is it?
What is it, sweetheart?
She's here! She's here!
I saw her!
- She's here!
- Who? Your mother?
Yeah! She's in there!
- Oh, my God!
- Who's in there?!
- Okay, calm...
- Where's my amulet?
What?
- She took my amulet!
- No!
- Baby...
- My mom!
- Nobody is inside.
- No, she's inside.
- Baby...
- I saw her!
I saw her! She was there.
Baby, there is no one inside.
Hey. You'll get cold.
I'll be okay.
I looked for the
amulet everywhere.
Look at all that junk. It's
definitely not in there.
It's probably somewhere
in the house.
Yeah.
What happened last night, Val?
And we're back.
What are you doing to me?
- You're doing it.
- No.
This is an initiation.
We go where you take us.
But I don't want to
take you anywhere.
No, you do.
You're stronger
than your mother.
- But I...
- Please.
Let me take you to your destiny.
May I?
Will you be bleeding
all over again?
Just breathe.
Here we go.
Let's go back to
where it all began.
Don't be afraid, Holly.
I'm here with you.
Just breathe.
Mother?
Oh, no!
Visitors, begone!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Hazel.
- We're back. We... We're back.
- No! You're a liar!
You're a liar!
You're crazy!
- Get out of my mind!
- You had to see it.
Get out of my mind! I
didn't kill my sister!
You had to see it.
- You can't leave now.
- You're crazy.
You're crazy, and you're a liar!
I didn't kill my sister!
Remember how you came here.
I invited you here.
If you leave me now, even
I can't help you, Holly.
You don't know where
you'll end up.
You might forever be trapped
in a maze of dreams, Holly!
She doesn't even know if
it's her dream or not.
I'm not sure she's
the master visitor.
Trust me.
She's the one. Go to her now.
It's your turn. She is
the master visitor.
I'll do my part.
I've been ready for
this all my life.
Tim?
Val?
Tim?!
Hazel.
You're okay.
Hazel? Hazel, you're okay!
Hey.
It's okay. It's me.
Did you go see Bruce?
What the fuck is going on, huh?
What are you trying
to do to her?
Hey. No, Tim!
Holly!
I have to abort
your journey, Val.
You're scaring her.
You're scaring me too.
I told you you'd get lost.
Didn't I?
Yeah.
Ah.
Where are you now?
In a dream again?
- I don't know.
- No.
You're lost in a maze now.
I'm you're only
chance to get out.
You have to go all the way
to the end of the tunnel.
You can't stop here.
Accept the mystery.
What the fuck?
Holly?
Valerie, are you okay?
This is how you repay my trust?
Please don't hurt him.
We're in a family meeting, Tim.
You can't be here.
I'm gonna fucking
take your head off.
But I love her!
No, you don't, Tim.
You're just a bad actor.
Trust me.
Let go.
Who are they?
They are my children.
They're born visitors.
Holly, this is not real.
Bruce. Bruce, please,
don't do this.
What are you doing?
Please, please, Bruce. You
don't have to do this.
Bruce, you don't
have to do this.
It's... It's all my fault.
Bruce!
I wanted you to be
a part of this.
I trusted you!
This is Holly's dream, hmm?
And when will I see her again?
No.
Time to wake up.
Make it quick, you bastard!
Val! No!
No!
Val!
Shhhhh.
It's okay. It's okay.
What's happening?
- What's happening?
- I know. I know.
What's happening?
I can imagine how
crazy this must seem.
But sometimes things just are.
You're ready.
Ready to embrace
your new family.
The master is here.
You all have been waiting
for this night for so long.
Hazel.
Hazel, is that you?
Is that you?
My dear queen,
you are ready to rise
as the mother of
the second coming.
Finally together.
We are ready to go.
Are you ready to go?
No! No! No!
We are all your servants now.
Oh!
Only the next of kin.
He is Bruce O'Hara!