Subtitles by explosiveskull
...spread of this,
happening outside the walls.
Tonight's storm is causing
all kinds of problems
around the Bay.
Pete Giddings will have
the forecast.
And we'll show you
what would happen to the Bay
if some scientists' predictions
come true.
All on 7 at 11:00.
What has 12 million eyes,
192 million teeth
and stretches from
the Golden Gate Bridge
all the way to the Twin Towers?
It's Hands Across America.
A 4,000-mile-long chain
of Good Samaritans
standing hand in hand,
through fields of grain,
past purple mountains,
and across fruited plains,
from sea to shining sea.
That's right.
This summer, six million people
will tether themselves together
to fight hunger
in the United States.
Visit your local record shop
to find out
how you can be a part
of Hands Across America.
Put some heat on that one.
Yeah, I guess
I missed my chance to go pro.
Oh!
Tell you what.
Right now, you could walk away
with a prize
from the second level,
or you could keep going for
a prize from the third level.
Okay.
What do you think, Addy?
Should we stop or keep going?
Don't look at me.
It's your birthday.
I want number 11.
- Yeah?
- That one?
- Yeah.
- All right.
Uh, yeah, uh, that one.
- Thanks, man.
- Of course.
Yeah.
That shirt better not
give her nightmares.
In trouble for winning
my daughter a T-shirt.
That's a new one.
She was terrified
when it came on TV.
You'd know that
if you were around, right?
Who let her watch it?
You know...
you know, they're filming
something by the carousel.
You should see if
they're looking for extras.
Uh... I need another beer.
I can't have a beer now?
Hey. How about the Big Dipper?
Addy, you want to try it?
Russel, you know she's
not big enough to do that.
And I sure as hell
am not doing it, so...
Whac-A-Mole!
Yeah, Whac-A-Mole, guy.
- That's what I'm talking about.
- How many tickets?
- Two tickets.
- Two tickets!
Two tickets!
Hey, Addy,
come to the bathroom.
I don't have to go.
Russel?
Russel! Can you watch
your daughter, please?
I'm watching.
Baby, stay close, okay?
- Glen.
- What?
- Stop it.
- I'm not doing anything.
You keep doing scissors.
Ah, I'm just cruising.
Come on.
Um, what?
- This is ridiculous.
- It's too rad.
Two knots. Come on, now.
What?
- This is... this is impossible.
- Oh, my God.
Don't do it. Don't do it.
These, the earth and water,
he divided into places
from which life could spring.
The mountains and the valleys
and the waters
were all where they should be.
Then Sotuknang went to Taiowa
and said,
"I want you to see
what I have done.
And I have done well."
And Taiowa looked and said,
"It is very good.
"But you are not done with it.
"Now you must create life
of all kinds
and set it in motion
according to my plan."
...and went
into the endless space
and gathered substance
to create his helper,
the Spider Woman.
"Look all about you,
Spider Woman," said Sotuknang.
"Here now is endless space,
"but in the world,
there is no joyful movement.
The world needs..."
We made it!
- Why?! Why?!
- No, Dad!
- 'Cause y'all sleep too much.
- All right.
Come on. Let's go.
Careful. Hey, hey, hey!
- Ah, whatever.
- Bags in the house first.
Look, look, look, look, look.
- Ew.
- Come on.
You're too old.
- You know the drill.
- Don't judge me.
Don't judge me.
- Little dude.
- The Wi-Fi's not working.
You don't need the Internet.
You got the Outernet.
Good one.
Okay, okay, okay.
Knock-knock.
- Who's there?
- You.
You who?
Yoo-hoo.
Open up the door.
My God, what's wrong with you?
- Can we get a dog?
- No, we can't.
You should run
while you're here.
Jason, eat something.
- Something.
- What?
- What's with all the attitude?
- For me.
I'm sorry.
Yay, track and field.
Whoa. You don't want
to run anymore?
You love track and field.
- Well, what's the point?
- The Olympics.
I'm not gonna make it
to the Olympics, guys.
You could do anything
you set your mind to.
Can I drive
while we're up here?
- No.
Well, that's what
I set my mind to.
- You know...
- Where you going, Jason?
- Jason?
- Well, Cara and Haley...
Yeah, I'm gonna get something.
You need to come
and finish your food.
Cara and Haley drove
with parent supervision.
Yeah, well,
you don't need to know
how to drive when you're
an Olympic-caliber athlete.
- Oh, my God.
- You run.
- You run on the sand.
- Why?
Because it's harder, okay?
- No traction.
- Mm.
Practice on the beach,
you get on dry land,
you take off.
We're going to the beach?
Yeah. Well, later.
Once we get settled.
- What beach?
- Santa Cruz.
Josh, Kitty and the girls
are gonna be there.
What are you doing?
It's a magic trick.
I left it here last year.
Okay. Let's see it.
This thing's kind of bullshit.
Hey. What, are we cursing
at the table now?
When you point a finger
at someone else,
you have three pointing
back at you.
What is that supposed to mean?
It's four fingers
pointing back at you.
What are you talking...?
Look. See?
One's a thumb,
and it's not pointing at you.
So, what is it?
I think she has
post-traumatic stress disorder.
She wasn't in 'Nam.
Okay? She got lost.
For 15 minutes. That's...
That can be very scary.
No, you don't know
what happened to her.
Anything could've
happened to her.
Okay, so... so how-how do we
get her to talk?
Look, I think
we need to encourage her
to draw, to write, to dance.
Anything to help her
tell us her story.
I just want
my little girl back.
It's gonna be okay.
- Um...
- I'm sorry.
- Is...
- I'm... I'm gonna...
I need to have a smoke.
I don't get
why we have a summer home
by the beach
and don't go to the beach.
What about the beach
right here?
- What beach?
- There's a beach right there.
That is not a beach.
That is a bay.
That is a shore.
I'm talking about a real beach,
with people and sand,
amusement park.
There's, like...
It's crowded there.
- Oh, come...
- And, like, there's weirdos
at that beach and...
I-I'm not going to that beach.
- We're not going.
- Okay.
I guess I'll just cancel, then.
Okay.
It just sucks, is all.
I mean...
I know Jason really was
looking forward to it.
This is the first summer
we've been back here
since Grandma died.
I know it's been
pretty hard on him.
We leave before dark.
Yeah.
Yes. Yes.
It's gonna be great.
- And you're gonna enjoy it.
- Mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm.
Are you really not
gonna kiss me?
Mm-mm.
You're not gonna kiss me?
Hmm? Mm...
Where's your brother?
Your brother... where is he?
I don't know.
Really?
Jason?
Baby, that's why
you can't play in here.
- Didn't this happen last year?
- Zora, please.
Yeah!
That's right.
What do you think?!
Daddy is home, baby!
Craw Daddy!
- He's kidding, right?
- He is not kidding.
Got a cassette player
and everything.
Leather seats!
Glove compartment!
- Wow.
- That's right.
It's even got
one of these, baby!
Oh, I got it, I got it.
Guy taught me how to do this.
It veers a little to the left,
so you got to hold on to it.
Least I got it really cheap.
- Will we all fit, though?
- You know what?
Y'all are spoiled.
Spoiled.
Did you know that there's
fluoride in the water
that the government uses
to control our minds?
I forgot. Nobody cares about
the end of the world.
Maybe you could just tell us
what's supposed to happen,
and then we can picture it.
Maybe you can
kiss my anus, Zora.
- Ew!
- Whoa, whoa! - What?
"Anus" isn't a cuss word.
Why are we even talking
about anuses?
- Why would you say that?
- I would have
actually preferred you use
a curse word in this case.
Mom, I can see you laughing.
- I am not laughing.
- Where'd you even learn that?
Okay, we don't always
have to be talking.
♪ I got more growing pains
than Maggie ♪
♪ 'Cause homeys nag me to take
the dank out of the baggie ♪
- ♪ I got five on it ♪
- ♪ Five on it ♪
- ♪ Got it good ♪
- ♪ Grab your 4-0... ♪
That's a classic right there.
- ♪ I got five on it ♪
- ♪ Five on it ♪
♪ Messin' with that
Indo weed... ♪
What does
"I got five on it" mean?
- It's about drugs.
- It's not about drugs.
It's a dope song.
Don't do drugs.
- Jason, come on.
- Hmm?
Get in rhythm.
♪ Don't need no crutch,
I'm so keyed up... ♪
There you go. There you go.
♪ Next time I'll roll it
in a Hampa to burn slow ♪
♪ So the ashes won't be
burning up my hand, brah ♪
♪ Hoochies can hit ♪
♪ But they know
they got to pitch in ♪
♪ Then I roll a joint that's
longer than your extension ♪
♪ 'Cause I'll be damned if
you get high off me for free ♪
♪ Hell no... ♪
Oh, yeah.
Welcome to Santa Cruz.
♪ 'Cause you know
you got asthma ♪
- ♪ Crack a 40 open, homey, and guzzle it ♪
- Huh?
♪ 'Cause I know the weed in
my system is gettin' lonely ♪
♪ I gotta take a whiz test to my P.O. ♪
♪ I know I failed 'cause I done
smoked major weed, bro... ♪
Santa Cruz!
- Santa Cruz!
- Okay, we get it!
Santa Cruz! Santa Cruz!
Santa Cruz!
- She did...
- Five minutes.
- You can't even talk.
- Look, I don't want to
- talk about who can't talk.
- Russ...
- What's gonna happen?
- If something happened to her...
What's gonna happen,
okay? She left!
Oh, my God.
- Don't look. Don't look.
- Is he dead?
You got to be kidding me.
- Hey.
- Hey! What's up? - Hey.
Thought you guys said 2:30.
Where's the efficiency, man?
- Us Wilsons, you know, we take our time.
- Hey.
- Hey. Look at you.
- Oh, my God, look at you.
- Yes.
- Welcome to paradise.
- Of course, man. - Hey.
- You look so pretty!
- Hi. How are you?
- Thank you.
Oh, the girls are gonna be
so happy to see you.
Uh, what do you want?
I can get some beer for you.
- Becca! Lindsey! Look who's here!
- No.
- No?
- The answer is no.
- Please.
- He's old enough.
- In a couple more years.
- Don't hawk her.
- All right, all right.
- Hi.
- No shit. You got the boat?
- Yep, I got the boat.
- Good for you, dude.
- Boom.
That's fucking awesome.
What'd you get?
- A dinghy? You get, like...
- Oh, shut up.
You got to make sure
you have the essentials.
- You got the life preservers?
- Got that.
- You got a fire extinguisher?
Do you have a flare gun?
I knew you'd fucking forget the flare gun.
We got to get out there
and do a double excursion.
We're right across the bay
from you guys, for fuck's sake.
Sure you don't want
anything to drink?
- No, I'm good. Thanks.
- This rosé is delicious.
Mm-hmm. I'm sure, yeah.
Did you guys have
a good summer so far?
Yeah, it's been great.
No, a little bit small,
but a classic design, you know?
You good?
Yeah.
What?
I have a hard time just...
you know, talking.
Oh, I get that.
Yeah, no, I totally get that.
You guys, uh, want something?
Got a full bar here.
No. All good. Water.
You want thirds, huh?
- Thank you.
- Okay.
I'm gonna get my wife
her medicine.
That's beautiful, isn't it?
Here you go.
- Just... - Mm, yeah.
- Ah, ah.
What do we say?
I hate you?
- That works.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Good.
Never stops.
I think about
murdering him sometimes.
- So nothing's changed, huh?
- Nope.
Oh, actually,
a little something has changed.
Oh, my God.
Did you get something done?
Just, like, an itsy-bitsy,
little... a little thing.
- Oh, fuck off.
- Yeah.
Well, you look just like
you did last year.
Aw, thank you.
I mean, that's the idea,
you know.
- Just, like, a little bit can go a long way.
- Mm.
Not that you need
anything, whore.
- Oh, man.
- Oops.
What was it?
Just a stupid tunnel.
That's all.
Ugh.
Beach toys are such baby shit.
Your brother's so weird.
He just has
a hard time focusing.
Are you going in the water?
- No.
- Why not?
Yeah, why not?
- Hey, where are you going?
- To the bathroom.
Why don't you pee in the ocean?
Jinx. Double jinx.
Triple jinx. Blackout.
- Shut up.
- You shut up.
Do you ever wish
you kept dancing?
Sometimes, yeah.
'Cause you were, like,
you were really good, right?
Yeah, well...
I peaked at 14.
Oh, I mean, didn't we all?
I think I could have been
a movie star
if the girls hadn't been born
at exactly the wrong time.
I went to Stella Adler,
and I booked two commercials
before I met Josh.
It's just, I stopped auditioning
when I got pregnant.
Then the move to San Francisco
was a career killer, and...
I was supposed to keep flying
back to L.A.
It's just...
Jesus. Watch it.
Ugh. That's crazy.
Been having so many
crazy coincidences lately.
Yeah, that's what he said.
- Anyways, we should go back to our place.
- Sure.
- I think it's vodka o'clock.
- Oh, yeah. Definitely.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Okay, good. Let's pack up.
Okay.
Where's Jason?
Mm...
Jason. Where's Jason?
Gabe.
Where's Jason?
Jason?
- Jason?
- Jason!
- Where were you?
- I was in the bath...
No! You don't do that.
You don't run off
without telling me.
- Ow.
- I'm sorry.
Okay, okay, okay,
okay, we're good.
- We're good. All right.
- You don't do that to me.
- Understand?
- Sorry.
I'm gonna get ready to go.
- Okay?
- I think we're gonna head out.
- Yeah.
- Okay?
- No worries.
- Yeah, we're...
The Houston
Astros were essentially short
one everyday player
heading into the season.
No incumbent...
You saw their new car, right?
He had to do it.
He just had to get that thing
to fuck with me, too.
I guess mission accomplished.
Don't run inside.
Way to freak Mom out.
And here's something you don't
see every day:
extra innings in Minnesota.
I'm gonna go say good night.
11-11,
tied in the seventh inning.
Yeah, you see, Hollister, known
for his late-inning fastball,
comes in at a cool...
You good?
I'm just gonna watch
the Giants highlights, okay?
I'll see you later
in the magic room.
Night-night.
- Good night.
- Phone off.
Mask off.
You thought I was dead?
Um, no. Uh, I just...
I just didn't know
if you were lost or...
taken or...
By terrorists and perverts?
Stick with me,
and I'll keep you safe, okay?
Look.
11:11.
Bedtime.
Who's this?
You know, I was thinking about
getting some fishing gear
tomorrow.
Four rods, we can all
go fish off the dock.
You know?
Of course,
there's the boat, too.
I'm just saying, if we could
get out there in open water...
I'm not trying to force anyone.
Hey.
Gabe, I want to go.
Where you trying to go?
I can't be here. I...
It's too much.
You serious?
Being here, it, um...
Hmm.
It feels like...
there's this, um...
...black cloud
just hanging over me,
and, uh...
I don't feel like myself.
I think you look like yourself.
Okay. Yeah.
When I was a kid,
I went to that boardwalk
with my parents.
I wandered off.
I don't know why. I just did.
I ended up
in that hall of mirrors.
There was another girl
in there.
She looked like me.
Exactly like me.
But you were in
the hall of mirrors...
She wasn't a reflection.
She was real.
She...
I ran as fast as I could.
My whole life, I've...
I've felt like
she's still coming for me.
Okay, well, whatever happened,
happened a-a long time ago,
right?
You know how sometimes
things line up?
- Yeah.
- You know, like coincidences.
Since we've been here,
they've been happening
more and more.
I think...
I feel like it means,
like, she's getting closer.
Who? The mirror girl?
You don't believe me.
I-I... I-I do.
I do.
I'm-I'm processing. Okay?
I just...
can't believe you kept
all this inside for so long.
Come on.
You know I'm here, right?
I'm pretty sure
I could kick your ass,
so if she looks like you,
then...
Okay. Bad joke.
All right.
I'm sorry. My bad.
I'm just trying
to lighten the mood.
Oh, shit.
We lost power.
Perfect timing.
See, this is why Josh has
a backup generator.
God! Hell!
Jesus!
Okay, we lost power.
Go back to bed.
There's a family
in our driveway.
What? There is not a family
Huh. Who is that?
Uh-uh.
Oh, it is a family.
What, y'all scared of a family?
A bogeyman's family.
Okay, all right.
Enough... enough of that.
No. Uh-uh.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
- Uh-uh.
What?
Zora, give me your phone.
- I'm not on it.
- Zora!
Sorry.
Is there someone outside?
It's just a family
standing outside.
It's probably the neighbors.
You're kidding me, right?
- Hello.
- I'm scared.
My name is Adelaide Wilson.
Are you seriously
calling 911 right now?
We're at 2311 Seagull Way. Shh!
Everything's good.
We lost power.
There are four trespassers
on our property.
- All right, sure, okay.
- Yes.
- You know what?
- What?
- I'm gonna fix this.
- No, we don't.
- I'm gonna find out who they are...
- What?
No, they haven't,
but I know they will.
...find out what they want,
and everything's gonna be fine.
- Gabe.
- Calm down, okay?
15 minutes?
No, no, no, that's too long.
Oh, boy.
No, you don't,
you don't understand. We...
How about we all just try
to keep calm...
- Gabe. - Dad.
- ...keep our heads,
and everything's gonna
be all right.
No, no. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Just one sec... Gabe.
Trying to have a vacation,
and my whole family lost
they goddamn minds.
Hi.
Can I help you?
Okay.
If y'all are out here
trying to scare people,
I think you picked
the wrong house for that.
Zora...
put your shoes on.
I... I asked you nice.
Now I need y'all
to get off my property.
Okay.
Okay, let's call the cops.
I did.
They're 14 minutes away.
What? 14 minutes?
Okay, okay, okay,
okay, okay, okay.
Okay, okay.
- Jason, give me the bat.
- What bat?
The baseball bat. The bat.
- There's one in the cl...
- Here, here.
- Thank you.
- Gabe?
All right, hold on.
I got this.
Let's try this again.
- Gabe?
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
All right.
- Gabe!
- I got this. I got this.
Now, I thought
I already done told y'all
to get off my property.
Okay? So, if y'all want to
get crazy, we can get crazy.
Now, the cops are
already on they way.
Hey. Hey, hey, hey!
Hey!
Oh!
Sh...
They're going around.
Is the back door locked?
- My window's open.
- Gabe... Zora, no!
Gabe, Jason!
Yo, I'm serious, man!
I will break your head!
If I were you...
Gabe.
- The key.
- What key?
- The damn hide-a-key.
- Hide-a-key?
What kind of white shit...?
Oh, shit.
- Mom?
- Just stay close.
What's going on?
What?
It's us.
We don't have anything here.
This is our summer home.
- Gabe.
- We just got in today, so...
Once...
upon...
...a t-ime...
...there was a girl.
And the girl had...
a sh-adow.
The two were connected,
tethered together.
When the girl ate,
her food was given to her
warm and tasty.
But when the shadow was hungry,
she had to eat rabbit,
raw and bloody.
On Christmas,
the girl received
wonderful toys,
soft and cushy.
But the shadow's toys
were so sharp and cold,
they'd slice
through her fingers
when she tried
to play with them.
The girl met a handsome prince
and fell in love,
but the shadow,
at that same time,
met Abraham.
It didn't matter
if she loved him or not.
He was tethered to
the girl's prince, after all.
Then the girl had
her first child,
a beautiful baby girl.
But the shadow,
she gave birth
to a little monster.
Umbrae was born laughing.
The girl had a second child,
a boy this time.
They had to cut her open
and take him from her belly.
The shadow had to do it all...
herself.
She named him Pluto.
He was born to love fire.
So, you see,
the shadow hated the girl
so much for so long,
until one day
the shadow realized
she was being tested by God.
Excuse me.
What do you want?
You could have my wallet.
You-you could have the car.
Gabe.
Yeah.
You can have the boat,
for all I care.
Nobody wants the boat, Dad.
How about this?
You take me to the ATM...
What are you people?
We're Americans.
Tether yourself to the table.
Addy, don't do it.
Maybe I should cut...
something off of you.
It's... it's okay.
Just...
Don't hurt my children.
Yo.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Get your hands off me.
- No. Gabe, no.
- No, wait, no. Dad!
Wait. Wait.
Get off me, man.
Look, Gabe...
Wait. Gabe.
Oh, please,
please, please stop!
- Stop, please!
- Gabe.
Stop, stop. Wait. Wait.
Wai... Please!
Okay. Okay.
- Mom.
- Little girl.
Run!
Go.
You want me, right?
No.
- He's not going.
- Careful.
He has a t-emper.
No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, not that shit.
No. No.
Okay.
- I'm scared.
- Look...
Look at me.
You're gonna be okay.
Show him one of your tricks.
Okay.
Go play, boys.
Don't burn our house down.
Stop, man.
Please stop.
No, no, stop, stop, stop.
Please.
Come on, man, stop.
Stop it.
I got a family, man.
Please don't. No.
What the fuck?
Get off my car!
Are you...?
Come here. Come...
Goddamn it,
get your ass over here.
I said, "Come here."
Kid, I'm talking to you.
What do you want?
What?
What do we want?
We want...
to take our t-ime.
We've been waiting for this day
for so long.
I call it...
"The Untethering."
That's yours.
It hangs to the left.
It hangs to the goddamn left.
Jason.
Baby.
Come on. Come on.
Let's go.
Keys.
- Mom! Mom!
- Zora!
This way. Come on!
Come on, come on!
Go, go, go!
Hey!
Come on.
Come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on.
Oh. Let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go, let's go!
- Josh? What was that?
- What?
I heard something outside.
Okay.
A rustling.
Walking, like a person.
There's a person walking around
outside our fucking house.
It's probably a squirrel.
I don't know.
Would you please get up
and look?
I'm busy.
I'm... I'm busy.
So...
Maybe it's a-a pizza guy.
Maybe the girls ordered pizza.
Get up and take a look.
I'm scared.
Oh, I don't want to.
I want to stay down here.
I want to just stay
in my cozy spot.
- Get up and look.
- Jesus Christ.
Hey, uh, Ophelia, lights up.
Turning lights up.
I feel like I heard the
backup generator go on, too.
What do you know
about the backup generator?
Can you stop being
an asshole for two seconds?
- Just look.
- All right. I'm looking.
I'll get my binoculars.
I see nothing.
I see beautiful stars.
Are you really looking?
Yeah, I'm looking.
Oh, shit.
No, yeah, I...
- There's something out there.
- Don't fuck with me, Josh.
I'm not fucking with you.
I'm serious.
There's something out there.
Look.
Look behind the car.
- Where? I don't see it.
- It's by the car.
- Look.
- I can't...
- Oh, shit.
- What?
Oh, my God, it's O.J.
It's O.J. Simpson.
What is wrong with you?
Seriously.
Ophelia,
give me some Beach Boys.
Playing "Good Vibrations"
- by the Beach Boys.
- Really? - Why not?
It's our last night here.
- Let's have a little party.
- Ophelia, turn it down.
Turning down "Good
Vibrations" by the Beach Boys.
Would you chill out, all right?
There's nobody out there.
Just go back upstairs.
I'll be up in a few minutes.
Everything's gonna be fine.
What's going on?
Uh, nothing.
- Nothing, guys.
- Jesus.
The backup generator went on.
We're just trying
to figure it out.
- Go back to sleep.
- Just because we're in our rooms
doesn't mean we're sleeping.
Fine. I don't know.
Go back to your rooms.
Guys, we have to be out of here
at 10:00 a.m. tomorrow,
sharp, so...
- Hello?
- Oh, my God.
Josh!
Please stop.
Stopping "Good
Vibrations" by the Beach Boys.
Ophelia...
Ophelia, call the police.
Sure.
Playing "Fuck tha Police"
by N.W.A.
Josh, we need your help.
Addy!
No!
No! No! No! No!
Go, go, go, go, go, go. Run.
Come here!
Huh? Follow me!
Yeah.
Let's go, Bad Josh!
Let's go!
Hey!
No! No! No!
Come on!
Goddamn it.
No, no, no, no. Please.
No, no. No.
No! No, no.
No, Zora. No!
Please, please.
No! No!
No, please, no!
No, no, no.
It was unlocked.
Boats are done.
I am done with boats.
I can't believe they're dead.
Why are they doing this?
I'm sorry,
but all of our operators
are busy at the moment.
Please hold, and the next
available operator will...
It's all just craziness.
I'm sorry,
but all of our operators
are busy at the moment.
Please...
How does 911 keep you on hold
all night long?
I just don't get it.
It's too many twins, man.
How many of everybody
is there gonna be?
The boardwalk
was getting ready to close,
and a bunch of us
had just gotten out,
and we were going to our cars
when the attack happened.
- Oh, shit.
- People were shouting, and...
- Don't curse.
- ...I-I just thought it was
somebody acting out,
and then we just saw red.
- Uh, you saw red?
- Yes, they were wearing red.
They didn't look right.
They had scissors,
and they were just walking up
to people in the crowd
and stabbing them.
You said
they were stabbing people?
Yeah, it was chaos,
and then we-we just
started running.
Where-where did they come from?
What? I-I-I don't know.
Someone said that they were
coming from the sewers.
The sewers?
Okay, how many are...
I'm sorry.
I think they're coming.
Uh, uh, ma'am?
Ma'am?
Um, okay, uh, so we certainly
hope everything is okay there.
It's too early to say
what exactly is unfolding,
but it does appear
we are in the midst
of a brutal
and terrifying attack
by people who are being
described as wearing red,
carrying scissors or shears,
and doing
what can only be described
as wreaking havoc on folks
- just out for a Friday night.
- And they look like us.
They don't even know that yet.
Okay, Chris,
I'm gonna cut you off.
- Okay.
- We have new images coming in here.
Here, we see a man
wearing red who...
Okay, this...
this seems to be
a group of individuals
engaged in some sort
of demonstration or protest.
It-it's not clear at this time
if or how
these people are connected
to the attacks.
- What is that?
- They are forming what looks
- like a human chain.
- That's them.
What are they doing?
I don't know,
but that would take
a shitload of coordination.
So, obviously,
if you have children present
watching us right now,
you should turn them away.
We aren't sure
what is about to happen.
- We have to go.
- What? You're joking, right?
Zora, Jason, help your father.
Wait, she's trippin'.
Where would we go?
- The police, right?
- No.
We need to move
and keep moving.
We take the coast.
- We go to Mexico.
- Mexico?
Okay. Whoa.
Whoa. Whoa!
We got everything we need here.
Food, water, backup generator.
We're as safe here
as we're gonna be anywhere.
Tell that to Josh and Kitty.
They're right here.
- You're scaring the kids.
- Too late.
They think like us.
They know where we are.
They won't stop until
they kill us or we kill them.
Then let's make
some traps or something.
Like, some Home Alone
type stuff.
That way, if she comes...
Tell me you did not
just reference Home Alone.
- You know what I'm talking about.
- Gabe.
They've been planning this.
They have the upper hand.
This is the time to run,
not to be sprinkling
Micro Machines on the floor.
What are Micro Machines?
What's Home Alone?
We're not going anywhere,
and that's final.
You don't get to make
the decisions anymore!
So...
does this mean
we get their car?
Come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on.
Who's got the keys?
Come on.
- Let's go.
- Get in the car.
Get in the car.
- I'm driving.
- No way.
I told her no.
Dad's leg is messed up.
You're handcuffed.
It's not safe.
I'm driving.
Zora, no.
I have the highest kill count
in the family.
You don't have
the highest kill count.
I killed both twins.
Wrong.
I just killed the second one.
I killed Kitty.
So that's one, one,
one and two. I killed two.
I killed myself and Josh, so...
Zo... It doesn't matter.
Zora, get in the back.
- Look! - No.
- Oh, shit, put the windows up.
Put the windows up.
Okay.
You're gonna want to...
back up.
- Buckle up.
- Huh?
- Zora!
- Whoa...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Where is she? Did I get her?
She's there, she's there!
Jesus!
Okay.
Zora.
Be careful.
Okay, you're going too fast!
She's dead now, right?
- What are you doing?
- Mom.
Where's she going?
Wait... And she left.
Your mom left the car.
Shh, shh.
Shh.
Whoa.
Is that our car?
It's the one
that looks like me.
Shit.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What, what?
Stay in the car.
Lock the doors.
What is she doing?
It's a trap.
Get out.
Please.
No.
Jason. Jason!
Jason?
Jason!
No! No!
- Addy!
- Mom!
Here.
- We can hide here.
- Okay.
- They probably got bandages and stuff.
Mom knows what to do.
Look.
It's the line.
Looks like some kind
of fucked-up performance art.
Where is he?
How it must have been
to grow up with the sky.
To feel the sun,
the wind, the trees.
But your people
took it for granted.
We're human, too, you know.
Eyes, teeth,
hands, blood.
Exactly like you.
And yet...
it was humans
that built this place.
I believe they figured out
how to make a copy of the body
but not the soul.
The soul remains one,
shared by two.
They created the T-ethered
so they could use them
to control the ones above.
Like puppets.
But they failed, and they
ab-andoned the Tethered.
For generations, the Tethered
continued without direction.
They all went mad down here.
And then... there was us.
Put some heat on that one.
Yeah, I guess
I missed my chance to go pro.
You remember?
We were born special.
- I want number 11.
- Yeah?
Addy, you want to try it?
God brought us tog-ether
that night.
I never st-op thinking
about you.
How things could have been.
How you could have
taken me with you.
Years after we met...
...the miracle happened.
That's when I saw God,
and he showed me my path.
You felt it, too.
The end of our dance,
the Tethered saw
that I was different.
That I would deliver them
from this misery.
I found my faith,
and I began to prepare.
It took years to plan.
Everything had to be perfect.
I didn't just need to kill you.
I needed to m-ake a statement
that the whole world would see.
It's our time now.
Our t-ime up there.
And to think,
if it weren't for you...
...I never would have
danced at all.
My baby. My baby.
I found you.
Oh!
Look.
Look, look, look.
They're all gone now.
Okay?
They can't hurt you.
You understand?
Uh-uh.
No.
Everything's gonna be
like it was before.
Yeah.
She wasn't in 'Nam.
Okay? She got lost.
For 15 minutes. That's...
That can be very scary.
No, you don't know
what happened to her.
- Anything could've happened to her.
- Okay, okay.
So how-how...
how do we get her to talk?
Encourage her to draw,
to write, to dance.
Anything to help her
tell us her story.
I just want
my little girl back.
Okay? She left.
- She...
- I told you to look after her.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Look at you.
- It's not my fault she left.
It's not my fault
she... Yeah, well, look at me.
Look at you. Look at you!
Subtitles by explosiveskull