Subtitles by explosiveskull
There's a great
spiritual awakening in America.
A renewal of
the traditional values
that have been the bedrock
of America's goodness
and greatness.
An overwhelming majority
of Americans
disapprove of pornography,
abor...
Knock, knock.
You scared the hell out of me.
- Knock, knock.
- Who's there?
Erik Estrada.
Erik Estrada who?
Erik Estrada from "CHiPs."
What are you drawing?
Uh, it's kind of like,
um, jungle temple.
Oh, that's... that's...
I mean, that's...
Wow.
How was your day?
It was pretty cool.
I was reading that book
about the galaxy.
That big, thick one?
Yeah.
It's pretty awesome.
What's your favorite planet?
Jupiter.
Yeah, no doubt.
How come?
Mm...
Well, because the surface
of its atmosphere
is a storm that's been raging
for, like, 1,000 years,
and the eye of the hurricane
is so huge
that it could just
swallow the whole Earth.
Yeah. That's...
That's my favorite planet.
- That's wild.
- Mm-hmm.
What's yours?
Um...
Saturn, probably.
Yeah?
Saturn's pretty cool,
and that was one of the first
ones that we discovered,
that humans discovered,
so there's, like,
a lot of cool ancient myths
about it and stuff.
I changed my mind.
What?
I like Galactus.
Galactus isn't a planet.
Yeah, but he eats planets.
Woof. Woof, woof, woof.
Hey.
Are you awake?
Yeah, baby.
What is it?
You were having a bad dream.
Uh-huh.
What was it about?
I can't remember.
Sometimes I wonder if we should
move away from this place.
Where?
I don't know.
No.
I like it here.
It's peaceful here, right?
This is, like, our little...
This is our little home.
Did I ever tell you
about the starlings
when I was a little kid?
No. I don't think so.
In the neighborhood
where I grew up,
there were all these starlings
flying around in the trees,
playing and chirping,
and they were so cute.
But my dad...
...he just hated them
'cause they were always eating
cherries from the cherry tree.
Anyway, one day...
One day, me and a bunch of the
other kids from the neighborhood
were playing in this empty lot.
And my dad came walking across
with a pillowcase...
...and a crowbar.
And there was something moving
around inside of the pillowcase,
like, squirming around.
And he said we should
gather 'round.
He had something to show us,
and so we all gathered 'round,
and he emptied what was in
the pillowcase on the ground.
And it was a...
It was a bunch
of baby starlings.
And he told us that he was gonna
show us how to kill them.
And he lifted
the crowbar up real high...
...and then...
...brought it down real hard
on the little baby bird.
So hard that it pushed it
in the ground.
It was so deep in there,
like a little grave, you know?
And then he gave the crowbar
to one of the kids, and then...
each kid took a turn in...
killing a starling.
What'd you do?
I, um...
...just watched, and then when
it was my turn, I just ran away.
Oh, baby.
Come here.
"Under the crimson,
primordial sky...
...surrounded by
the jagged rocks
of the ancient
volcanic mountain,
the wretched Warlock
reached into the dark embrace
of the fissure
until his hand touched
a smooth glassy surface.
Cold as ice.
His fist closed around
The Serpent's Eye.
Slowly he withdrew it
and held it before him
in the fading light
of the blood-red suns.
It glowed from within.
A ghostly emerald light.
Strange and eternal."
What's the matter, Jeremiah?
Are you all right?
No.
I'm not all right.
Did I do something wrong?
Wrong?
Everything you do is wrong.
I'm so sorry, Jeremiah.
Is there anything I can do
to make you feel better?
There is nothing you can do.
It's her.
I feel naked without her.
Naked.
Do you hear me?
I-I...
I said, "Do you hear me?"
Yes, Jeremiah.
I hear you.
"Yes, Jeremiah.
I hear you."
Really?
Because, sometimes, I don't
think you hear anything at all.
And I am truly
worried about that.
If you are not with me,
you will not ascend.
- Jeremiah, I...
- Please...
just be quiet
and go fetch me Brother Swan.
Okay.
I said,
"Go fetch me Brother Swan."
There you are.
What can I do for you, Jeremiah?
I need you to get me
that girl I saw.
I need her.
I need her now.
Jeremiah, consider it done.
Do you have the Horn of Abraxas?
Do you know what to do?
I do.
Hey.
Why don't we offer up
the porker, too?
Just to seal the deal.
That is such a good idea.
That lard-ass, he couldn't
find his nose in a mirror.
I knew I could count on you.
I can always count on you.
Buddy.
Oh, thank you, Jeremiah.
Thank you.
Before you go...
...send in Sister Lucy.
Of course.
That's a cool T-shirt.
Oh, thanks.
What you reading?
A novel.
Oh.
How do you like it?
Yeah, I think it's
Lenora Tor's best book.
Hmm.
I guess you live around here.
Yeah. We live just down
near Crystal Lake.
Oh, that sounds lovely.
It's 5 bucks.
Oh, yeah.
Well...
See you later.
Are you sure
this is the right place?
Yes. Of course I am.
What now?
Now we wait.
How long?
Shh.
Listen.
Blood for blood.
More.
First things first.
Aah!
Aaaah!
Jerry? Jesus Christ.
- What the hell is that?
- I don't know.
Oh!
Don't worry.
Those scary men are gone now.
They got what they came for,
and they're gone.
I guess you're wondering
where your hubby is.
Don't you worry.
He's just fine.
And he'll stay that way
as long as you're a good girl
and do as you're told.
Do you understand me?
You know, he thinks
you're so special,
and I hope you realize
what that means.
The responsibility
is on you, buster.
Open.
Very good.
Hold still.
I like to call that
the cherry on top.
It's all but a beautiful dream.
A dream he's having right now.
Won't you join us in that dream?
I'm sorry for all
this fuss and muss.
But when I saw you
on the road the other day...
...you called out to me...
...silently.
And I listened.
Look at me.
Look at me!
Tell me.
What do you see?
I see the reaper
fast approaching.
Well, I recognized you,
so I think in time...
...you will recognize me.
You know,
all he wants is for his children
to love one another.
Now, I find that he allows me
to express that love
in many ways,
but one of those ways...
...is music.
Do you like the Carpenters?
I think that
they're sensational,
but this is even better.
What do you think?
Shh. Shh. Wait.
It's about to start.
♪ Every seed
that gives us life ♪
♪ Every man must take a wife ♪
♪ Only one sun ever shines ♪
♪ Only one sun, yours and mine ♪
♪ Jeremiah Sand was a righteous
man whose heart... ♪
You know, I was ready
to stand tall
with the great,
grand glittery ones,
but those scumbags
couldn't recognize
a golden, radiant light
even as it was cast
right down upon them.
But thankfully...
Thankfully,
he showed me another path.
The path I have always
been truly destined for,
something far greater
than mere fame or fortune.
♪ ...lessons well ♪
♪ The light shines
through everything ♪
♪ The light is true,
the lessons learned ♪
♪ His song of you and me ♪
When I was at the bottom
of the pit...
...screaming in the darkness...
...racked with
unspeakable pain...
...for having been denied
all that was rightfully mine...
...he graced me with his light.
His hot loving light.
It flowed over me like
the pulse of a timeless wave.
A wave of pure heat.
A mainline of pure
and total acceptance.
And he talked to me.
Addressed me as a friend.
He said, "Jeremiah,
they were wrong.
And you are right.
So right."
And he blessed me
with his holy kiss.
He said, "You are not separate
from all that is.
So all that is...
...is yours."
And he gave me his deepest
and warmest permission
to go out into this world
and take what is
so very much mine.
All of it.
Mine.
My wants.
My needs.
My pleasures.
You know...
...I've been blessed to know
the comfort of many women.
But there are few
that have had your radiance.
You're a special one, Mandy.
I, too, am a special one.
Let us be so very special
together.
Be gentle...
...like me.
They...
You made this song?
Yes.
I did.
And it's about you?
Yes.
It is.
Shut up!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Shut up! Shut up!
Shut up!
Don't you fucking look at me!
Don't look at me!
Tell me what to do.
Please tell me what to do.
Come on.
Tell me what to do.
Tell me. Tell me.
Don't ever doubt yourself.
You and that ugly little whore.
You think you're so in love?
I'll show you love.
Lucy.
Kneel.
Now show him
how much you love me.
No.
Another pearl wasted
before swine.
Yeah.
Take a good look, you worthless
piece of human excrement.
This is the tainted blade
of the pale knight,
straight from the abyssal layer.
Poor, stupid pigs.
Born without souls.
You know what Jesus'
big mistake was? Huh?
He didn't offer up
a sacrifice in his stead.
The cruciform is a constant
reminder of that.
Now, we wasted the chemist's
finest on your whore.
But I think that you both
shall see the cleansing
power of fire...
...cannot be reasoned with.
The darker the whore,
the brighter the flame.
Who ate all
the macaroni and cheese?
Cheddar Goblin, did you eat
all the macaroni and cheese?
Nothing's better than cheddar.
Cheddar Goblin.
Cheddar Goblin by Duvane
has 60% more cheese
than the next leading brand.
Kids and goblins agree,
Cheddar Goblin tastes the best.
That's why Cheddar Goblin
was rated number one
three years in a row.
Cheddar Goblin by Duvane.
It's gobblin' good.
Cheddar Goblin.
This is a test.
This station
is conducting a test
of the Emergency
Broadcasting System.
This is only a test.
Can't you read?
Oh, it's you.
It's been a while.
Come for the Reaper.
Perfect condition,
just like you left it.
I'll get out of your hair.
So what you going to do
with that thing?
I'm going hunting.
If you're gonna go hunting,
I got some other shit
you might need.
I was hoping you'd say that.
One to the right.
Made it myself.
It cut through bone
like a fat kid through cake.
They're yours
under one condition.
Oh, yeah?
What's that?
You put them to good use.
So what you hunting?
Jesus freaks.
I didn't know they
were in season, man.
Yeah. Well...
- Just tell me, man.
- They lit her on fire!
They were weirdo hippie types.
Whole bunch of them.
And there was a muscle.
It didn't make any sense.
They were bikers
and gnarly psychos and...
Crazy evil.
Black Skulls.
Lookit, man.
For a while now, word's been
coming down from the big rigs
something dark
and fearsome out there.
No one knows where
they come from.
First, it was stories
from the interstate.
Leaving truckers for dead,
prostitutes vanishing,
and gutted bodies on doorsteps.
And always the same.
Biker gang, black bikes.
Only seen at night.
Weird shit.
There's stories that
there was a chapter
than ran courier
for a manufacturer of LSD.
Took a disliking to them and
cooked them up a special batch,
and they have never been
right in the head since.
I seen them once
from a distance.
What you're hunting
is rabid animals,
and you should go in knowing
that your odds ain't that good,
and you will probably die.
Don't be negative.
Last I heard on the CB,
they were spotted down
near Spirit River.
When I seen them things,
they were in a world of pain.
But you know what
the freakiest part was?
What's that?
They fucking loved it.
Aah!
Ah!
That was my favorite shirt.
You have a death wish.
I-I don't want...
I don't want to talk about that.
You're a vicious snowflake.
Ah!
Aah!
You ripped my shirt!
Ah!
She's still burning.
Aah!
She burns.
It's cool, man.
Jovan warrior sent forth
from the eye of the storm.
Mm.
That's Lizzie.
When she's calm,
I know it's good.
You're right.
Oh...
God.
You're right.
Bye, Lizzie.
Oh, man.
They wronged you.
Why they got to be like that?
You exude a cosmic darkness.
Can you see that?
Okay.
The children.
North.
This is really not ideal.
You're hurting me!
She... She burned
brightly, Mandy.
Don't you think?
Still, better to burn out
than fade...
Ah!
Jeremiah says...
...I'm the most sensual lover
he's ever experienced...
...because of my sensitivity...
...and my empathy.
I can anticipate
my lover's every move.
I meet them.
Like warm waves...
...licking...
the rocky...
hard shore.
Come no closer.
God is in this room.
Aah!
Oh.
Hi.
You can't harm me, man.
I mean, look at
what he provides.
It's all mine.
You're just meat.
Without a soul.
Without a brain.
Without anything.
Animal.
You...
You have no spirit everlasting.
No...
No radiant light.
I possess hallucinations
you will never know.
The psychotic drones.
Where the mystic swims.
You're drowning.
I'm swimming.
You unholy abomination.
You aren't even worth my spit.
It's all that hate
in your heart.
That's to blame.
Follows you everywhere, man.
Follows you everywhere.
I can still help you.
It's not just your life
I can save, no.
It's your goddamn soul.
No, no, no, no!
Please, please.
Please don't hurt me!
Shh!
Can't you see this was
all part of your journey,
the journey that led you to me?
To your salvation.
To your cleansing by my hand.
I'll blow you, man.
I'll suck your fucking dick!
Is that what you want?
Oh, please, please, please!
Please don't do it.
No, no!
I don't kneel before you!
You kneel before me!
I carry God's gift
in my heart, not you,
so you kneel before me,
motherfucker!
I'm your god now.
Aah!
Subtitles by explosiveskull