Subtitles by explosiveskull
I love it when you wear blue.
I mean,
I love you in anything.
But you wore blue
that first time I saw you,
so anytime
I see you in blue,
it reminds me of how I felt
at that moment.
How I never really knew what
being alive was until I saw you.
You unlocked something
inside me that day,
something I didn't
even realize was there.
And right then,
I knew that nothing in my life
was ever going to be the same.
In that moment,
I was transformed permanently.
You did that.
My job is to access and interpret
data to produce analytical results.
I did that job.
Taking your frustration out on
me will not alter the results.
You're quite within your rights to
take your business to another bank.
Another analyst may interpret
the data more to your liking.
But they'd be doing a bad job.
Good morning.
What?
Nothing.
Jill, what?
I... just hope he likes vinegar
more than he likes honey.
She.
Oh.
Well, then...
- Hey.
- Hi.
Have a seat.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
So...
that report...
That report
is faultless.
You are every bit as good
as I hoped you'd be.
I appreciate that.
You're going to do
really well here.
- I'm certainly gonna try.
- Good.
Good, good, good.
So, the ABA conference
is the last week of September.
Two nights at the Hyatt
Regency in New Orleans.
And... we should go.
You should... go.
I think I'd need
a little more experience.
Well, I could
help you with that.
- I should get back to work.
- Good.
Good, good, good, good,
good, good, good.
Of my new friends, I'd say, um,
Jill's probably the closest.
We go out after work
almost every night.
- How's your boss?
- He's great. I mean...
He has really high standards
and he's really demanding,
but when he says you got something
right, you know you got it right,
which is really rewarding, especially
since it's so competitive here.
I suppose that explains why you're
eating your lunch in such a rush.
Hey, at least it's green.
But I kind of do
have to get going.
I just wanted to let you know everything's
great. I couldn't be happier.
Yeah. Now that you're
450 miles away from me
and everyone else
you've ever known.
Mmm. Don't do that.
It was a fantastic opportunity.
I couldn't say no.
And besides, you know
what an impulsive girl I am.
Anyway, I gotta go.
Okay?
I love you. Bye!
Ooh. Look at that.
Can I talk to you?
Hey.
Yeah, that's me.
Down and... Mm-hmm.
Ah.
- Sawyer Valentini.
- Mm-hmm.
What a name.
Sawyer Valentini.
- It's a sexy-ass name.
- Thanks.
I'm named after my grandfather
on my mother's side.
He died of eye cancer.
Oh, shit. I'm sorry.
I didn't...
Your little face.
- That was you being funny?
- Hey, if we can't laugh at cancer, who are we?
Oh. That's dark.
Hail Satan.
- Promise me one thing, Jesse.
- It's Mark.
Yeah. Tonight's going to go
how you want it to go.
It's not even a question.
But afterwards, you don't call
me, you don't contact me.
It's like we never met.
You good with that?
Yeah.
Jesse's so good with that.
So,
this is my apartment.
Yeah. And, um,
this is my, um, room.
- Fuck! Fuck!
- What the fuck?
Oh, my God.
I-I thought that's what you said
you wanted. You initiated it.
Oh, fuck.
No.
Your life slips
away from you, you know?
Changing your phone number
and your e-mail becomes normal.
Changing your lunch hour
every day becomes normal.
Second-guessing
every single thing you say
in case it might
be misinterpreted?
Normal.
Taking out a restraining order.
Relocating to another city.
Normal.
But you still see
your stalker everywhere?
Well, rationally, I know
that this is my neuroses
colluding with my imagination
to manifest my worst fears.
I know that.
But I'm not rational.
I'm alone in a strange city,
and, uh, I never feel safe.
Not for one minute.
So what do I do?
Where do I go?
Or maybe I just surrender
and accept that this is my life.
That doesn't sound
like much of a life.
No. Not one that I want
to keep on living.
Do you often have thoughts
like that, Sawyer?
Thoughts like, um...?
Not wanting to keep living.
- Like suicide?
- Yes.
Do you ever think
about taking your own life?
I have, in the past.
And did you ever give a thought
as to how you'd do it?
Do you know
the therapeutic index?
It's, um...
It's the ratio that measures
the blood concentration
of if a drug is toxic
or when it's effective.
The larger the therapeutic
index, the safer the drug.
The smaller, the more dangerous.
That's how I'd see myself
spending my final hours.
Testing drugs.
That's pretty specific.
Yeah, well, my dad always said why would
you trust someone to do a big job
if they can't do a small one?
There's some more forms
you need to fill out.
- Just routine.
- That's it? I'm cured?
Well, we can discuss
treatment options
when you finish
the paperwork.
Well, I'd really like to book
another appointment with you.
You're a really good listener.
I'm obviously the first person
to tell you that.
Do I need to read
every comma and semicolon?
It's up to you.
Like I said, it's a boilerplate.
Privacy disclosures,
liability, that kind of thing.
I finished my homework.
If the counselor has a half hour
for me sometime next week...
Please have a seat,
Ms. Valentini.
Someone will be with you
shortly to discuss next steps.
No, we just discussed
the next step, so...
It should just
take a minute.
Okay.
- Sawyer Valentini?
- Yeah.
I'm Dennis.
Please follow me.
Wh... Look, I don't have
a lot of time.
I should be back
at work, so...
- What am I doing here?
- I need to look through your bag.
Why?
Don't worry. You're not
being singled out.
I look through everyone's bag.
It's procedure.
Uh, excuse me.
That's my stuff.
Good afternoon.
I'm Nurse Boles.
Can you strip down
to your underwear for me?
Please. Take off your clothes
down to your underwear.
And remove
all your jewelry.
Do you understand?
If you need help
removing your clothes...
- What?
- To check for identifying marks.
Scars,
birthmarks, moles.
It's to protect you, the other
patients, and the hospital.
Look, I'm not sure what's
happening here. I, uh...
The nursing assessment includes
a head-to-toe skin examination.
It's a hospital-wide
policy.
There's nothing invasive
about it.
Look, I have to go. I'm gonna
be late for work, so...
- The door's locked.
- For your privacy.
I need you to take off your
clothes down to your underwear
and remove
all your jewelry.
There's nothing wrong with me.
I just needed to talk to someone,
and the counselor said that I...
Did she tell you to do this?
Miss Valentini, are you
refusing to cooperate?
What happens if I do?
It would be better for everyone,
but especially yourself,
if you'd just do as I ask.
Turn around.
Lift your arms.
That's all.
Put this on.
Can I go now? I've done
everything that you asked.
You're upset.
Take these.
- Then I get to go?
- You'll feel better.
Follow me.
There's been
some kind of mistake.
Your name
is Sawyer Valentini.
You know that already.
By signing this, you've consented to
voluntary commitment for 24 hours.
No. The counselor said
the forms were routine.
You signed it.
Look...
you're just
doing your job.
And you've been so considerate of
my feelings and my well-being.
And you're right.
I signed those papers.
I'm here by my own volition.
It's for my own good.
Can I ask, do you think
I could just make a phone call,
just to let my family know
that I'm okay,
let them know
where I am?
You get a phone call.
That's allowed.
You're so nice.
You're saying you want
your phone call now?
Yes. Yes, that is
what I'm saying.
Oh, my God. It's like
you read my mind.
Yes, hi.
My name is Sawyer Valentini.
I am at Highland Creek
Behavioral Health Facility.
I am being held here
against my will.
Please send help.
Thank you.
I'll be out of here
in, like, 20 minutes.
Do you know how many calls the
cops get like that every week?
Those are from crazy people.
Let's go back
to the ward.
No, I'm not going anywhere
until the cops show up.
Can...
Can you stop taking notes?
I have rights.
Don't make me ask again.
Hi. Alison.
How's your baby?
Alison. The baby.
Hey!
Fuck!
Oh, what?
You think you're too good
to talk to me now, Alison?
Oh, my name's not Alison, but, yeah,
yeah, I am too good to talk to you.
Hey, bitch!
Listen, when you fall asleep,
I'm gonna cut your hair off.
All of your hair.
- Oh, yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
With what?
They let you anywhere near sharp objects?
I doubt that very much.
Oh, God. You're scaring me to
death, you fucking mental patient.
I'll be thinking about you
when I'm back in my own bed
in my own house, getting ready
to go to my own job.
Calling her a mental patient
isn't helpful.
We need to support each other.
Yeah, well, support me by not
talking to me or looking at me.
I shouldn't even be in here.
Yeah, so, uh...
So you got put in here
by mistake, I'm guessing.
Yeah. Yeah. That's right.
And the cops are on their way
right now to get me out.
The cops are on their way
to take you out of here?
Really?
- They said that?
- Yeah.
In those words,
specifically, to you?
Liar, liar.
Oh.
- Oh, man.
- Evening, Dolores.
Hi, Steve. How you doing...
Steve's partner?
Another
night, another 10-75.
Yeah, second floor
called down.
I've got her
admission form here.
You got any coffee, Dolores?
It's in the break room,
Steve. Help yourself.
Steve's partner
can't have any.
What's your favorite coffee,
Dolores?
Mmm. Expresso.
- Expresso?
- Expresso.
- Ex-presso.
Why don't you get one of those
new Nespresso machines?
I like that.
I like black coffee, little bit of cream.
You like cream?
- No. I like just sugar. Lots of sugar.
- Hmm.
- Lots of sugar?
- Uh-huh.
I gotta do Splenda.
I love coffee. You know what?
Your coffee? Sucks.
- But you're still mad I won't let you have any.
- I could get some if I wanted to.
We both know that.
Have a good night, Steve.
Not Steve's partner.
Wake up.
Wake up!
...like you.
It was like a paid intern.
Let her do all the stuff around
your house, kick around some shit.
- Yeah, why not?
- Really?
- I've done that. I've adopted them.
I'm like Drake.
- Yeah.
- What does Drake do?
He adopts strippers.
He adopts them?
Puts them in little homes,
in their own communities.
Must feel good to be back in
your own bed, in your own house,
getting ready to go back
to your own job.
Hi.
I'm Jacob.
Move.
Oh!
Let me out!
There's been
some kind of mistake.
Look...
I'm not supposed
to be in here.
I'm locked up in here with fucking psycho rapists!
Fuck.
The cops are on their way, and I
need to get out of here right now!
Fucking bitch!
No. I...
- Dennis!
- Yes?
What the fuck was that?
We don't hit them back. She does
that again, she goes downstairs.
No, I don't want...
Aaah!
Alison pissed the bed,
y'all.
- Good morning.
Hi, Sawyer. Just coffee?
Nothing to eat?
Good summation.
How was your night?
Are you settling in okay?
I'm not settling in anywhere.
I'm going home today.
Dr. Hawthorne asked me to bring you
to have a talk with him about that.
Finally.
A real doctor.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
All good points.
Really, good points.
Absolutely.
Tell Diane
we're on the same page
and that
it won't happen again.
Really.
This is a good thing.
To be continued.
Okay.
Bye.
Sorry.
Dr. Hawthorne.
Uh, you can see
I don't belong here.
You know there's been
some kind of mistake.
I can't spend
another day here.
I can't spend another minute.
I have a job.
I have a life.
Yes. Uh, well, we want you to
get back to enjoying that life.
Really.
That's our goal.
Good. So what can I do to give you
one less patient to worry about?
Well, it says here that
you've been assessed
as a danger to yourself
and to others.
So that means
more observation.
Doctor, look at me.
Look at me.
Doctor, I have a wonderful
support system around me.
I have family,
I have friends, coworkers.
I have neighbors.
The best thing for me is to be
surrounded by the people I love.
Now, did I indicate
to the counselor
that I sometimes,
occasionally, feel down?
Sure, I did.
But everybody does.
I'm building a new life
for myself, Doctor.
I'm meeting new people.
I run.
I'm going to adopt
a rescue dog.
That's what's
gonna help me.
Not being stuck in here.
Give my bed to someone
who needs it.
Doctor.
Uh, yeah.
But you see, um,
it says here that you
assaulted a staff member.
He looked like
someone I knew.
Yes, but it says here
that you attacked him.
I... No.
I was under a lot of stress.
The police
were supposed to come.
And it says here that you
assaulted a male patient, Jacob.
No. He...
Look, I had a rough night.
But look at me now.
Right.
So, because of the
multiple acts of violence,
we're looking
at another seven days.
What? Seven days?
I need to take this.
Uh... to be continued.
Yeah, hello, Diane.
How are you?
Okay, Hayley.
I'll take it from here.
First thing we do in these meetings is
go over the Highland Creek rules book.
Maximum use of a public
phone is ten minutes.
No smuggling food or drink
into the ward.
Uh, no touching
the other patients.
Masturbating in
their hair is fine.
That word?
That got you. Okay.
We use these meetings
to go over our daily goals.
Mmm. My goal today is to be
friendly and helpful to everyone.
What do you say?
Hmm.
Okay. Excuse me, y'all,
for one second.
Maybe I need to make
my consultations one-on-one.
What about you?
What are your daily goals?
Finding someone to believe
I don't belong in here.
Oh.
You're no different
from anybody else in here.
- You gave them an in.
- What are you talking about?
Not now. Later. Okay?
Okay.
They brought up suicide.
You bit.
That's all they need.
They've got beds.
You've got insurance.
But I'm fine. I just needed
to talk to somebody.
Yeah, that's why Highland Creek
and all the other Highland Creeks
and Tumbling Pines
and Cedar Valleys
under the ADS Health
Enterprises umbrella exist.
You talk, they find a way to
keep you and get you admitted.
And you stay locked up
until Aetna,
Blue Cross, Medicaid
or whoever insures you
will pay.
Soon as the money runs out,
you're cured.
- But that's...
- Business.
Business.
Highland Creek is just like any
other business in America.
They got a number
to hit every month.
They need to admit as many patients
to fill those beds to get that money.
You know,
the law of averages
suggests that a percentage of the
patients admitted to Highland Creek
are in actual need
of psychiatric care.
It also suggests
that a higher percentage...
Are just like me.
- They're locking up sane people for profit.
- Yeah.
I'm here for seven days because
my insurance company approved it.
Boom.
It's not that bad.
I mean, it's inhuman, but compared
to where you could have landed?
Tumbling Pines streams
meth addict cage matches.
This place has got Hayley,
plus some less qualified
and motivated employees.
There's really
no comparison.
And if you hook up
with the right people,
you don't gotta worry
about weed, booze, porn,
or whatever you use to make life
seem less of a crushing void.
I, myself, am in the throes
of kicking an opioid addiction,
so keep that shit
away from me.
Final words:
Do your time.
Keep your head down.
God, you're talking to me
like we're in prison.
You're welcome.
Don't cause any scenes.
Don't make any enemies.
Find a community, learn how
to live with the routine.
It'll be over
before you know it.
You've got any questions,
come find me.
Mm-hmm.
Ah.
Oh.
No.
No way.
You can't be
anywhere near me.
This won't work.
The Boston cops have got a
record of the restraining order.
I hope following me all
the way here was worth it
because you're going
to jail.
- Move, Alison.
- No...
George Shaw? Is that what
you're calling yourself?
This man
is called David Strine.
And he's been following me
and calling me and texting me
and showing up at my job and
breaking into my fucking house.
Take
your meds and move on.
No. I'm not going anywhere until
the cops haul his ass into jail.
George, did you do or say
anything to provoke the patient?
Stop calling him that.
His name is David.
He's followed me all the
way here from Boston.
I've never
even been to Boston,
though I am a Sox fan.
You're a fucking liar!
I want my phone.
I've saved all the text
messages you sent me,
all the really,
really sick ones.
Do you remember, David?
All the ones where you said you'd kill
yourself if you couldn't have me.
- You're crazy.
- Maybe I should go back to the other ward.
I'm not doing
any good here.
No one is fucking
buying this, Strine.
- It's George.
- No, I get it.
It's not hard to get a job here. You don't need
qualifications. You don't need fucking training.
I want my fucking phone call! I'm calling
the cops, and I want him arrested.
Your phone privileges
have been suspended.
No! I don't want to...
I don't want to be
in here with you!
I fucking hate you!
No, I'm telling you the
truth, I swear to God.
Get your hands off me!
He's lying.
Fucking lying!
Oh, Jesus.
You're hurting my arm!
Fuck off! No.
Get on that side.
Fuck you.
It's like you didn't listen
to a word I said.
You keep this up, and you'll be spending the
rest of your time down in the basement.
You said you wanted to help
me, so help me out of this.
Good night.
Uh...
Yeah. Yeah, this story's gonna
be like the biggest story ever.
Yeah, I've got evidence.
I got everything I need.
Finally just going
to shut it down.
Yeah, man. Yeah.
Let me call you back.
I don't know. She's,
like, a little tricky.
Sometimes she responds to me,
sometimes she doesn't.
- Yeah.
- You know.
Hi.
- What?
- Give it back, thief.
You took my last pack of cigarettes.
Where'd you put 'em?
- Hide 'em in your snatch?
- I was in fucking restraints, you idiot!
Oh! Fuck me!
Oh, well done,
Violet.
Sawyer,
based on what it says here,
you are one incident away
from being sent to the basement.
Look, I was sexually assaulted.
Where's the outrage?
Where's my advocate?
Who do I report this to?
And what's in the basement?
- What's in the basement?
- Solitary confinement.
Oh, my God. Send me there
right fucking now.
My stalker... You've read
the counselor's notes.
You know who I'm talking about.
He's here.
He's got himself a job
in the fucking hospital.
I talked to the second floor
about George.
No, he's not called George.
We did a thorough
background check.
Yeah, you did a thorough
background check on George.
I'm telling you, he isn't called George.
His name is David Strine.
I'm trying to tell... You're not even listening
to me. I'm trying to tell you the man...
And I'm adding a course of risperidone
and lithium to your meds.
What's that for?
To keep you
from hurting anyone else.
And yourself.
Are you serious?
That's your diagnosis?
You're sedating me
when I've just told you
there's a predator who's followed
me here from another city.
You should be protecting me.
What medication are you on?
That's funny.
Yes.
Well... to be continued.
Hi. I'm Jacob.
Sawyer.
Listen, I... I just want
to apologize, again,
if I said or did anything
to upset you.
I see the doctor's put a little
something extra in there.
I really hope it helps.
I hope someone cuts your balls off
and stuffs them down your throat.
What? Are you
fucking touching me?
You motherfucker!
It's him!
It's him! I'm telling
you, it's Strine!
- No, no, no, listen!
- Calm down.
He's been to my mom's house. He's been to
my fucking mom's house and stolen our mail!
I'm not fucking crazy! No!
Fuck you! No.
Ow!
Let me use it.
I... Excuse me?
Your cell phone.
I saw you.
I know you have one.
That's a major infraction
of the rules.
But guess what? I don't care,
as long as I get to use it.
Otherwise, I tell everyone.
Yeah. Your credibility
is sky high around here.
You really want
to take that chance?
You call the cops again,
they'll do nothing... again
but take my cell phone.
I'm not calling the cops.
I promise.
Hmm.
And I'll suck your dick.
Five minutes.
Don't get caught.
- Hello.
- Oh, Mom, it's me.
Sawyer, where've you been? It's been,
like, three days since you've called.
- Yeah, Mom...
- I expected to see your face on a milk carton.
Mom, I'm in a bit of trouble.
- How much do you need?
- No, no, no. It's not that, Mom.
I haven't got a lot of time.
I need you to listen.
Just don't panic.
But I've been involuntarily committed
to a facility called Highland Creek
here in Pennsylvania.
They said I was suicidal, but
I swear to God, Mom, I'm not.
It's just an insurance scam.
But listen.
There's this guy I never told
you about when I was in Boston.
- There was this guy who...
- Shh.
There was this guy...
He was kind of stalking me.
What do you mean,
kind of stalking you?
Mom, he got himself a job. He got
himself a job at the facility.
He's there,
in the hospital with you?
- Yeah.
- Have you told the doctors?
- Have they called the police?
- Mom, no one fucking believes me.
Sorry. I'm... I'm...
I'm... They drug me
and they tie me to a bed.
And I'm here for seven days,
and no one's helping me.
Oh, my God! Sawyer!
You know I'd never bother you with
this if I could find a way out,
but I need help.
What's the name
of that hospital?
Uh, Highland Creek.
It's, um...
It's off Highway 90. I don't know the
exact address. Mom, I've gotta go.
I love you.
Rain check
on the blow job?
I wish I could go one
day without hearing that.
I want to see my daughter!
Get her out here now!
I'm not leaving, and I'm
only going to get louder,
so you probably
should do something!
She didn't know
what she was signing.
I want her released immediately.
She's coming home with me.
Mrs. Valentini,
I understand your concern,
but right now this is
the best place for Sawyer.
Stuck in a hospital with her
stalker is the best place for her?
Repeat that.
I think you need to talk
to Administration.
Highland Creek is a very ethical
organization, Mrs. Valentini.
The decision regarding
Sawyer's admission
was made by an attending
psychiatrist
in consultation with members
of our clinical treatment team.
Are you going
to release her?
Sawyer is absolutely free
to leave
once we're convinced that she no longer
poses a clear threat to herself and others.
She doesn't.
You only made her
think she does
so you could describe her as
suicidal on your insurance claim.
Let's focus
on the positive work
we do here at Highland Creek.
I have letters and e-mails
and phone messages,
all attesting to the ways we've
turned patients' lives around.
I'd be happy
to share some with you.
- I'm calling a lawyer.
- You're quite within your rights.
As am I
to contact our team.
But...
is that really
in Sawyer's best interests?
No, seriously.
I'm concerned that coming off
as frivolously litigious
might adversely affect Sawyer's
current employment situation.
She hasn't been
in that job for long.
And it might make potential
future employers apprehensive.
Are we willing to risk
your daughter's future?
Can I at least see her?
I mean, if I could just see for
myself that she's all right.
This place does have
visiting hours, doesn't it?
Could I at least
have one visit?
Of course.
You've arrived just
at the end of visiting hours,
but I can give you
20 minutes.
So this is what it takes to get
you to call and ask for help.
I'm sorry, Mom.
- You don't have to apologize.
- Yes, I do.
I should have told you
about all this.
Should have told you about
Strine, the real reason I moved.
Is he here now? 'Cause I'll
haul him out of here myself.
No. He works
the night shift.
No visitors at night.
Stalker logic.
I'm getting you out.
That idiot doctor and that bitch
of an administrator can't stop me.
I'll go to the police,
to the FBI.
I'll hire the most expensive
lawyer in the world.
Whatever it takes, you're
coming home with me.
Now, how are you
otherwise?
You look tired.
I'd love to just be tired.
Mom, I'm scared.
What else
can I do for you?
What's with these clothes?
Unacceptable.
They're probably not
even laundered properly.
I'll bring you some of mine.
I always pack too much.
Hey. Listen to me.
I am getting you out.
You are coming back home.
And this man, this stalker
is done harassing you.
I just need one thing
from you, Sawyer.
This.
You and me talking.
Tell me the truth.
No more walls. You've been
building walls since...
Dad. Yeah.
Yeah, that was hard,
but, uh, this is different, Mom.
I promise.
You're a tough kid.
You always have been.
But... I'm your mother.
Let me help you.
So, how do I
reach you in here?
Well, my phone privileges
have been suspended,
but that guy's phone
I called you from... Nate?
Call him, and he'll find me.
Or I'll catch up with you.
Where are you staying?
I'm at the Lux Star Inn down
the road just two minutes.
I will mobilize
the troops
and I'll be back in a couple
of hours with fresh clothes
and an army
of cops and lawyers.
Hang in there,
sweetheart.
Cavalry's coming.
I understand,
Mrs. Valentini.
But there's nothing we can do unless you
have proof that a crime's been committed.
I'm sorry.
Pennsylvania state law
mandates that a patient can only be held
on involuntary commitment for
seven days without a court order.
And, look, they're not going to go to
the hassle of getting a court order
after her insurance
stops paying.
Is it inconvenient?
Sure.
Should something be done to
stop it happening? Absolutely.
As your lawyer, is it my priority
getting Sawyer back into your care?
It's number one.
Keep me in the loop
about the situation.
If you think there's legal cause to
intercede, I'll get right on it.
Hello?
Did you just hang up on me?
Okay, everybody.
Turn around.
- What are you doing here?
- Hello, Sawyer.
Just picking up
an extra shift.
Nice to see you all
during the daytime.
Violet.
Crayons. Crayons.
Where the fuck...?
Where the fuck are the crayons?
The fuck...
Where's... Where...?
Where are the fucking...?
Where?
Where did you fucking
put them?
Where did you put them?
Where did you fucking put them?
Where the fuck...
Get out!
Fuck!
Where the fuck...
Where the fuck?
Fuck you! Fuck you!
Fuck you! Fuck!
Sawyer. Sawyer.
Sawyer,
you need to calm down.
Calm down, Sawyer.
Calm down. Calm down.
No.
Maintenance!
What the fuck?
I didn't call maintenance.
W-We're checking
all the AC units, ma'am.
Uh, there was a critical fault
in the wiring in one
of the other rooms.
Nearly started
an electrical fire.
Just to be safe.
Thank you.
This will just take a minute.
We had an issue
with the Valentini girl.
She got a megadose of
methylphenidate this morning
instead of her
risperidone and lithium.
My Lord.
I'm still not sure
how it happened.
Everybody's
so overworked around here.
I'm sure an oversight is bound
to happen every now and again.
- Is she okay?
- Better now.
But it can't
happen again.
Double-check the meds against Dr. Hawthorne's
list for each and every patient.
Of course. Understood.
Something like this happens again,
we could all lose our jobs.
Nurse,
I won't let you down.
This... This job
means the world to me.
I know. Your work
ethic is unreal.
You're here day and night.
We could use more like you.
You're a gift from God,
George.
Yeah. Just trying to make sure all these
folks get the help that they deserve.
Hey.
So, uh...
I think
you broke the TV.
No.
God, I didn't mean to.
I love TV.
- I must be insane.
- Oh, no, no.
You're not insane.
I know the difference between
people who are supposed to be here
and the people
that end up here,
and you're definitely
in column two.
Oh.
Oh, I feel like
I belong in column one.
Ohh. What?
Come on.
You didn't think so
yesterday, so, uh,
what changed?
What did you want to be
when you were a kid?
- Me?
- Mm.
Shit!
I wanted to be
an astronaut.
Yep.
But, uh, I found out
that, you know,
you had to deal with all
these numbers and shit,
and, uh,
I'm trash at math, so...
Didn't work out.
- There's still time.
- Yeah. Sure there is.
Go to University of Phoenix, right? Maybe I'll do that.
What about you?
- It's too late for me.
- Nah.
I was going to be
this renegade medical student
who was able to
pinpoint diseases
that all the old traditional
surgeons couldn't see.
- Oh, okay.
- Mm.
It's a nice fantasy,
but I had no follow-through.
I-I had... I mean,
I had the ambition,
but I didn't have the drive
or the dedication to make it.
- Oh.
- I couldn't even make it through pre-med.
- Mmm.
- I had to switch majors when I was a junior.
But I still wanted
to do something, you know,
so I volunteered
at a hospice.
- Uh, well?
- Mmm.
That's where
I met David Strine.
"Most companies settle
with the government,
but several area cases involving
more than two dozen power plants
in the South and Midwest
are still pending.
Remaining suits demand fines
for the past..."
He was nice, you know?
Quiet, uncomfortable.
And I felt bad.
I mean, how do you
spend two hours a week
talking to your father
who doesn't even recognize you?
My father died when I was 15.
- Respiratory failure.
- I'm sorry.
No one saw it coming.
So while I was fantasizing
about being the savior
who would pull his father
back to clarity...
David was having
his own fantasies.
He would want us
to be together.
Okay, let's
talk about Sawyer Valentini
in Boston, year zero.
Um, obviously I would recommend sensors
on all your doors and windows.
I would swap the terrace doors
out for a steel-core door.
Um, update your dead bolts.
Uh, I want to talk to you about
situational awareness, okay?
Where's the nearest
police station?
fire station?
These are things that should always
be right on the tip of your tongue.
Yeah, parking...
Um, I know you have parking
in the rear of the building
with the back entrance.
I'm gonna ask you
not to use that anymore.
I know it's convenient,
but I would advocate selling your
car and using a ride service.
If you can't or won't do that, uh,
I would say park on the street,
preferably
under a light source.
And come back and walk through this
courtyard here where people can see you.
With your keys
in your hand, by the way.
You want your keys
always in your hand.
You don't want to be digging around in
your purse in the dark for your keys.
Um, and I'll talk to you about
and help you with a go-bag.
You know, just cash, credit
cards, uh, change of clothes,
flashlight, charger,
that kind of thing.
A firearm,
if you're open to that idea
of purchasing or registering a
firearm and learning how to use it.
Think about altering
your routine.
Uh, when you go to work, when you
leave work, um, that kind of thing.
How about social media? Are you
on any social media accounts?
Uh, I'm on Facebook,
but my account's private, so...
Right. Okay, that's no good,
because he'd be able
to, you know, figure out a friend
of yours from marching band
or a sorority sister
and go get photos from them,
create a bogus account and then
try to friend you that way.
Your friends know your e-mail.
Just... That's enough.
Just delete the Facebook
today.
Um, and then talk
to your friends, you know.
Be open about this. Inform them what's
going on. Tell them not to mention you.
Don't tag you on Instagram.
You know, uh, um...
You know, baby showers or, you know,
Chardonnay date with the girls.
You know, whatever it is, if
there's someone taking a picture,
you do whatever you can
to get out of it, all right?
And think of your cell phone
as your enemy.
And this: your new best friend.
And now he's here.
Or maybe it's all in my head.
Hey, come here.
Come here.
- Hey.
- Hmm?
Column two.
For life.
Give me some. Give me some now.
Come on.
- Ahh, hey!
- Hey.
You've been to the hood
a couple times, huh?
Sawyer.
I'm sorry you've had
such a rough day.
- Sweet dreams.
- Drop dead.
I need to use your phone.
- Now!
- God, hey!
- Shh, shh, shh, shh.
- I need to use it now.
Okay.
Geez, just keep
your voice down.
- Everyone's fucking asleep.
- What?
Hi, can I have
Angela Valentini's room, please?
Yep.
Mom, hi, it's me.
I left a message on your cell.
Can-Can you just give me
a ring back as soon as possible?
Thanks.
Thank you.
Hey.
Man, I don't even know
if she's telling the truth or not.
I mean, some days she's normal, but
other days it's, like, I don't know.
Maybe I just been in here
too long.
Forget all that. Look, I need you
to check on something for me.
And not because I like her.
Get any calls last night?
This morning?
No calls, no texts,
no voice mails.
Shit.
My mom didn't pick up
last night.
Not her cell,
not her motel room.
Moms call back.
That's what they do.
Yeah.
Hey. What's this, like,
day five in here for you?
- Mm-hmm.
- Well, focus on that.
You've done
most your time.
It's all downhill
from here.
Just keep your head down
for a few more days.
And you're free.
And I promise you,
on that date,
your mom will be standing
right there waiting for you.
Smiles!
- You're a good person.
- Ha!
I do a decent
impression of one.
Don't tell nobody,
all right?
How long have you got
left in here?
Well...
The opioid withdrawal program
is a four-week project.
I've done three weeks,
so, I got one week left.
So, uh, I get out
a few days after you.
- We should maybe...
- No!
- No?
- No.
- Okay.
- I don't know.
I mean, it's completely
different on the outside.
Plus, you'll have
your own phone.
My usefulness to you will
be dramatically reduced.
You've been a friend to me.
- And I'd like the opportunity to be one for you.
- Okay.
- If you let me.
- Yeah.
Once you're free, you might have a
completely different perspective.
And I don't blame you.
But should
that not happen...
maybe you'll let me
use your phone.
Maybe.
No hidden phones.
No personal relationships that can
impede upon another patient's recovery.
What's wrong with you, man?
What the fuck, man?
Ooh!
That's right, baby girl.
Your boo didn't show up to group.
Now he's blowing off lunch.
You think it's you?
You think
it's your personality?
Think it's your
little rat face?
Huh?
- Fuck you!
- Ow!
She had fucking
started it.
I don't feel safe
around her. No one does.
You don't know when she might snap.
She's fucking crazy!
I'm fine!
- I hate you!
- Well, I love you.
Your fucking face.
Oh, fuck! Oh, my God!
Look what he's done!
No, no, no!
She smuggled a phone.
That is not allowed.
- Look at the fucking phone!
- Get to bed!
Look what he's done!
I'm telling you... No, please!
- No, wait!
- Hold her down!
- No! Fuck you!
- Hold her down, guys.
Fuck you! No!
No!
Help!
A dead body
was discovered.
Oh, my God. What?
Nate Hoffman.
His body was found
in the old ECT room.
He OD'd.
Somehow got hold of
a shit-ton of fentanyl.
Poor guy.
He was doing so well.
Not a word of this
around the other patients.
And you hear anyone else talking
about it, you shut it down.
Of course.
I-I... I'm not gonna hurt you.
I'm not gonna touch you.
I don't want you
to feel uncomfortable.
I just want to be here
with you.
Oh, I disconnected them.
You going to kill me?
H-How could you even
ask me that?
I love you so much.
I mean, come on. You must
know that at this point.
From the moment we met,
I have loved you.
Did you kill Nate?
Nate... Nate chose
what happened to him.
Just like I choose
to protect you
from any and all threats
to your well-being.
My mom?
What did you do?
Angela is like family to me.
How did you get her ring?
She gave it to me.
No.
You're lying.
You're lying to my face
about my mother.
I told her about you.
I told her what you are.
She never would've...
She came all the way
from Boston for me.
So did I.
No, no.
She said she was coming back.
What did you do to her?
We-We-We talked.
Look, we shared
our feelings.
She-She told me
how her and your father met.
And then I told her
how you and I met.
And she said she wanted us
to have their ring.
Oh, my God. God.
Sawyer?
That ring can be as sacred
to you and me
as it was
to Angela and Mike.
Don't you fucking say his name!
Don't you ever say his name!
- Sawyer.
- Help me!
Help!
Fuck.
Sawyer.
Look.
I have this cabin in the
woods in New Hampshire,
in the White Mountains.
It-It's totally
off the grid.
It's got its own solar,
its own well. It's...
It's so beautiful.
Sawyer, we could be happy.
We will...
We will... We will...
We will be happy.
We will never be happy!
You could never
make me happy.
Look at where we are, David.
Look at what you've done.
There is no path
to happiness from here.
For either of us.
Sawyer, I've seen you.
I-I've watched you at work. I've
seen you with your friends.
Y-You're not happy.
Y-You just float through life,
and nothing ever touches you.
And you try... You try
really hard to fit in.
I've seen that.
But you can't.
You can't because...
there's a piece missing.
And you're what's missing?
Why not?
I fucking hate you is why.
And I love you so much.
You don't know
the first thing about me.
- How can you say that? We spent months together.
- No.
You were in the same room
while I talked to your father
because you had nothing
to say to him.
He didn't even know
I was there.
Yeah, well,
he was your father,
and you couldn't think of
two words to say to him.
You keep saying
that you love me,
but you're not capable
of loving anybody.
Not true.
Losing his mind was the best thing
that could have happened to him.
Do you think
he'd be proud of you?
How you've turned out?
- Stop it.
- What?
What? Too mean?
Not the girl you love?
- You don't fucking know me!
- I do!
Well, then love me
like this, David.
Love me like this.
Love me when I'm a bitch.
Love me when I cheat. Love me when I
shut down. Love all the shit about me.
That's not you.
That's what trying to make yourself like
everybody else in the world has done to you.
Really?
You're a fucking simpleton.
Do you know that?
- You are a fucking dunce.
- Sawyer.
That sweet,
kind girl in your head?
That's not me.
Can I ask you a question,
David?
Who did this to you?
Who rejected you?
Did she let you
down easy? Huh?
"I'm flattered, David, but I don't
want to ruin our friendship."
She ghost you? Hmm?
- She block your number?
- Stop.
She unfriend you
on Facebook?
Vanish from your life?
Or was it worse?
Did she look like she was
going to be sick? Hmm?
- Did she laugh in your face? Did she tell all her friends?
- It's not you.
No? 'Cause I'm telling you, David.
That's me.
That's what I would've done.
That's what I did.
That's who you love.
That's who you fucking dream of.
That's who you've been stalking
for the past two years!
Am I everything you'd
hoped I'd be, David? Hmm?
Is this what you imagine when you dream
of us living in your fucking cabin?
Two years!
- Two years, David.
- Shh!
- What a waste.
- You don't mean this.
What a fucking waste. You could've
met someone else in that time.
- You know? People are pretty pathetic.
- I love you.
Child-killers gets visits from
women who see the good in them.
Someone who loves a child-killer might
be able to see some good in you.
Because no one else fucking could.
No one else could, David.
No one else...
Do it. Fucking do it.
Now I see, David.
Now I see how you love me.
Check this out.
Our friend Nate
was taking notes.
All the shady stuff
that happens down here.
He's gonna need
a bigger notebook.
Second floor
should see this.
Um, you did the right thing
bringing this to me.
Good morning.
I...
I brought you
breakfast.
It's your favorite.
Two egg, bacon and cheese biscuit,
hash browns, large coffee.
You ate that at your desk
every morning.
You telling me that just killed
what little appetite I had.
Yeah.
Most important meal
of the day.
Thanks for this.
You're welcome.
I'm not used to people
being so considerate.
Most of the guys I know
would neither know nor remember
what I have for breakfast.
I know everything
about you.
I know your favorite book.
It's Pale Fire.
Your favorite song, "Walking
After Midnight" by Patsy Cline.
Yeah.
My dad used to play it
around the house.
I know you want to go
to Portugal.
You had your favorite vacation
there when you were 12.
Okay, enough.
Maybe you do know me.
You know you can't keep me
down here indefinitely.
People are going to be
looking for me.
My mom, my job.
You could call your mom
from the cabin.
You really want to go back
to that job?
How are we going to live,
David?
You secretly rich?
There's this old diner
that's for sale, by the cabin.
I was thinking
we could renovate it.
You've thought of everything.
I think of us
all the time.
How are you going to explain
my absence from the ward?
I already changed
the duration of your stay.
As far as
the administration knows,
they think your insurance already
ran out and that you're gone.
There's a back door...
leads out to the woods.
We could go right now.
What if I say no?
What if I say let me go...
and we'll start over.
We'll go out for drinks,
get to know each other.
I'd lose you.
You know that.
You'd go back
to your old life.
And I-I don't fit there.
I only belong with you.
I know it's a lot.
It's not that, Da...
It's not only that.
God, I don't know
how to say this.
W-What?
Sawyer,
you can say anything.
Have you ever...
Have you ever been
with anyone else?
Beyond your feelings for me,
have you ever...
had sex with anyone?
I'm not judging.
I'm not. It's just...
Fantasy and reality
are two different things.
I might not be
what you want.
You're all I've ever wanted.
You've got nothing
to compare me to.
That makes no sense.
I need you to see
what you've been missing,
and then decide
if you still want me.
David,
I might be your last,
but I can't be your first.
Uh, n-no.
No. No, sorry. No.
Well, you would
if you loved me.
You say all
the right things, David.
Or what you think
are the right things.
Greeting card clichs and romance
novel declarations of love.
But that's not love.
Love is giving yourself over
to what someone else wants
even if it goes against
everything you believe.
You say you love me.
Prove it.
How do I prove it?
You brought me down here.
Bring someone else down here.
Y-Y-You want me to...?
Fuck her in front of me.
I can't do that.
When you're thinking
about our future,
the one you've been planning
and imagining for so long...
it's really not that much
to ask.
J-Just... Just...
Just like
a random patient?
Violet.
Hmm?
Come on, wake up.
Come on.
What? Where am I?
You're coming with me.
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
- Where are we going?
- It'll just take a minute.
Come on. We gotta do
some paperwork.
Okay.
- What do you got?
- Have a look.
Prints from the John Doe
in the park.
George Shaw?
We're almost there.
Okay.
Ow!
What the fuck is that cunt
doing in here, huh?
Never mind me.
Act like I'm not here.
I'm impressed.
What's going on, huh?
Do it.
Show me.
Huh?
No, no.
No, no, no. No!
No! No, no, no!
David,
shut her up.
- Shut her up.
- No!
No, stop. Stop!
Violet, shh! Violet...
Hey, hey.
Hey. Violet.
We all get lonely,
Violet.
You push enough people away,
soon enough there's...
there's no one left.
I don't think you
wanted me to hate you.
Hmm?
I think you wanted me
to notice you.
Here I am, Violet.
Here I am.
David.
Come on!
Help!
No, Violet!
No fucking way!
- Move!
- Let me out!
No, no, no!
Hi, Mom.
We sent Nate
to follow up on rumors
that the hospital was committing
patients against their will.
I never thought this would be the
last story he ever wrote for us.
It's a really tragic incident, and I hope it
draws attention to a very important issue.
ADS Health Enterprises,
Highland Creek's parent company,
has issued a blanket denial of the
allegations made in Mr. Hoffman's story.
You're only delaying
the inevitable, Sawyer!
There's not a word
of truth in these allegations.
Highland Creek
and ADS Health Enterprises
pride themselves in
the care they take of patients.
To suggest otherwise is
outrageous and actionable.
Ladies and gentlemen, please.
Please direct any
further questions...
Miss Brighterhouse.
We have a warrant
to search the premises.
I'm proud of the work
we do here.
People leave Highland Creek
healthier than they come in.
No more running.
No more lying.
Ow!
You look so beautiful
right now.
Now I feel like I'm looking
at the real you.
That's the you that I saw
back at the hospice.
There's so many things
that I wanted to say to you,
all these things in my head.
But I-I froze up.
But now it's going to
be different...
'cause it's just you...
and me.
You'll learn to love me.
A year from now...
maybe... maybe two...
I was thinking that maybe we
could start a family of our own.
What do you think
about that?
A little girl with your eyes
and your smile.
Oh, that'd be perfect.
You'd make such
an amazing mother.
We are going to make sure,
from here on out...
Can I have the key
to that desk, please?
I can't believe we still have to
eat here after your big promotion.
I mean, you've got
an expense account.
Just live it up.
Jill.
I asked you here today
to tell you something serious.
The company wants to thank you
for all your hard work,
but, uh,
it's time to move on.
You need to
clear out your desk.
- You're so many assholes.
- Mm-hmm.
And you're paying
for lunch.
You love playing power games.
No. I just love
being the boss of you.
Jesus, be a bit
less obvious.
It's not just that she's
beautiful, it's that she's kind.
Even my father loves her,
and he doesn't like anyone.
She works at a bank
during the day,
but on the weekends
she volunteers at a hospice.
That's where I met her.
And, I don't know,
I just...
I feel like
she might be the one.
I can visualize myself
spending the rest of my life
with this girl.
Subtitles by explosiveskull