(grand orchestral
fanfare playing)
- (birds chirping)
- (indistinct shouting)
(bat strikes ball)
- (cheering)
- MAN: Come on!
You can do it!
Get in to second!
(indistinct chatter)
MAN: Come on, guys! You're
giving this game away!
Come on! Pick it up!
Come on, Finney. Come on.
BOY: Let's go. You got this.
(shoe digging in dirt)
- Play ball!
- You got this, Finney.
(indistinct chatter, whooping)
(Finney grunts)
UMPIRE: Strike!
Yes, Finney! Nice, Finney!
BOY: Let's go, Finney.
Two more strikes.
BOY: Swing, batter, batter.
Swing, batter, batter.
UMPIRE: Strike two!
- (laughter)
- BOY: Yeah!
(indistinct chatter, shouting)
MAN: Eyes open out
there. Eyes open.
(cheering)
Oh, no. Oh, no.
UMPIRE: Home run!
- (all sigh)
- (others cheering)
PLAYERS (chanting):
Bruce! Bruce! Bruce!
Bruce! Bruce!
Bruce! Bruce! Bruce! Bruce!
(cheering)
(players and coaches
repeatedly saying "good game")
BRUCE: Hey, dude.
Man, your arm is mint.
You almost had me.
- Good game.
(cheering)
("Free Ride" by The Edgar
Winter Group playing)
♪ The mountain is high,
the valley is low ♪
BOTH: Hi, Bruce.
♪ And you're confused
on which way to go ♪
♪ So I've come here
to give you a hand ♪
- (both laughing)
- ♪ And lead you into ♪
- ♪ The promised land, so ♪
- ♪ Ooh... ♪
♪ Come on and take a free ride ♪
♪ Free ride ♪
♪ Come on and sit
here by my side ♪
♪ Come on and take a free ride ♪
(explosive pop)
(laughs)
(song fades)
♪ ♪
(Finney slurps)
(slurps)
You think you can slurp
that a little louder?
I don't think they can
hear you up in Boulder.
(clatters)
(groans softly)
Sorry, Daddy.
GWEN: I don't know.
Everyone says Fonzie or Richie.
Millie says Potsie,
but I don't think anyone
should ever trust anyone
who wants to grow
up and marry Potsie.
I think I'll just stick
with my current plan
and marry Danny Bonaduce.
You're not gonna marry a
member of the Partridge Family.
He's so crucial.
I love his voice.
It's new.
What?
The flyer.
Mr. Yamada is putting
them up again.
You don't think they're
gonna find them, do you?
Not how they want to.
Come on. Let's go.
We're gonna be late.
- BOY: Come on!
- GIRL: Hey, come here!
KIDS (chanting): Fight!
Fight! Fight! Fight!
Fight! Fight!
MOOSE: You think
you're so tough, huh?
ROBIN: Let's find out.
I will pound you like a nail,
you scrawny little beaner.
- Then do it.
- (others chuckling, murmuring)
- Unless you're scared.
- (others exclaiming)
(excited chatter)
(grunting)
Get him, Robin!
(grunting, excited
chatter continue)
(grunting)
(onlookers groan)
(gasping, groaning)
(excited chatter)
Get up!
Hit him harder!
(excited chatter continues)
Come on.
Holy shit.
Let's go. Let's go.
(onlookers groaning)
What the hell?
- That was Moose.
- I don't care.
Moose is a giant asshole.
I know.
But last year, when he made
your nose bleed...-Gwen.
-He had it coming.
No one has that coming.
- Finney, he beat you up.
- I know, Gwen.
I was there, remember? I...
I just don't want
to talk about it.
Well, he was stupid to pick
a fight with Robin Arellano.
He's the toughest kid in school
since The Grabber got
Pinball Vance Hopper.
I wish you wouldn't
call him that.
Everyone called
him Pinball Vance.
No, I mean...
I know who you mean, jerk face.
Even the papers call
him The Grabber.
Just... I wish you
wouldn't say his name.
You don't actually believe
that story, do you?
- No.
- Because he can't hear you.
He doesn't really
take kids that say it.
- I know that.
- Finney.
- I said I know.
- Then say it.
(laughing): No.
Are you chicken?
I didn't mean it.
I know.
The inner core is solid.
The outer core is molten.
The next layer, called the
mantle, is mostly solid.
However, the thin outer
zone of the mantle
is partially molten.
Next slide.
The surface layer
is called the crust.
It is solid and very thin.
As the Earth
separated into layers,
it began to cool slowly,
but the interior
was still very hot.
(school bell ringing)
(students murmuring)
Hey, Finney.
GIRL: See you at lunch.
I'll save you a seat.
(indistinct chatter)
(door opens)
- MATTY: Hey, Finney.
- (door closes)
Come on out, dick weed.
Not fooling anyone, noid.
What you doing in
our bathroom? Huh?
See the sign? It says "boys."
Yeah, boys, not fags.
(door opens)
(door closes)
Dipshits, move.
Hey, Finn.
What's happening?
You know, just keeping
on keeping on, I guess.
Uh-huh.
Moose got some damn sharp teeth.
Knuckles bled all first period.
Wait.
Fuck with Finn again...
I fuck with you.
You can leave now.
(door opens)
(door closes)
Thank you.
You're gonna have to stand up
for yourself one of these days.
Yeah, I know.
Hey, why'd you fight Moose?
He was just shit-talking.
Pretty sure he'd back down.
- Nope.
- (both laugh)
I was so surprised when
he swung, to be honest.
I mean, did you have to?
Looked like you really hurt him.
I was just gonna
knock his ass down.
Whale on him a bit.
But that wouldn't draw no blood.
In a situation like that,
the more blood, the better.
For the crowd, you know?
It makes a stronger point.
I've seen Texas Chain Saw
Massacre Friday night.
- You seen it?
- That movie's rated R.
My dad would never
take me to see that.
My uncle takes me
to the drive-in.
We see everything.
But, man, that movie...
it's the best ever.
Better than Enter the Dragon?
- Well, okay. Maybe second best.
- (laughs)
You know, I want to see a
Bruce Lee movie one day.
Like, um, maybe if it
comes on TV, you know?
Yeah. Yeah, you will.
Hey, um, you got time to stop
by my house after school?
Is it math again?
Mr. Johnson talks too fast.
He doesn't explain it
right. Not like you.
Can you walk me through it?
If I get another
"F," I'm suspended.
Yeah, sure.
TEACHER: So, when we
subtract six from 11,
we find that the
value of "X" is five.
- (knocking)
- (door opens)
You wanted to see me?
Gwendolyn Blake, this is
Detective Wright and
Detective Miller.
Miss Blake.
They would like to talk
to you about something.
(Detective Wright sighs)
Is it... is it true you're
friends with Amy Yamada?
We have homeroom together.
Is she okay?
She's fine.
You know what this is about.
What did you say to Amy
about her brother Bruce?
Just that I had a
dream about him.
What kind of a dream?
Just a weird one.
What happened in your dream?
He was taken. That's all.
By a man with black
balloons in a van.
Yes.
WRIGHT: What else can you
tell us about your dream?
Why? It was just a dream.
MILLER: Who else
knows about the dream?
Nobody.
We found two black balloons
at the scene, Gwen.
Oh.
We also found one black
balloon at the scene
of Griffin Stagg's abduction.
And we never released
those details, so...
So the question is, where did
you hear about the balloons?
I didn't.
I'm gonna ask you again.
How did you know
about the balloons?
What aren't you
telling us, Gwen?
Either there's a leak in the
department, or...-Or what?
I'm The Grabber?
- WRIGHT: No.
You think I kidnapped
Vance Hopper last spring?
Is that it?
Vance got held back twice.
I've seen him
fight, and trust me,
he could kick the shit out
of either of you blindfolded.
Gwen, watch your language.
Yeah, I took him down 'cause
obviously I'm The Grabber,
you dumb fucking fart knockers.
Gwendolyn Blake!
Gwen.
What aren't you telling us?
That sometimes my
dreams are right.
There he is.
What was that?
(sighs) Nothing.
I'm staying over
at Susie's tonight.
It's Friday, so you
know what that means.
I'll look after Dad.
I'll be home in the morning.
And you better not
eat all the ice cream.
("Early Morning Blues"
by Blind Blake playing)
♪ Play that thing low
and lonesome, boy... ♪
(music stops)
(dramatic orchestral
music plays over TV)
(doorknob jiggling over TV)
(burbling)
(high-pitched tone
playing over TV)
(dogs barking in distance)
(Terrence yelling in other room)
- (belt striking)
- (Gwen screaming)
- (Terrence yells)
- (belt strikes)
(yelling and screaming continue)
I'm sorry!
- Dad, stop!
- Hey!
You stay out of this!
- Gwenny.
- (Gwen whimpering)
They came to my work.
Why did the police
come to my work?
I don't know! I'm sorry!
TERRENCE: You need to
tell me what you know
about this investigation.
- Nothing!
- Tell me what... What?
- Nothing.
- Huh?
Nothing!
- What?!
- Nothing!
Hit me again, and
I'm dropping it!
You drop that, and I will
beat your ass twice as hard.
(Terrence grunts)
- (bottle shatters)
- (Terrence yells)
(Gwen screams)
No, Dad!
That was an eight-dollar
bottle of goddamn vodka!
- (sobbing)
- Oh, now you listen to me.
Listen to me. You
are not your mother!
I know.
That means you do not hear
things that are not there.
You do not see things
that are not there!
Okay.
- They're not there, Gwenny!
- (crying): Okay.
And your dreams...
they're just fucking dreams.
- Do you understand me?
- GWEN: Yes!
- Do you understand me?!
- Yes!
Say it. I want to
hear you say it.
My dreams are just dreams.
Say it again!
My dreams are just dreams!
Say it again.
(panting)
(whimpering)
Go watch some
television or something.
And no ice on that
bottom, young lady.
I want you to think
about what you did.
(Terrence panting)
Did you know
anything about this?
Same goes for you.
You got that?
Now, get out.
Mm.
GOLIATH (over TV):
I told you, Davey.
- DAVEY: You hurt, Sal?
- SALLY: I'm okay.
You okay?
Yeah, but this is what
Officer Bob said would happen.
MOTHER: Sally, you're late.
(birds chirping over TV)
GOLIATH: Your bike's a mess.
DAVEY: So am I.
Officer Bob would
fix that wheel,
but I can't ask him now.
Why not?
♪ ♪
(phone ringing)
(phones ringing)
- (siren wails)
- (dramatic theme music playing)
I understand.
Thank you for calling.
Finney.
Yeah?
Do you know a kid
named Robin Are...
A-Ar... Ar... (sighs)
Arellano?
Yeah, that's it.
He's a friend from school. Why?
♪ ♪
(door opens)
(sighs)
I'm really sorry, Finney.
I know he was your friend.
Don't say "was."
He is my friend.
Sorry.
Gwen.
Can you do that dream thing?
It doesn't work that way.
Have you tried?
Of course I have.
Well, try again.
Please.
(sighs)
Jesus, I know you know
what I'm going to ask you,
but I'm going to ask you anyway.
My brother, he needs his friend.
And I know you can't
just let him go,
because you don't
interfere or whatever.
I don't know the rules.
But if you could help
me have a dream or two
and just see something
that could help the police
or me or anyone find him,
I will follow you forever.
- (light switch clicks)
- (gasps softly)
Amen.
TERRENCE: Don't think I don't
know what's going on in here.
No playing after lights-out.
Sorry, Daddy.
Go to sleep.
I love you.
Love you, too, Daddy.
(sighs)
(doorbell rings)
(Terrence sighs)
Goddamn it, Gwenny.
What the hell did she do now?
We're sorry, Mr. Blake.
Your daughter hasn't
done anything.
But is there any way
we can speak with her?
♪ ♪
(voices muted)
(grunting)
Fucking cocksucking cowards!
(Gwen yells)
(grunts)
Fuck you, too, ugly ass face.
- (Gwen grunts)
- (rock clatters against fence)
(yells)
(grunts, groans)
FINNEY: Gwen!
(grunting and groaning)
(grunting and groaning continue)
MR. HOPKINS: All right, class.
It is the day you've been
dreading all semester.
Frog dissection day.
Uh, pick a partner.
Remember, you will be paired
with this partner for
the rest of the year.
(students murmuring)
Do you need a partner?
Uh, no, no.
I-I mean, yeah, I don't
have a partner yet.
Those guys are assholes.
- What?
- This morning.
Everybody's talking about it.
Oh.
Your sister's
really cool, though.
I wish my brother and I
were friends like that.
MR. HOPKINS: Eyes up here.
All right, let's
cut open a frog.
(singsongy): Donna,
Donna, Donna.
(making smooching sounds)
-"Oh, Finney, will you be my lab partner?"
-Stop.
- (makes smooching sounds)
- Shut up, you jerk.
(laughs) All right,
see you tomorrow.
Where you going?
I'm staying over
at Susie's tonight.
It's Friday, so...
- I'll look after Dad.
- See you, kid.
(chuckling)
(bicycle bell dings)
♪ ♪
(grunting)
Oh! (laughs)
You goof. (laughs)
Well, isn't that
just peachy keen?
You need some help?
(laughs) You see that?
- Yeah.
- (laughing)
Would you hand me my hat?
Yes, sir.
I am a part-time magician.
-Would you like to see a magic trick?
-Yeah.
- (spray can rattling)
- Yeah?
-Are those black balloons in there?
-Yeah.
(Finney yelling)
(The Grabber yells in pain)
(Finney continues screaming)
(muffled yelling)
♪ ♪
My fucking arm.
I should snap your neck
for what you did to my arm.
♪ ♪
(sighs)
Jesus.
It's covered in blood.
It's like I killed someone.
You see that?
Not like you can see shit.
I know you're scared.
But I'm not gonna
hurt you anymore.
What I said about
snapping your neck...
(sighs)
I was angry, is all.
(laughing): And you
did a number on my arm.
I'm not gonna hold
it against you. Hmm?
I guess...
now we're even.
You don't have to be scared,
because nothing bad is
going to happen here.
On that I give my word, Johnny.
You like soda?
Hmm? I'll tell you what.
I'm gonna go get you
a soda, and then...
(phone ringing in distance)
Is that the phone?
You hear a phone ringing?
I'm gonna go see who it is.
Then I'll get you a soda.
And then I'll come back and
explain everything. Hmm?
(The Grabber sighing)
(lock clunks)
♪ ♪
(scoffs)
Gwenny, your dad's on the phone.
Hi, Daddy.
No, I haven't.
Not since school.
- (phone drops to floor)
- (panting)
♪ ♪
(voices muted)
(voice muted)
(phone ringing)
(gasps)
THE GRABBER: It doesn't work.
Not since I was a kid.
Hang it up.
I know you're scared
and you want to go home.
I'll take you home soon.
It's just that...
(sighs): Oh, everything's
all fucked up.
I got to be upstairs
for a while.
Something's come up.
What?
Never mind what.
Did someone see something?
Are the police coming?
If you let me go
before they get here,
I promise I won't tell.
(The Grabber laughing)
THE GRABBER: It's
not the police.
FINNEY: Someone, though?
Someone's coming?
I'll scream.
If someone's upstairs,
they'll hear me.
THE GRABBER: No, he won't.
Not with the door shut.
He?
(The Grabber sighs)
THE GRABBER: With
the door shut,
no one can hear
anything down here.
I soundproofed it myself.
So shout if you like.
You won't bother anyone.
FINNEY: You're the one
who killed the others.
Bruce.
Robin.
THE GRABBER: That wasn't me.
That was someone else.
I will never make you do
anything that you won't...
like.
If you try to touch me,
I'll scratch your face.
And whoever's coming
will see and ask why.
THE GRABBER: This face?
Hang up the phone now.
(breathing deeply)
I was down here
once when it rang.
(chuckling): Ooh.
Creepiest damn thing.
I think it's static
electricity that does it.
It went off while I
was right next to it.
I picked it up without thinking.
To see if anyone was there.
Was there?
THE GRABBER: No.
(door bangs shut)
(lock clunks)
Help!
Please!
(crickets chirping)
(muffled): Help me!
Somebody, please!
Please help!
♪ ♪
(grunts)
Stop. Stop. Stop it.
If anyone could've
broke that window,
they already would've done it.
Robin would've done it.
You're not getting out of here.
I'm not getting out of here.
(phone ringing)
(ringing continues)
Hello?
(clicking on line)
♪ ♪
(creaking)
(creaking continues)
Stop it.
THE GRABBER: Stop what?
(Finney gasping)
I'm hungry.
I need food.
How are your eyes?
They hurt.
THE GRABBER: Well, I can't
bring you anything to eat.
You'll have to wait.
Is there someone upstairs who
will see you bring me food?
THE GRABBER: Don't
you worry about that.
FINNEY: If you
weren't gonna feed me,
why'd you even come down here?
THE GRABBER: Just
to look at you.
I just wanted to look at you.
I'll go.
- (door bangs shut)
- (gasping)
(lock clunks)
(phone ringing)
(gasps)
(ringing continues)
(static droning over phone)
Hello?
Is somebody there?
I need help.
Hello?
- BOY (over phone): Finney.
- (gasping)
(phone ringing)
(ringing continues)
(ringing stops)
(ringing continuously)
(static droning)
BOY: Don't hang up.
I won't.
Who is this?
I don't remember my name.
Why not?
It's the first thing you lose.
First thing you lose when?
You know when.
How do you know my name?
We met once.
Your arm is mint.
You almost had me.
Bruce?
Bruce Yamada?
Y-Yeah.
Bruce.
Uh, I'm Bruce.
Your arm is mint.
You almost had me.
Did the phone ring for you?
It rang, but none
of us heard it.
Just you.
The Grabber hears
the phone, too,
but he doesn't
want to believe it.
Why are you calling me?
Your arm is mint.
You almost had me.
I'm glad it's you.
Finney?
Yeah?
There's a dirt section of
the floor in the hallway
where the tile is loose.
Okay.
Dig down underneath
the foundation.
I tried, but there wasn't time
for me to dig up and
out the other side.
Will I have enough time?
(static droning)
- (phone clicks)
- (static stops)
Hello?
Bruce?
♪ ♪
(distorted): I pledge
allegiance to the flag...
(distorted cheering)
(spraying)
Help!
(grunting)
(screams)
(panting rapidly)
♪ ♪
(voice muted)
- (door opens)
- (gasping)
I made you some breakfast.
What did you put in that?
THE GRABBER: Salt and pepper.
(giggles)
Oh, eat it, don't eat it.
You're already down here.
What do I need to drug you for?
- (phone ringing)
- (gasps)
Hello?
BOY (over phone):
Don't go upstairs.
Why not?
BOY: It's a trap.
FINNEY: Are you...
Are you Bruce?
Who's Bruce?
Uh, I was just talking to Bruce.
I don't know any Bruce.
He's the baseball player.
We don't play baseball here.
Who are you?
I don't remember.
Did you play soccer? Football?
I delivered newspapers.
Billy.
You're Billy Showalter.
Maybe.
No, you're Billy.
Do not...
go upstairs.
What is he doing?
He's waiting...
on the other side with
that fucking belt.
He didn't say you can leave,
so if you try, he'll punish you.
He'll beat you with that
belt until you pass out.
It hurts, kid.
It hurts real bad.
You'll cry.
You'll beg him to stop.
We all did.
But he just keeps beating you.
Hello?
♪ ♪
(steps creaking softly)
MRS. FULGRIM: Oh,
you poor dear.
Go to the nurse's
office and get a nap.
(phone ringing)
(static droning)
BILLY (over phone): You
said my name was Billy.
Billy Showalter.
Don't call me that.
I don't remember it.
It's not who I am now.
What do you want me
to call you, then?
What do you remember?
I told you.
I was a paperboy.
FINNEY: Okay. Paperboy.
See the wall in front of you?
See how the wall is
separated from the floor?
FINNEY: Yeah.
I tore a long cable
loose from down there.
I kept it hidden.
What am I supposed
to do with that?
♪ ♪
(distorted bell jingling)
(distorted cackling)
(gasps)
♪ ♪
(sighs)
(straining)
(yells)
(groaning)
(breathing deeply)
(sniffles)
Daddy?
(inhales sharply) Yes, honey.
Can I ask you a question?
Of course. Come sit.
Come.
There you go.
But you promise
you won't get mad?
I promise, honey.
It's about my dreams.
(sets glass on table)
What about your dreams?
Well, what if they...
you know, they're... well...
Gwen.
Your mother,
she was a special soul.
And she was smart,
just like you.
But, sweetheart,
she was also, uh...
touched.
She saw things and
she heard things,
and sh-she just
became so convinced
that her dreams meant something.
And eventually, they
told her to do things.
Terrible things.
And so she took her own life.
But they weren't
real, sweetheart.
They just weren't real.
I loved Mom.
I... I loved her, too.
I mean, I loved her
the way she was.
I know, sweetheart.
I... I... (sighs)
I just... I don't...
I don't want that future
for you, sweetheart.
Do you understand?
(breathing shakily)
But...
wh-what if it could
help me find Finney?
♪ ♪
(indistinct police
radio chatter)
- (knocking)
- (dog barking)
- MAX: Hey! Samson, stop!
- (clapping)
Come here! Come
on, boy. Come on.
- Hold on one second.
- (barking continues)
- Get in here. Go.
- (door bangs shut)
(barking continues in distance)
- Hello?
- WRIGHT: Good evening, sir.
We're canvassing
your neighborhood,
talking to residents,
and we were wondering,
have you seen this boy?
You're the police.
- Yes. Denver PD.
- Uh-huh.
-You're here for the missing kids.
-MILLER: Yes, sir.
And if there's anything
at all... No, no.
Come inside.
- Come on. Samson, stop it!
- (barking continues)
(dog growling)
Right. I want to
show you something.
Yeah, right over here.
So, all the kids live in
the same district, right?
They all walk to
and from school.
They were all grabbed on
the way home from school
except for Robin
Arellano... He was grabbed
on a Saturday afternoon on his
way to the store to get some
- pop and a candy bar, right?
- Sir, we're well aware of that.
Just listen. He has to be
able to grab these kids
and get them back to
his place very quickly,
which means he's got
a house with a garage.
And he can't risk
them getting away
or waking up if he's
knocking them out.
Which means that The Grabber
has to live somewhere
in this area right here.
- MILLER: Mr., uh...
- It's Max.
- Mr. Max...
- No, not Mr. Max.
It's just... it's just Max.
My friends call me Max.
And since we're all
working on this case together,
you know, I figured...
-How long have you lived in the area, Max?
-I-I...
No, I live down in Durango.
I'm just crashing here.
This is my brother's place.
I've been reading
about this case a lot,
and I'm in between jobs
right now, and you guys
could really use
my help on this.
You keep working at
this, but if you see
any of these boys,
give us a call.
Wait. Uh, or if I have
any new leads, right?
If you see any of
these boys, then call.
And, uh, might want to tidy up
before your brother gets home.
MAX: Oh.
Stupid, stupid, stupid moron.
Goddamn it, Max.
(snorts)
♪ ♪
(door clunks open)
(breathing deeply)
THE GRABBER (singsongy): I
know you're not sleeping.
I'm starving.
- Tell me your name.
- Why do you care?
THE GRABBER: I usually don't.
I find out eventually
in the paper.
They always print
a nice, big photo
with all the details
I could ever want.
All the things you
boys lie about.
What's different this time?
- THE GRABBER: Oh...
- (dog barking)
Oh, it's complicated.
It's... too complicated.
Everything's different.
Nothing's going right.
You could let me go.
THE GRABBER: I'm
thinking about it.
I promise I won't tell anyone.
You can blindfold me,
drop me off on the street.
I'll walk home.
THE GRABBER: Well,
tell me your name.
Taylor.
Taylor Mullen.
(The Grabber sighs)
(tray clatters)
THE GRABBER: I was really
starting to like you, Finney.
(kicks tray)
I almost let you go.
(trembling breaths)
(phone ringing)
(static droning)
Hello?
Bruce?
Billy... Paperboy?
- (phone clicks)
- (static stops)
♪ ♪
(snorts)
(sighs)
♪ ♪
(liquid dripping slowly)
(dripping continues)
(gasps)
♪ ♪
Hello?
(static droning over phone)
BOY (over phone): You
don't have much time.
The Grabber hasn't
been sleeping.
He thinks this might be it.
That he's gonna figure it out.
Who's gonna figure it out?
His brother upstairs.
(boy laughing)
Are you Griffin?
Who?
- Griffin Stagg.
- Probably.
It's all a little hazy,
but I imagine you
know all our names.
Every kid does.
I didn't know you.
Nobody did.
You spend so many
years invisible,
and then every kid in the
state knows your name.
You don't have much time.
Why hasn't he killed me?
You won't play the game.
You have to play the game.
If you don't play, he can't win.
What game?
Naughty Boy.
If you don't play Naughty Boy,
The Grabber can't beat you.
And if he can't beat you,
he can't move on
to the next part.
And the next part of Naughty Boy
is his favorite part.
What's the next part?
(Griffin laughing)
(sternly): You don't
have much time.
You said that.
He's not been sleeping.
You said that, too.
Yeah, well, he is now.
In his chair.
He passed out waiting
for you to play.
What good does that do me?
Wait. The door is
still unlocked.
The door is still unlocked.
Do I just go?
There's a combination lock
on the inside of the storm door.
- It was my bike lock.
- Your bike lock?
Yeah. He took it
when he took me.
What's the combination?
- I don't remember.
- Griffin.
I remember being
afraid I'd forget it.
That's why I wrote it down.
What? Where?
I carved it with a
bottle cap in the wall.
Which wall? Which wall?!
The one on the right,
about shoulder height
when you're sitting down.
♪ ♪
Two, three, three, one, seven.
Two, three, three, one, seven?
If you say so.
But is it 23-31-7
or 23-3-17 or 2-33-17?
- I can't remember.
- Griffin.
I can't remember.
You'll have to try them all.
And you'll have to be
very quiet about it.
Yeah.
Okay. Thanks.
♪ ♪
Two, three, three, one, seven.
(door creaks quietly)
(steps creaking quietly)
♪ ♪
(creaking softly)
(breathing heavily)
(snorts)
(snorting)
♪ ♪
(The Grabber snorts)
(The Grabber snoring softly)
♪ ♪
(dial spinning)
- (lock rattling)
- (sighs)
(clicks)
- (dog barking)
- (banging at door)
(grunts softly)
(barking continues)
(panting)
(tires squealing)
(screams): Help!
(grunts)
Help! The Grabber!
(grunting)
THE GRABBER: You say
one fucking word...
and I will gut you like a
pig right here in the street.
And strangle you with
your own intestines.
Nighty night, naughty boy.
(grunts)
MAX: Hey, what was all
that noise I heard?
THE GRABBER: Samson was
barking at something.
It's nothing. Go
back to bed, Max.
(lock clunks)
Jesus, what the fuck?
I mean, what the fuck?
I ask you for help,
and you give me
these clues that
don't mean anything.
And now this morning, I wake
up without any dream at all?
Seriously, what the
hell is wrong with you?
You let The Grabber
take Finney, right?
And don't tell me that
you don't get involved,
because you've been
giving me these dreams.
Unless...
(sighs)
Maybe you're not even real.
(groans softly)
Son of a bitch.
(phone ringing)
No.
- Fuck you.
- (ringing continues)
Goddamn it.
(static droning over phone)
What?
You gonna say something?
Do you even know who you are?
BOY (over phone): What the
shit kind of question is that?
Do you even know who you are?
I'm Finney Blake.
Yeah, well, nice to fucking
meet you, Finney Blake.
Right here.
- This is it.
- This is what?
The horrifying nightmare end
of your pathetic little life.
Holy shit.
You're Vance Hopper.
I remember you.
You used to scare me.
Trust me, Finney Blake,
if you knew what you had coming,
you'd be fucking terrified.
Today's the day, motherfucker.
("Fox on the Run"
by Sweet playing)
(electronic chiming
over pinball machine)
♪ I don't wanna know your name ♪
♪ 'Cause you don't
look the same ♪
♪ The way you did before... ♪
Vance, you're gonna
beat your high score.
Of course I'm gonna
do it, dumb shit.
I said I would.
Hey.
Oh, jackass!
♪ Fox on the run ♪
♪ And hide away... ♪
Motherfucker!
You fucked with my game!
WOMAN: Oh, for Pete's sake.
- Hey.
- VANCE: Come here, bitch.
(grunting)
(murmuring)
Don't fuck with me again!
(song fades)
♪ ♪
(distorted police radio chatter)
(radio crackling)
FINNEY (over radio): Do
you even know who you are?
What the shit kind
of question is that?
Do you even know who you are?
FINNEY: I'm Finney Blake.
Yeah, well, nice to fucking
meet you, Finney Blake.
Right here. This is it.
FINNEY: This is what?
The horrifying nightmare end
of your pathetic little life.
FINNEY: Holy shit.
- You're Vance Hopper.
- (The Grabber cackling)
I remember you. You
used to scare me.
VANCE: Trust me, Finney Blake,
if you knew what you had coming,
you'd be fucking terrified.
Today's the day, motherfucker.
(panting rapidly)
- (knocking)
- TERRENCE: Gwenny, hurry up.
You're gonna be late for school.
Sorry, Daddy.
FINNEY: Holy shit.
You're Vance Hopper.
I remember you. You
used to scare me.
VANCE: Trust me, Finney Blake,
(over phone): if you
knew what you had coming,
you'd be fucking terrified.
Today's the day, motherfucker.
Have you tried stacking the
carpets to reach the window?
I've tried everything.
No, not everything.
When The Grabber saw what
I had done, that was it.
And he took his
time with me, too.
What did you do?
Oh, that fucker had
to spend a fortune
- to repair all the damages.
- What did you do?
I'm getting to that, cunt wad!
Or do you have some
other important shit
you have to do right now?
No, no, no, no,
I'm... I'm listening.
There's an outlet
in the shitter,
across from the john.
Yeah, I've seen it.
On the other side of that
wall, there's a storage room.
You can't get into that room,
because there's a big-ass
upright freezer in the way.
Okay.
Break into the wall about
two feet above the outlet
till you get to a panel
with screws in it.
Get the panel off,
you're into the freezer.
And then out into
the storage room.
Thank you.
For what?
For helping me.
Helping you?
This isn't about you.
Fuck him...!
(groaning)
(screams)
(whimpering, panting)
♪ ♪
(grunting)
(slurps)
(panting)
(grunts)
♪ ♪
(grunting)
- (thudding)
- (Finney grunting)
(thudding and grunting continue)
(panting)
(sobbing)
(whimpering)
(phone ringing)
(ringing continues)
(static droning over phone)
What?
ROBIN (over phone): Hey, Finn.
What's happening?
Robin?
Hey, buddy. Don't cry.
I'm not.
Yes, you are.
I can see you.
- You can?
- I'm with you.
I've been with you
this whole time.
You have?
A man never leaves
a friend behind.
My dad didn't leave his buddies
behind when he went to 'Nam.
That's why he didn't come home.
And I'm not coming home, either.
And I'm not going
to leave you behind.
We'll be together again soon.
Fuck that. You ain't
gonna go like I did.
I've tried everything.
Nothing's worked.
- Yet.
- Robin...
Do you remember what I told you?
That I needed to see
Texas Chain Saw Massacre?
Before that.
That someday I have to
stand up for myself.
"Someday" is today, Finn.
Today's the day you stop
taking shit from anybody.
I'm not a fighter
like you, Robin.
You couldn't even take him.
You've always been
a fighter, Finn.
That's what we have in
common, why we were friends.
You were always afraid
to throw a punch,
but you always knew
how to take one.
And you always got
back up every time.
I'm not strong enough.
You have to be. You're
getting out of here.
If you can't do it
for you, do it for me.
What does it matter?
Because I don't want
to die for nothing.
I want to at least
have died for a friend.
And because I can't
kill that hijo de puta,
you have to do it for me.
How?
You're gonna use a weapon.
What weapon?
The one in your hand.
The phone?
Fill the receiver with dirt.
Pack it in tight.
Give it some heft.
Then what?
Then you practice over and over.
You raise the phone.
Take a fast step back.
Step forward, step
back and swing.
- Try it.
- Now?
Yes.
You raise the phone.
Take a fast step back.
Step forward, step
back and swing.
Again. You raise the phone.
Take a fast step back.
Step forward, step
back and swing.
Again. You raise the phone.
Take a fast step back.
Step forward, step
back and swing.
Again. You raise the phone.
Take a fast step back.
-Step forward, step back and swing.
-(grunts)
You got it.
Now fill the phone with
dirt like I told you.
Will I still be able
to talk with you?
This was the last call, Finn.
It's all you from here on out.
I miss you, Robin.
Then get out for me.
Use what we gave you.
I will.
Bye, Finn.
Bye, Robin.
♪ ♪
Please, dear Jesus.
Please, please.
I'm sorry I said
you weren't real.
Please be real. Please.
Please, please, please.
(screams, grunts)
♪ ♪
(panting)
Detective Wright, please.
("On the Run" by
Pink Floyd playing)
(snorts, inhales deeply)
♪ ♪
(sighs)
(creaking)
♪ ♪
(creaking continues)
(lock clunks)
(sighs)
No fucking way.
I knew that he was hiding
something from me down here,
but holy Mary, mother of God.
Please, help.
C-Can you call my
dad? Call my sister?
Oh, listen. Don't
worry, he's not here.
He-he had to go into work.
Uh, I'm Max, man.
Stay-stay calm.
No wonder he was freaking
out this morning.
Hey, you want to know the story
about how I found you, man?
- No, no, no, no...
- Hey, no, no, no.
Don't worry about it. We
can talk about this...
(screams)
(Finney hyperventilating)
(grunts)
(tires squealing)
Is this the house?
- Yes.
- Are you sure?
I'd never seen it before
today, except in my dreams.
The tree, the door,
the address, the gate.
Every detail.
Okay. Okay, you-you s-step back.
Stay with her.
(indistinct chatter)
Please hurry.
Okay, let's go.
Look what you made me do.
You made me kill my brother.
(panting): No.
It wasn't me. I...
He was an idiot.
But he was my idiot.
I'm sorry, Max.
Now I'm gonna have to
put you with the others.
(sighs)
Looks like you'll find those
naughty boys after all.
Open up! Police!
(squishing)
(grunts)
What's up with the phone, huh?
I told you it doesn't work!
(breathing deeply)
Normally, I would use a knife.
But you are special, Finney.
I'm gonna take my time.
I want this to really hurt.
- Samson!
- (barking)
(growls)
(barking, snarling)
- MILLER: Clear.
- OFFICER: Clear!
(Samson growling)
THE GRABBER: Good boy.
- It's empty.
- It's the wrong house.
- (laughs)
- (Finney yells)
(barking)
(grunts)
(yelps)
(bone cracks)
(screaming)
(grunting)
(growling)
(Finney yells)
(screaming)
(The Grabber groaning)
- (gasping, choking)
- (Finney yells)
- (phone ringing)
- (Samson barking)
(ringing continues)
(Samson whines quietly)
(static droning over phone)
It's for you.
VANCE (over phone): Welcome
to the nightmare end
- of your pathetic little life.
- (Griffin laughing)
GRIFFIN: You don't
have much time.
(Griffin laughing)
VANCE: Today's the
day, motherfucker.
ROBIN: I can't kill
you, you hijo de puta,
so Finn is gonna do it for me.
BRUCE: Finn's arm is mint!
- (grunts)
- (neck snaps)
(Samson barks)
(barking)
(barking fades)
OFFICER: Wait.
We've got a basement.
♪ ♪
(door opens)
MILLER: It's the missing kids.
This is where he buries them.
WRIGHT: I think he kills
them someplace else.
MILLER: I think you're right.
♪ ♪
- (siren wailing)
- (tires squeal)
(indistinct police
radio chatter)
(urgent chatter)
♪ ♪
(indistinct shouting)
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey. Come with me.
(officers shouting indistinctly)
- Basement.
- WRIGHT: Basement.
MILLER: Get the
kids out of here.
♪ ♪
(birds chirping)
(officer speaks indistinctly)
OFFICER: Behind the barrier.
(indistinct chatter)
(Terrence breathing heavily)
(voice shaking):
I am so sorry.
I'm-I'm...
(sobbing): I'm
so... I'm so sorry.
Please forgive me.
(sobbing)
♪ ♪
(indistinct chatter)
My name is Chief Walker
of the Denver Police Department.
Our community's long nightmare
has finally come to a
bittersweet end tonight
with the rescue of the
missing Blake child
but also the discovery
of five bodies
we believe to be the other
missing children in the area.
Here are the facts of the
case by the men who broke it.
- Detective Wright?
- Thanks, Chief.
The perpetrator known as
The Grabber owned two homes,
one where he kept the
victims while alive
and a second empty
home across the street
where he buried them postmortem.
(school bell ringing)
(students murmuring)
- Is that him?
- That's him.
Oh, shit.
- Did you see him?
- I thought he would be bigger.
He's the one who
killed The Grabber.
- That's him.
- No way.
The Grabber was like
seven feet tall.
I heard he stabbed him.
How could that kid
strangle him to death?
- It was an axe to the head.
- My dad's a cop. I know.
I heard he beat him
to death with a phone.
♪ ♪
STUDENT: Good morning.
(quiet murmuring)
Hi, Finney.
Call me Finn.
♪ There's a smile on your face ♪
♪ It's a long way
from your home ♪
♪ Far from all the pain
that you have ever known ♪
♪ Gone without a trace ♪
♪ Up from the fire
this bird has flown ♪
♪ As you spread your
wings in grace ♪
♪ You're not alone ♪
♪ And your fear ♪
♪ It is gone ♪
♪ Left it all inside that home ♪
♪ You will never be alone ♪
♪ As I have been ♪
♪ All of the feelings
you have had ♪
♪ And a hurt that felt so bad ♪
♪ Make you strong,
won't make you mad ♪
♪ It disappears ♪
♪ And there's a
smile on your face ♪
♪ It's a long way
from your home ♪
♪ Far from all the pain
that you have ever known ♪
♪ Gone without a trace ♪
♪ Up from the fire
this bird has flown ♪
♪ As you spread your
wings in space ♪
♪ You're not alone ♪
♪ You're far from home ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Gone without a trace ♪
♪ Up from the fire
this bird has flown ♪
♪ As you spread your
wings in space ♪
♪ You're not alone ♪
♪ You're far from home ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Yes, there's a
smile on your face ♪
♪ It's a long way
from your home ♪
♪ Far from all the pain
that you have ever known ♪
♪ Gone without a trace ♪
♪ Up from the fire
this bird has flown ♪
♪ As you spread your
wings in grace ♪
♪ You're not alone ♪
♪ You're far from home ♪
♪ You're really far
from here, yeah ♪
♪ You're not alone ♪
♪ There's nothing
left to fear now ♪
♪ You're really far from home ♪
♪ You're really far
from here, yeah ♪
♪ You'll never be alone ♪
♪ You'll never be alone. ♪
♪ ♪
(song ends)
♪ It's the weekend ♪
♪ I think of good friends ♪
♪ Sometimes forget they died ♪
♪ I want to see them ♪
♪ Because I need them ♪
♪ It can make you cry ♪
♪ And it goes on ♪
♪ It goes on ♪
♪ It goes on. ♪
(song ends)