Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
Oh, really? Okay, okay.
Yeah, why not?
Hey, isn't that Mia?
I'm so sorry, I-I must have slipped.
Did you have a nice swim there?
Don't touch me.
Oh, my God!
It was an accident, I swear.
Dude, your sister is so lame.
She's not my sister.
Come on.
Let's go.
Oh, my God!
Such a loser!
Why is she all wet? I swear!
I'm sorry about that.
But we are going to
see you tomorrow, right?
Yeah. Tomorrow.
Okay. Bye.
It's going to be amazing! I promise!
Amazing! Bring your bikini!
Do you want to tell me what happened?
You should just drive.
Hey, Mrs. Riley.
Hey!
Whoa, did you go for
a swim in your clothes?
Shut up, Ben!
Hey, Mimi!
Don't call me that!
Why are you all wet?
Why is she all wet?
I have to talk to her, babe.
What happened? Hey! What happened?
Somebody pushed her in the pool at school.
No big deal.
It's not my fault that nobody likes her.
You know, that's a real nasty thing to say.
Sorry.
Sasha!
Look, I know it's tough moving here,
but you two got to look
out for each other, okay?
Okay.
Thanks.
You guys about done?
Yeah, you are all loaded up, boss.
Alright. Thanks, Ben.
See you tomorrow?
See you tomorrow, Carl. Get some rest.
Yeah. I will do.
Alright, thanks.
Hey. Mind if I come in?
What's going on?
I hate it here.
Mia, you're so much stronger
than you think you are.
And if your Mom were here,
she'd be really proud of you.
Well, she's not here, is she?
Well, I'm proud to call you my daughter.
Look, I know you and Sasha have a
hard time sometimes, but we're family.
She's not my sister.
It's very good.
It's great.
Hey, I almost forgot to show you
guys what I found this morning.
Look at this.
That's a shark tooth.
Yeah.
Is it a great white?
I think so.
Where did you find it?
We uncovered a passageway that
leads to a new part of the city.
Nice.
But how did the shark get in there?
I don't know.
Maybe he swam in from
the sea, chasing a seal,
Got lost in the tunnels
hundreds of years ago.
That's so cool!
You can keep it.
That kind of brings me
around to something else.
Girls, I know I said I was going
to hang with you this weekend,
But opening this new passageway,
It means that there's this
team of archaeologists.
- They fly in from Europe next week.
- It's fine, Dad.
So I got to finish mapping
the caves, laying the lights...
You don't have to explain.
But your father planned something
very special for the two of you.
What?
Well, the shark tooth is a clue.
Girls, come on. Here, show them.
There you go.
A glass bottomed boat ride
To see great white sharks
in their natural habitat?
Sounds fun to me.
No. This is for tourists.
Well, we're kind of tourists.
Girls, it's going to be awesome.
They take you out to where
the great whites feed.
You get to watch them through this
viewing gallery in the bottom of the ship.
It's awesome.
No. I have plans for tomorrow.
Well, you'll just have
to rearrange your plans.
And besides, I think this is a
wonderful way for the two of you
- To spend quality time together.
- Yeah.
Where are you going?
To let Alexa and Nicole know
that I can't hang out tomorrow.
Is that okay?
Watch your tone.
Well, I am sorry about tomorrow, but
the sharks are going to be really cool.
And maybe next week you
and I can go scuba diving.
Remember how much you used
to like diving with me?
Yeah, I was, like, ten years old, Dad.
Ten years old. The youngest
person I'd ever seen scuba dive.
Come on. Are you kidding me?
And the cutest.
Yeah, you were like a little sea monkey.
Alright, guys. Who's ready
to see some sharks today?
I'll pick you up on the way home. Okay?
Alright.
Hey, Mimi, don't get eaten by a shark!
Stop!
Yeah, Mimi, don't get eaten by a shark!
Hey, if you start to drown,
we'll come and save you.
I'll save you!
Look!
I can't believe she's here.
Oh, my gosh!
What the hell are you guys doing here?
Come on. We had plans.
I told you, I can't.
Dude, I am going to
take you to a place that
no tourists would ever
find in a million years.
Chance of a lifetime.
Or would you rather stay
on this stupid boat instead?
Yeah.
I mean stay. Stay if you want to.
Hey, maybe you can become
friends with Catherine.
Talk about how beautiful she is!
She is beautiful though.
Dude, shut up!
It's up to you.
- Come on!
- One second.
You really want to spend all
day on a boat with those girls?
Come on.
She's so scared.
What do you think?
I don't know.
Don't let those girls get to you.
Catherine.
Come on.
Goodbye, Catherine.
Let's go. Come on.
Okay, watch your step.
Guys, come on! We're almost there.
You keep saying that.
This time I mean it.
Oh, my God!
Whoa!
I mean, how did you even
find out about this place?
Ben took me here.
Ben? Like my stepdad's assistant Ben?
Oh, she... stop with that. Oh, my God!
Okay, so how do we get down there?
So there's a path that'll
take us around and down.
Or you could go that way.
What are you waiting for?
It's amazing!
I don't know, I...
We should take the path.
That was amazing!
Screw the path.
That's so cool.
Look at all this stuff.
Whoa.
That's a lot of scuba gear.
This is all the equipment that your
stepdad and Ben have been storing
for the archaeologist team
that's coming next week.
Is this the entrance to the City?
Guys, if my Dad finds
us, he's going to kill us.
Chill. I talked to Ben.
Your Dad is on the other side,
mapping out the new tunnel they found.
They will never know we were here.
Doesn't look like much of a city to me.
It's Mayan.
It was built underground,
out of their burial sites,
to hide from the Conquistadors
when they invaded.
Rising sea levels put
most of it underwater.
Thank you, Professor.
Did Ben ever take you diving into the city?
Yeah, once.
What's it like?
It's pretty insane down there.
I mean, we only went as
far as the first cave.
It was built as an entrance to
- ...is it Xibalba? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Xibalba! Yeah!
- Place of fear.
- Yeah.
Like I was saying, the Mayan underworld.
Burial caves.
Yeah, it's pretty scary,
but it's really cool.
They have all these old
statues, and altars, and stuff.
So what are we waiting for?
Come on. Just the first cave.
- But my Dad...
- Is miles away!
Yeah, they have a different way in.
Here, look. Everything we need.
I mean, there's no fins, so...
Come on! It's the first cave.
We're not swimming the whole city.
Guys, cave diving is dangerous.
Cave diving is dangerous!
No. Mia is right, Nicole.
I don't really know about this.
Look, we've come all this way and
we don't even see the temple? Really?
- It's unlike anything you ever seen before.
- Yeah.
We should just go in, go once
around the first cave, and then out.
Yeah. Come on.
When was the last time you went diving?
Years ago.
- I used to go all the time with Dad,
- Perfect.
But I've never been in caves before.
It's like riding a bike, right? I mean...
Come on, Mia!
Mimi!
Yeah, she's going to do it!
Let's go! Let's go, that's great!
- Let's go, Mia! Yes!
- Come on! We're doing it, let's go!
Hey, it's going to be fun, okay?
Just remember, keep your
movements nice and small.
Last thing you want to do
is kick up silt down there.
You won't be able to see your own hands.
Okay. You guys ready?
I'm going to lead. Keep
behind me at all times.
One circuit around the
first cave, and back.
Yes, teacher.
Nicole, I'm serious. Either
you do as I say, or...
Yeah, I hear you.
We don't do it at all.
Let's go, ladies. Get a move on.
Everyone okay? Sasha, are you good?
Yeah.
Mia?
Yeah, I'm good.
Everybody check your air gauges.
You should all have a full tank.
Mine's on 100 percent.
Me too.
Come on, I'm getting old already!
Okay. Turn your lights on.
Follow me. The entrance is
just at the bottom of the steps.
Let's go.
You guys are going to freak
out. It's insane down there.
Come on!
Oh, my God. Are you sure about this?
Yeah, trust me.
Oh, my God! This is so crazy!
I can't believe we're doing this.
Look at that.
Run out of air in a cave, and your last
chance is sucking the air from those.
Seriously?
For sure. You want to try it?
The corridor gets narrow
up here, so single file.
Just through here.
You all okay?
- Yup.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I'm good.
Sasha, you could barely
get your ass through there.
Shut up, Nicole. At least I have an ass.
All okay? Mia?
- Yeah.
- Sasha?
Nicole?
Yes, teacher!
You guys ready for this?
Holy...
...crap!
That's so cool!
I told you guys.
Xibalba.
This place is insane, right?
Hey. Nicole! No!
Keep behind me and keep together.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
One lap around the altar,
and then we head back, right?
Right.
Let's go.
Oh, my God!
They made human sacrifices here.
Creepy.
Guys, did you see that?
I think I saw something move.
There's nothing down here, Nicole.
There was something there.
Oh, come on, Nicole.
Maybe it was a mermaid.
Shut up, Sasha. I'm serious.
Come on, Nicole. Stop messing around.
Maybe it was my Dad.
Your Dad's on the other side of the city.
There's nothing there.
Nicole's just being an idiot.
I heard that, Alexa.
Come on, let's just go back.
We said we would come in, and
then head straight back out, right?
Nicole!
Nicole?
Nicole, stop being an idiot.
Come, look, look!
Look!
Oh, my God!
Where are its eyes?
It doesn't have any.
It's a Mexican tetra... a blind cave fish.
Wait, I heard about these.
No light down here, so they
don't need color or eyes.
They evolved without.
How does it know where it's going?
Heightened senses.
I didn't know they got this big.
It's probably never known a human.
It's hiding from us.
Well, who says it's us it's hiding from?
Stop!
- Here, fishy fishy! Nice to meet...
- No, Nicole. I wouldn't.
No!
No, stop it from falling!
Guys? Guys?
I can't hear you!
Nobody move!
Anyone? Nicole? Sasha, where are you?
Guys? I can't see you guys, where are you?
Sasha... I can't hear
you, guys, where are you?
Sasha!
I can't see anyone.
Alexa, I can't see!
Mia!
Mia! What are you doing here?
Oh, my God! I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- We were at the lake and...
- Whoa, whoa. Whoa, whoa.
- Calm down, alright? It's okay.
- It was really stupid, I'm sorry.
Let me guess. Alexa persuaded
you to come down here, huh?
And then we knocked over a stone column,
and I got totally lost in the silt.
You didn't think to come
down here with a guideline?
Mia! Mia! Thank God!
Oh, man, I should've known.
So you thought you'd try a
little bit of cave diving, huh?
I'm... I'm so sorry.
Honestly, we were supposed to just go
in and then straight back out again.
That's the last time I'm showing
you any of my secret spots.
I take it Sasha and Nicole are close by?
They're waiting by the exit.
Yeah? What a surprise.
Let's just get you guys the hell out
of here before your Dad finds out.
You're not going to tell him, are you?
Are you kidding me?
Alexa, where are the others?
MIA, FRANTICALLY: Where are
they? Sasha? Nicole? Sasha?
Mia! Where are you?
Sasha! Look they're here, they're here!
Guys, there's a shark.
Mia, what is it?
There's a shark. I'm serious.
It killed Ben.
What?
We have to go. We have to go now.
You're really freaking me out right now.
Guys, if this is some kind
of joke, it's not funny.
Sasha, behind you!
Yeah, right.
Shark!
Swim! Swim! Go on!
Guys, come on, move! Move!
The tunnel is starting to
collapse. We need to hurry.
Keep going, come on, go, go!
Alexa!
What do I do, Alexa, what do I do?
Push. Help me push. Come on.
Push.
Help me move these rocks.
We're trapped.
There has to be a way out.
Come on.
You guys, it's pointless.
It's pointless. Alexa! Alexa!
Alexa! Look at me.
You said Ben and my Dad went
through a different entrance.
Sasha, this place is a maze. I
would never be able to find him.
Guys! Guys, there's a line.
Ben... Ben, he had the guideline with him.
It leads back to where they were working.
What about the shark?
It looked blind. Like the tetra fish.
It must have evolved down here.
When my dad opened up the new
cave, it must have let him through.
Mia, was that a great white?
Yeah, I think so.
Everybody check your air.
I have about forty percent left.
What about you guys?
I have forty.
Thirty eight.
Thirty five.
Okay, we don't have much of
a choice, as far as I can see.
Everyone needs to stay close, okay?
But what about the shark?
We can do this, Alexa.
It's going to be okay.
Okay, come on. Let's go.
The guideline.
I can see it.
Stay close.
If we follow the line,
it will take us to Grant.
Yeah. Come on, let's go.
The line leads down here.
This way.
Are you okay, Mia?
Yeah.
Oh, my God! What is this place?
Catacombs. This city was built
out of their burial chambers.
The line's caught on something.
Come on. Sasha, we need to move.
Guys.
What are we going to do?
We need to keep going.
We're going to die down here.
No. Grant has to be close.
We can't give up.
No, no, it's a dead
end. We have to go back.
There's no other way. Where
are we going to go back to?
We're going to run out of
air. We're going to drown.
We're going to drown!
Wait! Wait!
Where are they? Sasha, where's Dad?
He must be close. Grant!
- Dad!
- Grant!
- Dad! Where are you, Dad?
- Dad!
- Grant, can you hear us?
There's another way through.
Get down!
Turn it off!
This way.
Keep going.
Go! Go now!
Come on!
Come on, get in! Go!
This way!
Come on!
This way! Let's go!
Hurry! Come on!
Did the shark follow us?
I think we're safe here.
It's too narrow for the shark to follow.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
Guys, the air tastes bad.
It's an air pocket. It's been here a while.
We can't breathe it for long.
So what do we do?
I can't see any way out of here.
How much air do you have left?
I've got twenty two percent.
- I'm on twenty.
- Nineteen.
Twenty one.
Do you hear that?
Shhh. Listen. Listen.
I think it's music.
- That's impossible.
- Yeah.
It's coming from over here.
It has to be my Dad.
It's a dead end.
ALEXA, SASHA, NICOLE: Mia!
'The Look' by Roxette).
Mia! Mia, are you okay?
- There's a gap.
- Okay?
- Yeah. I can get through.
- Okay.
I'll let you know when
I'm on the other side.
No. We should stay together.
There's no point in
all of us using our air.
Are you sure you can do this?
- Yeah.
- Please be careful.
- Okay.
- Okay, we're going to be right here.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Dad!
I was mid jam right now.
Grant?
Ben?
Come on, guys. Seriously,
stop messing around.
Track error. Please reset.
Track error.
What?
What is that?
It's an emergency alarm.
Designed to help locate a diver in a cave.
Dad!
I'm through.
Can you see anything?
Dad?
I can't see anything,
but I can hear the alarm.
Carl?
Dad!
I see it! I see the alarm!
Guys!
Guys, I can't hear you!
Dad!
Dad! Help!
Why isn't she back yet?
Mia! Mia!
Mia!
She's not responding.
We have to go help her.
What if the shark got her?
Guys, guys, I'm lost. I can't hear you.
Can you hear me?
Guys, I can't hear you.
What are you doing here?
We just wanted to see the main
entrance, but then the tunnel collapsed.
Ben and Carl are both dead.
Where's Sasha?
We found a small air pocket.
She's back there with Alexa and
Nicole, but I can't hear them any more.
It's because these columns are
breaking up the radio signal.
You're low on air.
- We'll get them. Follow me.
- Okay.
Mia! Mia, behind you!
Over here! Over here!
Hey! Over here!
Over here!
Over here! Over here!
Swim!
This way!
Swim! Come on!
We did it!
Oh, Mia!
You guys!
I love you guys!
- We made it!
- You saved us, Mia!
I thought we were going to die down there.
Okay, girls, this is an ascender.
You got to get yourself into this harness.
Get your foot in this loop.
And this, you got to work up and down.
Pump down, push up. Pump down, push up.
- Yeah.
- Okay?
- We'll get out of here soon.
- Okay.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
- Okay. Push.
Yeah! You got to use all your strength.
- Okay.
- Push and pull.
That's it, yeah!
I'm a natural.
- Alright, go back. Come on.
- Okay.
One more time. Hard as you can.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Okay.
Yeah! Keep going.
Guys! Guys, there's a shark!
Get me out of here!
Nicole, I can't pull us both up.
Get off, Nicole!
I got to get out of here!
It's not going to hold both of you.
- Let go, Nicole!
- Alexa!
Nicole, you got to get down!
Oh, my God, there's two sharks!
- No!
- Alexa!
I got to get out of here! I'm sorry!
- No!
- Please let go!
Alexa!
Unhook yourself from
that harness right now!
Unhook yourself!
Alexa!
- Girls!
- Mia, quick!
Help! Someone help!
Nobody can hear you, Alexa.
Someone will hear us.
They'll hear this.
Help! Someone help!
- Help! Please!
- Alexa, no one can hear you.
- Turn it off!
- Girls. Girls.
- Shut it off!
- Don't!
Girls! Girls! Look!
They're gone.
Where did they go?
They're scared of it.
The sharks... they've evolved blind,
and they have a heightened
sense of hearing.
It must be the frequency.
Maybe we can use the
alarm to scare them away.
I mean, someone's going to come looking
for us when we don't
come back tonight, right?
The only people that know
where we are, are right here.
I just found the entrance to this cave.
I'm the only one who knows where it is.
And there's no way we can get
back up without the ascender.
What are we going to do?
We got to go back down.
There's no other way now.
- What?
Listen, this cave goes out to the sea.
If we follow it, we'll
come out in the ocean.
There'll be strong currents there
that are going to try and suck us down.
So we're going to have to keep together.
No. We're going to die down there.
If we stay here, we'll die.
We're going to watch each other's backs.
And we can survive this.
Okay? Girls, I believe in you.
Dad!
Dad! Dad!
No!
Mia, get back! Mia, get back!
Sound the alarm!
Are they gone?
Are they gone? Can you see it?
I don't see it. I don't see it.
What are we going to do?
We have to do what he said.
- No!
- Yes, we have to go back down.
I can't. I can't do this. I can't. I can't.
Mia, we have to go. We
have to do what he said.
We have to go back down.
He wouldn't want you to give up now, okay?
Do we even have enough air?
We have no choice.
What if we're wrong?
What if the alarm has nothing to
do with why the sharks are gone?
We got to try.
You ready?
I can't see them. Where did they go?
Wait. Current!
Sasha! Give me your hand!
No!
Help me!
No! No!
Give me your hand! Come on, I got you.
Help!
Come on, I got you. Come on.
I can't hold on!
The current is too strong!
Come on! Hold on! Give me your hand!
- I can't hold on!
- Mia, help! I'm falling!
Mia! I'm slipping!
Hold on, Sasha, come on.
No! No!
Sasha!
No! No! Mia!
No! Sasha!
Mia! Mia, she's dead.
There's nothing you can do.
No, you don't know that.
Mia, look at me.
I'm going.
We have to keep going, or we
are going to die down here.
Do you understand me?
No!
Look. Over there.
That's the way out.
The current is going to drag us down.
We'll be okay if we stick to the side.
It's our only chance. Okay?
Okay? I won't leave you.
Grab my hand. Let's go.
You okay?
Keep moving.
Almost there.
Mia! Give me your hand!
- Alexa!
- Give me your hand!
I'm coming. I'm coming.
Grab my hand! Grab my hand!
I got you! I got you!
Are you okay?
Mia, this has to be the way out.
We're almost there.
The exit can't be far.
Alexa!
Oh, my God, you're alive!
You're alive!
We're trapped, Mia!
Mia, we're going to
die. There's no way out.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Don't be.
No, no! It's my fault. If it
wasn't for me, you wouldn't be here.
Stop! You stop it, okay?
We can't give up now.
We can share air. I have
a little more than you.
Five percent.
We're not going to die down here.
- Look!
- Where are you going? Mia?
Sasha, come here.
Look. Maybe there's a way through.
The current is too
strong, it'll drag us down.
We have to try.
It's a dead end.
No, it can't be.
There! Come on!
I think I can see the sunlight.
It's too narrow to climb through.
There must be another way.
It's circling. Oh, my God! Mia!
Mia! I'm stuck!
Mia! It's coming!
I'm stuck! I'm stuck!
Keep going. We can do it. We can make it.
Just keep going. We're almost there.
Come on, Mia!
Come on, Mia! Keep going!
Come on, Mia.
I see light.
Come on. We're so close.
Mia, I'm stuck.
We're so close.
I have to take my pack off.
Come on.
Hold your breath.
Help!
Oh, my God! Mia! Mia!
Mia! We made it! We did it!
There has to be a way up.
Maybe, maybe we could climb it.
Mia! Mia!
Mia, look!
- Oh, my God! Help! Help!
- Help! Over here!
- Help! Help!
- Help! Help! Help!
- Help!
- Over here!
Mia, we have to swim.
We have to swim. We can do it.
Help! Help!
Come on.
Over here!
Help!
Wait.
Oh, my God, it's chum! No!
Whoa! Come over here.
Move!
Oh, my God!
Are you all seeing this?
Stay back! Stay back!
Sasha!
Get out of my way!
Move!
Come on! Come on!
Watch out!
You're okay?
Look at me. Look at me.
Breathe. Breathe.
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. You're okay.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org