Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
I've always known you were no saint...
drowning in your own anger...
blinded by your own ghosts.
But I still chose you
as father of my children.
I had no idea what you were capable of.
Honey? Is... is that you?
Do you remember the day we met?
It was so damn hot, the street
looked like a river of oil.
But in that moment, next to you,
I just felt like a normal person...
You know
it was a good feeling...
I remember that day
like it was yesterday...
and I curse that moment every
single day of my fucking life
I lied because I didn't want to
involve you in my shitty life...
and I was scared...
scared that my job...
killing people...
you would never accept me.
I can UNDERSTAND why you
lied to me all this time...
But I can't ever FORGIVE you.
If I knew who you really were
I wouldn't have brought
our son into the world.
He deserved better than this.
You abandoned him,
I didn't abandon you.
They killed me.
They fucking killed me.
THEY
FUCKING
KILLED ME!!!!
Frank?
Witch?!!!
A... are you still alive?!!!
Of course I am
although I am still imprisoned
within this rotting carcass.
I don't know what any of
that cryptic shit means
but I'm fucking glad you're still here
It means that we must find
the second element of your soul
the Ice
the second step towards your resurrection.
But now
we must also find a new shell for me.
What happened to your voice?
Nothing. This is my voice.
It has always been this way.
Take me with you
strap me to your back
'tis the best way for us to bond.
How the fuck can you still talk?
Damaging the shell
doesn't harm me sweetheart
it only pisses me off.
You know, I was growing attached
to that dusty old carcass
Whatever Witch. What do we do now?
Witch?
Why do you still call me Witch?
We need to get to the Castle of Screams where we'll
find the Ice element, and the Keeper who protects it.
But before we kill the Keeper
you need to gear up and heal that hand...
there is still lots to do, sweetheart.
That sarcophagus. Its a secret
passage that leads to the river.
We'll reach the Castle of Screams and the
frozen borough before you can say "borough"
Fucking "borough". Are we there yet?
I don't like sarcasm
sweetheart, no-one in Hell does.
Let's leave this cursed
river before it's too late.
So, borough, castle, cathedral. Is
everything in Hell fucking medieval?
Of course not. This artificial place the
Pentaculum, or whatever they call it now...
Hotel Inferno
the most fucking ridiculous
name they have ever used!
Still, I'd expect nothing less
from that jerk Jorge Mistrandia.
As I was saying, this Hotel
Inferno is not pure Hell
it's more like an artificial tunnel
for entering and exiting parts of Hell.
Hell is life's pain and suffering.
Any shade of pain, any kind of suffering, past,
present or future, that is what the Inferno is made of.
The Mistrandia family and their cult
created Hotel Inferno during the Middle Ages.
All of the pain and suffering they caused in the process
manifests here, like an indestructible living painting.
But it is also very personal.
The Inferno adapts to the soul
of the person who stares into it.
Where are we?
The frozen square. But the structures and surroundings are
changing. Take that building, for example: it wasn't here before.
I... I've been here
before, when I was alive...
when I was young, I know it... but I can't
remember. I feel like... I need to go inside
You'll remember, don't worry.
You will remember.
Farmers they aren't particularly
clever or dangerous on their own.
Unfortunately, they tend to congregate
so... be careful.
Holy mother of fuck!!!
Frank, Ice Keeper. Ice Keeper,
Frank. He's so pretty, isn't he?
Yeah, pretty as a dirty hairy asshole.
Can we get the fuck out of here now?
I don't wanna be swatted like a fly.
Don't worry! He can't hear you.
They're sedating him
We need get out of here
you're still too weak to fight them.
Fuck!!! Stay away from me!!!
Holy shit, holy shit!!!!
Fuck that building, I'm not going
back into that shithole. FUCK
Well, at least we found
this. Let's try this scope.
WHAT THE FUCK!!!!! AAAaaahhhh!
It hurts!
Of course it hurts,
otherwise it won't work.
Ooohh... that is a nasty wound sweetheart.
I'm not gonna die
don't worry...
We have to take care of your shell.
So, do you remember that building now?
I think it's related to my mother...
she was here... but I can't remember why
Well, the Ice element's corresponding
emotions are sadness and loneliness.
If you are seeing memories of your mother I
guess she was really a shitty parent ahahah
Mind your own fucking business Witch
Go and find the mine.
The door is hidden somewhere
on that boundary wall.
Other memories...
Other fucking memories...
they hurt... they hurt so much.
What are we doing here?
We need to find an infernal firearm.
The miners always keep a gun or two in their loot, even if they
don't know how to use them. They are fascinated by that kind of thing.
The miners are slow, but they're
also strong and very aggressive.
You don't fucking say!!
They only die if you decapitate them
or bash their brains into a bloody pulp.
I told you to destroy their heads.
Do you wanna take my place,
you fucking piece of shit?
Now it's gone
Stop sweetheart, take that piece of meat.
I can help you to make a "head lantern".
What I'm supposed to do?
Let me guide your hands.
How?
I'm strapped to your back, it
won't be difficult, just relax.
We are done.
This little friend shines every time you enter in a dark room, you won't
need any torch. Just pay attention to not hurt him, or he'll explode.
Here you go, the Flesh Hand Gun
Are you sure this is going to work?
That fucking Gatling gun is
broken, it jams all the time.
No, my sweetheart. You just
don't know how to use it.
Everything requires a pain
sacrifice here in Hell.
Pain makes infernal weapons work.
If you kill a demon, or if
you're hurt, you get bullets.
How many bullets
Just one
What!!! So I need to kill a demon or anything else with my
bare hands, just to get one lousy bullet for this motherfucker?
Yes, or you can hurt
yourself if you prefer.
This Flesh Handgun can
hold only one bullet.
Only one bullet?!! What a fucking joke.
And how am I supposed to know if the weapon
is ready to shoot? I don't see a magazine.
Infernal Firearms have eyes
one for each shot.
If the eyes are open, it means the gun is
ready to shoot. What else would it mean?
Let's use this portal. These pyramidal
structures will teleport us to the Alchemist.
That kind soul will help to heal your
wounds... and that isn't all he'll do
This is worrying
What?
The Alchemist isn't here.
He's infested the area with those minor demons to
protect his possessions. Stay alert, sweetheart.
Fuck these shits, and fuck that Alchemist.
Back in the cathedral, was
that thing really my wife?
It was just a surrogate.
You retrieved the Fire element, the first layer
of your soul, which is made of love and happiness.
I guess your wife was the thing
you loved most in your life.
Why did I have to kill her?
You need to destroy the emotion that corresponds with
the element: in this case, your happiness and love.
The Alchemist is a lonely demon, and
he is very protective over his stuff.
He hates the idea of strangers
touching his instruments and potions.
Without the Alchemist, we
have to do it ourselves.
Put me on the table... well...
place my shell on the table.
What am I supposed to do?
Now cut off my right hand
Are you sure?
Do you want a new hand or not?
I suppose so
Then chop off my right hand!
Hey Witch, is this your right hand?
Don't you know left from right?
I was kidding, you moron. I was trying to distract you... You
know, before I fucking hurt you? To ease the... No? Whatever
Aaaaaahhh, sweet agony...
now attach it to your stump
How?!!
Just stick it into your wound,
my hand will do the rest.
Take that green potion
on the gauze...
Where the fuck is it? Aahh... shit...
I can't see a shit...
Pour the potion on the gauze...
and there we go.
Just don't use that hand straight away
it isn't ready yet.
When will it be ready?
You'll know, don't worry.
The Alchemist won't be happy that
we've messed around with his stuff.
Speak of the devil.
Calm down motherfucker,
we used your stuff, yes...
Hey!!!! I'm sorry... but we
needed it... do you understand?
Oh fuck off, I'm not good with words.
Let's teach this motherfucker
some old Frank manners.
Subdue him, but don't kill him!
We need him.
Are you calm now? Are we cool?
He respects you. He said that because you
have given him pain, he will gladly help you.
What the fuck is this sadomasochistic bullshit?
So, we are mates because I kicked your ass?
Yeah, there is nothing like an
ass kicking to clear your mind.
He said you are funny, and he doesn't
like funny people. Neither of us do.
How do we get back to the frozen square?
That door leads to many places.
The Alchemist can change
the destination at will.
What now?
We found a proper
weapon, but now it's gone.
You can't wake the Keeper up and
murder him with your bare hands.
There's a secret passage in the Castle of
Screams. It leads to the frozen borough.
That is the only place left where
we can find another hellish weapon.
Welcome to the Castle of Screams.
Can you see those SCREAMER up there?
They're sedating the Ice Keeper
We have to stop their
sublime melody to wake him up.
Wake him up? What a fucking brilliant idea.
This way, through that hole in the wall.
Ooooh, incredible, can
you feel it, sweetheart?
This borough is swarming
with farmers and their beasts.
Hey Witch, look up at the sky, a
big "fuck you" is flying towards you.
Nobody likes your sarcasm here!!!
We need to loot every house
and find a better weapon.
Go into that room.
Check in that pile. Quickly!
It looks like they are macerating a flesh
shotgun between all of those corpses.
Great, another shitty weapon that
needs one kill to get one bullet.
Yes Frank, but this shotgun can be
upgraded. We'll fix that, don't worry.
It has to be there, I can feel it.
We're lucky, this weapon
is strong, very strong.
Dang... dang...
Can you smell that, sweetheart?
It's the stench of the Purulent Chickens,
nasty hideous and dangerous beasts.
Take care
Relax, this is only the henhouse. This is
where they keep their food alive for later.
There aren't any chickens here.
I thought you just said 'there aren't any
chickens here'? Then what the fuck is THAT??!!
That bastard wasn't meant to be here.
Hurry up, take his aborted egg.
Not the eggs on his chest:
they are just decoration
Not the eggs on his chest: they are
just decoration to attract females.
The real egg is in his anus.
Oh, come on!!!
Look in those cages. You
should find some Rotten Gloves.
AAAaaaaahh... what the fuck did he do to me
He impregnated you
What?!!! So that was his... fuuuuuck!!!
I fucking ripped his dick off??!!
Take cover Frank, he's going kamikaze!
What?
Ruuuun!!!!
Wearing them will help
your body to heal faster.
Crack the egg
Hey, are you gonna give me a degree in "fucking infernal
nonsense" after all these shitty lessons about Hell?
I warned you not to make jokes...
pull out the core and squeeze it.
That will help to mask your odor.
They won't recognize
you as human for a while.
Just remember: no loud
noises and don't touch them.
Great
two extra eyes for the flesh shotgun.
Now the shotgun can hold three bullets.
Whoops, does that count
as a loud noise? Fuck!!!!!
I told you we could upgrade this weapon.
If you attach the scope to the flesh shotgun, it will
temporary turn the shotgun into a Flesh Sniper Rifle.
Amazing!
Remember that every sniper shot takes
three eyes, or bullets as you call them.
You will get one eye for killing
a demon or harming yourself.
I realize you are so fucking old that you probably
have Alzheimer's tap-dancing around in your head
but my short-term memory works just fine,
so you don't need to fucking repeat yourself.
I warned you not to make jokes...
Kill all those Screamer, we
need to wake up the Keeper.
I think that was the last one
he's awake
We still have time to make another
upgrade to the flesh shotgun
the harpoon
That will help you to defeat the Ice Keeper
Do we really need to
fight this son of a bitch?
Do you want to resurrect
and save your wife, or not?
Okay... Where do we find this harpoon?
The Alchemist
Aaaaahhhh... what the
fuck is happening to me!!!
We forgot: you were impregnated
by that purulent chicken.
Look at your beautiful son! Ahahahaahah
What's so fucking funny?!
You, sweetheart. It's
hilarious when you suffer
Fuck you Witch, just fuck you...
How many eggs did this
motherfucker squirt into my stomach?
Hey, are you there?
Hey, my perverted friend. We're back
we forgot to take the...
the harpoon
So, you've learned something after all!
You're not as dumb as you look.
Fuck you
He said he will give us the harpoon, but only
if we help him with the "thing" in that room.
Thing? What thing?
I don't know sweetheart,
but it sounds scary.
Aren't you curious to find out?
What the fuck is wrong with you, Witch?
Why do you keep calling me "Witch",
sweetheart? That isn't my name
What the fuck was that!
What the fuck am I supposed to do?
Don't worry, your odor is still
masked by the smell of the egg.
The Alchemist said that he needs a
piece of its body, any piece will do.
Is a piece of shit fine, motherfucker?
Fuck you and this thing!!!
Look out! He's drinking his own blood!
Don't let him turn into a Blood Drunken.
Here we go with that cryptic shit
again. What is that supposed to mean?
When a demon drinks its own blood or the blood
of another demon, it turns into a Blood Drunken.
They are particularly dangerous
because they're so unpredictable.
What the fuck just happened to the weapon?
If you kill a Blood Drunken with
a weapon, it will become enchanted
more lethal, but also fragile.
Heart...
we can use it later.
Take his head too.
Shit, now we're talking. This
hand is... fucking awesome.
Glad you like it, sweetheart.
Eventually, we'll merge perfectly.
What the fuck is that supposed to mean?
I can help you to make a "Void Bag".
Let me guide your hands.
Now you can carry any object you
find, an unlimited number of objects.
But this gift isn't without cost: the more
objects you carry, the more pain you'll feel.
Of course it has to hurt...
of fucking course...
Fuck you, you sadomasochistic fuck, all
this mess just for a lousy harpoon?!!
You should give me all your shit
after what I've been through.
He said that you're right, you did an excellent job,
so he is giving us a gift: a bottle of Christ's Urine
Christ's what? Are you serious?
Oh no, it's not really Jesus's piss
it is just an acid, an
incredibly strong acid.
We call it Christ's Urine here, because..
Well we don't really have
time for that story, do we?
Wait
he said that you need to complete
a ritual before you can use it.
You must drink demon
blood, from a bone chalice
Wow, what a coincidence! I am so thirsty, and I was thinking to myself,
"when are we going to find a refreshing chalice of demon's blood?".
Can you believe that? Thanks so much, you are a life
saver... let's see... bone fucking chalice... and yeah.
We still have that demon's heart somewhere. Here
you go, some drops of blood... some drops of...
what the fuck is wrong with this heart.
Come on!!!
FUCK!!!!
And of course not even a
drop inside the chalice.
Lucky I'm not a fussy drinker, eh?
Do you have an olive? No? Fuck it...
Cheers, motherfuckers!
Now leave me here, on the ground
Why?
You need to get inside that building, Frank
No fucking way
The Keeper will recognise my smell.
If I stay strapped to your
back, he'll find us immediately.
Those walls will protect you
from the Ice Keeper, trust me.
You have to stay silent and invisible, so hide in
there or you won't last a minute. Leave me here.
Don't worry, the Alchemist
will take care of me
Okay, here you go.
Fucking Christ!!!
I'm just getting started with you
Fucking ice, fucking
sliding motherfucking ice.
Solid walls my ass!!!
He's still alive!!!
Just fucking die.
Drink this, motherfucker.
And now, super fucking knife!!!
Why don't you just die, you
little cunt. Oh, fuck off you demon
ohh you fucking bastard
Motherfucker!!!
You made it! The Keeper is gone.
You are perfect, my sweetheart.
I saw it the moment you
stepped into that hotel.
What are you talking about?
Let me guide your hands.
But you haven't got the Ice element yet.
Go into that room.
What is this place?
You'll find a familiar soul in there.
I've told you already: after killing the Keeper, you need
to destroy the corresponding emotion to get the element.
The Ice element's corresponding emotions are
sadness and loneliness, and your mother...
What is going on??!!!
Well, she is the source
of all your sadness...
so...
You have to take her face, sweetheart.
How the fuck is this going to help?
Rip her fucking face off!!!
No!!!
I won't!!!
Do you want to see your wife again,
or would you prefer to rot in here?
Do it now!!!
Now take her place
What you are doing?!! Stay
the fuck back, motherfucker
One final touch, and
we'll merge completely.
You are my new shell, Frank.
What the fuck have you done?
Isn't that what you've always wanted?
To be resurrected, to kill
Mistrandia and save your wife?
What the fuck are you
talking about, Witch?!
You can't save your wife alone, sweetheart.
You need my strength, and I need a new shell.
We're helping each other, you and I.
Shut the fuck up, Witch
Why do you keep calling me Witch? That's the name
of my previous shell, and that shell is gone now.
Who are you?
You know who I am Frank, we
already met in that hotel.
I need to see my face...
You know what Mistrandia used
to call me? The Plague Spreader
W... what have you done to me?!!
Now, we are one
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull