[heavy breathing]
[grunts]
-Time!
-[stopwatch beeps]
Holy shit.
-What is it?
-Guess.
5:19?
5:07.
That's enough for Ridgewood?
Yeah. That's almost enough
for the Olympics.
Let's get you some dinner.
-5:07
-Yeah, man.
[door opens]
Woo.
Hey, how was it?
We are in the presence
of a future Olympian.
Just guess my time.
Okay. Five...
-5:07.
-What?
-5:07? That's incredible.
-Right?
-That's my best.
We made that.
Did you know we made you?
-Okay.
-We made you with our bodies.
-I know.
-Okay.
Go take a shower.
I'm making breakfast for dinner.
[sniffs]
[grunts]
Oh, fuck. [exhales]
-It won't change until you talk to Jim.
-I gotta catch him on a good day.
-He's in a bad mood.
-Yeah, he's always in a bad mood, Brian.
-You just have to sit him down.
-Okay, I hear you, all right?
Brian, I'm looking for work too, but--
[clears throat]
-There he is.
-Hey.
-I'm gonna go get some eggs. Wanna come?
-Sure.
Hey, get milk, too, okay?
["Rip Van Winkle" playing]
♪ You're sleeping all your moments away ♪
♪ I'm counting every breath
That you take ♪
♪ You've been snoozing 20 years
And lengthening... ♪
-God.
-Right?
-Yeah. It's fucking great.
-Yeah, I'm obsessed.
[laughs]
All right. I'm going in.
You staying? Or are you going?
-I'm staying.
-Okay.
♪ ...have given up for good ♪
♪ You say, "Hey" ♪
Hey. Can you bring me something?
I'll think about it.
♪ I said, "Hey" ♪
♪ "I'm all right" ♪
♪ Every time I turn around ♪
[door chimes]
-Hey, Tommy.
-Hey, man.
[humming]
♪ You can spot a hawk a mile away ♪
♪ Cursing all those old blue jays ♪
♪ But every time I turn around ♪
♪ And have given up for good ♪
[tires squeal]
No!
[indistinct chatter]
I guess the driver had a heart attack.
-It's awful.
-Yes.
[knocking on door]
[Naomi] Logan?
Yeah?
The Kellmans are leaving.
Okay.
Are you guys gonna stay here?
I can't afford the rent.
With me being out of work and now...
You should stay at our mountain house.
-No.
-No, I'm serious, Naomi.
I mean, it's just sitting there, and...
You know that Bruce won't have
a problem with it.
I want to help.
I thought you guys were selling...
We are, but...
You just have to leave for a bit
on Sundays during open houses.
-It's nothing.
-I don't know, Ally.
-Having people living there is not--
-It'll be fine.
Okay? You can look after the place.
Logan would kill me if I pulled him
out of school right now.
Okay, look, it's just until
you get back on your feet.
And you'll come back.
I just can't believe it.
He's dead.
Okay.
[sighs]
Ready?
Yep.
[engine turns over]
No, you're not listening
to what I'm saying.
I am the executor.
Well, yes. He was my husband.
What?
Hello?
Can you hear me?
[phone thuds]
Damn it.
[sighs]
[instrumental music plays over radio]
[turns off radio]
How long did you say
we were gonna be here for?
-I don't know, Logan.
-You said I'd be back before graduation.
I said I don't know,
and I'm gonna do my best, okay?
[Naomi sighs]
Can you pass me my phone?
It's at your feet.
[grunts]
Hey, Mom! Shit!
[tires squeal]
Oh, sh--! Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Please tell me he's okay.
[breathing heavily]
He's-- he's not there.
What?
Hey, let's just-- let's just go.
I could have killed him.
[panting]
Mom, your nose.
Oh, shit.
Hey, uh...
Here.
It's just the altitude.
Oh, shit.
-Sorry.
-[laughing] Oh, no worry at all, honey.
Wait a minute.
You must be Logan.
Hi?
Oh, and hold on...
Naomi.
-I'm sorry?
-Oh, forgive me. I'm Martha.
Bruce and Allison's neighbor.
She told me her sister and nephew
were coming in.
She emailed me a picture,
so I knew exactly who you two were.
Oh, okay.
So sorry for what happened
to your husband.
Allison told me all about it.
So gruesome.
You must miss him dearly.
Yeah, we-- we do.
I lost my husband a few years back.
Not a day goes by
that I don't feel the void.
-Mom, should we--
-Oh. Oh, yes.
I won't keep you any longer.
If you need anything,
my house is just west through
the woods. You can't miss it.
Thank you. [clears throat]
It's very kind of you.
It's always nice to know
you have someone nearby.
The quiet out here can get real loud.
Buh-bye now.
[Naomi] You okay?
Yeah.
[engine turns over]
Oh. Whoa.
[Naomi] Yeah.
Leave it to Ally to have
the biggest house on the mountain.
How have we never been here before?
It's fucking huge.
Language.
[sighs]
But yeah.
It is huge.
Okay. Let's go.
Well...
Home sweet home.
[telephone ringing]
Hello?
Uh, yes.
Just got in.
Oh, okay.
[chuckles]
Thanks.
Who was that?
Martha...
the neighbor.
Just...
calling to see if we got in okay.
[cell phone ringing]
I was kind of hoping
I wouldn't have reception up here.
Hello?
Oh.
Hi.
Oh, no, no.
Well, you know...
we've been driving all night, so...
[Naomi sighs]
But, yeah...
Yeah, I know.
He's okay.
I know.
We're at my sister's house.
It's a big, nice house.
I think he likes it.
[Naomi continues speaking indistinctly]
[sighs]
[hinge squeaks]
[door thuds]
[light switch clicks]
[stairs creak]
[exhales]
[yelps]
[breathing heavily]
Jesus.
Logan?
Yeah?
Did you get a chance to sleep today?
Not-- not really.
Well, you'll sleep like a rock tonight.
First open house is tomorrow,
so we gotta be out of here by 11:00, okay?
Okay.
Honey, are you sure you don't want to keep
that stuff in my room?
No, no, it's okay.
Okay.
Well, I'm gonna head to bed.
Love you.
[clock ticking]
[knocking at door]
[car engine idles]
[honking]
[car drives away]
Who are you?
What are you doing on our property?
Ma'am?
What do you want?
Ma'am, this is our house.
-Do you need help?
-No!
Oh, God!
[cries in distress]
[inhales]
[exhales]
You need to get up right now.
The open house is starting in 15 minutes.
Ed, come on. You gotta get
the sign-in sheet out of the car.
-You kidding me?
-The open house ends at five.
Ed is gonna be running the show today,
which means he will turn off
all the lights, he'll lock up.
And Ed, don't forget
to leave the key under the mat.
Got it.
Oh, okay.
-And do I need to do--
-Oh, God, no, no.
You don't have to do a thing,
except one:
Do not come back here until after five,
because we do not want to upset
any potential buyers.
-Mom, why didn't you wake me up?
-Oh, sorry.
-I got a call and then I didn't--
-They scared the hell out of me.
Ed, make his bed.
You two really have to get going.
Really. Now.
[doorbell rings]
Hey, hey. No, hey.
Welcome.
And if you have any further questions
today, just sign in right there,
and otherwise,
take a cookie, look around,
and, uh, I'm here to help.
[Naomi] So, why would she knock?
She's nuts.
Maybe she was lost.
I just don't think the people up here
know what privacy is.
Excuse me? Your card was declined.
Do you have another one we could use?
Oh.
Uh, you know what?
I'll just use cash.
Okay.
Here. I-I got it.
No. Honey, you don't even--
It's birthday money.
-Uh, here you go. No change.
-Thanks.
[clears throat]
Where'd you get birthday money?
Aunt Allison.
It's okay.
Thank you.
[sighs]
You know what?
Let's play a game.
-What?
-Yeah. Come on, it'll be fun.
Uh, if you won the lottery...
what would you do with the winnings?
I don't wanna play.
Come on.
Amuse me.
Fine. Uh...
I'd...
I'd pay off our debt.
Okay.
We're not that bad off.
But I would let you.
I'd buy us a new house back home.
-Can we have a pool?
-And a track.
I'd go to the Olympics in Japan.
-Can I come with you?
-Yeah. First class.
Other than that, I'd probably
just give the rest to you.
No.
I don't need it. You...
You'd probably spend it
on things that matter.
Well, I personally think that...
your dream of going to the Olympics
and owning a home
with the biggest backyard ever
are things that matter.
Thanks.
Okay. My turn.
Debt.
And then I think I would...
start doing photography again.
-Really?
-Yeah. I think so. I used to love it.
You should...
You should start again now.
-Please.
-You should.
You don't have to win the lottery
to do that.
Now you sound like your dad.
["Jingle Bells" playing]
♪ Dashing through the snow ♪
♪ In a one-horse open sleigh ♪
♪ Over the fields we go ♪
♪ Laughing all the way... ♪
[man] I don't think I've seen you before.
[Naomi] Oh. Oh, yeah.
We've been getting a lot of that.
[man] Oh, yeah.
Everybody knows everybody
in these small towns, huh?
Mm-hmm. I have noticed.
It's good to see some new faces.
-Especially pretty ones.
-[Naomi laughs]
I just mean the mountain folk
can get a little, uh...
scruffy at times,
and I am not talking about the men.
Whereabouts are you from?
-Uh, well, we're from California.
-Mom, can we go?
Hey, buddy. How you doing?
Mom?
-Uh, I'm so sorry.
-No.
You didn't have to be rude.
[exhales]
You were flirting.
Logan...
He was just talking to me.
I was being friendly.
Are we allowed to go in yet?
Yeah.
Said it was over at five.
-[Logan] There's no key.
-[Naomi] What? Is it unlocked?
Hello?
[door closes]
Oh, Jesus!
-Oh!
-Did you not-- did you not hear us?
Sorry. I was just locking everything up.
We ran long.
Uh, Jonie's picking me up right now,
so I, uh...
I'm rushing, but your keys--
I left them right there,
and, um, that should be everything.
Okay? So, um... have-- have a great night.
Thank you.
Turn on the light.
Mom.
Have you ever thought about
how, like, weird open houses are?
What?
I mean, you give your keys
to someone you hardly know,
they stand in one room and welcome in
a bunch of complete strangers,
and those people
just roam around the house.
And the realtor doesn't check the house
when it's done, right?
They just... turn the lights off and go?
Okay, well, now I'm not
gonna sleep tonight.
Maybe you shouldn't sleep tonight.
Stop.
[inhales, exhales]
[Man on TV]
But a suicide generally leaves a note.
[Man 2] Well, this one didn't.
Probably didn't have time.
[pauses movie]
I have to pee.
Okay.
[exhales]
[door squeaks]
[sighs]
[telephone ringing]
Just gonna watch it ring?
Hello?
Who is it?
It--
Can you hear me?
Is anyone there?
-What?
-It's just us.
Like, I could just hear echoing.
[Man 2 on TV] Or they might have been
in South America...
[TV continues indistinctly]
[shower running]
Hey, Mom, have you seen my phone?
Uh... no. Sorry, babe.
I haven't.
I'm gonna use yours real quick.
Okay.
[loud thudding]
[grinding noise]
[thud]
[Naomi screams]
-Logan!
-Oh, shoot! Sorry, Mom. God.
You scared me.
The water is ice cold.
I have to go check the tank.
-Wait, that's in the basement.
-I know.
-I heard something banging down there.
-Yeah, it's probably the old pipes.
[stairs creak]
[flashlight clicks off, thuds down]
Oh, come on.
[match strikes]
Ugh.
Jesus.
Okay.
[exhales]
[door slams shut]
Logan?
That's not funny, Logan.
-What?
-You slammed the basement door on me.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
[sighs]
Maybe the door is broken.
[breathing heavily]
-Time! [exhales]
-[stopwatch beeps]
5:34.
-Nice.
-It needs to be faster.
What? That's great.
No. Come on, you don't get it.
It needs to be faster.
Honey, you're on a mountain.
Maybe you ran more than a mile.
No, I mapped it out.
Are you sure you started
the second I left?
You can do it yourself if you want.
Did you find your phone yet?
No, it's gone.
Well, it's not gone.
It has to be somewhere.
-I don't know.
-Who's that?
Hey.
Oh...
It's you guys.
-What are you doing here?
-Right.
This looks bad.
I was just on the back roads,
saw the "For Sale" sign.
[clears throat] Honey.
Logan.
[door closes]
I'm sorry. He's, uh...
No, no need to apologize. I can relate.
-You have teenagers?
-No, but I was one once.
Well, this is my sister's house.
We're just staying here for a bit.
Lucky us.
Yeah. Um, you could call the realtors.
They're the ones that set up the showings.
Got it. Thank you.
I'll do that.
You know what?
While we're here...
would there be any way at all
I can just peek inside?
-So you looking to move?
-Thinking about it.
I'd kill for this kind of privacy.
I don't think I caught your name.
Uh, Naomi.
Naomi. It's nice to meet you. I'm Chris.
Well, I'll let you do your thing.
Don't mind me.
Great.
[keys clacking]
[presses key, "Rip Van Winkle" plays]
♪ You're sleeping all your moments away ♪
[door creaks open]
♪ I'm counting every breath
That you take ♪
♪ You've been snoozing 20 years ♪
No!
Chris?
Hello?
Who are you talking to?
Um, that guy...
wanted to see the house
since he missed yesterday.
He's still here?
He's probably left.
He was just looking around.
I was in my room.
[turns faucet on, off]
Logan?
[sighs]
[blows air]
[camera shutter clicks]
[exhales]
Okay. [exhales]
What do you want to have
with your mac and cheese?
Hot dogs?
Or...
hot dogs?
I'd have to say hot dogs.
Great.
[doorbell rings]
I'll get it.
[exhales]
Hello there, neighbor.
Uh, hi, um...
-Martha.
That's okay, Naomi.
I won't hold it against you. [laughs]
Oh, my goodness. I love this little house.
So nice to see it lived in again.
I can't tell you how sad I was
when I saw that "For Sale" sign go up.
It's definitely a beautiful home.
I'd feel awkward if I didn't tell you...
We came to the open house yesterday.
We just wanted to see the place
one last time
before some stranger snatches it up.
Oh, okay. Yeah...
Oh, I almost forgot.
I do that a lot these days.
Uh... I brought you banana bread.
You and Logan are gonna love it.
Everybody does.
Thank you.
Where is that handsome young boy?
-Oh, he's in the kitchen.
-Oh.
We're making dinner, so...
Well...
I just was gonna swing by
and check in on you.
If you need anything,
don't hesitate to come by.
My husband can't wait
to meet the two of you.
I'm sorry, um...
but I thought...
I thought you had said
your husband passed away.
Passed away?
Oh.
Why would I say something silly like that?
No, no. The Devil himself
couldn't slow him down.
You have yourself a good one.
Buh-bye.
Bye, Martha.
[gasps]
Shit.
Ugh.
[sighs]
Logan!
[clattering]
[flashlight clicks off]
[striking match]
Oh, fuck.
[matches clatter]
[striking match]
[clock ticking]
[exhales]
[sighs]
[urinating]
[flushes toilet]
[inhales, exhales]
[grunts]
[inhales]
[exhales]
Ally, I was married to a plumber
for 16 years.
I think I know
when a water heater is broken.
[breathing heavily]
Thank you.
[sighs]
[panting]
[retching]
[coughing]
Logan?
Logan, sweetheart. Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Oh, honey. Let me walk you home.
No, no, that's all right.
Nonsense. Come on.
Come on.
[grunts]
Where did you come from?
Oh, I always like to start my day
with a nice stroll through the forest.
The nature... the air...
How you liking the neighborhood?
It's fine.
Just hoping that the house sells soon
so that we can go home.
[scoffs] You're not going anywhere
anytime soon.
[chuckles]
I'm sure of it.
Houses up here take some time to sell.
What happened?
I'm-- I'm fine.
Poor boy got sick on his run.
But not to worry. I was watching on.
-Are you okay, honey?
-[sighs] It was just a cramp.
Nothing that a hot shower
and a good breakfast can't fix.
Well, thank you, Martha.
I appreciate it.
Hey, um...
I hope you're both doing all right.
Death...
It's like it moves in and...
never leaves.
Buh-bye now.
She's so weird.
[engine turns over]
[doorbell rings]
I'm here for the water heater.
-Great. Uh, it's just in the--
-In the basement, right?
-Yeah.
-I've been here before.
[presses key, "Rip Van Winkle" plays]
[grunts]
[turns faucet on, off]
Ma'am?
-Oh! Oh, my God!
-Sorry.
Oh, shit. Sorry. Um...
I didn't hear you.
-How did it look down there?
-Normal.
Relit the pilot. It's burning.
Then I changed the thermal coupler.
You should be good to go.
Okay.
-Wll, sorry for the inconvenience.
-No, not at all.
I'm out here almost daily.
This Martha down the road,
she lost her husband a few months back.
She gets kind of sad.
I think she'd flood her house
if it meant me stopping by
for a few hours.
So, her husband did die.
What, she told you something different?
Yeah.
She got Alzheimer's a few months back,
so she gets things
a little confused from time to time.
-That's terrible.
-Yeah.
Oh. And hey, I, uh...
I found this by the water heater.
Thought you might be looking for it.
♪ I'm all right ♪
[music stops]
Found your phone.
Okay. Well, where was it?
In the basement next to the water heater.
Oh.
I must've left it down there
when I went to relight the pilot?
Logan, your phone
has been missing for days.
You just went to check the pilot
last night.
What's your point?
And then I found this...
in the trash.
No. I didn't do that.
Have you been messing with me?
Have I been messing with you?
Are you kidding me?
No, I'm not an idiot, Logan.
First the basement door,
and then the water heater, and now this?
What you talking about?
Is it because you're pissed at me?
I don't know.
Because I have so much on my plate
right now that I can't deal with you too.
I didn't do anything, Mom.
You're completely fucking insane.
-Excuse me?
-Just get out of my room.
-No. What'd you say?
-Get the fuck outta my room.
No! You do not get to talk to me
like that. I am your mother,
and I'm allowed to be upset.
I know this sucks.
I know it's not what you wanted,
'cause guess what?
It's not what I wanted either.
So grow up, Logan.
I fucking hate you.
All you do is put your shit
on other people.
Dad's gone, and you don't even care.
He died in front of me. You haven't
asked me one time if I'm okay.
You dragged me out of school,
brought us to this shitty town.
You don't care if I'm okay with it.
We wouldn't be in this situation
if Dad was still here.
Wanna be an adult and know the truth?
Your father is the exact reason
that we are in this situation.
Your father left us with nothing,
because he was irresponsible,
and he couldn't care less about me
or about you!
[inhales]
I fucking wish it was you.
[exhales]
[thudding]
[clock ticking]
Hello?
[grinding noise]
Oh, my God.
Hey, Dad!
[groaning]
No, no! Dad!
-[gurgling]
-Dad! No!
[panting]
It's okay. It's just a nightmare.
You were having a nightmare.
What?
We have a showing in an hour,
so we gotta go.
Wait a minute. What time is it?
1:00 p.m.
You slept all day.
Logan, let's go!
-Is your room clean?
-Yeah.
-Where are you going?
-For a run.
[breathing heavily]
[gasps] Oh!
-Hi.
-Oh, Naomi, uh...
-Yeah, hi.
-Sorry.
No, no. Um... you just startled me.
Wow. I'm so glad I ran into you again.
-How are you?
-Good.
I'm, uh, just picking up some photos
I had developed.
-Oh, are you a photographer?
-It's just a hobby.
-That's great.
-Uh-huh.
Hey, sorry I sort of disappeared
on you last time.
Couldn't find you.
Figured I'd just get out of your hair.
No worries.
[Chris] I know you don't know me.
Last thing you need right now is
some guy scaring you in the parking lot
and stalking your house. [chuckles]
I just wanted to give you my number...
in case you guys ever need anything.
You know I just know
you guys are new around here.
No pressure.
Well, thank you.
That's very sweet of you.
[door creaks open]
[cell phone chimes]
Naomi, it's Allison.
We got a call from our realtor
that our house was broken into.
Call me.
Logan, get in the car.
Get in the car.
["Silent Night" playing]
Oh, my God.
Mom.
[telephone rings]
Hello?
Mom, we have to call the cops.
[indistinct police radio chatter]
Ma'am, we searched the entire house.
There's no one here.
Did you check the basement?
Yeah. Top to bottom.
It's definitely creepy,
but we didn't see anything.
Mom...
Uh, well, we had an open house here
a few days ago,
so maybe someone found
a spare key laying around, or...
Or maybe someone stayed.
I know it sounds stupid, but other things
have happened before this.
Things moving from one room to another.
Weird phone calls.
From anyone in particular?
No. No one would respond.
Don't look at her. I'm not lying.
Okay, look.
I know that we probably sound
like the crazy new people in town,
but this is my sister's house, and we're
supposed to be taking care of it, so--
Look, I understand the fear
in these situations.
Okay? I do.
But it's likely the front door was
unlocked and some kids snuck in.
Are you kidding me?
Look at this.
You think some kids did this?
It's not uncommon. Okay?
Kids get bored. They do weird things.
They were probably trying to scare
the newcomers.
Okay. [clears throat]
Is there nothing else you can do?
If it makes you feel any better,
we can come by in the morning.
Yeah. Yeah, please do.
Okay.
Let's go.
You all have a good one.
[door opns]
-[Logan sighs]
-[door closes]
[Naomi exhales]
We have to stay in a hotel.
Honey, we're fine.
No, Mom. Something is clearly going on.
Look, I know you think I did
all that shit before, but I didn't.
-I swear to God.
-Okay. No, but you heard them.
There's nothing to worry about.
Mom, please.
Logan, we can't afford it right now.
Okay?
We're fine.
Hey.
Mom...
-I'm going to bed.
-Okay.
You all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
You wanna stay in here tonight?
Sure.
What is this?
It's just the guy from the store.
He gave it to me
in case we ever needed anything.
He was just being friendly.
You can throw it out if you want.
I don't care.
I'm gonna go brush my teeth.
Okay.
[doorbell rings]
[clock ticking]
Logan?
[doorbell rings]
Hey.
Chris. What are you doing here?
[Logan] Uh, Mom.
It's okay. I called him.
The cops weren't worried at all, huh?
No.
-They said some kids probably did it.
-Well, that's possible.
A lot of them are assholes up here.
It didn't feel like kids.
Oh, what did it feel like?
Like...
personal.
Like someone had been here before.
I don't know. Maybe I'm-- maybe I'm crazy.
Well, it's just the two of you
up here, huh?
Yeah.
[locks door]
Anything?
All clear.
Thank you.
Yeah.
-Hey.
-Oh.
-Appreciate it.
-Yeah. Need anything else?
Uh, no, I'm good, buddy.
Yeah. Go get some rest.
Hey, thank you for doing this.
Yeah. Not a problem.
Look, this place is weird sometimes.
Yeah, it took me a while
to get used to it, too.
I'm sure it's nothing, but, uh...
I'll be here.
I'm sorry, um...
-if I was rude before. I just--
-No, no, no, no. No need to explain, man.
We're all good.
-Night.
[exhales]
[thudding]
[thudding, door creaks]
[clock ticking]
Chris?
[engine turns over]
Chris. Chris!
Chris!
[grunts]
[panting]
[exhales]
[toilet flushes]
Logan...
[screaming]
[choking]
[Naomi groaning]
[Naomi quivers]
[Naomi exhales]
[groans]
No.
Logan.
Logan?
[footsteps approaching]
[gasps]
No, no!
No.
Aah-- aah. Aah.
[crying]
No. Please, no.
Please, no.
Logan!
[grunts]
[coughing]
[crying]
[screams]
No! No!
[crying]
[fingers crack, screaming and crying]
[fingers crack, screams]
[crying]
[gasps]
[shivering]
No! [crying]
[groans]
Fuck.
Logan!
Hey, Mom! Mom!
Mom?
Mom!
Mom, hey.
Mom! Mom, what happened?
-Look at me.
-Logan.
-Here, get up.
-[Naomi cries]
Get up. Come on.
You're so cold. [crying]
What did he do?
What did he do to you?
I should have listened to you.
Where's Chris?
He's dead.
What? Oh, my God.
Oh, no.
He's gonna come back.
We have to get out.
We're gonna get out. Okay?
Yeah, yeah.
[Naomi whimpers]
Look at me.
We're gonna call the cops.
-I don't have a phone.
-I need to go downstairs, Mom.
-No, baby. No!
-Hey, I'm gonna be fine.
I'm gonna be fine, okay? I love you.
Mom.
I love you so much.
I love you, baby.
[Naomi cries]
[ragged breathing]
["Rip Van Winkle" playing]
♪ You're sleeping all your moments away ♪
♪ I'm counting every breath
That you take ♪
♪ You've been snoozing 20 years ♪
♪ And lengthening that beard ♪
♪ You whittled a squirrel for me ♪
♪ And counted lemons on your tree ♪
♪ And every time I turn around ♪
♪ And have given up for good ♪
You say, "Hey"
[phone disconnect tone]
♪ "It'll be all right" ♪
♪ I said, "Hey" ♪
♪ "I'm all right" ♪
♪ And every time I turn around ♪
♪ And have given up for good ♪
♪ You're haunted by the things
That you've seen ♪
♪ I know they give you terrible dreams ♪
♪ We all know you'll wake up soon ♪
♪ And rattle off that dust ♪
♪ You can spot a hawk a mile away ♪
♪ Cursing all those old blue jays ♪
♪ But every time I turn around ♪
No.
♪ And have given up for good ♪
[Naomi] Logan!
[grunting]
[panting]
Mom! Mom?
[Naomi] Help!
[Naomi] Logan!
[grunts]
[clanging]
[ragged breathing]
[Naomi cries]
Mom?
Logan! [yelps]
[Logan gasps]
[Naomi gurgles]
Mom?
No.
[Naomi gasping]
Run! Run!
No! Mom!
[Naomi falls]
[gasps]
[screaming]
[muffled groaning]
No!
-No!
-Now run!
Help!
Somebody help me!
Aah!
[panting]
[branches snapping]
[footsteps approaching]
[gasping]
[coughs]
[screams]
Please!
Don't hurt me! Please.
No! Don't hurt me! No!
No!
[screaming]
[instrumental music playing]
["Evanesce" playing]
♪ I thought you'd blow up my phone ♪
♪ At 5:00 a.m., and I'd call you ♪
♪ I watched the mountains and trees ♪
♪ Blue, foggy breeze surrounds you ♪
♪ Thought it was you ♪
♪ That I saw there ♪
♪ Hands reaching out there ♪
♪ You're farther ♪
♪ Evanesce ♪
♪ You were away for a while ♪
♪ I was too long to follow ♪
♪ Hands reaching in there ♪
♪ You're farther ♪
♪ Evanesce ♪