The world is not made of atoms.
It is made of stories.
Aah!
Hello, child.
You've left your camera!
Suck it, creep-o!
Creep-o.
That's a new one.
What is life but a story?
A single narrative thread
in the tapestry
that binds us all.
And as with all stories,
it is not the length
of the tale that resonates,
it is the quality
of the content within.
I beseech you, friends,
that even as we mourn,
let us celebrate as a tribute
to this young man's story.
Let us seek solace that
we have been granted impunity
from eternal rest.
That death would not
eradicate us,
but in the pages of life
we will continue forth
and we cannot die!
Uh, and now a reading
from Corinthians.
Thank you for coming.
Please drive safely.
Sorry for your loss.
Thank you for coming.
I wouldn't.
This world,
this business,
it's not as neat and tidy
as one might expect.
The coffin...
It's so small.
A tragic thing,
indeed.
Montgomery Dark,
resident mortician,
indentured servant
to the great beyond.
Dark. Really?
Mm.
It's a family name.
Oh, I'm Sam.
Sam.
My condolences.
Were you close with the child?
Oh, no. I'm sorry.
I saw a sign out front.
Sign?
Yeah, "Help wanted."
Are you still looking?
Yes.
Always.
Please.
Have you any experience
in the mortuary arts?
No, but I'm a fast learner.
Mm, most people would
find it unmanageable.
Huh.
I'm not most people.
We shall see.
Please have a seat.
This is... This is
one serious collection of books
you've got here.
The mere tip of the looming,
lumbering iceberg,
I'm afraid...
An archive of the various ways
in which clients
have found themselves passing
through our hallowed halls.
So, these are all stories
about how people died?
Not just how,
my dear, why.
Huh.
That's pretty cool.
Yes, it is, isn't it?
Tell me one.
Tell you one what? A story.
Something...
dark and twisted.
Something awesome.
Mm. Perhaps we should
stick to business.
We have much to do.
Oh, come on, Monty.
If I'm going to be working here,
I need to know what
I'm getting myself into.
You are not hired yet,
young lady.
Right because you have
a stack of applications
to go through.
Something dark,
twisted, and "awesome," eh?
Well, see how
this one grabs you.
Uh, someone's in here.
Hoping you're
not trying to hide from me.
I wouldn't dream of it.
Okay.
Meet me on the veranda in 10?
Look, I've just got to say that
talking with you back there,
I felt this connection, and
I feel like you felt it, too.
A-Am I being crazy?
I'm being crazy.
I'll see you on the veranda.
Ahh.
Okay.
Ahh!
Damn it.
Aaaah!
Can somebody help me?
Help me, please!
Aaaaah!
It's not bad.
I was expecting something
a bit more substantial.
Maybe an ironic comeuppance
or a big twist, but...
it was fun.
Fun?
Well, I have more stories.
Many, many more.
I was...
just warming up.
Here.
Sign here,
initial here and here.
It's a bit far-fetched,
don't you think,
an octopus
in a medicine cabinet?
It was not an octopus.
And.
It is not the validity
of the story
that concerns me,
but the message within.
And the message is...
don't stick you nose
where it doesn't belong?
In a most basic sense, yes.
But on a deeper level,
it is about the universal
balance of all things.
Universal balance?
There we are...
Nice and neat.
Shall we begin?
The foyer, French for
where the fire is kept.
Oh, who are these ghouls?
Ghouls?
These are morticians,
my dear,
some of whom were called
to serve in this very house.
A distinguished group,
to be sure.
Yeah, distinguished.
Come.
There's much to see.
Of course, you've already seen
the viewing parlor.
Very elementary.
The mourning sit here
and up here
resides the rhapsodist.
How old are you?
Ironic, is it not,
that one so old would preside
over the passing
of one so young.
So, what is the story here?
I would rather not.
Some tales even I find
too unsettling to recount.
Tell me another one, then.
You say you have better stories.
I want to hear them.
You've heard the phrase,
"better safe than sorry,"
I presume?
Well, this young man
had to learn it the hard way.
Karl Marx said that
social progress can be measured
by the social position
of the female sex.
Now, ladies,
as a straight, white male,
I'm going to be the first
to admit the tides are turning.
The patriarchy is falling,
and in its place
is a brave, new world
of equality and sexual freedom.
A world where both men and women
are entitled to have sex
whenever and with
whoever they please
as long as they do so safely
and with the proper protection.
Just... like... that.
You're empowered.
Please, have some condoms.
Guys, listen...
We are having a party tonight
at the Sig Delt house.
You should stop by.
Okay?
So... is that true
about the patriarchy?
No, idiot.
Patriarchy is solid.
Karl Marx said that...
You don't even know
who Karl Marx is.
Yeah.
Yeah, I do.
Yes, I do.
Jakey, can you please tell me
what we're doing here?
We are providing an important
service to the incoming freshmen
who are young, impressionable,
and vulnerable.
Guys, it is our job to help them
make informed decisions.
And that decision is to have sex
with you hopeless jerks
at the party tonight.
A-And what, the girls
who take the condoms
are the ones who want to party.
Oh!
And party means sex.
Anyone want condoms?!
Condoms suck.
Uh, hey!
Miss!
Hey, excuse me,
Oh, Miss.
Hey! Can I...
Hey, I was just wondering
if I can offer you
a, uh, prophylactic?
I'm sorry?
Um, uh,
it's slang for a condom.
We're giving them away to show
how the patriarchy is dying.
You know,
it's almost dead.
I mean,
we're white guys and...
Do you know who Karl Marx is
'cause he would want you
to have one?
Uh, thanks.
No problem.
Uh, just one
'cause we've got plenty,
and they're all free. Hey, buddy.
Hi.
So, um, the girls lacrosse team
just showed up at the booth,
and, um...
we're out of bananas.
Wha... Like,
the lacrosse team?
The girls lacrosse team.
That's like the fastest sport
on two feet.
You got this?
Yeah. Yeah,
I'll do my best.
Okay.
Uh, yeah, we don't have
a girls lacrosse team.
I'm Jake.
Uh, Sandra.
You don't look like a freshman.
No. It's 'cause
I'm not.
I just come to these things
to get laid.
Oh, me too.
What?
I w...
I was...
I-I'm joking.
I-I'm working at
the stay safe booth over there.
I-I'm just trying to give back.
I don't know.
I'm just doing my part.
I like that.
Hey, uh, Jake!
Could I just borrow you
for one second?
Yeah.
I'm so sorry.
I got to go, but,
um, yeah.
It was a... It was a pleasure
meeting you, Sandra.
You know, um...
there's a party tonight
at the Sig Delt house.
We're throwing it.
Uh, it's probably going to be
fun, so you should come.
Yeah. Maybe.
Maybe?
Yeah, maybe is, uh...
Maybe's great.
Okay, well, uh, maybe
I'll see you there.
Uh, hang on!
Yep!
Yeah!
Did you want
some liquid courage?
Hmm? No.
Okay. Uh, bottoms up!
Something wrong? You've kind of
been acting a little weird
ever since this morning?
No, I'm fine. I'm just, uh...
yeah, I'm just laying low.
Oh, yeah, that's cool.
I'm laying low, too.
You know, just laying real low
'cause I'm cool.
We're cool.
Oh, is that girl coming?
What?
The girl from this morning.
I don't know, maybe.
Cool. Maybe, who cares?
Whatever. You know.
Whoa!
Hey, what is that?
No! No! No!
Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait!
Oh, you dog!
What?
Jenny Si...
Jenny Simon, the head
of the history department?!
Yeah, I had to brush up
on the cultural relevance
of Mesopotamia
in the 21st century.
How do you do it?
I mean, you look good.
That's a given.
There's something else.
It's...
Carter, girls aren't
some complex puzzle
that need to be solved.
They're the same as you and me.
They want the same things.
They... They want sex and...
And a companion.
I mean, like everybody,
they just... want to feel
like they're worth it.
Look, if you can give
a girl that,
even if it's just
for one night...
you can have any girl
that you want.
Look alive,
Sig Delts!
I am a robot,
and this is my fuel.
Aah!
Let's do it!
Hey, haven't you heard
about all of those missing guys?
What guys are you talking about?
Yeah, there's fliers
all over campus.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, those guys,
that's terribly sad.
It's heartbreaking.
Aren't you worried
about your safety?
I mean,
you barely know me.
I could be...
a serial killer.
Are you?
I have something for you.
Oh, yeah?
What is it?
Oh, great.
That's...
Yeah, you know, uh, I don't need
one of these, right?
Yeah but I want to be empowered.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
Empowered.
Just placing it over and...
Okay.
Turn over.
What? Turn over!
Hey, good morning!
How did it go last night?
As expected.
Oh, yeah!
Yeah, so, that's like,
number 67, right?
It's really weird
that you know that.
Hey, uh, did you... did you
forget to wear a condom?
You know, maybe, uh,
maybe she had
poison ivy or something.
It's probably
just from friction.
Mm, well, either way,
you probably should
get that checked out.
Uh, it's fine.
Okay.
You know better than me.
Yes I do.
Yeah, you do.
Okay. I'll see you later
'cause I got some things to do.
Son of a bitch.
So, you got a case
of the cooties, did ya?
Um, c-come here.
You know,
I think it's one of...
Mm. You think
it's this one? Yeah.
Well, if it's this one...
we're gonna have to amputate.
W-What?
I'm just screwing with you, kid.
They won't let me near a scalpel
and... for good reason.
No, I'm sure it's nothing
a good ol' fashioned dose
of penicillin won't clear up.
Let's just take a look
at your labs here.
Okay.
Wait a second.
What's wrong?
Must be... Ah, this must be
some sort of a mix up.
Just lay down on this table
for me, will ya?
What do you mean a mix up?
We'll get to that in a second.
Just lay down.
I wanna... Something.
Yeah, just relax.
Take a deep breath in.
Good, again.
What the hell?
What? What?
What's wrong?
Wha... Wha...
Um... no,
everything's... fine.
I'm just gonna... go check
on something really quick.
You just stay put.
I'll be right back.
No. No. No. No.I'll be right back!
What do... What do you
have to go check on?
523...
This is Telecom Industries.
Can I help you?
Hello?
No!
Please. Please. Please. Please.
Please. Please.
Hello? Hi, Sandra?
Yeah? It's Jake. What's up?
Jake?
Yeah, from, uh... from the party
last night, remember?
We, um... We hung out.
Oh, hey. What's up?
Not much.
Not much at all.
I just, um... I've got
the afternoon...
...off,
and I was wondering if maybe
you wanted to hang out?
Yeah, okay.
Okay. Okay, yeah.
Yeah, that's great.
Um... what's
your address?
No. No. No. No.
Welcome, brother.
It was our forefather,
Ezekiel Durkas, who wrote...
Durkas wrote.
That a man can measure his worth
by the notches on his bedpost.
Each groove represents
not only a conquest for himself,
but for the brotherhood
as a whole.
The honor is ours to share.
It was recently
brought to my attention
that Jake of the family Matthews
has reached
the sacred number 67.
No. No. No.
Put it back.
A holy number which represents
the 67 founders
of our great fraternity
and is honored
with the 67 cherry trees
spread across this great land.
67 cherries for Sig Delt and
67 cherries for Brother Matthew.
You got to sit down. I don't want to sit!
It's tradition!
Come on.
You, sir, are bronze.
Give me your keys.
I am so proud of you, man.
Brother Matthews,
as is your right,
you may now hang your name
on the sacred mantel.
Great.
Thank you, Todd.
No. No. No.
No. No. No. No.
We're gonna need more.
Aah!
Keys.
Give me the keys.
Hey!
Can I help you?
Uh, I-I'm looking for Sandra.
Sandra Patricia Marie,
get downstairs now!
Oh, God!
God! God! God!
Oh! Oh, God!
Okay.
It's perfectly natural.
Natural?
Are you kidding me?
In what world is this natural?!
You!
What did you do to me?!
What did I do to you?
I thought you wore protection.
Um... I...
I-I did...
I didn't.
I'm sorry.
You got...
You got to understand.
I-I used to be fat.
Like, I was like,
really, really fat.
Like, kids would pick on me.
They... They'd throw stuff
at me, okay?
Girls... Girls like you
wouldn't even look at me...
until the day
that I made a decision
that I was going
to change myself.
And then things got better.
Okay, they got better,
and I got worse.
Look at me.
I'm hideous.
I'm a monster.
And I'm fat again!
Sandra where are you going?
Where are you...
Hey. Looks like
I'm free after all.
It's nearly there.
Big breath.
I got a question for you.
How is this going to work?
Where is it going to come out?
Uh, well, uh...
It's going to come out
the same it got in.
You got a blanket?
That was a story.
Ah, you mean it? Absolutely.
There was romance,
suspense,
horror,
social commentary.
I mean it was...
It was everything
a story should be and more.
Now you're being glib
aren't you?
Only a little.
Wait here.
Don't touch anything.
Impressive,
isn't it?
Be careful.
I wouldn't want you
to take a tumble.
Shall we continue?
This house was built with all
the modern conveniences...
...of 1825.
Coming?
The embalming room.
This is where the sausage
is made, so to speak.
Hm.
Every corpse tells a story.
It is our task to listen
to uncover the clues
and extract the truth.
Looks like you're extracting
a little more than just truth.
Care to give this one a try?
Wow, she looks...
perfect.
Look closer.
The devil is in the detail.
Here.
See this mark?
Ugh.
The bed sore... very unusual
in one so young.
And if we examine
the upper palate,
we will find traces
of magnesium,
an essential element
used to treat patients
in perpetual catatonic states.
Oh, and she was married.
Indeed.
Is there an inscription?
"Till death do us part."
Oh, how...
predictable.
"Till death do us part."
But what if even death
provides no reprieve?
Do you, Carol Peters,
take Wendell Owens
to be your husband
to have and to hold
in sickness and in health,
till do you part?
I do.
And do you,
Wendell Owens,
take Carol Peters
to be your wife
to have and to hold
in sickness and in health
till death do you part?
Aaah!
Hey. Hey.
Yes?
Hi. Uh, can you buzz me in?
I forgot my keys.
Sorry, what? Huh?
C-Can you... Can you buzz me
into the building?
Thank you.
Hey, old timer.
Hey, Miss Avery,
how are you?
Look at all that food.
Special occasion?
Yeah, something like that.
I'll get that for you. I love a good meal.
My girlfriends and I
went on this
all-inclusive cruise
last spring. Uh-huh?
Have you ever been on one
of those all-inclusive cruises?
No, I... I take care of Carol.
Oh, you got to go.
All the food you can eat,
and it's all free.
That's the all-inclusive part.
When Arthur was alive,
we never went anywhere,
but now that he's gone,
I am seeing the world.
That does sound nice. Are you coming?
Uh, no, I don't like elevators,
especially this one.
I'm going to take the stairs.
12 stories at your age?
How old do you think I am?
I get it.
Got to stay in shape.
I'm going to Cancun
this Christmas.
Uh-huh. They have nude beaches.
Neat.
Yeah.
Tell Carol I said...
It's spring time in Raven's
End, and love is in the air.
Stay tuned for
the local forecast
where things are going
to get... foggy.
It's summer.
The locals are wondering
if they will ever see the sun.
Bundle up, Raven's End.
Fall is in the air.
What was that?
Carol?
It's fine.
So, you, uh, ever thing about
taking some of these walls out?
Giving yourself
more of a open floor plan?
How's she doing?
Uh, she's...
She's doing well.
She's... well?
How can that be?
Yeah, I know.
It's hard to believe.
But you know her...
She's a fighter.
Her vitals are solid.
I'd keep an eye
on her bed sores...
Sorry.
Uh, she's improving?
No, that's not what I said.
She's... stabilized.
So how much time does she have?
What are we talking?
Uh, it's...
It's kind of tough to say.
Um, at this rate...
another year,
possibly more.
A year?
Yeah.
Possibly more.
How am I supposed
to make this work?
Al we have is... is bills
and bed pans
and vacant,
empty stares.
I just can't do this anymore.
I might have something
that could help.
It's a pain medication,
but it's... it's very strong.
If Carol were to take
more than two of these
in a 24-hour period,
the results could be disastrous.
Great. I will
add it to the rest.
You understand what
I'm telling you, Wendell?
What?
Those pills right there...
they don't leave a trace,
so it would be impossible
for someone
to determine
if she took too much.
She would just drift off
to sleep, not wake up.
Oh.
Yeah, "oh."
You look really nice tonight.
Mm.
I got something for you.
It's a surprise.
Here.
I'll open it for you.
That is an Arctic hare.
It's pretty creepy, right?
Sorry.
I know they used
to cheer you up.
Carol I need you to...
do something for me.
'Cause I can't do
this alone anymore.
Can you give me a sign
that you are there?
Please?
Do it right now.
Right now.
Now!
I'm sorry.
Here we go.
That's it. You're all done.
You're all done.
Carol?
No! Oh, no!
Carol come on!
Get it up!
Come on!
I'm so sorry.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Sorry. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry.
Honey?
Aah!
Kubler residence.
She fell on an Arctic hare,
and, um, there's a lot of blood
and, uh, I don't know
what to do.
An Arctic hare?
What are you talking about?
I gave her the pills,
alright?!
And then she moved.
And she grabbed my arm,
and I turned her over.
She moved? Yes, she moved!
Okay?!
Now she's dead.
She's really, really dead,
and I don't know what to do!
What do I do?!
Help!
You got to get that body
out of your apartment.
Toss it in the ocean
and pray the sharks do the rest.
What? Just do it!
Don't call back.
Ugh.
Aah!
Hey, buddy,
hold the elevator for me.
- Thank you a million.
- Yeah.
Hey, I said, hold it!
We don't want to wait
20 minutes for the next one!
Hold the elevator! I'm sorry.
Aah!
Wendell?
Wendell,
is that you?
Hey, Mrs Avery.
Well, is the elevator stuck?
Looks that way, huh?
Um... I wouldn't worry
about it, though.
Well, I never heard it make
that sound before.
Maybe I'd better
call the police. No!
Uh, listen, I'm sure she'll come
back to life any second now.
I'm fine.
All the same,
I'm calling the police
just in case.
No, Mrs Avery. No,
you don't need to do that.
Mrs Avery!
Aah!
I wish I'd never...
Carol?
In sickness and in health,
TILL DEATH DO US PART.WOMAN: Sir?
Sir? In sickness and in health,
till death do us part.
In sickness and in health,
I kind of hated that story.
Oh.
I mean, he did what anyone would
do in his situation,
yet he was punished for it.
We must each fulfill
our destiny, young lady.
Who are we to question fate?
Yeah, and what was
Wendell's fate?
He went mad.
He was committed
to the local asylum.
Kirksdale?
Do you know it?
Everyone knows Kirksdale.
A vile and tragic place.
What wood is this?
Oh, you'd be surprised
what we find in people's colons.
Oh.
Ready for the best part?
Yeah.
When the house was built
at the turn of the century,
there was no electricity.
We had to think of creative ways
to keep the bodies cold.
Hence,
the sub basement.
Give me a hand,
will you?
Gently.
Don't take this the wrong way,
but all of your stories...
are a little predictable.
Predictable?
Someone commits a sin,
they pay a horrible price.
Rinse, repeat.
The form may be familiar,
but the message is timeless.
No evil deed goes unpunished.
You don't really
believe that, do you?
Completely.
You're going to love
this next part.
This is the heart of the house.
This poor soul's journey
has come to an end.
In dust we started,
to dust we return.
Wait!
I lied.
I'm not here for the job.
I'm here for him.
You said no evil deed
goes unpunished...
but you're wrong.
In real life,
bad guys win all the time.
Logan is proof.
It's all my fault.
Please, can I see him
one last time?
I want to tell you his story.
And with the handsome
knight by her side,
the princess knew that she would
be safe...
...forever and ever.
I wish I had a knight
like that to keep me safe.
You don't need a handsome
knight, you got me, you twerp.
Now go to sleep or your parents
are going to kill me.
Aw.
Denver residence.
- Hey, sexy.
- Hey, Bart.
Want me to grab
some drinks on my way over?
What part of "no guests allowed"
are you still grappling with?
So, now I'm a guest, huh?
Well,
no pervs allowed, either.
I'm not a perv.
I'm just worried
about you, is all...
Home alone with that psycho
on the loose.
Plus, I haven't seen
you in a week.
I'm dying over here.
Well, put an ice pack on it
because you're not coming over.
Okay, I get it.
Have fun babysitting.
Aah!
Mind if I join you?
Bart, you creep!
Well, I didn't see
that one coming.
Hi, Sam.
It looks like we're going to be
a little later than we expected.
Might be a good idea
to check in on Logan
every one in a while
to make sure
he's actually sleeping
and not playing
in his closet again.
Or the hamper.
This is Dr. Kubler.
Honey.
Honey, shh, shh.
If you get hungry, help
yourself to anything you like.
Call me if you have
any questions.
Bye.
Power outages have been
reported throughout
the Boggy Bay area.
What did you want to show me?
Oh, you know. Just the seven
wonders of the world.
Why don't we start
with Mount Rushmore.
I actually don't think
Mount Rushmore's one of the s...
Ohh.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we interrupt your regularly
scheduled programming
for an Action 4 News
special report.
The Kirksdale
Mental Asylum, or KMA,
home to some of the most
dangerous criminals
in this country was thrown
into chaos earlier today
when a power surge fried
the building's security system,
and a bloody riot broke out.
Uh, we can't confirm
at the moment
whether or not
any of the inmates
actually managed to escape
the perimeter of the property.
But out of an abundance
of caution,
we're asking residents
keep your doors locked tonight
and keep an eye out for crazies.
Yep.
Stay tuned to Action 4 News
for the latest updates
on this story as it develops.
We now return you
to your regularly scheduled
programming.
So, what'd you think
of, uh, Stonehenge?
Smaller than I imagined. Hey, what?
Got a killer on our hands,
so I'm gonna make this quick.
"Caucasian, 36 years old,
stands about 6'10", chained.
A dozen teenagers
turned up dead.
All the victims have been young,
and all the victims
have been female
have been babysitters.
He has no fear,
no remorse.
He will stop at nothing
to get what he wants.
And what he wants, mind you...
is blood.
Aah!
Can you help me?
Do you know where you are?
This isn't my house.
I'm going to be in trouble.
You're bleeding really badly.
I know.
Let me help you.
No.
Don't.
Wait. Wait.
Wait.
Wait!
What are you doing?
I'm... I'm trying
to help you.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Why the hell aren't you
answering the phone?!
Listen there was a riot
over at the asylum,
and a psychopath escaped.
It's the same one responsible
for all those kids
that were mutilated and...
Ugh. Lock the doors
and stay with Logan
until we get home.
Oh, my God!
Sam?!
Hello?! Sam?!
Aah!
Where's the boy?!
- Logan?!
- Sam?!
Where... is he?!
Where's the boy?!
Wait.
You're not a killer.
You're right.
I'm not!
This is over.
You're right.
Aah!
- What was that?
- I'm going around the back.
Harold, wait.
Aah!
Is it over?
It's over.
This is for ruining my dinner.
Aah!
The window's broken.
Stay behind me.
Oh, my God!
Who is that?
Sam?
It's the babysitter.
Logan!
We interrupt your program
for another Action 4 News
special report.
Police have confirmed
that the missing patient
is Charlotte Gibbons.
Known locally as the
Boggy Bay Tooth Fairy,
Gibbons was convicted on 12
counts of murder and 10...
Debra?!
I can't find Logan anywhere!
I've done his room!
Ohh, I see what you did there.
Burying the lead
to throw me off... very clever.
But I'm still confused.
Why come back?
You have your collection...
...and I have mine.
You're not going to tell anyone
my story, are you?
Oh, of course not,
my dear.
I'm sorry.
In real life,
the bad guy wins.
Oh, bravo!
Bravo, my dear.
But you committed
one fatal storytelling sin.
You have underestimated
your audience.
The job is yours.
There's no use running.
You're only making this harder
on yourself.
Getting to know the place?
What is this?
I believe it's a library.
You know what I mean.
You know,
I was once just like you,
a traveler from the outer
regions of experience
unbounded by the laws of nature,
or so I thought.
Then I found my way
to his house,
this... assignment.
And everything changed.
Throughout history, it has been
the role of the storyteller
to remind us that each and every
action creates a ripple,
each and every story
has repercussions.
And you would be surprised
how many stories
in this library...
are yours.
I told you...
No-one escapes fate.
I don't care
what you say, old man.
I'm the master of my own fate.
I say how my story ends.
Ends?!
Oh, my dear girl.
Your story is just beginning!
Aaaah!
Aaaaaah!
I'd better get going.
So soon?
I was just about to make dinner.