Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
Ladies and gentlemen.
The Producers of this picture
thought it would be only fair
To give you ample warning of
what you are about to witness
This motion picture contains
elements of horror,
Terror,
and.... Demonic possession.
So, if you are of a weak
disposition or easily offended,
please leave this screening at
once.
The management will be more than
happy to refund your tickets.
Have they gone?
Good.
Those of you who are brave
enough to stay
You have been warned.
So, without any further ado
It is my pleasure,
Or should I say displeasure?
To present our feature
presentation...
Have we passed Westwood Station?
Oh, no, no, two more stops.
No need to fret, pilgrim, just a
force of habit is all.
Care for a gut warmer?
Woah! Strong stuff!
Takes some getting used to I
guess.
George Walker
Oh! George Walker?
Not THE George Walker, the
American oil tycoon?
I would have had you as being
much older.
You're thinking of my Pa.
Ah... so you are
A Junior.
I don't think I got your name.
Jeffrey Bank.
Pleasure, I'm sure.
So, what's a Yank oil man doing
in this part of the world?
I'm visiting an old friend from
my Oxford days
He just acquired a 'Westwood
Manor'
What? You didn't have me pegged
for an Oxford scholar?
No no no... it's just Westwood
Manor
Now that is interesting.
Interesting how?
Oh no its just... local gossip
I wouldn't want to waste your
time with all that nonsense
Well, until this train pulls
into Westwood Station
I got all the time in the world
Spin me your nonsense.
Well then... I mean
Westwood Manor has stood empty
for most of it's life
People have come and gone
But they've never stayed more
than a year or two.
Then a few winters back a strange
individual took up residency
He never went into the village
He was something of a hermit
And then, ah, well,
The noises started
And every night the noises got
louder,
and more terrifying
The villagers wouldn't even
leave their homes after nightfall
And then, just as suddenly
The noises stopped
And the house stood silent and
empty once more.
And the hermit? What became of
him?
Well no one knows
But the villagers were so
terrified...
Even the bravest will not enter
that house to this day
You can't try frightening me,
You English folk are as slow as
a Sunday afternoon
My station's just coming up
It's been very nice passing a
bit of time with you.
And, ah...
Tread carefully, Mr Walker
You're not in Texas any longer.
Must you drive so fast?
Cars are built for speed.
No point driving if you're gonna
go slow.
But you know that it makes me
nervous.
We're all going to die,
Elizabeth
The one thing we can choose is
if we do it with style.
And crashing into a ditch is
with style?
Very well
Thank you.
What's the matter?
You've barely spoken since we
left London
Nothing, I'm fine
You're a terrible liar, you know
that?
I wish we weren't coming this
weekend.
Why?
What are you afraid of?
What if nobody likes me?
How could anyone dislike you?
You're simply charming.
Well I'm not exactly...
Not exactly what?
I'm just a solicitor's secretary
I'm not in the oil business,
or...
A famous tennis player
A famous tennis player who hasn't won
a match in the last two tournaments
At that rate my dear
You're far more successful than
me.
Christine.
Hello George.
I didn't see you board the train
at Paddington
Been some time.
Hasn't it?
How have you been keeping?
Just fine, thank you.
Well you look as pretty as a pie
supper
How are you?
Better now.
Shall we head inside?
Inquire about a car?
After you.
Let me take your bags.
I'm sure I'll manage.
It's magnificent
And it's all Victor's?
Yes, his father was a very rich
man
They despised each other.
Why?
He disagreed with Victor's
lifestyle
Too much time in restaurants and
clubs
And not in libraries and
university
But then he died
And left Victor a small fortune.
Can't say he's been spending it
wisely
What do you mean?
Victor is a creature of appetite
But he also has a very short
attention span.
Fads come and go.
A few months ago it was all
about Polo
Then it was hot-air
ballooning...
And now it's this house.
God knows what will be next.
It's rather sinister isn't it?
Yes... I suppose it is.
Come. Let's go find our host.
Hello??
Freddie, old boy!!
Well, what do you think?!
I love what you've done with the
place
You know you really should put
me in touch with a decorator
My apartment has far too many
upright walls.
Ha ha! Oh very funny
How are we?
Oh much better now that you're
here
And this must be... Elizabeth
Elizabeth Barton
How do you do?
Very good to see you!
This house is...
Terrible.
What on earth possessed you to
buy it?
All in good time, but first
Let me show you to your
quarters.
Then we can crack on with some
serious drinking
Don't mind if I do!
The Master Bedroom!
How cosy.
It's a little run down
But the bed seems to be in
perfectly good order.
Thank you.
Well, we'll leave you in peace!
Freddie, I'll show you your room
Drinks in about... half an hour.
Just this way, Freddie
George! You big American
bastard!
Wonderful to see you again!
You too.
What the hell happened here?
It's a work in progress old boy.
And my dear sister... how are
we?
Vicky.
Um, is something wrong with my
hand?
Oh my god you're right!
Drinks in ten minutes everyone.
Let me show you to your quarters
Mind the, uh, debris...
Not ready yet?
Oh! You startled me
I'm sorry... need help with my
cufflinks.
Rather silly, a grown man who
still can't do his own.
Luckily you have me to help.
Yes... about that.
I was wondering if you'd always
like to help me with my cufflinks.
What do you mean?
I'm asking you to marry me you
little fool.
Really?
Yes. Not the most romantic way
to ask, I know
But there you go.
Well?
I don't know what to say...
Well... yes of course
Yes!
Good girl.
Now that's settled you should
really get changed.
Victor hates to be kept waiting.
Here we are.
Thank you
And Bourbon, no junk for our...
Transatlantic friend
Now you're talking!
Where's Freddie?
Is he late?
I believe he's changing
I heard he's got a new pet
Now now Christine we must not -
Ah, speak of the devil!
Look what the cat dragged in!
Hello old boy, it's been a
while.
Ain't it just
Christine... a pleasure
I'm afraid I'm simply too weary
from my journey to stand.
Of course, how rude of me
This is Elizabeth Barton
Elizabeth, this is George
Walker, Junior
Pleasure to meet you little lady
And allow me to introduce
my darling sister, Christine.
How do you do?
I'll be right as rain as soon as
I finish this
And Elizabeth...?
Oh, no thank you
I don't drink.
How very proper.
Well isn't this nice!
All of us, back together again
Like the good old days!
Here's to a weekend in the
country
Cheers!
Is this safe to eat?
Haven't had the chance to hire
any staff I'm afraid.
This is the product of my
afternoon in the kitchen
Oh god, well in that case this
is a miracle.
Well Victor
You may have let us down in the
kitchen
But you certainly made up for it
in the cellar
This 1895 Chateaux Palmer is a
wonderful wine
Well drink up everyone
there's plenty more where that
came from.
Oh, I am sorry there wasn't
anything apart from water for you.
Water's fine, thank you.
I must say, Elizabeth
It's a pleasure to finally meet
you.
Freddie's normally so shy about
introducing us to his friends.
Well I've been so busy with
practice lately
I've hardly been off the court.
You know I think there's a
tennis court
somewhere on the grounds
Maybe we could have a game
tomorrow
By the sounds of it you need all
the practice you can get!
To hell with you.
So how did you two meet?
Arthur Brown's Christmas party
drinks.
You've been keeping her hidden
since Christmas?!
Poor show.
Well, didn't want to give you
any ideas
Did I, old boy?
And what do you do?
Christine.
What? Can't I ask her anything?
A secretary.
A mute one, no doubt?
For a solicitor.
And what does being a
solicitor's secretary involve?
Mostly arranging meetings,
and typing letters. That sort of
thing.
But my real passion is writing
Well what sort of writing?
Are we in the presence of the
next Jane Austen?
No I don't think so
More Shelley than Austen
Oh please...
Well come on, tell us more!
It's not very interesting
Oh no it sounds simply
fascinating
We all wanna know!
Well... it's a ghost story of
sorts
And what happens in this ghost
story of sorts?
It's about a girl.
A little girl who is raised in
an orphanage
And she's haunted by ghosts
Only as she grows up, and the
story continues
She realises that ghosts aren't
the ones to fear.
Well what are the ones to fear?
The humans.
Oh! I am so sorry
Elizabeth!
Oh no it's fine!! No don't
worry...
No don't... don't!
Don't worry Victor
It was only a cheap dress.
Is everything alright Elizabeth?
I'm... I'm fine
It was an honest accident
Just let me clean myself up.
...eventually we reached the
summit
Even though we walked downhill -
Elizabeth, I am so sorry for
before
Not to worry
So... Christine
I don't think I heard
What is it that you do exactly?
Do??
Well darling, I do this!
And you do it better than anyone
else could!
Oh you're too kind
How very... rewarding
I'm sure.
Oooh! Christine you better watch
out
This one's got claws!
Shut up Victor.
If I may be so bold
I'd like to make a toast.
Oh, everyone, charge your
glasses!
Proceed.
Well I wasn't planning on saying
anything just yet
But, why not?
Seeing as we're all here
And maybe this wine has got the
better of my senses
But we're engaged
We are to be married
I say!
Congratulations
Thank you
Congratulations.
Christine.
Hello again.
Did you receive my letters?
Yes...
Well I didn't get a reply
No. I thought it would be
kindest that way.
Kindest?
What would you know about
kindness?
Well the last time we saw each
other
You were telling me you never
wanted to see me again
Can't a man change his mind?
I must say...
When I read your first letter
I was very surprised when I got
to the end
and saw it was from you.
Why? Who else would it be from?
Does it matter?
They were all signed
George Walker Junior.
Don't call me Junior.
I must say, George
That's a very big knife.
I do hope you're not trying to
compensate for something.
How about a game of bridge?
No no...
I have specially arranged
entertainment for us this evening.
What time is it?
Nine twenty-five
Good. She should be here soon
then.
Who should be here soon?
All will be explained shortly.
Yes... but let us retire to the
games room!
Well, sit, sit
Make yourselves comfortable.
Oh, would anyone like a drink?
Whiskey, neat.
I'll have one too, with ice.
I think we have some sherry...
Sherry?
Sherry.
Sherry... Sherry?
Sherry? No I...
Elizabeth doesn't drink,
remember?
Of course, how silly of me
I'll just fetch you some water.
Whiskey, no junk.
So old boy. Save the
theatrics...
What's this all about?
Well...
If you're so determined to ruin
my fun
This is no ordinary house.
This house was owned by
Ichabod Quinn!
Who?
I'm not sure how much you know
about the world of the paranormal
But over the past few months
I've become
quite fascinated by it
What, ghosts and monsters? That
sort of nonsense?
Exactly.
But I wouldn't call it nonsense.
What's all this got to do with
this Ichabod character?
Mr Quinn was one of the greatest
occultists
who ever lived.
He pushed the boundaries of
magic to its utmost limit
Going further than anyone else
before
He was also a painter
He would take various substances in
order to connect with the other side
Once in a trance-like state, he
would begin
to paint what he saw.
But when he fell gravely ill, he wrote to his mentor
that he was close to acheiving his life's work
"After years of searching... my
quest has come to an end...
I have found the birthplace...
of desire and destruction
Tonight, under the eye of the
moon
I will pull back the veil of
this world
And go to the utter blackness
I am close, so very close.
Close to what?
A gateway to the other side
Then one day he vanished
Never to be seen again
Legend has it that if a séance
is conducted
one can raise his tormented
soul.
Are you suggesting we...
Yes!
That we perform a séance tonight,
and we make contact with Mr Quinn.
But why would anyone do such a
thing?
Why? Why not?
Beats bridge at any rate.
Do you even know how to conduct
one?
No... not exactly. But from what I
read it's not as hard as one may think.
All we require is a medium.
A what now?
Someone who has the power to
communicate with the dead.
Very shrewd Elizabeth.
A medium will soon be joining
us,
one that has been personally
recommended to me.
Well, who is this medium?
She's supposed to be very good,
in fact
She put old Percy King in touch
with his deceased father
in order to get the combination
to his safe.
I assume it worked?
Take a look at his new mansion
If I'm not very much mistaken
That will be her now.
You're looking a little uneasy,
George.
Another drink? Settle your
nerves?
Please
George Walker Junior, afraid?
Now that is a first.
I just think its dumb as dirt to
go messing with things
we don't know diddly-squat
about.
Well I think it's a ripping
idea.
Here's to the paranormal.
Ladies and Gentlemen...
Madame Bellrose!
Good evening!
Let me introduce you to -
Mr Turner, the tennis player
Ah, yes...
And you must be Mr Walker
Junior, the oil man
Yeah, but don't call me
Junior...
Ms Hall
And Ms Barton, I presume
Wrong way round
Ah well, can't get them all
right.
How do you already know our
names?
Oh... a name is a name is a
name...
Curious...
What's curious?
Is everything alright Madame
Bellrose?
Oh yes, perfectly fine
Just... a feeling.
What kind of feeling?
Oh, probably nothing
These old houses are full of
stories and lives
Would you like a drink Madame
Bellrose?
Well, if you offered me a dry
martini...
I'd have a dry martini!
Of course.
So, Ms Bellrose, tell us
When did you realise you had
these... remarkable powers?
Well, it was on my sixth birthday,
and I was playing hide and seek
with some other children in the
woods
And I'd just found a rather good
hiding place
in an old oak tree.
Little did I know that this
particular tree was home
to a surprisingly aggressive
magpie
Well, on his return he was very
displeased
to see a grubby six year-old
hiding in his tree.
And this beastly bird started
pecking me
and attacking me
and I misplaced my footing
and down I fell, crashing to the
ground.
The next thing I knew, I was in
bed
with a bandage round my head
sporting two missing teeth,
and the ability to speak to the
dead!
What a fascinating tale!
And does anybody else in your
family possess these abilities?
Second sight is not like curly
hair my dear
It's not hereditary.
Is there any chance... I mean
could it be dangerous
to meddle with these sorts of
powers?
I do not consider myself a
meddler!
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to
offend.
Ah don't worry, don't apologise.
Oh, I congratulate you on your
dry martini!
Thank you.
Well like anything exciting,
there's always a degree of
danger.
But, no more so than...
slipping on ice,
or burning yourself with a
match.
So you've never had a bad
experience?
I've slipped, but never fallen.
There you are George. There's
nothing to fear.
Forgive me, Victor, but this is
an enormous stick-up,
ain't it?
You know you actually had me
going for a second there.
Pardon?
You can't really be buying this?
This... what?
This... Hogwash!
Do you think you know the world
so well, Mr Walker?
Just 'cos a chicken's got wings
don't mean it can fly.
What on earth does that mean?
It means, I ain't taking part in
this sham any longer
It's fine, Mr Walker
to be a little afraid.
I ain't yella
Oh do pipe down George,
you're ruining all our fun.
Well I'm game. If everyone else
is.
Great show! Christine?
Oh why not...
Elizabeth?
I can't say I'm not a little
nervous about the idea...
But what about your novel?
You're writing a ghost story.
Simply think of this as...
research.
Yes... and I thought the ghosts
weren't the ones to fear
Remember?
Come on, it's just a bit of fun.
Very well.
Splendiferous!
Well... just you then George.
Fine! Why the hell not?
I'm in the minority here
anyways.
Let's get this over and done
with.
Aha! What a riot!
Madame Bellrose, is there
anything else you need
which I haven't already laid
out?
No, Mr Hall, you've done very
well at following my instructions.
Now, if you wouldn't mind taking
your places
Now, place your hands on the
table, like so.
Make sure your fingers are
touching
Very good.
Now I ask you do not speak
or make any sudden movements,
and try to clear your mind of
any thoughts.
You want us to think of nothing?
Should be easy for you, Victor.
Yes, clear your mind, it makes
for a better connection.
Is it likely that we'll make
contact?
I can't promise anything...
but if we do, I ask you do not
break the circle.
Do you understand?
Yes
Right, we're ready.
Spirits, we bring you gifts from
life into death.
Commune with us! And move
amongst us.
Is that rotten bread?
Yes, my dear, it enhances the
flavour
Spirits have very weakened taste
buds.
Now don't interrupt again.
Spirits, we bring you gifts from
life into death.
Commune with us, and move
amongst us.
Maybe they've got food
poisoning...
Do you see us, beloved one?
Spirits, can you hear us?
Is there anyone here who wishes
to make contact
with someone from the other
side?
Yes
I wish to make contact with Mr
Ichabod Quinn.
Spirits of the past, move
amongst us
Mr Ichabod Quinn, be guided by
the light of this world
and visit upon us.
Is that you, Mr Quinn?
Can you see him?
I can't see anyone.
Look closely, can't you see?
I can see clearly...
A pale man, in a black suit
headed towards us.
He's coming this way.
Is that you, Mr Quinn?
This is all just -
Don't break the circle!
Come! Come again!
Come forward...
Oh!
But your eyes!
What's happened to your eyes!?
No!! No no no!! Go back!
Go back!!
Madame Bellrose?
What on earth is going on?
Is she alright?
This house... will become your
tomb.
Your flesh will be torn, your
bones crushed to dust
and your souls extracted to a
painful and terrifying eternity
What the hell is she talking
about?
When the dawn breaks
The twelve kings and twelve
dukes of Hell will be released
upon this earth.
Flames will engulf you
and the great beast will rip you
limb from limb
for all of time.
They will sit upon the throne of
blood...
in an Eden of pain!
Careful!
HERE COMES HELL!!
My god!!
Well I think another drink is in
order?
She's still kicking.
What happened to her?
She must be having some kind of
seizure...
or attack of the brain.
She seemed to get stronger!?
Is that even possible?
Strong as a bull!
So what do we do with her now?
We should call for a doctor.
This house has no line.
We should drive to the village
then.
I think she's trying to say say
something.
My god!!!
Freddie!!
Quick! Put pressure on the
wound!
George you just shot my guest!
Whiskey!
Deep breath, deep breath
calm down.
Drink that.
You're going to be fine
My serving arm!!
Do you always bring a gun to a
dinner party!!??
I think it might be time we made
ourselves scarce.
It won't budge!
Stand back!!
Is there another way out?
Yes, the rear door. This way!
It can't be!
I told you not to mess with this
paranormal shit!
She can't see us... move back,
quietly
Sorry!
Don't mess with Texas.
How much ammunition did you
bring?!
Flee!!!!
Freddie!!
Drink! I need a drink.
Just something to... take the
edge off.
Christ!!
Who's there?
Please!
Come on....
Father?
Father, is that really you?
You have disappointed me, my
son.
All my fortune I have worked so
hard for my entire life
You are throwing my life's work
to the wind.
On boat trips, and pony girls,
and holidays to India!
And vintage champagne.
What has become of your
potential?
Father I'm sorry! I'm sorry...
Ha ha ha!
You cannot escape!!
You will burn!!!
Father, no!!!
What kind of bloody house is
this!?
Let me see your hand!
It's nothing, stop fussing!
Let me!
We need to cut it off.
Don't be stupid. It's just a
little infected.
Dear God!!
Freddie!!
What... what's happening to me?
What's happening to me?
No, I'm shrinking! Victor I'm
shrinking!
Victor, help me! I'm shrinking!
Freddie!! George?? I'm
shrinking!!
Why am I shrinking? Help!
Help me! Why aren't you
helping!?
Victor!!
Why can't you hear me!? Victor!?
Freddie??
Come on George, I know you can
hear me!
Can't you hear me, George!?
Please, please help! I'm down
here!!
Can't you hear me!!??
Please!!
George I know you can hear me!
Any of you...
Please!
Elizabeth!! Please!
Please will you help me?!
Christine??
What are you doing down there?
Elizabeth please will you help??
Elizabeth? Elizabeth... no!!
Look everyone, I found
Christine!
Gosh, she's so small!
I didn't even notice she'd gone.
What's she saying?
I'm still here!
So insignificant!
Get rid of her!
Yes... squash her!!
Don't squash me, please, I'm not
insignificant!
Squash her!!
George?
Christine?
Thank god, you're safe.
I've started to see things.
I'm so afraid... will you protect
me?
Of course I will, you know I
always will.
Oh George, you're so kind.
I was such a fool to ever give
you the ring back.
God I can be so cruel...
Every day this past year I've
regretted that decision.
I've always loved you.
I...
Fuck me!!
Kiss me George!!!
Don't you love me, George!??
So much for compensating for
something.
This way.
Christine!
Victor!
You scared the life out of me!
God you gave me a fright!
Shut up!
In here!
Quick, into the games room!
It seems to be all-
George!
Stay back!
What the bloody hell do you
think you're doing?!
Stop talking and do as I say
Or I will gun you down like a
dog in the street.
Sit.
What's gotten into you?
Ain't a question of what's
gotten into me.
It's a question of what may have
gotten into you.
These spirits, or whatever you
want to call them
Can take on the form of us.
We're not evil spirits, George,
we're human.
Now whatever the hell this is,
it's trying to play games with
us.
It wants to beat us.
You have to believe me.
Maybe you're telling the truth.
Maybe you aint.
Until I am one hundred percent sure
that you are who you say you are...
I'm gonna keep my gun trained on
you.
Is that crystal clear?
Now, where's Freddie?
Dead.
What?
He's dead.
How?
I killed him.
Why? Why!?
Hold up there.
Now I've got the gun.
So let's just calm down -
George!
Look at me! Look at me...
Everything's going to be
alright!
Oh god!!
Everything's going to be fine...
everything's going to be just fine
George!!
It's gonna be fine... just
fine...
George? George?
George?
Oh George, you poor fool...
What have you done, Vicky?
I'm sorry... it was just a
mistake
It just went off...
Oh god... why is this happening?
We haven't done anything we just-
Performed a séance. We wanted to
make contact with Ichabod Quinn
and we did.
And now he's back and he wants
to finish his life's work.
We've opened Hell.
George was right.
We shouldn't have meddled with
this.
This is all your fault! You made
us do that bloody séance...
Don't blame me!
All of this was just meant to be
a bit of fun!
You've damned us all you fucking
idiot!!
Try and calm down you're being
hysterical!
That's enough!
There's no use in pointing
fingers now.
We're all in the same boat. If
we want to get out of here alive
we're going to have to start
working together.
What can we do?
Remember what Madame Bellrose
said?
At dawn, the moon will consume
the sun.
We need to end this now, or God
knows what will happen.
But how?
We need to find the gateway to
Hell and close it for good.
The basement. That's where Ichabod
would conduct his ceremonies
to contact the other side, at
the lowest point of the house.
That's where we saw that thing,
Madame Bellrose, heading.
The party's over.
Whiskey?
She doesn't drink, remember?
Chin chin.
Coast is clear.
It's faster if we cut through
here.
Where do we go now?
Through this door, then turn
right.
Much too slow, Christine!
Damn!
Let me see!
No, don't bother. I'm done for!
No, no you're not!
I don't want to turn into one of
them!
Don't let me!
No, no you can't! Please!
It's the only way! Don't worry
about me,
darling sister.
Sorry again for spilling wine on
your dress...
Let's get this over with.
No, I'll do it.
Some party, hey?
A real one to remember.
Come on.
We have to go now.
There's the staircase to the
basement.
I can't! I can't take it any
more.
First George, and now... and now
poor Victor.
Look at me! You need to stay
strong, I need your help
I can't do this on my own!
I can't... I can't take it.
Yes you can! And you have to!
It's the only way! When we end
this,
maybe they'll all come back, all
of them.
Will they?
I won't stop until I see the
real Freddie again.
Don't you want to see your
brother again?
And George...
But how do you know?
I don't. But there's only one
way to find out.
Let's end this, once and for
all.
You and me.
Victor... kills!
What is it?
It's George!
Wait!
It might not really be him.
I have to be sure.
Christine!
Christine! Come back!
George?
Is it really you?
Please?
Bye Vicky.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
We must be getting closer.
And the dragon sat on the rock
and the rock was the moon
and the moon consumed the sun and
out of the night came the blackness
and from the blackness came the
dawn...
Now what?
Let's kill the bitch.
...comes fear, and fear spawns
power...
Clever little girls to get so far,
but I'm afraid it will be of no use.
The gate is opened!
And it will remain open until
all Hell is set free.
Shoot it Elizabeth!
Christine!
My darling. I'm so glad you came
to me my love.
I knew you would.
I'm ready to be together
properly now.
No more fooling around.
No more toying with other
lovers.
Now we can be together for an
eternity.
We'll never be apart again.
You're the love of my life,
Christine.
Don't listen to him, Elizabeth!
Is it true?
Oh, Elizabeth. Did you really think
I marry someone as small as you?
How pathetic of you to even say
yes when I asked.
We were only together for a few
mere months.
Were you really that desperate?
I was only with you to make
Christine mad with jealousy.
And it worked.
Is it true?
Elizabeth you have to listen to
me -
Just answer the question.
Yes.
So is that why you were so awful
to me?
I was a fool to behave the way I
did
you have to believe me, I was
just in love with the wrong man!
Yes... poor George.
He's down there now, burning for
eternity.
I'm bored of this now.
Christine, my love.
Let's be together forever!
Elizabeth!! Elizabeth please!!
She's far too feeble to do
anything.
I'm so sorry Elizabeth!
Elizabeth, please!!
You fucking bitches!!!
Help!! No!!
Christine!!
Elizabeth!!
Hold on!!
No!!
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org