Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
[exhales]
[up-tempo music plays]
What up, kids? It's Cole.
This is ERL.
I just got out of the bathroom.
And I am so high.
30,000-feet-in-the-air high!
Sorry.
Anyway, this month marks ten
years of having doing this.
Ten! What?!
[imitates beeping sound]
You better buckle those safety belts because
ten years of filming is a ton of footage.
And before we left on this
trip, I went through all of it.
Or most of it.
Or some of it.
There's just so much!
Did you see that?
It's hard to believe how many
adventures we've been on together.
[growls]
Before any of that stuff,
my parents were filming me.
[Cole's dad] Cole, Cole, Cole.
Watch out! Hold on. Hold on, buddy.
[Cole] All the time.
- Hey, look. It's tiny me.
- [Cole's mom] Happy birthday, Cole.
[Cole] Once I got my hands on a
camera, I was filming everything.
- [Cole screams]
- [Cole's mom screams]
- [Cole's mom] Come on, Cole, you got it!
- Oh!
- [Cole] Ouch.
- Thomas, keep your eyes on the road.
And when I got older,
I started this channel
and began sharing my videos
with you and it blew up!
Now I get to do this
for a living!
Which is nuts!
I traveled all over the world,
looking for the wildest
experiences to entertain you guys.
A 100,000... 250...
Half a million followers.
I'm in Brooklyn! Birmingham, Alabama.
I'm in Detroit.
ERL is in Nepal.
[crowd cheers]
You watched, commented...
[chuckles]
[Cole] and told me
what to do next.
What up, kids, it's Cole.
I challenge all of you to find
something that scares me.
I dare you! Come on!
[grunts]
And I listened!
Hey. Hi.
OK, go, go. Shit.
- Sir, you can't film here.
- I'm not, it's not on.
I'm in a coffin
being buried alive.
[dirt hitting coffin]
OK, it's not so bad.
Hello? Oh, shit.
Looking at all this crazy shit
we've done together,
and this escape from real life,
none of this would've been
possible
- if it wasn't for this vlog and for all of you.
- [Cole] Shi...
So thank you.
Woo! [laughs]
All right, the nostalgia trip
is over.
So, if you remember back
in August,
we asked you to vote
on where we should go
to celebrate this amazing
occasion.
Over a million of you
weighed in and...
Moscow.
My friends pulled all the
stops
and they hooked us up
with first-class tickets!
That's right!
As usual, I'm taking you somewhere
you've probably never been
to show you something
you've never seen.
I know where we're going
but I have no idea
what we're doing
because they won't tell me!
- Dash!
- Evening!
- Samantha!
- Yo. Yeah.
Actually, Samantha wasn't
supposed to be here because
she's usually training
for the X Games,
But for the first time in
forever, she didn't qualify.
[female] Ooh! Oh!
- Ouch!
- Fuck you, OK?
- Hey, hey, hey. Children are watching.
- [Samantha chuckles]
- And... Erin is here!
- Hi, guys!
Yeah, it's her first time
out of the states.
- Are you serious?
- [Erin] Mm-hmm.
- Besides Mexico.
- [Samantha chuckles]
Which does not count.
But you can plan on seeing
a lot more of her!
Really?
Yes, they will.
So, we're almost there
and then you kinda have to
tell me, OK?
I think I've waited
long enough.
OK. Not a chance.
[Cole] OK, fine.
You know what?
That's all for now.
No, wait, wait, wait!
- I'm turning this off.
- Wait, wait.
Get ready.
[screams]
Oh, my God!
This is my best friend
in the world, Thomas!
Oh, yeah! First class.
I see you, big dog. OK! [chuckles]
Dude, wait, where were you
this whole flight? [chuckles]
Coach. I wanted it
to be a surprise.
Thank you so much.
You guys are the best.
[Thomas] Thanks, bro.
Anything for you.
[Erin] Here, let me get this.
[Thomas] OK.
[Cole] All right.
[Thomas] Happy ten!
[Dash] Happy ten years, buddy.
[Thomas] Love you, man!
You guys are
the best friends ever.
Cheers!
[indistinct chatter]
[Dash] Oh, finally.
He's finished.
Oh, look who's done.
[Cole] All right. [sighs]
What the hell we doing?
'Cause, 'cause, like,
come on.
I've been waiting, so...
you... you, like, tell me,
like, for real.
You gonna tell me, or...?
All right. So...
I have a buddy in Moscow
named Alexei.
This guy is next-level loaded.
And when I told him you're
coming,
he watches ERL. Loves you, bro.
He wants to take us everywhere.
I'm talking the best clubs,
the best restaurants,
And when I mean "the best," this
guy's so rich, that everything he does
is legitimately the best.
OK, OK.
Clubs and restaurants,
but like what are we
actually doing there?
- [Thomas] Are you done?
- Yes, go ahead. Sorry.
We are taking you to an escape
room experience in Moscow.
[chuckles] Seriously?
You're serious?
That's what it is? Yeah?
We're flying all the way to
Russia to go do an escape room?
- I've been to escape rooms, man. Come on.
- No, no. Yeah.
[Cole] Dude, I can't vlog an escape room.
What are you, nuts?
I get it, you been to an escape
room but not one like this, bro.
This one you have to be
personally invited to.
It's custom-made.
It's scary as hell.
And that means it's
perfect for you.
OK. No one else
could do this.
They built it for us.
[Dash] Swear to God.
- [Cole] OK.
- [chuckles]
[Cole] OK! OK. OK.
All right,
say that one more time.
You're taking me to
an escape room?
- We're...
- For those of you who don't know what an escape room is,
it's a game where they lock
you and your friends in a room
and you have to solve puzzles
to try and get out.
- [blows raspberry]
- [Dash] Why does that need to be explained?
Oh, and they don't have
the same rules we do, so...
Exactly! Thank you.
Which means, Cole, dear friend of mine,
you can't be a pussy!
Oh, dude! Come on, man!
You know that I am up
for anything!
Oh! Give me that!
You guys heard him, he said anything!
Give it! All right.
They're letting us tie into
their cameras,
which means, you guys are
gonna be able to see it.
OK. How do you know
this Alexei guy?
His dad is some politics
or some shit,
I don't even know.
But the last time I met him,
he was throwing around
money like an idiot, bro.
It was insane.
We ended up on a yacht
for, like, a fuckin' week.
[chuckles] Oh, shit.
Delete that last part.
No, dude. This is live.
Samantha's responsible for me.
So there you go.
Mystery revealed.
A Russian escape room.
What could possibly go wrong?
This goin' be lit!
Peace out, kids!
[Thomas] "This 'gun be lit.
Peace out, kids."
- [chuckles]
- [replay]
Oh, yeah, you gonna have
to delete that. Come on, bro.
No, no, no.
For real, though.
How's that going over there?
Mm-hmm. She's cool.
- [Thomas] "She's cool"?
- [Cole] Yeah, dude.
I see it all up in your face.
You really care about her, don't you?
Yeah, man. Like, you can tell?
Like, right now?
You can't hide that.
White people do that.
[Cole and Thomas laugh]
Ah, man. Yeah, no. She's...
She's the first girl that I've
been with who really sees me.
You know? She's great.
That's dope.
I'm happy for you.
[turbulence]
- [screams]
Shit.
- [laughs]
- Whoa! No, no, no, sir. Oh!
[Cole] You OK, babe?
[Pilot over PA
speaking in Russian]
[indistinct chatter]
Hey, yo!
We are in Russia, baby!
And I have a quick question
for my fellow friends.
Have you ever wondered
what's back there?
[All] No, not once ever. No.
So, we all agree I should
go back there?
- [Samantha] No.
- [Erin] No, couldn't care less.
OK, I'll be right back.
- [Thomas] He plays too much.
- [Cole sighs] Yo.
Yo, Dash!
Where'd he go?
- [Samantha chuckles]
- [Cole] What is he doing?
Dash, what are you doing?
Oh, no. Oh, no. We lost Dash.
OK. Cole? Cole?
Whoa, hey. Whoa, whoa!
Whoa, whoa, w-wait, wait.
[Dash] I swear to God,
I wasn't gonna... Cole!
W-wait, wait. Wait one second.
Wh-what happened?
[speaking Russian]
Uh, sir.
- [speaking Russian]
- [Cole] I... I... uh...
I'm sorry, my friend's
an idiot. One... one second.
[speaking Russian]
I...
Hey, hey. Whoa.
[speaking Russian]
Oh. [speaking Russian]
OK.
[pleading in Russian]
Mm-hmm.
[speaking Russian]
Thank you.
[Dash] What's up, bud?
Uh, I was throwing money
around like, uh, like an idiot?
[chuckles] Uh, no, no.
Like, um, no, no, um...
[chuckles] Come on!
I'm fucking with you!
[laughs] But I do, huh?
You're a legend, bro.
This is Cole.
- Cole.
- Alexei. Welcome to Moscow.
Thank you.
Where's the rest?
It's great to finally meet you,
Cole, huh?
And see this motherfucker again.
- [Dash] How've you been, bro?
- [Alexei] Very good, very good.
[Dash] Whoa.
Everyone, this is Victoria.
Hello, everyone.
- Hi.
- [Cole] Hey.
And this is Sergei.
Vitali.
Personal driver and security.
Now, they go everywhere
that I go.
OK? It's very cool.
Now... [speaking Russian]
[chuckles]
Everybody, we go.
[Thomas] Oh, yeah. That's it, Cole,
you bringin' me on all those trips.
This place is fucking
amazing, huh? Come on.
Who wants a drink?
[Alexei] Only the best
for you guys.
[Cole] Oh, what do
we have here?
- [Alexei] Dash...
- France all over again.
- [Alexei] Welcome.
- Pleasure.
- [Alexei] Ooh, wow.
- [Victoria speaking Russian]
[indistinct] Cole.
OK. Everyone.
Welcome to Russia. Huh?
[all] To Russia!
[Thomas] What is this?
[Victoria] Here we go.
[Dash] Yeah,
this about to be dope!
[Thomas] Oh, this doesn't
look sketchy at all.
Yo, Dash,
this your scene, right?
OK. OK.
[Cole] Erin, look.
It's a real Russian club.
[Erin] Obviously.
[Cole] Oh! Whoa! Look at this!
So much content! Whoa!
Yo, Cole, you see that?
[Dash] Sam. How about this? Divide and
conquer. Whoever gets the hottest girl wins.
- Yes!
- Oh, shit. We get our own table?
[Cole] H-hey, fire!
Dude, this is sick!
[Sam] All right, so which one?
- Her. The brunette.
- That's easy.
- Easy for what?
- [Sam] I could easily do that.
So you're telling me,
you could do that?
Hell, not a chance
in the world.
[Dash] You said it like
I'm a joke. Oh, my God.
- We know each other very well.
- [Speaking Russian]
This is Mina.
She's beautiful, isn't she?
Yeah!
What?
[both speaking Russian]
[Dash] Oh, shit.
She's coming over.
How you doin? Oh, a shot.
We're gonna drink... Oh!
[speaking Russian]
Oh, this is happening.
Samantha.
All right, yup. I'm ready.
[Erin] Let's dance.
[cheers]
[all] Moscow! Whoo!
Alexei, you drink like this
every night?
That's right! Hey...
You party all the time, too.
Come on!
No, no. That's just
for the camera, man.
[chuckles] I remember the first time
we got drunk. You remember that?
- I do remember that.
- Oh, shit!
- [all] Oh!
- [Thomas] Sorry.
[laughs]
OK, OK, OK.
ERL is in the club!
Hey, guys!
[cheers]
[Cole] So we came halfway
around the world.
What do you have
planned for us?
- You have never seen anything like it, OK?
- OK.
- Every experience is tailored to the player...
- [girls] Hi, guys.
Hi.
Uh, we watch you all the time.
Oh, you do? Oh, well,
actually, we're live right now.
Oh!
All right, actually, hold on.
[Alexei] It's... it's better,
better by bar.
Uh, I'm Alina. This is my
sister, Alisa.
[Cole] It's nice to meet you.
Hey, uh, Cole?
Hold on one second, man.
They watch my vlogs.
All right. Where are
you girls from?
[girls] St. Petersburg!
[Cole] St. Petersburg!
I've never been there before.
[girls] You should come...
Hey, uh, Cole.
Well, maybe we should. Hey,
Thomas, how far away
is St. Petersburg from here?
Cole, look!
[Erin] Cole!
[speaking Russian]
Hey, get your fucking hands
off her!
[screams and grunts]
Oh, shit! Cole, Cole, stop!
You don't know who these
guys are.
I don't give a fuck who they
are... let go!
[speaking Russian]
[Erin gasps]
[grunts]
[Erin] Tell him stop!
[speaking Russian]
Motherfucker.
You and your friends
are fucked!
[speaking Russian]
I'm watching you, you bitch.
- Hey, you OK?
- Yeah.
Who the fuck were those guys?
Hey, you OK?
- Yeah. Let's just go.
- OK.
Sorry about that.
Let's get the fuck out of here.
Let's go. Come on.
[Cole] Let's get the fuck
out of here. Now. Go.
- What was that? What the fuck?
- Let it go.
Come on. Ooh!
I apologize for not
coming sooner.
I wouldn't know what would've
happened if you didn't get there.
I mean, like, who were those
fuckin' guys?
I feel like they knew Alexei
or something.
Those clubs are [in Russian].
How you say? A bad type.
Mr. Koslov should know better.
Well, thank you.
For, you know... Thanks.
Eh, [speaking Russian]
I wonder if Alexei
got any of that on camera.
Sorry.
I'm just glad that we're all...
safe, you know?
[sighs]
[inaudible dialogue]
- [Erin] Cole.
- [Cole sighs]
[Erin] You've gotten used to all
of these people following you
and watching everything you do.
And it's exciting.
But I finally get to be
a part of it with you.
I'm not sure what these trips
are normally like.
But it looked like
we were in real danger.
And you were too busy
with your fans to notice.
That guy pulled a gun on us.
And afterwards, I couldn't tell if
you were more concerned about me
or how many people
were watching.
I know there are
two sides to you.
The public Cole.
And the real Cole.
My Cole.
They both have their place,
but...
I always thought you knew
the difference.
[sighs]
[Dash and Mina chuckle]
- [Dash] Don't forget. At Dash.
- [Mina] OK.
- [Dash] Dash! Don't forget to call me back. Cool.
- [Mina] Mm-hmm.
[Erin and Cole] Good morning.
- Morning!
- Good morning.
[sighs, then moans]
[Samantha] Morning, guys.
[Erin and Cole] Morning.
[Cole] How was last night?
[chuckles] Now you know
your boy can't drink.
He's still in
my room, asleep.
Oh, he ended up
in your room?
I kicked him out of
my place last night.
You have no shame at all.
No, no. Did you see her?
Exactly. You would've
done the same thing.
[chuckles]
Oh, I think Alexei's sending
a car for us at two.
Yeah.
Oh, do you guys mind if
I steal him for the day?
- [Dash] What?! No, I thought we were gonna go sight-seeing.
- [Samantha] Absolutely.
Thomas is not getting up no time soon.
We can just do our own thing.
[tsk] Fine, whatever.
Who needs you guys?
We have a fireplace.
We have a spa.
We have room service.
That's all paid for, yeah?
[chuckles]
[Dash] Yeah, we don't need
you guys.
It's two o'clock.
It's the only car here.
I guess this ours?
[Erin] Obviously. [chuckles]
Hi. Are you here for Cole...?
Cole. Turner.
Please, step inside.
- Um...
- [engine starts]
Please, step inside.
Thank you.
That's so pretty.
- Should we get out and walk? The Red Square's right up here.
- [Cole] Oh yeah.
Mr. Alexei told me to stay
with you. I wouldn't want to...
Yeah, but that's OK.
Stop right up here.
Yeah, yeah, stop right up here.
It's perfect. We'll meet
you back here later.
Uh, can you unlock the door,
please?
Can I just take you to the place I
was told to take you? And then...
She... she wants to see Red
Square, and we're kinda tourists.
So we'll meet back here later.
OK. OK, I'll pick you up
on the far side.
Perfect.
Baby, we haven't exchanged
currency yet.
Uh, do you know where we
can get...?
You don't have any rubles?
How about 100 dollars?
No worries.
Most places will not
take credit.
Thanks, bro.
I need to have you by eight!
You...
[inaudible dialogue]
[Erin] So it's 6:15 here,
that means at home it's...
8:15 AM.
I always keep the watch
on LA time. Ha!
You're so weird.
I thought I'd have
terrible jet lag and...
Mm. Everything last night.
Hm.
Oh, that bed was so comfy.
I slept like a rock.
Me, too.
I'm glad I get you almost
to myself today.
[both chuckle]
So am I. This was good.
I'm glad we stumbled in here.
Imagine that.
Oh, my God.
Not having to ask anyone.
- I mean, I'm actually really proud of you.
- Thank you.
- How will anyone even know that we were here?
- I don't know.
I mean, that we had so much fun?
And it was so beautiful.
- OK. OK.
- [Erin chuckles]
[speaking Russian]
Oh.
- Thank you.
- [speaking Russian]
Hey, uh, how much, uh...
[Erin] What's wrong?
Well, it's not US dollars.
- [distant]
- [Erin chuckles]
[distant] Cole?
Do you have cash?
Uh, [scoffs].
Do I have enough cash?
[clicks tongue]
OK.
Oops.
[grunts]
Looks like it.
You're really cool.
Thanks.
You get that a lot?
I do.
Yeah, you clearly like
the lifestyle. I get it.
I'm slowly picking up on that.
I'm Russian-rich.
Um, Mr. Koslov
has taken care of your meal
and the driver
is waiting outside.
Wait, Alexei?
OK.
Oh!
This is yours.
Huh?
What is this?
Mm.
Hey. How did Alexei
even know where we are?
[Erin] I don't know.
Is that cool or creepy?
Uh, yeah,
A little, yeah.
Excited for tonight?
You know me,
I'm gonna hype anything.
But I hope that
it is big enough.
No, I wouldn't worry
about that.
Like, just wait.
Oh, my...
Cole.
Yeah?
What?
This is all for you.
So if tonight gets too intense,
I hope you know...
Too intense?
We're going to an escape room.
Come on. Stop.
All right. [sighs]
What?
OK.
Do you remember who you're
talking to right now?
Oh, shut up.
Come on, let's go.
Actually, hold on.
Wait, for real.
Hey, kids. It's Cole.
I just wanted to hop on
really fast and thank everybody
so much for their suggestions.
AlisaV34, the Bolshoi was mmm...
Amazing! Yes!
And I don't know why everybody
shit-talks Russia so much,
besides all the guns and
gangsters, actually not that bad.
It's not!
You know.
OK?
So anyway, in three hours,
we will be going live from
this mysterious escape room.
See what happens
9 PM Moscow time.
- [Erin] Let's go.
- [Cole] And we out!
- [Erin] This is stupid.
- [Cole] OK, OK.
[Erin indistinct]
Oh, actually...
Hey, thank you so much.
No, Mr. Cole.
Uh, you keep it.
I... I insist, please.
You keep it. Please.
Oh.
Shit!
[Alexei] You two ready?
[Erin] What?
Hey.
- Are you OK?
- Yeah.
He didn't give you
any trouble, did he?
'Cause I will fucking fire him.
No, no, no. It's no big deal.
- Want to stay here? I should
get changed before we go.
Yeah, yeah, sounds good.
OK, then. [speaks Russian]
I am so happy for you.
I wish I could go again.
You can't go twice?
No.
This is all he could talk about
for a month after we went.
About how intense it was.
And how it gave him life.
Hey. [speaking Russian]
OK?
Yeah? [speaks Russian]
[speaks Russian]
Hey, man.
What'd you get into today?
Oh. Room service.
Fire. I got a massage.
I know you're jealous.
I know.
I'm on vacation, baby.
About to get ready
for tonight. [chuckles]
[sighs]
- Hey.
- Hm.
[Dash] Oh, this place is fire.
[Thomas] Oh, yup,
this has got me out.
OK, now.
Remember. As real
as everything might seem,
OK?
You're safe.
That's dramatic.
Let's do it.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
[Alexei] OK.
[buzzing]
OK.
[Thomas] Not sketchy at all.
Tonight! In true ERL fashion,
we are taking you to the most
intense,
the most hyper-exclusive,
escape room in Moscow.
That's right! Just for you,
they're letting us tie
into their cameras
so you all can watch
what's happening live.
And because every experience
is completely different,
You never know what's gonna
happen! Oh, my God.
Alexei, come here, come here.
Is there any way they can find
this place online
Do you have a website?
Do you have a profile?
Do you have a hashtag?
Do you have any...
- [Alexei] No.
- No, you don't! Because ERL is the only place
you can get this content.
That's right! Uh!
[laugh]
- [Cole] You guys ready or what?
- Not as much as you. Jesus Christ!
- All right, let's do this.
[Alexei] OK, Cole,
they will begin streaming it
- directly into your device.
- Let's do it.
OK.
All right.
[Cole] Don't lose that.
Don't lose that phone.
[Alexei] They are good to go.
[Cole] My backup phone.
Hope they don't find all my nudes.
Just kidding, just kidding.
Erin, stop.
It's a joke.
[Erin] But how much fun
would they be?
- Scared?
- No. [chuckles]
So, what do you think
they're doing?
I don't got a clue.
- [chuckles]
- It's like that.
Fuck.
[Samantha] Who are these guys?
[Alexei] They'll be
taking you inside.
But they only speak
Russian.
So I told them I'd give you
instructions in English.
You're being held
in a Bolshevik prison.
This is a facility where
enemies of the state
were tortured, questioned
and killed.
The last man executed
is still inside.
He stole the cell block key and
hid it in the only place he could.
They tortured him.
Starved him.
But he never gave it up.
You must release
your companions
before the timer runs out.
And they are executed.
Fuck.
[sighs]
[Cole] What?
[chuckles] This is crazy.
[chuckles]
[alarm sounds]
Ugh.
Yo, guys, this place is legit.
[Thomas] Hey, Cole!
Yeah?
Is anybody else
down here?
[Thomas laughs] Yeah, me.
[chuckles]
[Thomas] I'm... I'm strapped
into some kind of... machine.
OK.
Ugh.
[Thomas] Cole!
OK, hang tight!
OK.
Oof.
This guy real?
Holy shit.
I think I'm supposed to
cut this guy open?
This is really weird.
Super creepy. I, uh,
am feeling a little weird about it.
No one's gonna stop me?
[whispering]
Oh, my goodness.
I got this.
All right.
This is so sketch.
I'm gonna do it.
Oh, shit.
Ugh.
Ew, weird.
Uh... I don't know
what I'm looking for.
OK, it's not there.
Sorry, man, it's weird
for me, too.
[chuckles]
This is so sick.
Oh.
Oh!
Ugh.
[sighs]
[grunts]
Erin!
Erin! Are you OK?
[muffled] This is
so fuckin' crazy.
[muffled] The key. The key.
I don't know what to do.
[man] Hello!
OK. I'll be right back.
OK.
[chuckles]
Hey, Sam.
How you doin'?
Nice to see you
doin' good.
Man, this shit
is uncomfortable.
Hey, Alexei was not joking.
Do you guys think
this is a real prison?
I think it's a real prison.
[Alexei over speaker]
Ha ha! I told you!
Oh, so you guys are watching.
[Alexei over speaker]
Better get going, baby face.
Your friends don't have
much time left. [chuckles]
Baby face.
Hey, everybody.
I'm gonna solve
all these puzzles quick.
Watch this.
[Dash] Hey, something's
happening down here.
'Kay, coming.
[Thomas] Hey, seriously.
Get down here, man.
This is starting to hurt.
[gears spinning]
Finally.
Wow. Look at you guys.
Where's Erin and Sam?
You guys are all in
different torture devices.
Sam's in an electric chair,
and Erin is down there
in some sort of a tank?
Oh, OK.
Yo, what happened to your hands?
The key that I used
to get in here,
I had to cut out
of a guy's stomach!
This is blood!
Like a real dude?
Yes, Dash.
Like a real dead Russian.
From the war.
No! I don't know, man!
I don't know.
- I don't know.
- [Dash laughs] Crazy.
I mean, look where we are.
You had me, though.
Not gonna lie. You had me.
Guys. O-OK,
serious, though.
Uh, when that door opened,
this started pulling.
- This door?
- [Dash] Hey!
This thing right here
is starting to close.
[Cole] O-OK.
Uh, each of the rooms
across from you guys
have puzzles and those are
the only doors that are open.
I guess I just need to
solve them and... and
I'll get you guys out.
Just stay right there.
Don't move.
[Dash] OK. I mean, we
can't go anywhere but, yeah.
- Hang tight.
- [Thomas and Dash] Cole!
- I know.
- [Thomas] Jesus!
Huh. So these probably connect
to Dash's cell.
And then there's more
in that room. Huh.
OK, please hurry.
[Dash] Hey... Yo, where are you going, bro?
These things are sharp!
[Cole] You'll be fine.
[Dash] Hurry!
Oh, yeah.
What up, kids?
I'm using gears to solve puzzles
to save my friends' lives.
- Lives are at stake.
- Hey, Cole!
Yeah, buddy.
I don't mean to sound
like a wimp
but this is starting
to get uncomfortable.
[Dash mocking] Aww, Thomas.
Is this a little scawy for you?
[Thomas] Man, whatever, G.
You sound like a wimp!
I'm gonna need you
to hang tight.
[grunts] Oh! Ah!
Oh, boy.
Hold on!
[grunts]
This is gonna be
a piece of cake.
- [alarm sounds]
- What was that?
Sorry.
OK, all right.
Dude, these things
are coming close.
- [grunts]
- [Dash] I think now's a good time
to let you guys know
I'm claustrophobic.
Yup! I think it's this one.
[Thomas]
Cole, it's tightening!
[grunts] Oh!
Cole!
I got it.
[Thomas] Get me out
of this shit!
Oh! Uh, yeah, man.
You probably should speed up
for his sake.
- OK, whoa. Whoa.
- [Thomas yells]
Yeah, hold on!
- [Thomas screams]
- [Dash] Whatever you did, don't do it.
It's getting faster!
Yes! Almost done!
Yo, where are you going?
- Where are you running?
- [Thomas grunts]
I gotta do the other side!
[Thomas yells]
Seriously, this is starting
to hurt!
[grunts] So heavy, dude.
Hold on.
OK, whoa. Whoa.
Uh, this is not OK.
- [alarm sounds]
- Oh, dammit!
- [Thomas] Ah!
- [Cole grunts]
[Dash] Fix my shit first!
OK, OK, OK...
B-b-b-b-b-back!
Ooh-ooh. Great. OK.
[grunts]
This is starting to get
a little fucking painful!
Hey, Thomas, hold on!
[chuckles]
Hold on! [grunts]
[grunts]
B-b-b-b-b-b!
[screams]
[Dash] Whoa-whoa-whoa!
[screaming and yelling]
Last one!
[screaming]
- [machines stop]
- [Dash] Oh!
Ooh-oh. Oh! Oh, shit.
[grunts]
Thank God. That was
way too fucking close.
[Cole] Oh. It worked.
Guys! I think I did it.
[Dash] Let me tell you how
claustrophobic I was getting.
[pants]
[Cole] All right! Thomasito,
I'm coming for ya.
Cole, get me out of this shit.
[pants]
[Dash] I know Alexei said this was
gonna hurt, but that shit was intense.
Look, we're running
out of time.
[Alexei over speaker] Oh,
you better get moving, guys.
Even he saw that.
Come on. Phantom Alexei.
[Thomas] Get this shit
over with.
[Dash chuckles]
[laughs]
Oh, God. This is
even kinky for you.
- I'm not gonna lie.
- Just get me out of here.
- We can't hear you.
- Get me out of here!
[muffled] Guys, I ain't
fucking... [indistinct]
Just come on, man.
All right.
We'll be back.
Unless you don't want us
to help you. Do you need help?
Come on, man.
Fuck you, man.
- What?
- Nothing. Get me out of here!
You... you like the chair?
You like... [laughs]
- [Samantha] You play too much, come on!
- [Dash] What?
[Thomas] All right, this looks
pretty straight-forward.
- [Dash laughs]
- Yeah.
- It's just a maze.
- Duh, it's a maze, Cole.
This is pretty cool, though.
OK, so...
You gotta go this way, yeah?
I guess it goes around?
- [sharp metal sound]
- Damn!
[Samantha screams]
[Dash] Whoa! Yo.
I think you just shocked her.
[Alexei over speaker] Hey,
you should be more careful with that, huh?
[Dash] Oh, OK. Let me see
this. Move, move, move.
Yeah, but, hey. But did you
hear what they said?
- Yeah.
- You got to be careful.
- [mocking] Be careful.
- Guys, guys. Come on. Let's get out of here.
All right. OK.
All right, so what'd you do
to shock her? You just... that?
- [electricity buzzes]
- [Samantha yells]
Oh ho. Whoops!
- [electricity buzzes]
- [Samantha yells]
[chuckles]
Easy, easy, easy.
- [electricity buzzes]
- [Samantha yells]
This is crazy. Look.
Dash! Dash, stop! Stop!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
[Samantha moans]
- [Thomas] Stop, guys! Easy!
- Thomas, relax.
-Yo, what the fuck?
Look! I think it's actually
hurting her!
[groans]
Relax, bro! It's a game!
Samantha, is this hurting you?
[grunts]
Should we get them
to stop this game?
What the fuck?
Here, give it to me.
- Be easy!
- Stop! No! Let go.
- It goes this way.
- I know where it goes.
[Thomas] I'm just tryin' to
tell you, I mapped it already.
- Make a right!
- It's all right, I got it.
[Thomas] Be quick about it.
Make a right.
[Samantha] No!
[electricity buzzes]
[Samantha yells]
Come on,
come on!
Easy, there.
You got a right.
- [electricity buzzes]
- [Samantha screams]
- [Thomas] Easy, easy!
- [Dash] Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Left.
[Dash] OK!
[Thomas] Make a right.
Shit.
[grunts]
You got a right,
and then a left.
[electricity buzzes]
[Samantha screams]
You guys, how you doing
in there?
I'm trying, shut up!
I'm trying to help you!
[electricity hums]
[grunts]
[Thomas] Now you gotta make a
right up here and then a left.
- [electricity buzzes]
- [Samantha yells]
Come on, you got it.
You're close, you're close,
you're close.
[Dash] H-hey!
[Cole] You got it!
Let's go!
[cries and moans]
Get this off me, man.
[Dash] What just happened?
I'm so sorry, Sam.
How bad was that?
I feel sick.
[gasps] That shit wasn't
right, man.
That shit wasn't right at all.
Well, Alexei said that this
was gonna be pretty intense.
- Fuckin' Alexei, man.
- This place is pretty intense.
Y'all think this is funny, huh?
Yo, yo, Sam. It's a game.
It's supposed to be...
Fuck that, Cole! This shit don't
feel like no game no more, man.
Sam, if you want to leave,
we can just leave right now.
You know I want to leave, man.
I don't wanna stay here no
more, Dashell.
I wanna go!
Look, why is nobody
answering us?
I don't know.
Alexei, hello?!
Guys! Hello?! Hello?!
What do you mean you don't
know? This is your guy.
- You were just talkin' to him.
- [Dash] yeah.
Where's he at now?
I don't know him all that well!
- What do you mean you don't know him that well?
- What?
I don't know, I met him
and he said he loved his vlogs.
He's some rich guy.
He said he did this before.
There's no way
this kid did this, man.
I don't know
what to tell you guys.
All I know is just as much
as you guys.
They change it every
single time.
It's intense.
But it's a game!
Dash. We're in Russia
with some guy
that you barely know
in some old prison?
Or wherever we are.
Are you fucking crazy?
How could I be
so stupid?
- This is so like you.
- What do you mean? Fuck... Fuck you!
What do you mean
"it's like" me?
You came on this trip, too.
Just fucking chill.
He's probably laughing at you right now.
He's messing with us.
He's not messing with us, Dash.
[Thomas] Guys?
What?!
[Thomas]
Get over here.
Oh, my God. Erin!
- [Dash] Shit!
- [Cole] Erin, are you OK?
How long do you think
it's gonna take to fill up?
[Dash] I don't know, if she's
OK... Are you OK?!
[muffled]
She doesn't know
what's going on.
She didn't even see
what happened to me.
- That's true.
- [Cole] I don't think she can even hear us.
Erin! Can you hear us?!
Cole. Can you hear her?
Fuck!
All right, where did you guys
just start from?
From down there.
Our devices hurt but not as bad
as that electric chair.
I bet.
Alexei, what gives, bro?!
What's next?
Are you even there?
Hello?!
Dash, they're not
gonna help us.
We're on our own.
OK.
This is just like
the other rooms.
We need to figure it out and
get her out now!
Now, now, now!
We're gonna be
right back!
[Cole] Uh...
What the hell
is this?
Ugh.
OK. Uh, three L, five L
Well, it's like that thing
from Die Hard.
I mean, then we also did it
at school once, too.
What?
Come on, man. We used to
love that movie.
It's an old puzzle.
Well, just, get her out
of there, OK?
- Let's solve it and get her out.
- All right.
OK, I got this, guys.
Use the three-liter jug
and the five-liter jug to get
precisely four liters of water.
So first we need to fill up
the five-liter jug.
[Cole] How she doing
over there?
[Dash] She's not freaking out,
so that's good.
Great. Now we pour
the five-liter jug
into the three-liter jug.
We need to fill that all the way up.
Help me out here.
That's in the three-liter.
Try to help me, all right.
Thank you.
Careful, we can't waste
any of this.
All right, stop.
Now.
That leaves us with two
liters of water
in the five-liter jug.
So now we need to empty out
the entire three-liter jug.
Um...
[Samantha]
Come on, Thomas.
Great. Now quickly.
Let's put the two liters
in the three-liter jug.
Help me out again?
Great, keep going.
Yup.
- All right.
- [Cole] OK.
[Thomas] Sweet!
All right. Now two liters are
in the three-liter jug, OK?
Which gives us room
for one more liter.
Let's fill up the
five-liter jug...
All right. Now time to top off
the three-liter jug.
Last step, guys.
Come on.
Thank you.
You remember all this from
Die Hard?
And perfect. Stop!
All right, great.
That should leave us with
exactly four liters of water
in the five liter jug.
- Come on, Thomas.
- [Thomas] How are we lookin'? How's Erin doing?
[Cole] You're really
cuttin' it close.
[Thomas] I know, I know.
Hold on.
There.
[gate unlocks]
- [Cole] Oh, my God, Erin!
- [Thomas] Shit!
[Cole] Erin!
Are you OK?
[Dash] All right, we need
to get her out of here.
How are we supposed
to do that?!
[muffled] This is the key!
The key, the key, uh...
Is there a latch
or something?
- [Cole] I don't see anything.
- I don't see any.
Hey, there's a hatch on top!
OK, uh...
Here, grab one!
- [Cole] Dash!
- [Dash] She has the key.
Hold on.
[grunts]
It's rusted shut!
What do you mean
it's rusted shut?
- It's rusted shut, man!
- It's not rusted shut!
- Just pull harder!
- That's what I'm doing, man!
Turn it! Turn it at the same time.
Come on!
[grunts]
God, fuck!
Oh, my God.
Come on!
[Cole] Ah, it should be
fucking opening!
What's going on?
She's gonna fucking drown!
Find something to
break this open, Cole!
Erin!
[whimpering]
Fuck. I don't know
what to do.
I don't know what to do.
- [screaming]
- I know.
[Samantha] Cole, she's gonna
fucking drown!
Alexei, what the fuck!
That's enough!
Stop the game!
We can't get her out!
Alexei! Victoria!
Stop the game!
We can't get her out!
Fuck!
Alexei!
Anyone?
[screaming]
Fuck!
Alexei! Anyone!
[Dash] Erin!
No, no, no, no!
Alexei! Where the fuck
are you?!
Fuck, man.
We're never gonna
get this off!
Shit. Shit.
[grunts]
[screams]
Move! Move!
[grunts]
[cries]
Fuck!
[grunts]
[gasps]
Erin! [shouting indistinct]
[grunts]
Help me! Help me!
Help me!
Erin!
[grunts] Help me!
Yeah. Oh, God.
Erin! Erin! Erin!
Slow, slow, slow.
Watch her head.
I don't know.
[Cole] Erin! Erin!
[Samantha] Oh, my God.
Erin!
- Erin!
- [Samantha] She's not breathing!
[Dash] What do we do?
[Samantha]
Give her mouth-to-mouth!
[coughs]
[all] Oh, my God!
Oh! Oh, my God!
Oh!
Get her up, get her up,
get her up.
[Dash] Thank God
you're OK.
[coughs]
Thank God, thank God.
[alarm sounds]
What the fuck is that?
Is it over?
Fuck that.
Are you OK?
[coughs] I'm OK.
OK, OK. She...
[Erin] I'm OK
- [Cole] You good?
- Uh-huh. OK.
Fuck!
I don't get it. Why the fuck
didn't they come?
Why did they say?
I tried to... I... We
couldn't do anything!
Because Alexei was helping us
and then he was just gone!
We was yellin' to them the
whole entire time, Erin.
We... we... Let's go.
[Cole] Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wait, hey, hey. That's...
that's gotta be the key
for the end
of the hall.
Yeah, let's go.
Let's go.
- Can you get up?
- Mm-hmm.
[coughs]
Fuck this place.
Alexei, what the fuck?
What the fuck?
[Dash] Whoa, shit!
Alexei?
Hello?
[Erin] What the hell is this?
[Dash] Alexei?
[Thomas] Dash,
the door, the door!
- [Dash] Fuck!
- [Cole] Fuck!
No, no.
[Thomas] What happened here?
I... I don't know.
But whatever it was,
it was bad.
- We were just talking to Alexei and then he stopped.
- [Erin] OK.
What if this is
still part of it?
No, fuck, no. We lost.
Look at the timer.
It's over.
Someone should be here.
Someone should've been here
a long time ago
after what happened in there.
Maybe the audience saw it
on my feed and they're
sending help or...
I don't think so.
I don't see any cameras.
- There's blood on the wall.
- What?!
Fuck!
-[Erin] Cole!
What do we do?
Uh, I don't know. Uh...
It's jammed, the door's locked!
[Dash] This won't open either.
OK, hold on.
Let me try.
[Cole] Shit!
[Dash] OK, think.
Maybe we can
break the lock.
OK, hold...
Maybe we should
stay here.
[Dash] If there's actual danger,
this is the best place to be.
We'll just wait for the security
to come back.
[Thomas] Yeah, he's right.
That makes sense.
[Dash] What are you doing?
Cole.
[all] Cole! Cole! Wait! No!
Dude, what the fuck?!
We're getting out of there now.
Fuck that, I'm not
going out there.
None of us should.
Everybody, listen.
We don't have any
identification.
We are in a strange country.
We don't have our phones,
our wallets,
our passports, anything.
We need to leave now!
We're gonna stick together
and find help!
[Erin screams]
Oh, what the fuck?!
Oh, my God.
[woman cries]
[speaks Russian]
- [speaks Russian]
- [Dash] No, no, no! Wait!
[screams]
Oh, my God!
[grunts]
[Cole] Erin? Thomas?
[speaks Russian]
[Cole] What are you
doing to us?
What do you want?
Where's Alexei?
[speaks Russian]
[Cole] What do you want
with us?
[Cole] Let go of me!
Where are my friends?
[speaks Russian]
[Erin] Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
[grunts]
[speaks Russian]
Hello, Cole.
Who... who is that?
How do you know my name?
[gasps]
Who are you?
What is this?
Oh, my God.
Please, please, please.
[man] You fucking Americans.
This is... this is a mistake.
[man] You think you're so safe?
M-misunderstanding.
[man] Mm?
I don't know...
I don't know who you are.
When a man is shot
in the head,
there's so much blood.
Nothing can prepare you
for it.
It goes everywhere.
[chuckles]
[speaking Russian]
[man] Who am I?
I'll show you who I am.
- [man] Bam!
- [Cole screams]
Fuck! [sobs]
[laughs]
My friends and I
were just visiting,
having fun.
We went to a club,
I... I don't know what happened.
We just want to go home.
Please, please, please.
[speaking Russian]
What is this?
Are you broadcasting this?
[speaking Russian]
Exclusive.
American [speaking Russian]
[speaking Russian] Huh?
[speaking Russian]
Celebrity!
Celebrity.
[Cole] No.
[speaking Russian]
[shouts]
Gah!
You know how much they pay
to watch people like you
get torn apart
piece by piece?
[Cole coughs]
- They love to watch.
- [Cole] No!
[Cole] What are you doing?
[man] They love to decide
how we do it.
[Cole] Oh, please.
No!
And first up, is the girl!
No, don't you fucking...
Don't you fucking touch her!
[speaking Russian]
No, no, please.
We'll kill one of you
every half hour.
No! No!
[speaking Russian]
[Cole] No, no, no, please!
[muffled grunts]
[muffled] Please, please!
[door slams]
[pants]
[Erin grunts]
[Erin pants]
[Cole] Oh, my God.
[pants]
[Erin sobs]
Fuck!
[faint screams]
Oh, my God.
[faint cries] Oh, my God!
[indistinct]
[Samantha] What the fuck
are you doing, man?
[speaking Russian]
[Samantha] Come on, man.
We can work this out...
[speaking Russian]
[Samantha] Are you fuckin'
filming this?
[speaking Russian]
[Samantha] I promise if you
let me out of here,
- I'm gonna fuck you up, man!
- [speaking Russian]
[Samantha] What is all that
stuff you're sayin', man?
Man, what are you doing, man?
[pants] Huh?
What's all of that? One of you guys
gotta speak English. Talk to me!
[speaking Russian]
[Samantha] Fuck!
- [speaking Russian]
- [Samantha] Come on, man! Come on!
No.
[Samantha] Just chill...
The fuck you gonna do with that?
- No, no, no!
- [Samantha screams]
[Samantha screams]
Please stop!
[Samantha cries]
No.
[Samantha] Fuck you!
My fuckin' eye!
[speaking Russian]
[Samantha cries]
Now, come on.
Come on, come on.
Please stop!
[Samantha screams]
[gurgling]
[gasps]
[cries]
[coughs]
Goddamn it!
[grunting]
Oh, shit.
[sighs]
[trembled breaths]
[grunts] Ow!
[faint screams]
[grunts]
[man speaking Russian]
[speaking Russian]
[Dash] What do you want?
[man speaking Russian]
Dash.
[Dash] What? What the fuck?
What are you talking...?
[Andrei] And you,
been chosen.
What if... what if we
talk about this, man?
What if I could do
something?
- Like you...
- You know I have a lot of...
...you have audience,
I have audience.
OK.
Mine is just a little
more selective than yours.
[Dash] We can talk about this.
You don't have to fuckin' do this.
[Andrei chuckles]
What the fuck
are you doing?
[screams]
You know how much they pay
for an American?
[Dash screams]
Huh? They love to watch.
[speaks Russian]
You have any preferences?
[muffled] Fuck you!
[Andrei laughs]
[Dash cries]
[mock crying]
They've chosen.
- [machine whirrs]
- [Andrei speaks Russian]
[Dash screams]
[screams]
[Andrei] Still alive?
Final words?
- [gasps]
- [Dash whimpering]
[Andrei] I can't help it.
I enjoy this.
[speaks Russian]
- [Andrei chuckles]
- [machine whirrs]
[Dash screams]
[pants]
[speaks Russian]
[gasps]
[man speaks Russian]
[speaks Russian]
[men speaking Russian]
[grunts] Fuck.
Oh, my God.
- [beeping]
- [door unlocks]
Mister Cole, I'm so glad
you found...
You!
What the fuck is this?
No! Please,
no, no, no, no.
I have been trying to help you.
Help me? You're the fucking
driver. What is this?
Listen to me!
I couldn't say nothing earlier
because he is always watching.
Who? Who is always watching?
There's no time. Please.
You need to go.
Please! You need to go,
right now!
Go where? What the fuck?
What about my friends?
There is no help
for your friends.
You have the chance to escape.
Take my car.
Please, go.
They are coming!
- Who's coming?
- They are coming! Go!
Why are you helping me?
Hide!
[speaking Russian]
[grunts]
[coughing]
[speaking Russian]
[grunts]
[pants]
[whispering] Thomas.
Holy shit. You're alive.
Cole?
I'm gonna get you out of here.
You OK?
- I'm so glad you're here.
- What did they do to you?
Oh, your face.
I can't see shit, Cole.
Wait, wait.
Can you walk?
Yeah, yeah. OK.
[grunts]
[Cole grunts]
Go, go over here.
Go, go, go!
[Cole] Go, go, go, go!
[man speaking Russian]
[Thomas] Cole, Cole, Cole.
I can't see.
- Oh, yeah, OK.
- [men speaking Russian]
[Andrei shouting Russian]
[man speaking Russian]
Shh.
[metal clanging]
[metal scraping]
[banging]
[speaking Russian]
[sighs]
[metal scraping]
[both gasp]
[grunts]
[pants]
[Cole sobs] Sorry.
Oh, my God.
What are they doing to us?
[Cole] Torturing us.
People are paying to watch.
Sam and Dash are...
[Thomas]
Sam and Dash are what?
[sobs]
They're gone.
I couldn't do anything,
Thomas.
[cries] They died right
in front of me.
[sniffs] Have you seen Erin?
No.
How do you get these
things off?
They took mine off.
I was put in rusty handcuffs.
Broke mine off when
I pulled this. [grunts]
OK, wait, stay here.
I'm gonna find something to break those.
Yeah.
[grunts]
[door bangs]
Shh!
[banging]
[banging continues throughout]
Well, where the hell
do you think it goes?
I don't know.
I'll guide you.
Just trust me.
[grunts]
[Andrei speaking Russian]
[Cole] All right, let's go.
[Andrei yelling in Russian]
- [Cole] Up here.
- [Thomas] Where are we going?
[groans]
I'll help you up.
[grunts]
OK, OK. Stay here.
[men speaking
faint Russian]
Someone's coming.
Come on, Thomas.
OK, OK.
There's gotta be some way
out of here.
[indistinct]
[Thomas]
What do we do?
Can we turn
this on?
[gun cocks]
Fuck!
[Thomas groans]
Cole!
[thud]
[inaudible dialogue]
Oh, fuck.
[man speaking Russian]
[speaking Russian]
[men speaking Russian]
[Andrei speaking Russian] Hey!
[Andrei speaking Russian]
[Igor speaking Russian]
[Alexei speaking Russian]
[groans]
[speaking Russian]
[men speaking Russian]
[pants]
[Erin grunts]
[jiggles door handle]
[screams]
Erin?
[men speaking Russian]
[Erin screams]
[Erin screams loudly]
Stop! Stop!
No further.
Let her go or I'll
fucking shoot you.
I don't think so.
One more move and I kill her.
- [Erin cries]
- [Cole] Please let her go.
I will do whatever you want.
We... we didn't do
anything to you.
Please let her go.
My men will come rushing
through the door any second.
[Erin gasps] No!
I'm so sorry.
What the fuck is this?
What the fuck are you doing?
What do you want?
Do you want money?
I will give you... I'll pay you.
I'll give you all my money.
Please, please, let her go.
[Erin pants]
They pay me more.
[Andrei] You think you're fast
enough?
Huh?
[indistinct pleading]
- Cole...
- [Andrei laughs]
[Andrei] Do it!
[Andrei] Oy. [laughs]
- [Erin gasps]
- Do it!
[Erin sobs]
[Andrei laughs]
[whispers] I love you.
[Erin screams]
[Andrei shouts]
[gasps]
[Andrei grunts]
Wait!
[distant] Erin!
No, no, no!
[men speaking Russian]
[shouting in Russian]
Oh, my God.
[men shouting]
[grunts]
Fuck!
[groans]
Cole...
[speaks Russian]
[Alexei] How does it feel
to lose everything, huh?
[whispers]
Motherfucker!
[Alexei] Come on.
Hey, hey, hey, Cole.
[Cole] How could you
do that to them?
- Hey, hey, Cole, please!
- [Cole] Fuck you!
Let me explain!
[Cole] Fuckin' piece of...
I'll kill you!
- I'll fuckin' kill you!
- [grunts]
Fuckin' piece of shit.
We trusted you,
you motherfucker!
[Alexei] It's not real!
They're all... they're all...
[screams]
[Alexei groans]
[pants]
[Cole on recording] So in three
months, my friends and I
are gonna be doing
something special.
They promised me it's gonna be
amazing.
Thank you all so much
for watching,
for voting, and for following.
[Dash] Yeah, we got drinks,
motherfucker!
[chatter and laughter]
[Alexei] Every experience
is tailored to the player.
[Dash] Oh, my God.
- [speaking Russian]
- [cries]
[cries]
[murmuring]
Oh, my...
[Igor on recording] I need
to have you back by eight!
This is yours.
[Cole on recording] That's enough!
Stop the game! We can't get her out!
Oh, my God.
[Cole on recording]
Where are you!
Help! Fuck!
[gasps]
[man on recording] Erin, Samantha, Dash.
We're taking you...
- [Cole panting]
- [Dash on recording] So sick!
Ah!
[laughter]
[panting] What the fuck?
[panting heavily]
Hey, babe.
Where are you?
Oh, great, you're almost here.
We'll see you
in a second. Bye.
He just pulled
in the driveway.
[Cole] You want anything?
No, I'm good.
FaceTime Thomas.
- Hey, what up, Dash?
- All right, so he still doesn't know.
So just tell everybody to keep
it on the low.
Dude, this is gonna be crazy.
He's not gonna even see it coming.
When's the last time you
guys even seen each other?
Must've been some years, bro.
OK, I'm gonna have to
let you go. He's coming.
OK, sounds good.
I'll see you soon.
All right, see you, bud.
What's up, guys? Dash here.
And check this out.
- We just picked up Thomas!
- Hey!
He still has no idea.
[Dash] We got Alexei.
Hey. See you soon.
[speaks Russian]
It'll be so crazy.
Oh, my gosh.
I can't believe he
just has no idea.
- You don't think he does?
- What's up?
[Dash] He's gonna know
that this is fake.
[man] He won't, trust me.
I'm taking care of everything.
[Erin] Aren't we worried
this isn't too much?
[Dash] He's always looking for
something to actually scare him, right?
If we pull this off,
this is it.
There's no turning back now.
Remember, dude. We love you.
This is crazy even for you.
- [Dash chuckles]
- You'll love it, bro.
- All right, man, good luck.
- Peace.
Peace.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org