Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Seven-fifty.
Is there no chance you can
spare us a dollar or two, huh?
Right.
How's your dad doing?
He's hanging in there.
Hey. Hey!
Do I know you?
Look at me like that again
like you did inside of there,
and I'll knock your fucking
lights out... China boy.
I'm Korean.
Same fucking thing to me.
All right. See you, man.
You think you're
better than me, don't you?
I saw the way you
looked at me back there.
No! No!
What are you,
some kind of computer whiz?
- I don't know...
- Shut the fuck up!
Yeah. You're all the same.
You flood into our
fucking country
and you take all of our jobs.
No, no, no...
You're a little rat,
aren't you?
Say it.
I'm a little rat.
Louder.
- Louder!
- I'm a little rat!
I'm... I'm a little rat.
Don't you ever come
back here again, rat.
What are you looking at?
Ah, Prasumas.
My favorite.
Johnny...
What happened to your face?
It's fine.
- Huh?
- I said it's fine.
Ay, Johnny, it's all...
You're bleeding.
Who did this to you?
Seriously, it isn't a big deal.
I should have been there.
I can take care of myself, Dad.
They're scared of you
because you're different.
But that's not your fault.
Different doesn't
mean you're bad.
I know.
Johnny, one day...
I won't be here
to look after you.
Who is looking after who?
You're not going anywhere.
Is this some kind of prank?
What...?
Crazy.
It's crazy.
Who is this?
Friend.
I like your music.
Is it?
It's kind of depressing.
Sad but not mean.
I guess.
What is that?
You can hear that?
I hear certain sounds.
What's happening?
Bad things.
What do we do?
Nothing.
We can't do anything.
Not our problem.
- Um, hello.
- I can help.
But I need your help
and permission.
What are you going to do?
Stop the bad things.
And, uh...
What kind of...
help do you need?
I want to see through you.
I don't get it.
I want to be part
of your world.
The real world.
See. What do you see?
Um...
Okay, okay.
No!
No. Please.
Help me, please.
911.
What's your emergency?
Hello?
Hey, rat!
What did I tell you, huh?
I told you not to come
around here anymore.
Didn't I, rat? Huh?
Don't call me that.
I'll call you whatever I want.
Someone else calls you
that nickname, right?
Oh. They don't know, do they?
Shut the fuck up.
Mommy went to jail when
Dirk was a little boy, huh?
Shut the fuck up.
Do you hear me?
When daddy gets lonely,
he gets drunk.
He must have hit you a little too
hard inside of your head, huh?
- Come on, Dirk.
- 'Cause now you're out picking on rats like me.
You know it's
really something.
All the shit you can find
when you dig
into someone's cell phone.
You my fucking shrink now?
What's happening?
Bad people.
Don't look at me like that.
- Stop.
- Don't fucking look to me like that.
I want to help.
Do it.
Mm...
These must be the best Prasumas yet.
They're so juicy.
I like when you're happy.
It makes me happy.
I can't always be happy.
I guess that this
will have to do.
Don't you have to get that?
What is it?
You're punishing him.
Sorry?
Your father... it will spread
quickly and he will suffer.
You're punishing him.
No.
He wants to be with me.
You are the one causing this
pain but it didn't... like this.
Let me help.
- No.
- Let me help.
Absolutely not.
You sound like a bad man.
I won't let you do this.
I don't need your permission.
Johnny!
Stay away
from anything connected.
Quick! We have
to get out of here.
We have to get out of here!
Oh, my God!
Shit.
No!
No, no, no.
Stay away from him!
I'll do anything.
Just don't hurt him.
Find me another.
Hey, how you doing back there?
Hm?
Nice and comfy?
You don't say much
but you are great company.
Hello, Jonathan.
Where am I?
That is
everybody's first question.
Totally normal reaction.
The real question is,
where do we place you?
It says here that you are
good with computers.
You actually
build your own rigs.
I do, too.
In fact, I've actually built
one of my own right here.
I think you might appreciate it.
Would you like to go see it?
Right.
You know, somebody
with your skill set
could really rise the ranks
around here.
Interesting.
You know, reactions tell us
so much about the human mind.
For example...
you spitting in my face tells
me you tend to get bullied...
that you're not very good
at protecting yourself.
What does my reaction
tell you about me?
You know,
you look like somebody
who used to be here
a very long time ago.
Same disrespect.
Jones!
Our patient has
had a very long day.
Let's make sure
he feels at home.
Yes, sir.
Where to?
Block 10.
Campers!
Jonathan, I'd like you
to meet your new friends.
It's Johnny.
Are we being a little shy?
All right, allow me
to make the introductions.
Over here. This is Alma.
She's a little bit
of a crank pot. Stay clear.
This one is Emma.
Ignore her scar.
She can be very sweet... at times.
Hi, Emma.
This is our mommy, Renee.
Pleasure.
And that cot right there
is designated for,
well, Sami.
She's getting ready
for her session.
Let's get him dressed.
I can't wait
to show you the lab.
It's funny, after so many
years of experimentation,
the solution is so simple.
Target receptors in the brain
by a homemade
cocktail designed by me
that allows to extract
the sensation known as fear...
into an easily contained gas.
Please. I can't do it again.
They tend to get like this after
they've been here for a while.
You see this canister?
This is our future.
It holds the gas.
Sami, why don't you show
the new guy how it works?
All right, I'll help.
So, you're just gonna leave?
Harry, please, just stop.
It was a fucking accident.
- Shut the fuck up!
- Stop.
This is exactly why
I need to get away from you.
You're fucking twisted.
Harry, I didn't mean to.
Come on.
You know I didn't mean to...
Bullshit! You fucking used me.
Harry, please just wait...
Babe, babe, babe, come on.
Babe, look at me.
Look at me.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Babe, what about us?
- Hm? Come on.
- "Us"?
There was no fucking "us".
It was all about you.
How am I gonna do this?
I can't do this alone.
You should have fucking thought
about that before you did it, huh?
Come on. Let's just go back.
Everything will be fine.
I'm just freaking out
right now.
Come on. Let's just fucking go.
Get the fuck away from me,
you crazy fucking bitch!
What the fuck
are you looking at?
Fuck!
Fucking...
Fuck.
Fuck! Fuck!
Oh, shit!
Pick up the fucking phone.
You know what to do.
Fuck.
Fucking shit!
What the fuck?
Fuck.
Fuck. What the fuck?
Fuck...
Fuck.
You know what to do.
No.
Come on, baby.
Come on.
Yeah.
Fuck!
Oh, my God.
We can finally
get a place.
Just you and I.
Maybe with a garage.
Where we can practice.
Maybe get that new guitar.
No shit.
I don't think they see him.
Every day at 6:00,
he takes a drawer to the bank.
Hey.
Just do what we talked about.
Everything will be fine.
No one gets hurt?
No one.
Just scare him a little.
He's an asshole,
but he's not stupid.
He'll give it up.
Ready?
You got this.
Hey, I'm right here.
Okay. You got this.
You fucking got this.
Give me the fucking money.
Over my dead body,
you little shit.
I'm not fucking
around with you!
Give me the fucking money.
You don't have the balls
to take my money, son.
Come on, Harry!
Fuck.
What the fuck
have you done?
Just shut the fuck up.
Shut the fuck up.
Open the fucking trunk.
Yes. More.
That's good.
More.
Don't! Make it stop!
Damn it, Sami!
Well, at least we got some
of what we needed.
Get him out of here.
No! No! No!
Hey.
Hey, Emma. It's all right.
It's all right.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry.
There's nothing there.
What's going on?
Too many of those
fucking sessions.
I just want it to stop.
I just
wanna get some sleep.
Hey,
keep your voice down.
You don't want them to take
you back to the shrinker.
Why do they call it that?
Too many tests in it
shrinks your brain.
The more you talk about it,
the better you'll feel...
and the less
the machine will affect you.
- Hi, husband.
- Wife.
How come
you're not asleep?
I don't know,
grading papers,
waiting for you.
Yeah. Uh,
that's why I'm calling.
I gotta be here a little bit
later than I was thinking
to spend the night
at the office.
Come back and see you tomorrow?
It's, like,
four nights in a row.
I'm starting to think
you're having an affair.
Look,
I'll just come back in the morning.
Get some sleep.
Take a break from grading.
They're middle schoolers.
How complex are they?
You'd be surprised.
I'll believe
when I see it.
- I love you.
- Love you.
Hello?
Who is this?
Fuck.
Who the fuck is doing this?
Who's in my house?
Get out of my fucking house.
Get out of my fucking house!
Hello?
Olly olly oxen free.
Damn, Blaire. Got her good.
Fuck yeah, I did.
You see this?
Your sister's done good.
Want to taste the blade?
How are we gonna do her?
Stab her
till she bleeds out, I guess.
Won't that be too much blood?
Yeah, Grady.
Bodies have blood in them.
So, yeah, she'll have a bit
more blood to come out.
Why are you doing this?
What are you doing here?
Stop talking.
I'll cut your lips off.
Isaac...
Hi, Miss Palmer.
- Isaac, don't look at her, man.
- No, Isaac, look at her.
I want everyone to look at her.
He's cute.
Real handsome.
Blaire, come on.
You like to fuck
married men, do you?
Would you like to fuck our dad?
Blaire, stop.
I'm sorry.
Sorry for which part?
Fucking our dad?
For ruining our family?
Why don't we just curb stomp
her outside and then...
stab her to death.
We can't just bring her outside
and curb stomp her, dumb shit.
Fuck. There's rocks
in your brains.
- Why not?
- 'Cause the neighbors will see.
No one's gonna see it.
They're all gonna be asleep...
You're one
clumsy bitch, Miss Palmer.
You coming?
You want dad to be a fucking
punchline for the rest of his life?
Let's go.
You kids don't think you're gonna
really get away with this, do you?
Shut up.
We're gonna do her or what?
I'm starving.
Strip.
What?
Blaire, stop this.
I want you
to take off your clothes.
No.
I'm sorry... what?
I'm not doing that.
You're acting like
you have a choice.
Why?
'Cause we want some
foreplay before we kill you.
Come on, Blaire.
That is enough.
Isaac, one more time...
Let me out.
Calm down, calm down.
It was an accident.
Shit, Blaire.
I think he's dead.
What the fuck did you do?
Help!
Get the fuck off me.
911, I'd like
to report a murder.
We were just messing around.
But then she just snapped.
Stay right here. We'll make
sure you get home safely.
- Mom?
- Sweetheart.
- Mom.
- It's okay.
I'm just freaking out.
What is going on?
Get the hell away from me.
Okay, okay, okay.
- Get away from me.
- Okay, okay, relax.
Who's up first?
Please let me see him.
- Okay.
- Now.
- Let's get you hooked up.
- In person.
Please, he's so young.
I'll go instead.
Oh, I love volunteers.
But, sadly,
that's not how this works.
Come on.
Up you go. Yeah.
Full cannister, please.
Clear.
Drop it. Put it down!
Move. Get down on the ground.
There's two in here.
Put your hands
where I can see them.
Shut the fuck up.
No.
Oh, shit.
- Come on.
- What the fuck, man.
Hey, take him outside.
- Get the rest.
- Clear.
Take all the time you need,
all right?
I'm gonna go make sure
everything's in order.
Let's go.
Mama.
Mr. B said I'm
sounding pretty good so far.
Yeah? Let me hear some.
Okay. This is the D
major scale.
I can't believe
you just started lessons.
It is sounding so good.
Yeah. It's really hard.
Oh, try it. Try it.
No. You know
I can't play anything.
- Oh, yes, you can.
- No, I don't even know how to hold it.
Okay, so you put
this hand right here,
and then you hold the bow
on the other hand,
and then you put
the bow right there.
And yes.
Why is it not making any sound?
Oh.
- I'm much better at singing.
- No, no, no, no.
- What's wrong with my singing?
- You sing horrible.
Go, go, go!
Carlos, get down.
Down on the floor.
Carlos!
Mama! Mama!
- Mama!
- Sorry. I'm sorry.
It's okay, Mama.
I was playing with this and
I don't know what happened.
How many times
do I have to tell you
not to play
with this violent game?
Huh?
Who gave you this?
Who fucking gave you this?
Chris let me borrow it.
Well, tomorrow at school
you take it right back to him.
Okay? You hear me?
- Si?
- Si.
Perdon.
I got an idea.
Did you finish your homework?
- Mm-hm.
- Yeah?
Why don't we go try this place
that Tia Arianne told us about?
- Yeah?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Okay.
- It sounds good.
Yeah. Let's go.
Mm.
Looks so good but I'm so full.
Well,
I can make you a bacon sandwich
with the leftovers tomorrow.
- That sound good?
- Mm-hm.
I'm gonna run to the restroom.
Stay right here.
Okay.
Hi, there.
How's everything so far?
Oh, so good.
You ready for me
to take anything?
- Um, just these.
- All righty.
All right, buddy.
How about another milkshake?
It looks like
you finished this one.
Yeah. Quick
before my mom gets back.
- I forgot to tell you something.
- Mm-hm.
Mr. B said he entered our
music group into a talent show.
That's fun.
Where's it gonna be?
Well, he said here,
but if we win that round
and a couple more,
we can go to New York and
perform in front of everyone.
We have to make
our own original song,
and we have to play our
instruments and everything.
Wow.
That's... that's amazing.
So you better
start practicing...
Yeah, when we get home,
I'll practice them all.
Have you been
to New York before?
- Huh?
- Have you been to New York?
- Get down. Get down.
- What?
Let's go.
Get down. Get down.
- What?
- Get out of here.
Come here. Come here.
- Mama, Mama, stop it.
- Let go now!
Hey, stop,
don't touch her.
You're insane.
- Mama! Don't touch her.
- Stop it.
- You can't put me away...
- We're gonna need you to...
- Son, you need to calm down.
- Mama!
- Calm down.
- Carlos! Carlos!
- Mama.
- Carlos.
Mama, Mama. Stop.
- Let her go.
- Son, you need to calm down.
...seized along
with a small amount of cocaine...
Thank God there's only so much they can
pull out of this dusty old brain of mine.
Hey, come over here.
Hey.
What do you want?
A companion.
Not you. I just meant
in general.
Oh.
I want your teeth.
You'll hardly miss 'em.
What the fuck? Go away from me.
Just messing with you.
You got a twisted cuspid.
I can do way better than that.
They do that to your face?
No.
This is all my own doing.
Why?
Well...
When you have a fear like mine,
you don't really have a choice.
You want to hear about
what happened to me?
As you know, the Ronaldo Group
is the number one architecture
firm in the country.
And I've been their top guy
for over a year.
I just wanted to mix it up,
and, uh,
I don't think moving here to
Boucher would feel like a step back
since I get to work
with all these lovely ladies.
I mean women.
I mean female architects.
Uh...
What's with the gloves?
Oh, I wear these while
I'm working on the models
and the office is always
so cold.
I've just been leaving them on.
Yeah.
Thanks for coming
in such late notice.
Mister...
McNerney.
Yeah.
- We'll be in touch.
- Yeah.
Oh!
Yeah.
It's Mr. Boucher
on the other line for you.
Put him through.
This Steinhardt proposal
is a complete fucking disaster.
What's the problem?
The calculations
were off six degrees
and now half the roof
is in the ground.
- What?
- You heard me.
- Okay.
- This isn't rocket science.
Get those girls' heads out
of their asses and fix it.
I'll take care of it
right away.
Jesus. You have no sense of
direction, just like your mother.
Dad, this is the first
I'm hearing of it.
And I'm sorry.
Yes, Ms. Boucher?
I need everyone from
the Steinhardt team
in the conference room with all
the project materials right away.
I'll send them right in.
We have a serious problem.
We know. We hadn't anticipated the
Brocol group pulling this imminent...
I'm not talking about Brocol.
The foundation's
calculations are off.
Uh, the surveyor reported...
I'm not talking
about boundary lines.
- Our crew...
- I'm not talking about boundary lines.
Our crew measured
multiple times.
What's gonna happen
to the roof
if the structure slopes
an additional six degrees
toward the ground?
We'll be that much closer
to Kevin Bacon?
Get the fuck out of my office!
I was kidding.
It was a joke.
Get the fuck out of my office!
Um... the
measurements taken on May 16th
are congruent with the data
collected on June 3rd.
And we made sure
to accompany the crew.
And what were the findings?
Um, we did mark a discrepancy
in our numbers.
Well, what matters now
is that we fix it.
I'm going home.
I expect you there
with a plan in place.
We'll stay up all night
if we have to.
No one rests
till this is resolved.
- Yes, ma'am.
It went really well.
I mean, I think we were
vibing a little bit, too.
- That's great.
- Yeah.
I mean, you'd be the first guy
we've had in a while.
That right?
Yeah. She likes her employees
young and pretty.
Well, that explains
why you're here.
Um, but...
you don't want to get
on her bad side.
One wrong move and
you're out of here.
Yeah. Excommunicated.
Buried and never
heard from again.
Mr. McNerney.
You're hired.
Uh, wow. Um, thank you.
Lia and Natalie will update you
in the conference room
and I expect you three
at my house later tonight.
Yeah. No, you got it.
Thank you again.
- Take your shoes off.
- Okay.
Wow, groovy place.
You still cold?
Yeah.
Brr.
Do you mind if I put this down?
No, no, no.
Why don't you set it in here
on the coffee table?
You're gonna help yourselves
to something to eat,
and we're gonna get to work.
We think we found a solution.
It might even cut our costs.
I'm so sorry.
That's okay.
Stay right there, I'll get it.
I can't...
- Gross.
- Oh.
You're awake.
Oh, goodie.
I am so excited
to show you this
now that it's ready.
It's time for
the maiden voyage.
Come on, Johnny. Get in.
Get up!
Let's go. We're gonna take this
for a little bit of spin.
Stay!
I'm not gonna be much help.
Why would you say that?
I thought you would want
to be part of history.
Help!
They're not gonna
help you, Johnny.
Help!
Your cooperation is greatly
appreciated, Johnny.
Thank you very much.
- How's your dad going?
- He hanging in there.
What are you
going to do?
Stop the bad things.
Don't fucking
look at me like that.
No!
Find me another.
What the hell!
You tortured my father.
And I have taken care of him
every single day
since he came back
from this place.
Rot in hell.
We need to get out
of this place.
Move, move!
You all find a way out.
I'll stay with him.
Where the fuck are we?
It's a government
testing facility.
They've been using your fears to
infect and control the population.
They're weaponizing fear?
Against their our own country?
We need to get out of here.
I have an idea.
Go, go, go.
Dr. Wright!
Get off of me!
What... what is that?
What's going on?
Get off, get off!
Get him off!
Get him off me!
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull