Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
Hey, guys, Graham here.
How's it going?
Today marks
the two-year anniversary
since I've been making
videos for the internet.
Whoo.
So because of that,
I wanted to do something
a little bit different.
So I'm going
to tell you two stories.
Two stories that I think sum up
what it's like to make
videos for the internet.
And it might get
a little abstract,
so please bear with me.
First story is about
paratroopers in World War II.
Obviously.
But specifically
I'm talking about D-Day.
Now, obviously,
there were a lot of
fatalities and, um,
casualties that day.
But there was one bizarre
and common injury
that was caused
not by the enemy,
but by the perceptions
of the soldiers themselves.
You see, a lot of paratroopers
missed their targets.
They ended up in ponds
or lakes or trees or whatever.
Some of them ended
up on rooftops.
Now, think of yourself
in that situation,
you land on a rooftop,
what would you do?
You'd probably try
and climb down into a window
on the upper story
and get inside,
just take the stairs downstairs.
Well, what a lot
of these paratroopers did...
was they walked up
to the edge of the roof...
and just jumped off.
Just multiple stories,
straight down to the ground,
breaking their legs or worse.
You see,
what was happening was...
they'd just jumped
a thousand feet and survived.
So to them,
looking down from the roof...
the drop to the ground
was nothing.
With just a slight change
in their perception...
they'd managed to change
an inherent truth...
that if you jump off of a roof,
you're going to hurt yourself...
into a fallacy.
That's the first story.
Second story
is a little bit more personal,
and is about my friend Stephen.
So, Stephen's a photographer
and a traveler.
He went all around the world,
took photos wherever he went.
And I thought that
he should share these online.
So I encouraged him
to set up a blog.
He was resistant at first,
but ultimately he did it.
And people started following and
sharing their opinions on his work.
Some good, some not so good.
This is the internet after all.
And it was around then
that things got scary.
He sent me a photo
with only this caption:
"Can you see it?"
This is the photo.
Can you see it?
After Stephen insisted that
the photo wasn't faked...
he proceeded to send more.
But that wasn't
the weirdest thing...
I asked him what
he thought was causing it,
or what it was.
And what he said to me really
freaked me out for a long time.
He said,
"Can't you see it, Graham?
It's you."
I didn't hear from Stephen
for a good while after that.
And it wasn't until
a couple of years later
that I bumped into him
and I was able to ask him
about the photos,
and whether he was still getting
any weird apparitions in them.
And he said to me,
it, it was funny.
He hadn't seen anything
strange in the photos
since the day that
he shut his blog down.
Anyway, that's, uh,
that's all from me today.
Sorry it's a bit
doom and gloom today.
Um, things will be back
to normal next week, um.
Uh, it'll be a bit more
upbeat, hopefully.
Um, but, yeah, as always...
what's the worst
that could happen?
Where to start?
Hello!
Walkies.
Walkies. Walkies.
Graham...
He's a fud.
I've never met anyone that could
dedicate so much time and energy
to just doing something stupid.
Got any, uh...
- bags for life?
- Aye, they'll cost you extra.
- Target's holding, move, move.
- F###!
No, no, he pretended
he didn't give a shit
what people thought but,
he obviously did.
He would do anything
if he thought
it would make people laugh,
or advance his career
or his persona or whatever.
When you find
yourself hiding a stash...
I don't know if
I'd call him obsessed, but...
He was obsessed.
He didn't think things
through before he did them.
And a lot of times
his ideas were just bad ideas.
And they often failed.
He's an asshole,
but he's my asshole.
This is
the ice bucket challenge.
I nominate Iain
and Barack Obama.
So how did
this whole thing start then?
Well...
it was
the laser eye surgery video.
Um, obviously...
it wasn't like
any of his other videos,
he mostly stuck to
comedy, of course.
But now...
now, I don't really know
what to think.
Why?
I just, I can't, I can't watch
that video any more.
Why not?
It scares me.
I mean,
I've dramatized
it after the fact...
exaggerated a little,
some would say sensationalized.
But, watch the video
for yourself,
I'm not going to tell
you what the fuck to think.
The video was live streamed,
so once it was done,
it was online, and...
...people were scared.
Great, so, that is,
you ready now?
Okay, where's the button?
- Um, that one.
- Cool, yeah.
And that's going
to start the live stream.
- Okay, cool.
- Cool.
And the camera's rolling, yeah?
- Yeah.
- Okay, cool.
Cool.
- Happy? Okay.
- Yes.
Right,
I'm going to head out then.
- Um.
- Okay.
- I will be 20 minutes or so.
- Aye, should be long enough.
Yeah, do you want...
- I'm going to grab party rings.
- Nice.
Because we love party rings.
- Beer.
- Yeah.
And, yeah.
- That'll probably be it, really. And, yeah...
- Awesome.
Just sort of, don't be weird
and don't do anything stupid.
- Okay.
- Don't take off your bandages.
- Yeah, yeah, okay.
- That's really important, the doctor said that.
I know, he said it,
like, five times.
I know, well, remember it,
it's important.
- Okay, okay.
- Okay.
- All right, okay, bye.
- Bye, see you.
And hopefully that's
us streaming.
I am Graham,
welcome to my live stream.
Uh, this was the one that
I mentioned on Twitter
that I was going to be
doing about the aftermath
of my laser eye surgery,
which I had this afternoon.
Uh,
clearly, it didn't go to plan.
You know, you don't usually come
out of laser eye surgery
with a blindfold on,
or bandages,
or whatever it is
they've put on me.
But, uh, yeah,
they made a mistake.
So I am blind
for the next 24 hours,
until I can take this off.
They said that if I, uh,
take it off too early,
I could get permanent damage.
So I've not to take it off
under any circumstances, um,
but that's fine, because Erin's
coming back in 15 minutes,
and she's going to look after me
for the rest of the day and,
um, make sure I don't destroy
the flat with, you know,
some Mr. Magoo style antics,
just bashing
into things and stuff.
Um, but, yeah, I was going
to be answering your questions
as they came in, but...
Erin?
Oh, Jesus!
Erin.
Erin, are you fucking with me?
Because that's pretty mean.
Erin?
Please tell me
you're fucking with me.
Okay, fuck this.
Erin?
I can't see fucking shit here.
Oh, my God,
what did I just watch?
Actual evidence, finally someone
records a ghost sighting
on a camera that didn't go out
of production in the '60s.
Hallelujah.
Either this guy staged it,
or he had the weirdest
home invasion in history.
Halle-fucking-lujah.
Still creepy though.
Well, ghost or not,
something was in his house.
And that's what made
it really scary.
I'd seen his acting,
he's not that good.
I assumed he just used
like, fishing line
and maybe tried to remove it
post production or something,
but I didn't think Graham
had it in him
to do something like that,
or to fool us like that.
People wanted to know more,
so, that was our way in.
You know you're going
to have to go back.
I don't want to talk about it.
Yeah, well, it's been
three weeks now, so.
I'm trying to do something here.
Graham, you can't
just ignore it.
Look, what's your plan here?
You're just going
to stay in my flat and what?
Make bottle videos?
For your information,
bottle flipping
is a legitimate skill.
And it's trending
massively right now, so.
Ah, fuck's sake, Graham.
Look, listen to me!
Whatever you saw,
whatever happened,
you can either get the police
to investigate it...
or you.
You can go and investigate it,
yourself.
Oh, man, look, you've been
waiting for a video
to go viral for years.
And now there's one that's just
handed to you on a platter,
and, and you're just
going to ignore it?
Just do it.
Just use it.
I'll come with you,
we'll go back to the flat,
we'll, we'll investigate it,
we'll document it.
And if it's real,
whatever you saw...
Oh, my God, like,
can you imagine?
A real fucking ghost.
Look.
Think about it.
You in?
So, here we are, uh,
back at my flat.
Erin convinced me to come back,
um, you know,
to investigate the ghost.
The ghost, this alleged ghost
that exists in his flat.
Yeah, alleged, alleged.
Alleged.
So, yeah, we're going
to go in there, um.
Erin's packing heat.
- You know...
- I'm ready. I'm really prepared.
I'm, I'm kind of,
I'm pretty nervous,
I feel a bit weird,
but I'm...
I'm, I'm just going to stand
behind Erin as she...
- Yeah, okay.
- But, anyhow, here we go.
- Okay.
- Let's see.
Do it! Am I going first?
Yeah, of course.
Of course you're going first.
You're too kind. Oh, my God.
Okay, all good.
This is really creepy.
Why am I so nervous?
It's stupid.
I don't know, it looks all fine.
There's no reason
to be nervous or, uh...
- Fuck.
- What is it?
You're fucking with me.
- You're fucking with me!
- What? No.
Yeah, you are, oh, my God,
what the hell?
Fucking flat.
Holy shit.
It's like...
what, what,
why would someone do that?
Like, if someone come into
your flat, what, would they just
tip things all over the place?
That makes no sense.
Like, that's really
freaking me out, Graham.
Well, it wasn't me.
Shut up, I don't believe you.
I don't believe you!
Are you serious?
- You didn't do this?
- I didn't do this, no.
This is really,
that's really horrible.
They've left the laptop.
- Oh, good.
- And the TV.
Well,
ghosts don't really use laptops, so.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God,
that's really messed up.
- What is it?
- Look.
What the fuck is that?
Oh, my God, that's like...
sorry.
It's like,
"Prepare for laughter."
That makes no sense whatsoever.
It's really freaking me out,
it's really, like,
I don't know, like, why would
someone come in here and like,
like, fucking write
on your wall?
It's just some sort
of sick joke or something.
Yeah, unless you're still
pulling my leg, because.
No, no it's not, no, come on.
Because that'd be really
messed up if that is,
- no, not impressed.
- No, Erin, honestly...
Oh, my God!
What?
Can you stay here tonight?
It's kind of unsettling
to think that the message
is still going to be
underneath this paint.
Like, I'm not getting rid of it,
it's, it's still here.
Hey, do we have
a bigger paintbrush?
I'm scared.
I'm scared too.
- What was that?
- Shh.
What's that?
- Ah, jeez, what the fuck?
- What?
Oh, my God, oh, my God,
oh, my God, wh... what was it?
- There is a person.
- What? Graham, just go check please.
- Fuck.
- Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck!
I've not been through there.
Fuck.
What the fuck?
Graham lived on the third floor.
The front door was
locked from the inside.
That video made a believer
out of a lot of people.
People that were unsure before.
Erin, I think
we need professional help.
And I've got someone in mind.
This, this is ghost hunting.
So, I've got 120,000
YouTube subscribers.
I'm getting a lot of vibes
from different areas,
all sorts here, there's a lot of ghosts here,
there's a lot of people been killed here.
Nine million views.
We managed to capture
it on film, we got it.
This is very good evidence.
One at a time, you go first.
I've got 10,000 Insta followers.
Look at that, somebody's...
tried to...
make this seem...
a benign place by putting
a smiley face here, but...
it's far from benign.
That's obviously not a ghost.
Oh, I've got a lot
of Twitter fans.
A lot, we're talking
10,000, 12,000.
Did you hear that?
We got it.
Doing, doing all right.
And I was a big deal
even before Graham
started out.
So during the 1920s, this place
was rumored to have a contagion
which led to mass hysteria,
that's why it's
shut down just now.
Local legend now says,
"Don't even bring
your dogs here,
if you let them off the lead,
they come in as if something's
drawing them in."
And the dogs
are never seen again.
Although I can see them.
Tell me you got that.
Be calm, Stuart.
We need to cut the last part.
Basically, right,
obviously I've seen
a lot of paranormal
activity in my time.
But Graham's videos
were a little bit...
on the nose.
I mean, as a ghost hunter,
you're talking about
if you hear a sound
or a spirit orb even,
you, you're getting lucky.
So...
Graham's videos were
a little bit more
sensational.
Dubious...
one might say.
Steve, Steve annoyed
the fuck out of me.
Oh, man, um,
he thought he was a big deal.
No, sorry, 15,000
Instagram followers now, so.
And to be honest, if Graham
hadn't had those two viral videos,
I don't think he even
would have messaged us.
He's, uh,
he's pretty up himself.
But, you know, Graham insisted.
You know, he'd been
a fan of his for years.
And I guess it was good
to have someone with a bit of
"experience."
He was freaking out. He didn't understand
what he was dealing with, right?
I've been around
the block before though.
So, you know, I was happy
to hear him out, I wanted to,
to hear his experience.
Okay.
- Steve. Nice to meet you, thanks for coming out.
- Graham.
- No worries.
- I thought we could film this for posterity.
Well, I like where
your head's at and,
it's good to meet you and Erin.
Hey.
Yeah, no worries.
Oh, have a seat, by the way.
Uh, okay.
Um, do you like my house?
- You grew up in places like this, right?
- Yeah, yeah.
So, yeah, I mean,
you've seen the videos, right?
- The ones...
- Yeah, they're good, they're good, they're promising.
So do you think there's
something paranormal
going on in our flat?
I mean, we've watched
it a lot, uh.
There's something
definitely weird going on.
Right, I've been doing
this job for ten years,
I've never seen anything
quite like that.
That's what we thought as well.
Yeah, I mean, there's definitely
something going on.
Well, I guess
the bottom line is, um...
do you think you would,
you know,
be able to help us
investigate it?
Maybe collaborate
on some videos?
Do some cross promotion
sort of stuff.
Graham, definitely.
Listen, I don't think
there's a bigger priority
in the paranormal world
than figuring out
what's in your flat right now.
It's, it's weird.
Yeah, I didn't realize
what a relief
that would be to hear
until I actually heard it.
Mate, no problem, man.
Great.
We'll get to the bottom of this.
- Thanks.
- We'll find the truth.
Which we always do.
Let's hunt some
motherfucking ghosts.
That was a bit too far,
but okay.
Listen,
I can tell you right now...
that thing in your flat,
whatever it is,
that's a money making machine.
You just need a bit
of business savvy about it,
I can provide that.
Honestly, we'll be making some
seriously fucking
hard cash that way.
That's a little bit crass,
but I have been saying that
to Graham for weeks now.
I mean, I definitely want that.
But we're going to uncover
the truth of it
along the way, right?
Aye, right, of course, you know,
paranormal investigating
is for life, man, but,
you know,
"hashtag fucking fake news."
You know what I mean?
The audience are into clickbait,
spectacle, and shaming people.
We can provide the first two,
if the truth is revealed
along the way,
that's just a bonus, right?
Oh, shit,
your mic's still on, hold on.
Oh, get it off me.
If the truth
is revealed along the way,
that's just a bonus, right?
Oh, shit,
your mic's still on, hold on.
Oh, get it off me.
Listen.
My work speaks for itself, okay?
Secondly, in regards to
what I said about
your average internet user...
everything after
what happened with Graham
and this whole mess,
can you really say that
I'm not justified
in what I said?
Was what I said wrong,
after everything that Graham went through?
That's what I make of that.
So, that was the start
of our work with Steve.
And his first suggestion
was really out there.
He suggested...
Seance.
First ever 360 degree
live streamed seance,
never been done before.
So, if Graham and Erin's place
was really a hotbed
of paranormal activity,
we're talking internet gold.
Right?
That's what we're talking.
And even I underestimated it.
Which was unfortunate
for Graham.
Yeah, kind of backfired on him.
- Right.
- Okay,
okay, yeah.
And camera's on.
Have we got enough
candles now, Steve?
Um, no, I don't, actually.
Okay, is everyone ready to go?
- Yup.
- I'm ready.
Uh, once I hit live,
that's it, we're live.
Ready? Yeah, okay.
And we're live, hello,
fellow followers.
Uh, I'm doing a conjoined stream
here with special guest,
uh, special guest
Graham and Erin.
And this is the first ever
VR live streamed seance.
That's right,
we have our 360 degree VR camera
in the middle of the room,
which means it captures
all 360 degrees of this room,
so if anything spooky
or paranormal happens,
this camera will see it.
Exactly, so, if you like
this video, please like it.
Subscribe or comment,
we're on Instagram,
we're on Twitter,
we're on YouTube.
Okay, now that's out of the way,
we can seance it up.
- And, uh...
- Seance it up.
Yes, it's a Victorian saying.
- Sorry.
- Right. Okay.
So, yep, Steve,
you're the expert,
do you want
to walk us through this
- lovely set up we have here?
- Yes.
So basically,
we've got a lot of candles,
it's almost midnight,
we've got a quiet room.
Uh, these are all good
prerequisites.
Uh, phones are off?
- Yes.
- Yep.
- Phone's off.
- Okay, great.
And Steve, can you tell us a bit
about why we're using whisky?
No.
That'll be explained later.
Okay, so, now, all we need to do
is... well, first off,
get your hands
on the table please.
This grounds us
to the physical realm.
I'm going to read this prayer,
which is going to protect us,
it's hopefully going
to get the spirits...
out...
or in this room.
"In the name of God,
Jesus Christ...
the great brotherhood of light,
please protect us from
the forces of evil
during this session.
Let there be nothing but
light surrounding this table,
and its participants,
and let us only communicate
with powers
and entities of light.
Protect us, protect this house,
the people in this house,
and let there only be light
and nothing but light, amen."
So spirit, if you're here,
please let us know.
Is something supposed to happen?
I'm hoping, uh...
Spirit, if you're here,
please, please, let us know.
Use the whisky.
Should we maybe...
Did someone push the table?
No.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
- Oh, my God.
- Fuck!
Sit down,
don't break the circle.
That's... incredible.
Okay, spirit,
who are we speaking to?
- Fuck.
- Jesus.
What's it doing,
why's it coming?
Fuck!
Oh, my God!
You guys saw that, right?
Yeah.
I assumed there'd been some
sort of trickery, something,
he'd managed
to work something out
that he thought was quite good,
but, um,
I couldn't figure it out.
Well, the reaction
was even bigger
than all of the other
videos put together.
I had to call him straight away,
it was just crazy.
I think people just
wanted confirmation.
And they got it.
Did you see this video?
This is completely fucked up.
Well, I underestimated it.
Genuinely had trouble
sleeping last night.
Who is this guy? That ghost's
some scary ass shit, boy.
Well, it was by far
my most successful video,
um, even to this day, um.
It was the beginning
of a beautiful friendship.
I thought.
Well, I mean,
the fact that anyone
over the age of five thought
these hauntings were real,
um, just sums up what's
wrong with society today.
It was clearly just three people
making short horror films,
and I've got
nothing against horror,
but the fact that they were
presenting it as real,
manipulating people,
taking them in,
there were some people
that really bought it,
and it really hurt them.
I, I've got some comments
on some of their videos.
Right, here.
Okay. "This is amazing,
I always suspected,
my husband passed
away three years ago,
can you help me get in touch?"
This one, "Graham, Steve, Erin,
thanks for showing
everyone the truth,
now I can talk
to my dead grandparents
at night knowing I'm not crazy."
I mean,
they weren't helping anyone.
Look at this one, uh,
"Please, please,
help me talk to my mom,
she passed in April,
I know you can help me,
please respond to my messages."
That one really breaks my heart.
It really got on my nerves,
to be honest.
Um, I sort of developed
a bit of a grudge against them.
I really wanted to just
prove them and...
Do you know what,
I can show you.
Hi, sorry, you're early,
just come through.
Um, you can set up in there.
Uh, make yourselves comfortable.
It's pretty tacky, right?
What is it?
It's a souvenir from
my first big debunk case.
What happened?
Well, these newlyweds
had moved into a new flat,
and they found
this doll in the attic.
Understandably,
they found it a bit creepy,
so they left it there.
After a while, they started
to hear strange noises,
scratching, scraping,
sort of sounded like
little feet in the attic, um.
Then things
got even weirder, because
they started to find the doll
in random places in the flat.
Uh, it would show up in
cupboards, washing up baskets,
and both of them insisted
they weren't moving it.
So how did you get involved?
Well, they recorded the case,
and uploaded the videos,
um, like Graham's,
and when I saw them,
I just wanted
to get to the bottom of it, so,
did some digging,
and I figured it out,
it was the dog walker.
The dog walker had also seen
some of their initial videos,
and thought it was a great
chance to fuck with them.
So whenever they were out,
the dog walker would
move the doll
to different places.
So, once I figured it out,
of course,
they fired the dog walker.
And that was it, that simple.
And what about the sounds?
It's just rats.
There's always an explanation.
That said, um,
they still didn't 100% believe
that the doll
was just a harmless doll.
Uh, so they asked me
to take it off their hands,
and now I keep it
on my mantelpiece,
like my own little
personal Annabelle.
Anyways, come and look at this,
this is the footage
that I had ready for you.
Okay, um, so you have to look
pretty carefully here.
Watch the mug, okay?
There, okay?
Did you see that?
There, can you see it?
Erin?
There. Did you get that?
It's a wire.
Which means that
this wasn't shot live at all.
So if that was faked,
what else was?
Things keep
falling off that shelf.
I like to joke that
the doll doesn't really like
sharing the space
with other ornaments.
Am I being stupid, or has
that doll moved since we've been here?
I don't think so.
It's just a doll.
I don't know if the mic's
picking that up, can you hear that?
I think it stopped.
Jesus Christ.
I'm sorry, guys,
I couldn't help myself.
Just wanted to make a point.
You see, it's really easy
to fake stuff like this.
The doll's remote controlled.
I've got a speaker
on the mantelpiece,
and I also included a little
mechanism that pushes her off.
It's so easy to fool people,
and that's why I wanted to
show everyone what people
like Graham are doing.
So was the story
about the dog walkers true?
No.
I think I've got it.
Steve and Graham agreed
to have a meeting with me.
I told them
I wanted to write a piece
promoting their work.
Of course, they believed me,
their big egos.
Yeah, what was
that reporter lady's name?
Alice Harper.
Yeah, Alice Harper,
right, so anyway,
she's wanting
an interview with Graham.
She's into debunking
paranormal investigators,
internet fraudsters,
that's her business.
So, obviously she's going
to try and, you know,
debunk us, even though you can't
debunk somebody who's legit,
who's, uh,
unbunked, so, you know,
I don't know why.
But anyway, I told Graham,
"Let's do this,
we'll fucking beat her
at her own game."
I took an improvised
little spy camera to our meeting.
I cut a hole in a pencil case,
lined the camera up.
I got my pal Kevin
to do some second camera work,
just in case I couldn't
get a good enough view.
What I didn't count on, which,
in hindsight should have
been fucking obvious,
is that Graham and Steve
planned on doing
a little bit
of filming of their own.
Do you guys mind if I take
some notes while we do this?
No, as long as you don't mind
us filming the interview.
No, fire away, okay.
Uh, so...
It was fucking mind games,
they were trying
to throw me off.
Graham, what do you make
of these allegations
that you, Erin, and Steve have
been faking these hauntings?
- Well...
- Preposterous.
Thanks Steve,
I was actually asking Graham.
Yeah, Steve, it's okay.
I mean, this footage,
if it's genuine,
is perhaps one of the most
amazing things I've ever seen.
- Thank you.
- Earth shattering,
some might say
it beggars belief.
Well, sometimes
I wish it wasn't true.
You know, a lot of people
don't realize
that this has been more
of a curse than anything else.
Yeah, well, sometimes when
people find fame and fortune,
they realize it's not
everything they wanted.
You know that's
not what I meant.
Look, I've been researching you,
and you weren't always into
this ghost hunting shit,
or whatever you want to call it.
We're paranormal investigators
and extra-dimensional experts.
That's what we are,
you need to do some research
before you start interviewing,
- just a thought...
- Thank you, thank you, Steve.
Okay.
You've tried every trend going,
I've even seen
your planking videos.
Did you like them?
This is what I think's happened.
You played a prank,
it was successful,
it went viral.
You liked how it felt,
and that's why you got involved
with this two-bit
"quasi-celebrity" over here.
Now wait a minute.
I've got a question.
Why did you use air quotes
when you said celebrity?
Have either of you guys looked
into an internet shaming?
Because, you know,
if you are faking this,
then you've got a massive
shaming coming your way,
and it is not going
to be pretty.
This is your interview?
You, you're just telling
us things.
Plus you're not
writing anything down,
I told you what exactly
our jobs are,
you didn't write that down.
That's okay, Steve, I think
I've got everything I need.
I'm going to get the bill.
I have read up on shamings, man,
and they are fucking brutal.
Right, don't worry
about that, okay?
- Yeah, but what if they...
- Don't worry about it, okay?
Just, we've got a good
thing going on here, just chill.
Yeah, but if they fucking find
out we've been faking it,
then we're going
to be in so much shit.
That was...
probably the most satisfying
moment of my career.
I mean...
I uploaded the video that night,
and got a little
viral fame of my own.
Don't worry about it, okay?
Just, we've got a good thing
going on here, just chill.
Yeah, but if they fucking find
out we've been faking it,
then we're going
to be in so much shit.
Ha, whoops,
he didn't see that one coming.
I feel so betrayed.
Graham deserved his comeuppance.
He's shitting himself.
He looks more scared now
than he did
when he thought
he'd seen a ghost.
Graham...
went off on a massive
spiral at that point.
Just go kill yourself.
You guys,
this is from the heart...
I really thought that
for once there was proof,
you have no idea what
that meant to me.
Steve got off okay.
No backlash for me,
no backlash for me.
I wasn't in the spotlight
as much, so.
All my followers,
they know my work
is 100% authentic.
He was asking for it.
I can't believe I didn't
do it sooner, to be honest.
They knew that I was just
getting tied into some kind of
dubious stuff.
I mean...
the insults,
criticisms, death threats.
He got to experience
what it was like
to be a woman online,
for a minute.
I mean, for God's sakes,
I got death threats,
rape threats,
for writing an article
on cheesecake,
you don't see me
crying about it.
Steve left him out to dry.
It's funny, all the focus
seemed to be on Graham...
I mean, I guess he was
the instigator, but...
I was lucky.
I don't really have
an online presence,
I was only in a few
of the videos, so.
And you knew
it was faked from the start?
Mm-hm.
I see it like all of Graham's
videos, it's an art piece.
It's challenging people
about what they think is real,
and what they think is not real.
And you don't
think that's problematic?
No.
I'm glad we did it.
I'm really sad to see it end.
That's what I told them...
The fallout for
Graham was terrible.
...fireworks and stuff.
He just became
a different person
at that point, I mean...
The things that people
would say to him,
they'd say to him online.
Fuck.
Can you stop filming?
Please.
And then came the apology.
Graham had been reading a book
about public shaming,
and in the book the person
had apologized,
and everyone accepted
the apology,
and everything was fine again.
So Graham thought
he would do the same.
Even though I said to him,
"Just let it blow over."
But Graham is very
single minded.
And he did it anyway.
As most of you know,
it was revealed last week
that the recent spate
of hauntings that were
recorded and documented
in this flat
were faked by myself,
with the help of some others.
I want to apologize from
the bottom of my heart
for misleading all of you.
I understand that some of you
were questioning your faith
because of these videos,
and for that, I am truly sorry.
It got out of hand.
The moment got away from me,
and I was encouraged
by those closest to me.
It was never my intention
to hurt any of you.
I only wanted to entertain.
And I guess I failed.
I just hope we can all
move on from this...
and forget about this blip.
I'm truly sorry.
Okay, well, there's
a few things wrong there.
First off, terrible apology.
"I was encouraged
by those closest to me?"
Why should he throw Erin
under the bus?
He also tries to shift
the blame off himself.
"I just wanted to entertain,
and the moment
got away from me."
Just admit that you lied
and go from there.
None of this half-assed shit.
When people found out that
he'd monetized the video...
...that was some
major schadenfreude.
And it was
like the internet shaming
had started all over again.
And then...
I properly lost it over this...
another ghost.
Well, the first thing was
the figure in the background.
What was he thinking?
And then there was the picture,
and this was so subtle
that I wondered why
it was done at all.
I really don't get
his thinking on it.
It wasn't really noticeable
at normal speed,
but if you sped the video up.
I just don't get why he did it.
And did you believe him?
I do now.
So if you could just
tell us your name, occupation,
and spell it, so we have it for
the onscreen graphics, please.
Yeah, okay,
it's Doctor John Watson.
I know, hold the jokes.
It's J-O-H-N, W-A-T-S-O-N.
And I'm a social psychologist.
Would you like me to spell that?
Yeah, so it's been well
documented that...
social media is addictive.
I think we all know that.
When you get a notification,
that little red dot appears,
or your phone buzzes
in your pocket,
that sends a little micro dosage
of dopamine to your brain.
It says, "Oh, this is good."
And in the same
way that a drug addict,
sex addicts, gamblers,
or any form of addiction,
the same happens
to the social media addict.
I've found that the more
exposure, the worse it gets.
Take someone like Graham,
you know, he was getting dozens,
if not hundreds
of notifications a day;
comments, likes,
subscribers, views even.
Each one a little parcel
of dopamine right to the brain.
Now, what hasn't been explored
is what happens
when the trigger that gives
you that little dopamine shot
becomes a negative stimulus.
Imagine, for example,
a heroin addict.
Getting their buzz as normal,
and then all of a sudden,
the object of their addiction,
heroin, makes them feel bad.
Every time they inject,
it's a negative experience.
But the issue is,
they still crave it.
They're addicted to it,
and they can't stop
taking the drug.
Well, the dopamine hit
is still the same,
but the emotions
are all negative.
But now instead
of making them happy,
it becomes an oppressive,
antagonistic force
in their lives.
When they don't have it,
they crave it, and when
they get it, it's
a deeply negative experience.
That was the world that
Graham was living in.
You know,
he craved social media.
When he did get fulfillment,
at best,
it was someone telling
him he sucked,
and at worst it was someone
telling him to kill himself.
It's no wonder he fell apart.
I don't know
if I'll post this one.
Just finding it easier
to talk to
the camera than
a person right now.
I really fucked up.
I don't know why,
why we let it go so long.
Steve's abandoned me.
Haven't seen Erin in a few days.
And the abuse from online
is just getting worse.
Things in here have
been weird as well.
Still weird shit going on.
Just finding things out
of place...
things moving around...
noises.
Wonder if
someone's broken in, or
maybe they saw
where I live online.
Fuck knows.
Oh, my God!
Welcome to the show.
Back after a short break,
I have very good
news for Graham.
I believe
the hauntings were real.
And I have proof.
Now what we had before
wasn't strictly paranormal,
that's fine, but
I've re-looked at the footage,
and I believe there's
more to this whole story
than meets the eye.
This is Graham's flat,
I think he'll be
very happy to see us.
Hey, Graham.
Still a little bit
down in the dumps.
Maybe.
Graham, Graham, buddy.
Listen, I do have
something very important
to show you man,
I think it'll cheer you up.
Graham, please,
open the door, trust me, man.
Well, fortunately,
I actually have a set of keys
that Graham gave me
whilst we were
in the thick
of our investigations,
which,
wouldn't normally advocate
breaking into
anyone's house, but
he's mentally unstable, so,
you know,
we've got to help him out.
Graham, we're here to help.
Steve, what the fuck?
Get out of my flat,
I don't want to talk to you.
Right, just calm down,
all right?
Trust me, you need to see this.
Oh, trust you, yeah,
worked out well
last time I did that, didn't it?
Jesus.
You know, it was his idea,
faking it.
Still got your fans, I see.
Wake up, people,
he's full of fucking bullshit.
Erin's told me you've
not been keeping well.
Yeah, well.
She said you've been seeing
things moving about the flat.
Been talking to Erin much,
have you?
Um, well,
I'm on your side, okay?
Right, okay, watch this.
I'm pretty sure that there's
real hauntings here.
No fucking shit.
I've been telling you
that for weeks.
Have you not been listening?
Just because it wasn't
profitable for you?
You know, you come here
with your crew,
just because you finally
see that there's
something in it for you.
What, what am I doing,
just get out.
Wait, right, wait.
Okay, you need to put all
that to the side, because
there is something bigger here,
we need to get to
the bottom of this.
Like all of earth's
wondrous mysteries,
there is a big, profound,
deep meaning to this, which we can...
- What the fuck are you talking about?
- Wait, just let me finish this.
- Which we need to excavate...
- What?
Steve, drop, drop the act.
It's just you and me.
Just ignore the cameras,
help me out,
like, I'm going
through something here.
Okay.
But there is something bigger,
and there is a big mystery,
and we need to get
to the bottom of it.
Just fucking leave.
Graham, let's just talk about...
Well, that didn't go very well.
It couldn't have gone
any better, I mean,
we had
one million views on YouTube.
I think we called it like,
"Shamed Ghost Hunter Freaks Out,"
it did really well,
because he was acting
like an asshole.
Which is always good on YouTube.
So you have
evidence of the hauntings, then?
Can we see that footage?
Well, you can, all right,
let me just explain, so,
that footage, at that point,
I didn't realize
he was faking it, right?
So, I came to him
with the footage, thinking...
I gave him the benefit
of the doubt, at that point.
You know, there was
some suspicious things,
there was little blurs
and sounds,
and, you know, at that point,
I still thought
there might be
something in this.
Then he slammed the door
in my face, and...
I don't know why he persisted
in trying to make it look real.
So...
So I'm struggling
to sleep tonight,
and it's not just because
it's the 5th of November,
and it sounds like the
fucking Gaza strip out there.
I started looking up
the history of the flat.
Seeing if there was
any clues as to like...
why this is happening.
Why, why's that happening here.
And I found this news story
from a few years ago.
Seven years ago.
About this girl who used
to live in this flat.
And she was what the Japanese
would call a "Hikikomori."
So she was basically a shut-in.
Sometimes the other tenants
in the building would see her
roaming the halls, or
in the stairwell or something,
but aside from that,
she never left the building.
Just got everything delivered,
did everything online.
The tenants stopped
seeing her in the halls.
And then there was a smell...
coming from her flat.
When they finally got
the police to investigate,
there was nothing.
Nobody.
The girl wasn't there.
But the smell was.
They never found her.
But that wasn't the thing
that's keeping me up.
I, uh, I found
this function on street view
where you can
actually look back...
um...
previous years.
And I looked up this flat,
looked up seven years ago.
And this is what I saw.
Just...
I feel like
I'm fucking losing it.
Well, let's go and investigate.
Here we go again.
Hello? Erin?
If that's you I'm going
to fucking kill you.
Not even joking.
Hello?
Erin?
Fuck.
Why is it always a sheet?
You know what?
Fuck this,
I'm phoning the police,
and you can hunt them,
you spooky cunt.
The tale behind this building
is one of addiction,
shame, and woe.
McCarthy's Canal House.
This is where McCarthy himself
became an isolated,
paranoid obsessive.
Where he basically boarded up...
- Steve.
- ...every exit and entrance.
Graham, how...
It's okay, it's okay,
just keep filming.
Fuck, give me my keys back.
No, what the fuck, man?
- What's wrong with you?
- Give me my keys back.
Keys, now.
You just fucking
punched me in the face.
Now why did you do that?
You fucking attacked me
in my flat last night.
No, I didn't.
- Okay? No.
- It was you. It was you.
- It was you.
- I wasn't there!
Look, I didn't break
into your flat, man.
Look, if it wasn't you, then.
Just fucking give
me my keys back.
You're fucking losing it,
there you go.
Don't know why you
gave me them anyway.
You're losing it, man.
Do you even know what's real
and what's not any more?
It's on camera.
That doesn't mean anything.
Stay the fuck out of my flat.
How did you know I was
going to be here anyway?
You posted it on
Twitter, you fuckwit.
All right, fair point.
Did you get all that?
Get some B roll,
the wheat field.
Back in the 70s, an artist put
on a revolutionary exhibit.
You know, it's one that's
always stuck with me.
The artist stood
in the middle of the room,
and she was completely still.
And she surrounded herself
with dozens of objects.
A feather, a rose,
some bread, grapes,
scissors, a scalpel,
a gun loaded with one bullet.
Well, the point
of the piece was to
allow people to act
how they wanted to interact.
She didn't intervene,
they had carte blanche.
She rendered herself powerless.
And at first it was fine.
You know, people found
it amusing and fun.
You know, some played with the
perfume, played with the feather,
and some even gave her a kiss.
But then things turned sour.
Eventually, some of the audience
intervened and saved her life.
Afterwards she said what
she'd learned was that
when you leave it
up to the public,
well, they can kill you.
And, this is
the kind of social contract
we take out when
we put ourselves online.
You know, we open
ourselves up for abuse.
And...
In a sense, we're allowing
perfect strangers
access to our most
intimate moments.
And when people
are allowed anonymity,
and permission, well, you don't
know how far they'll take it.
I don't know what to do.
I took the keys from Steve.
But it's not changed anything.
I just need
a little bit of help.
I just need help.
Graham, hello.
Oh, my God, are you okay?
What is this?
Feedback.
What are you filming?
Just, you know,
more evidence.
What are you talking about?
You know, the haunting
that's been going on
in this flat for months now?
That no one believes me about?
Okay.
Well, I'm a little
worried about you.
Come on, let's just
turn off the camera.
No, no, no.
Graham, this isn't real.
We faked this.
So, why don't you just
come back to mine,
relax, take it easy, yeah?
It was real.
It is real.
Graham, it wasn't real.
It wasn't real, we, we faked it.
Okay, and you need to come
back with me,
and I need you to come
back with me, okay?
The sounds that are
happening in this flat,
the things that are moving
around on their own,
they're real, they're real.
Graham, you're scaring me.
Look, they want me to...
What do you want though?
Tell me, what do you want, okay?
Is this important to you,
is this not important to you?
Am I important to you?
God, come on, answer me,
what do you want?
I want you to leave.
Wait.
Sorry.
It's fine, just.
I'm worried about you, okay?
I just need one more night,
one more night.
And then I'll, I'll come back.
And we'll forget about all this,
just one, one more night.
Okay.
So, it's come to this.
The last night in the flat.
I mean, fuck it,
I'm just renting anyway.
I don't know what use there
is staying one more night.
I don't know what I could
possibly catch on camera that
would convince you
that hasn't already.
But...
I just feel like
I have to do this.
It's two a.m.
Nothing to report other than
the usual bumps and whispers.
Usual.
It's weird that you
don't really hear about
stuff happening in places
like this, new builds.
Maybe it's built on an ancient
Glaswegian burial ground,
and they're trying
to communicate with us.
Ouija board.
So, it's three a.m.
I don't know what
I'm still doing here.
I think Erin was right.
So I'm going to pack up.
And that's...
Okay, fuck this.
What...
the fuck?
What the fuck?
Come on.
Concussion, broken wrist,
three fractured ribs...
dislocated shoulder.
He survived, but it was
touch and go for a fair bit.
I was in visiting him
in hospital every day.
It was a struggle.
He clearly wasn't himself.
Not like he was
when we were kids.
It was my idea for him
to check into care.
And the doctors did a lot of
tests and things and decided
it was best for him to have
a bit of time to recover.
Think it was best for him not
to be in the flat any more.
Doesn't matter about
all the ghost shit.
If it's real, if it's not,
it's irrelevant.
He got put through the ringer.
Did he bring a lot
of that on himself?
Yeah.
But in my opinion,
the punishment
didn't fit the crime.
I mean, it's funny, like,
after he almost died,
people seemed
less willing to criticize him.
The whole thing just
quietly blew over.
I still see him once a week.
He seems happier.
And I have not been back
to the flat since.
Um, he's not had
any internet access.
And I think he's really trying
to kick this addiction.
Cold turkey.
So as far as I'm aware,
if he's seen anything,
he's not told me about it, so.
I kept asking him if I could
write a follow up biography.
People would read that.
Um, but he stopped replying
to my messages,
and ultimately
refused to see me.
What can I do? Fuck him.
No, I don't see him
anymore, I mean,
he seems healthy now,
why would I interrupt that?
Plus I've got a lot
of things going on, you know,
uh, did I tell you about
my new YouTube series?
No, oh, right, okay,
so, well, it's called...
It's about as happy
an ending as we can hope for.
Graham's, like, mentally
the best he's ever been.
And in the end...
isn't that all we can ask for?
To be comfortable
in our own skin.
It's not care about likes
or views or whatever the fuck.
How important are views anyway?
But the views are important.
I wasn't keen on
this whole neat conclusion.
Um, Graham has
a near death experience,
goes into care, gets well again,
finds public love again.
Um, good for him,
but I didn't buy it.
I hate loose threads,
and it felt like
there were tons of
loose threads left over.
So, I did some digging.
What I found was
Graham's YouTube channel.
It was still live.
And this was
when he was in care,
and had no access
to the internet.
Seems a little
insensitive to me.
Something stood out when
I was looking at his channel.
I checked the about page,
and the email address
for business inquiries
looked familiar.
"padthemouse," I'd seen
that somewhere before.
It was the same as
Steve's business address.
Well here's where
it gets interesting.
Erin claimed to have
no media presence really,
she wasn't on any social
media accounts
or anything like that.
But, she did have
an Etsy account.
Selling her "art."
And when you go to contact
the store owner,
guess who? "padthemouse."
- Just chill.
- Yeah, but if they fucking find out
we've been faking it, then we're
going to be in so much shit.
So I find it odd that
through all of that tension...
Help me out.
...animosity.
- You're losing it, man.
- Just fucking leave.
Through all of that,
they shared
a business email address?
Did he not once try
to split their businesses?
But the really strange thing...
These channels and shops,
they were all set up
before Graham and Erin allegedly
started collaborating
with Steve.
Before they even met him.
It makes me think
that everything,
including the internet downfall,
all of it had been orchestrated
and faked,
more than anyone realized.
Well, I like where
your head's at,
and it's good to meet
you and Erin.
Hey.
If you look closely,
the clues are there.
Graham, Erin, and Steve
had met each other
before their first
alleged meeting.
Aye, it'll cost you extra.
Target's holding, move, move.
F###!
They'd made sketches before.
There's the shirt on
the radiator in Graham's flat.
This was a month
before they claim
to have met for the first time.
It's fine.
I just need one more night,
one more night.
Erin left that
night, didn't she?
If that's the case, then what
was she doing back later,
bursting out of the wall?
The deeper you look,
the more the evidence piles up.
Haven't seen Erin in a few days.
If you haven't
seen Erin in days,
then what's she doing
in your flat?
Look, the evidence is there.
It may seem
more implausible to you,
but there are only two options.
Either this is
one of the most well documented,
incredible cases
of a real haunting ever...
or it's an elaborate prank.
I guarantee you,
in a few months,
once everyone's forgotten
this story,
Graham's quietly going
to leave care,
rejoin society,
and he's going to have
a ton of cash in the bank.
I can't force you to believe me.
Unfortunately, evidence isn't
enough for people any more.
Have you heard the allegations
that Alice has been
making about you?
Which ones?
That this whole thing
has been faked,
and that you
were working alongside
Erin and Graham this whole time.
Oh, yeah, that one's a good one.
Um, okay, so listen,
I cut ties with Graham,
as soon as I gave him
the flat keys back, that was us.
What about the evidence
she's brought forward?
Well, can you believe
everything you see on camera?
No.
Like, seeing is believing,
that just doesn't apply
any more.
Does it?
This could be faked.
You could be fake.
Who's to say what's real,
what's not?
So what do you make
of the allegations
that you and Steve
and Graham conspired
to fake this whole thing?
Well...
We actually spoke, Alice and I,
and she showed me her evidence,
and as far as I'm concerned,
she has no evidence.
I don't know, I don't know
what to believe any more.
All I know is what I did
and what I didn't do, and...
I guess I have
to take comfort in that.
Some people say all sorts
of things about me,
but I know what's true,
and I know what's not true,
as well, and life goes on.
As does the afterlife.
If you believe that
sort of thing, so.
I'm back.
I've had a lot of time to think.
And I've been back online, and
looking at everything
that's been posted.
Everything that's
been said about me.
About the things that's
happened in this flat.
And I've had some time
to think about
what's really important to me.
And...
I know that there's
only one thing I can do.
To, to prove...
that this whole
thing has been real...
and that I meant
every single word of it.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org