♪
Beth: Josh, come down and eat.
Fine.
♪
Yo. Eat up, buddy.
- You do you're homework?
- Yep.
Of course he did.
He always does.
Hey.
Okay, keys.
Keys. Where are my keys?
Seriously? What?
- You're ridiculous.
- See... yeah.
I was testing you. Hmm.
That was a test. Hmm.
You failed. Aw!
And you... thank you.
Okay.
I'm out. Knuckles. Pound it.
Boom. Nice. Thank you.
- 'Kay.
- Love you guys.
Bye, dad. Come on.
Hurry up.
They're gonna be here soon.
Hey, Daniel.
Hey, Josh.
Looks like you finally gave in.
Yeah. Well, it keeps him quiet
on the drive, at least.
So are we still on for
girls' night next week?
Anything to get away
from this little monster.
Right? All right, hey.
You guys be good at school.
- We know. Love you, mom. Bye!
- All right, bye.
- Good luck with that.
- All right. Bye.
♪
Teacher: I saw some of you guys
were answering the questions
with numbers,
some had happy faces.
I like all the answers,
but how many muffins
are we gonna eat?
♪
Okay, go ahead.
Hey. Sorry.
Shh.
Hear that?
Hold on.
Josh: What?
Here, uh, you can move your guy.
Here. I'll let you go first.
Okay.
Uh, then we set them
up in a line.
And you're like, four...
Four, five, or six each.
Yeah, sure, but how many
do you want to put on first?
Six? Yeah, sure. Here.
I'll have six, too.
I think Josh has
an imaginary friend.
Ah, that's cute.
I guess.
Okay, time for your ni-nights.
Good night, mom.
Good night, dad.
And goodnight, matchie.
Mm. Anybody else?
Goodnight, Chewie!
Mm-hmm.
Okay, give me a kiss.
- Goodnight, mom.
- Love you.
You want it open or shut?
- Open.
- Okay. Night.
Bye, mom! Bye, honey.
Good morning. Seatbelts?
- Yep.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Shit.
Hey, mom.
How you feeling?
Where's your sister?
Uh, yeah, she should
be here soon.
Can I get you anything?
I saw your father.
He looked just the same.
He hadn't aged a day.
I could smell his Cologne.
♪
Ah.
Is that for your new friend?
I don't think
we've formally met, Josh.
What's your new friend's name?
Are you gonna tell us?
He doesn't want me to.
- Oh.
- Okay.
Hmm.
They want to know your name.
Okay. Yeah.
Okay, sounds good.
♪
Wz"?
Yep.
Nice to meet you, z.
He says,
"nice to meet you, too."
Oh, wow.
He's very polite.
♪
Mom, no! The floor's hot lava!
Stop, stop, stop!
The floor is hot lava.
Only step on the rocks.
Yeah, okay, good. Come on.
Let's go. It's time for bed.
No, no! You're melting!
You're melting!
Aaaaah!
No! No!
Come on.
It's time to brush your teeth.
Come on, z, let's go.
Okay.
Make one more move.
Just come on.
Oh! Oh. Whoa, whoa.
This floor is hot.
So, now... ha!
You're stuck, z!
Okay, Josh, come on now.
Fine.
♪
Good night, mom.
Good night, dad.
Good night, matchie.
Good night, Chewie.
Mm, sweetie, you sure you still
want to say good night to him?
Just because he died
doesn't mean he can't hear me.
Okay. All right.
Love you. Love you, too.
Wait. Close it.
Are you sure? Yeah.
Z likes it dark.
So, what are we gonna
do about this?
About what?
What do you think?
What, his creepy
imaginary friend?
I don't know.
He'll grow out of it, I guess.
Yeah.
Yeah, probably.
Did Daniel say anything?
That they weren't gonna
come today?
Josh, did Daniel say anything?
Beth: All right,
have a good day.
Love you.
♪
Hello?
This is.
This is never
an easy conversation to have.
I just don't understand.
Suspended indefinitely?
Listen, Josh is one
of my favorite students.
Well, what did he do exactly?
I don't even know
where to start.
Um, the language is
unacceptable,
and now he's started
hitting his classmates.
What? Hitting?
This was all detailed in the
red cards I sent home with him.
W-what red cards?
This is your husband's signature
isn't it?
Sorry, Beth.
Until Josh can behave
in a classroom setting,
I... 1 just don't see
any other options.
♪
"Josh left class
without permission
and refused to come back
when asked.”
"Josh was caught harassing
other students,
both verbally and physically."
"Josh has been using
vulgar language repeatedly,
was asked to stop
but continued.”
Sh... shall I keep going?
Okay. I'm sorry.
It's just, kids get
into trouble sometimes.
It's what they do.
Well, our kid just got
suspended, Kevin,
so great job.
That's good parenting.
And he refuses to take
responsibility for any of it.
He blames all of it
on his new best friend.
Okay. So what do you want to do?
Dr. seager:
Having an imaginary friend
can come from several things...
Boredom, loneliness,
a need to establish boundaries,
and sometimes means acting out.
So, does he need to be
on something?
Beth.
Jesus. Were not
medicating our kid.
No, I don't think
that's necessary.
A lot of children develop
imaginary friends,
and oftentimes it can be
a positive experience.
So, is there anything we can do
to help him be less...
You know, destructive?
Well, you could try playing
with him more at home.
You could be there for him
like his friend is,
help him see that it's all right
to be himself
around real people.
Okay.
So, that's it?
I think so.
I think he's a perfectly normal
8-year-old boy.
Okay.
Nice to see you again, Beth,
although I wish it was
under better circumstances.
- Oh. Yeah.
- Josh, let's go.
Come on, z.
27?
Yeah, that's what he calls it.
Listen, thanks for everything.
Uh, yeah.
We'll follow up
in a couple days.
- Of course.
- Okay.
- Thank you very much.
- Thank you.
Okay. Hey, Josh.
♪
You know, you really gotta
go see mom.
She's... she's looking rough.
She keeps asking about you.
I know. I know.
It's just, I can't see her
like that.
It actually makes me
feel sorry for her.
I don't think that's possible.
What has she been saying?
She talks about dad a lot.
He's having fun.
Wish I had a friend like that.
Ah, just make one up.
That's what he did.
Hm.
♪
Kevin.
Josh?
Josh. Hi, mommy.
Z doesn't want crust
on his sandwich.
Okay, honey.
Can you just give me that... no!
I have to finish. He's hungry.
Okay, why don't you
just give me the knife?
Careful now. Good boy.
I'll tell you what... we will
finish this in the morning.
Okay? Right now,
let's just go back to bed.
♪
Thanks.
Is this for me?
Ah.
So, what are you two
getting up to today?
We're going to play zone!
Hey, you show your mom
a good time, little dude.
And you, remember...
Just be the friend he needs.
All right, I gotta run.
I love you guys.
Knuckles. All right.
Yeah! Yeah!
Oh!
I'm gonna get you!
Whoo!
Ha, ha, ha! 1 won!
You lo-0-0-0-0st! Now, come on.
Let's go on the big slide.
Big slide, big slide.
- No. No.
- Yes!
- I don't like the big slide.
- Yes, yes!
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
No, I don't like it.
Oh.
Oh, my god.
♪
Hey, mom, look at me!
Come on. Come play.
- Josh?
- Help me!
Josh!
Ah! Josh!
Okay, okay. Josh!
Ha, ha, ha!
I got you! I got you! I got you!
Oh, my god! You should have seen
the look on your face!
It was classic.
Mom! Yeah.
Can you get me and z some milk?
Sure.
Oh, hey. How was play zone?
It was awesome. Yeah?
But she was way too scared
to go on the big slide.
Every time.
Wait! Grab the 2%.
Let me tell you a secret.
You tell her you're going
on the small slide.
You sneak around
to the big line-up.
She never has a clue.
Hey, you think z would mind
if I have a piece
of his garlic toast?
Thanks, z!
Ugh. Kevin, don't, please,
talk to it like it's real.
Give me your glass.
Thank you. Here you go, bud.
♪
What's on your mind?
Is it a certain letter,
perhaps the last one?
Something happened.
What do you mean?
So, Josh was playing
at play zone and, uh...
It was like for a second...
Ool == I saw... I saw it.
I... I saw z.
♪
God, I wasn't gonna
say anything.
But a couple nights ago
when I was heading up to bed,
I swear I saw something standing
in the corner watching me.
You know, at first
I second-guessed it.
I... 1 closed my eyes,
and I told myself
it wasn't there.
But it was, Beth.
Something was there.
Really?
No, it was my jacket.
Z isn't real.
Grow up.
Thanks.
Look, it's our kid's
imaginary friend.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
♪
Josh: Cheer up. Okay.
Uh, I like baseball.
Mm-hmm. Mostly center field.
Oh, yeah, that's for sure.
Ah, there's a crazy tiger!
Yeah, or is this a leopard
or cheetah?
♪
What does she look like?
Eh, the same, just deader.
Oh, shit.
You should go up there.
Dead bodies freak me out.
Yeah.
She's our mom.
♪
Mechanical voice: Z.
Z.
♪
Hmm. Hey.
I couldn't do it. Let's go.
Hey, Anne, it's Beth,
Josh's mom.
Yeah, hey, listen,
I... I just was wondering
if maybe Josh could have a play
date with Thomas this afternoon?
Oh, okay. Yeah.
No, we can... we can
just do it another time.
All right, thanks.
Hey, yeah. I == 1 just...
And, uh, I just thought
maybe Josh could come over
and have a play date with her.
Hi. It's Josh's mom.
Listen, I was...
Wow.
Hello?
♪
Georgia: So, how is everything?
I feel like I haven't
seen you in forever.
I'm sure you heard
Josh got suspended.
Where's Daniel?
Uh, he's upstairs,
but I think he might be
taking a nap, and...
It's like my son's
one of those children
of the cornfield or whatever.
Of course not.
I'm sorry about... you know.
Ghosting me?
Yeah, that.
He's a good kid, you know?
He's just got a really...
I don't know,
a vivid imagination right now.
It wasn't just my choice.
Daniel was really freaked out.
He said Josh was talking
about hurting animals.
What? No.
He would never do that.
All I know is that Daniel
was coming home crying,
and I need to protect my son.
Daniel!
- Aaaaah!
- Oh, my god.
Oh, my god!
Oh, my god, Daniel!
Georgia: Call 911!
Daniel! Daniel!
Ah!
♪
I am so sorry.
I don't even know what to say.
Just stop it! Just go away!
I never want to see you again!
It's okay, baby.
Mommy's right here.
♪
Oh, hi, mommy.
Wanna play?
Hi, baby.
♪
Yeah, you just... you let us
know if you need anything.
Okay, yeah, and... and we're s...
I... all right, bye.
Jesus.
How is he?
I don't even know
where to start.
It's not good.
What do we do?
♪
Josh!
Honey, come and eat!
Josh.
I've been downstairs
calling you.
Josh.
Joshua, I am speaking to y...
Do you like it? It's z.
Um...
I would like you to come down
for lunch, please.
Okay.
♪
Come on. Eat up.
I'm not hungry.
Well, if you're not gonna eat,
at least drink your milk.
Make you big and strong,
just like z.
Z says I shouldn't.
Really?
Okay, here we go.
I'm gonna drink some.
See?
It's good, huh?
Want some carrots?
♪
Why don't we just hire
some movers to do this?
I don't know.
You want to pay for it?
Good point.
Hey, what's up with Josh today?
Uh, I don't know.
I guess he's...
He's just a little off.
J new friends along the way j
j we love to sing
and we love to play j
♪
Oh, no way!
Nice.
Oh, my god. Wow.
Oh. Oh, wow.
Here, let's get a shot of that.
For when you find
your Princess charming.
Oh, yeah, right. Could happen.
I should just douse this place
in gasoline.
I'm sure insurance would have
to be worth something.
Like 10 bucks.
Seriously. God.
Whoa.
She kept all of this stuff?
Yeah, tucked away
in her basement
along with all the rest
of her forgotten shit.
You were cute, though. Mm.
What happened to you?
Mm.
What did you inherit
when your mother died?
Oh, a giant bag of badges
from the 1970s.
Josh?
♪
Hey, you shouldn't be
in this room.
Come on. We're all done packing.
Josh.
Hey, come on.
What's going on with you?
I don't want you coming
in this room anymore.
♪
Man: Come on, Jenna. Yeah!
Oh, that's...
J toyou j ahhh!
You want to blow this out?
No, I'll wait. Where's Beth?
She's up there?
Elizabeth.
Beth, what are you doing?
Let's go.
Beth! Okay.
Come on, z.
Ooh!
There you go!
Come on, z.
Let's go.
Beth!
Come on, z.
♪
Oh, this is going to
take a few coats.
Shit is dark.
At least he's not playing
with this thing anymore.
Yeah.
Josh, come and eat!
Hey.
You okay?
I don't feel good.
Oh.
Ah, you know what?
Don't... don't drink that.
Here.
Oh, baby, you're burning up.
Kevin, can you bring me
the thermometer please?
Josh?
Are you okay?
Oh!
You know what?
That's it, that's it.
Get it out.
Josh:
It's okay, buddy, get it out.
You're all right.
Well, do you know when he'll be
out of his appointment?
Well, he wrote my kid
a prescription,
and now he's having a reaction.
He's vomiting.
Well, I... I don't know.
Do we put him on
something different?
You put our son on medication
and didn't tell me?
You're not here, Kevin.
You're not seeing
what I'm seeing.
You don't understand
how bad it is.
He threw a kid
off a fucking balcony.
You don't know that, Beth!
He said he didn't do it.
Bullshit! Give me the pills.
No. Give me the pills.
Kevin. Don't. No! Ugh!
Like you don't keep things
from me, Kevin?
How about the red card?
Huh? How about those?
You don't think it would be nice
to know about those
before everybody in the school
decided that we were
terrible parents?
This is not about us!
This is about him.
Beth: J sleepy time
sleepy time j
I now it is your sleepy time j
j and go to sleep j
mechanical voice: Z.
Z.
♪
Beth.
Z.
I, m, a, g, I, n, e, z.
I, m, a, g, iln, e, z
"Imagine z."
♪
Beth!
It's okay.
What happened, Beth?
What happened in there?
Z is real Kevin.
He... he's re... real.
Beth, what you're saying, its ==
I know. I know how it sounds.
You just...
You have to trust me.
He... he was my friend, too.
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
♪
Jenna.
Beth, I...
Jesus. What are...
What are you doing here?
Are you okay?
Are you all right?
I didn't... get to see her.
I just, uh...
I, uh... I messed up.
No. No, you didn't.
It's okay.
Mm.
Okay, no, no. Okay.
Come on. It's okay.
We'll sort it out.
She's our mom.
She's all we had.
We still have each other, huh?
Ah. I...
I just need to... to lie down.
I just need to lie down. Okay.
Ah.
♪
It's time for your ni-nights.
I don't want to do "em.
Why not?
I don't feel like it.
Honey, what's wrong?
You saw z, didn't you?
What do you mean?
He saw you, too.
♪
Hello? Dr. seager?
Um, I'm sorry to call so late.
It... it's Beth.
Dr. seager: No, no, it's fine.
Is everything all right?
I ju... actually,
just was wondering
if maybe I could schedule,
um, an appointment?
Is everything's okay with Josh?
♪
Um, it's not for Josh.
Mm. It's for me.
It's happening again, isn't it?
Same thing that happened
when you were a child.
♪
When I heard your son
say the name z,
I realized I'd heard it before.
♪
What is this?
You were a patient
of mine, Beth.
Your father brought you to me
when you were Josh's age.
He begged me to help you.
He was terrified.
Your friend was unlike anything
I'd ever encountered.
He was... dangerous,
destructive, obsessive.
Of course, when he stopped
bringing you in,
I... 1 thought
you'd outgrown it.
I had no idea
what had transpired.
I want to show you something.
♪
Dr. seager: Hello, Elizabeth.
Hi.
Hello, z.
So, Beth, your dad told me that
you didn't love him anymore.
Why would you say such a thing?
Because it's true.
Your dad said that you're
refusing to go to school.
Z says I don't need school.
He says he'll take care of me.
What happens when you outgrow 2?
Every child outgrows their
imaginary friend, you know.
Z says when I'm older,
he'll find me,
and we'll get married,
and we'll have lots of babies.
♪
It's been waiting for you, Beth,
and I think it's using your son
to try to reconnect with you.
But it wants only you.
♪
Oh, come on, come on.
Just pick up, please.
Hey, this is Kevin Parsons
I'm not avai...
Oh, shit.
♪
Kevin, please.
Please pick up.
Hey, this is Kevin Parsons
I'm not available...
Aghl..
To take your call right now.
♪
Hi, buddy. I love you.
Come on.
Get out of the way!
♪
Oh, Josh.
Mechanical voice: Z.
Z.
♪
Kevin!
Josh!
Kevin.
♪
Mommy!
I'm scared!
Josh!
Aah!
Josh! Let him out, please!
Ah! Ah! Ah!
♪
Please! I'll be yours.
Please don't take my baby.
Z, I'll be yours, okay? Please.
Please just let him out. Please.
Ah! Ah!
Ah! Josh!
Mommy? Josh!
- Mommy.
- It's okay.
Okay.
Okay, baby.
Mommy.
Nena
♪
You don't want me to be taking
care of Josh right now, Beth,
trust me.
I don't have any choice.
You're all I have left.
He's not safe with me.
He won't be safe
with me, either.
It's not forever, okay?
It's just until
I figure some things out.
Take this,
and you clean yourself up.
If not for me, then for him.
Okay?
♪
All right.
Just...
Imagine z.
♪
Three... two...
One.
One...
Two...
Three.
Ready or not,
I'll find you, z.
♪
I'm gonna find you.
I found you.
I forgot 2%.
I'm sorry. I forgot...
I know.
2%.
♪
Dr. seager: Beth?
I know you're in there.
I spoke to your sister.
She told me what happened.
Dr. seager.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
I heard about Kevin.
I'm so sorry.
Is someone in here with you?
No.
Canl come in?
I don't... I don't think that
that would be a good idea.
Please.
Beth...
I think I can help you.
♪
Oh! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Is Josh here?
Uh, no, he's at my sister's.
♪
Uh, maybe we could...
Sit in the living room.
He's here with you,
isn't he, Beth?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Is this what you want?
To be with him?
♪
I... 1 think
you should go, please.
Please.
Listen to me.
You created this thing.
It's all in your head.
♪
This is not real.
No!
Stop, please.
Please stop!
Please! Stop!
I'll be right out.
Okay?
♪
What do you want for breakfast?
Z, I can't find you.
Do we have to
play this game tonight?
It's so late.
♪
Ah! Ah.
I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
The floor... is lava!
And you can't step
in the lava...
Or else you'll get burnt.
Come on, z.
Ha! You're stuck, z!
♪
Hello? Jenna.
Jenna: Beth? Oh, my god.
Why aren't you
answering your texts?
I know. Listen, I don't have
a lot of time to talk, okay?
I'm on my way up!
I can find you.
Can you put Josh on the line
for me, please?
Josh: Mom?
Hey! Hi, Josh.
How are you, baby?
I miss you.
Listen, I'm gonna see you
really soon, okay?
You tell aunty Jenna
that I will call her
as soon as I can.
You stole my friend!
Josh?
♪
Oh, shit.
27?
♪
Hello? Beth: Jenna.
I need you to get Josh
out of there right now.
Whoa. Slow down are you
with him right now?
Do you see him? Yeah, he's fine.
I'm looking right at him
right now.
Okay, listen, I want you
to put him in the car
and just get as far away as you can.
We're fine.
It's just, how much longer do
you need me to keep him for?
Ugh! You're not
listening to me. Please!
I want you to just get Josh
out of there right now.
It's not safe. He's
fine, Beth, I promise.
What you mean he's gone?
You said he was right there.
Beth, I know. Just... Josh?
Just give me a second.
What do you mean
give you a second?
Where is he? Josh.
Oh, shit.
Answer me. Where is Josh?
I have no idea.
He was just sitting right there,
and he just disappeared.
Just give me a second.
Please, I need you to
tell me you see him.
Oh! Where is he?
Josh!
Jenna, please talk to me!
Where is my son?!
♪
Ma'am, open the door.
We're here to help you, Beth.
Jenna?
Jenna, are you there, please?
Josh!
Jenna, please tell me
you're there.
I'm looking, okay?
Just give me a second.
Jenna, please.
Come on, z. Choo-choo-choo!
Chugga-chugga-chugga-chugga-
chugga-chugga-chugga...
Choo-choo!
Chugga-chugga-chugga-chugga-
chugga-chugga-chugga...
Choo-choo!
Chugga-chugga-
chugga-chugga-choo.
Josh!
Chugga-chugga-chugga choo-choo!
Chugga-chugga-chugga-chugga...
Josh!
Jenna, tell me
you have him, please.
Is z in there with you, Beth?
He has my son!
Remember...
This is all in your mind, Beth.
No, I don't know.
This thing... you got to get it
out of your head.
You created it.
Only you can stop it.
♪
I can stop it.
Josh!
♪
Jenna: I got him.
I got him, Beth. He's okay.
Oh, Josh is okay.
He's okay.
Josh: Mommy?
All right.
Here we go.
Good.
♪
Jenna: Okay, Josh.
Try to get some sleep.
♪
Can ldo the ni-nights?
Not tonight.
We'll do them tomorrow.
♪
Josh: Good night, mom.
Good night, dad.
Good night, aunty Jenna.
Good night, matchie.
Goodnight, z.
Subtitles Diego Moraes(oakislandtk)
www.opensubtitles.org
♪