Go to hell
Leave this place
Rubbish dump
Get out now!
Divine punishment?
Sofue
Sorry, baby.
Did you miss me
being alone like that?
Keep Out
Sadako's cave has been blocked.
You are Sadako.
The reincarnation of Sadako.
Everything's all right.
There is nothing to fear.
Forever will you be with Mother.
Sadako!
You shouldn't be allowed to live.
That's why
this is the only way.
Did you...
summon her?
No!
Sadako
Kurokawa Memorial General Hospital
Good morning.
Dr Akikawa.
- Good morning.
Clinical Psychologist: Akikawa Mayu
Thank you for waiting.
How are we feeling?
A full recovery!
I can sleep well
and my appetite is back.
I'm eating so much.
Great.
You look healthy, Ms Kurahashi.
You're like a whole new person.
That's you.
At first,
I thought you were too young
but no one's looked after me
like you have.
It's been tough, no?
Are things okay?
Isn't Dr Fujii strict with new staff?
You're perceptive.
I knew it!
Just kidding. He's not.
If you have any trouble, tell me.
I'll kick his ass.
No one's stayed on this floor
longer than me.
The thing is, I owe you so much.
You must let me thank you.
I know a nice restaurant.
Why not go together?
It's my treat, of course.
I couldn't.
No, don't be shy.
I know you must be busy.
So, when you have some downtime,
let's go and take it easy.
She called me strict?
You'll never find a nicer boss.
Ms Kurahashi looked good.
Can't believe
she'd been here so long.
But, be careful.
She baked you cookies, no?
Maintain a professional
distance with the patients.
I know it's not easy but
that's a basic rule for us doctors.
Yes, sir.
Hey! What's going on here?
Too much noise.
I said, keep it down!
Shush!
Yeah, but take a look at this!
What is it?
Kazuma?
His feet got hurt badly!
There! The Wrinkled Mug!
He thinks he's young.
See you in the next video!
This was Fantastic Kazuma.
Subscribe to my channel!
Yum!
It's great.
Very soft.
This. Explain.
Look, Sis.
I'm betting my life on this.
I've always said
I'd work at giving children dreams.
Know what kids wanna be?
They wanna grow up
to be media streamers.
What about school?
You wanted to be a programmer.
I quit.
Wasn't my thing.
- What about the enrollment fee?
- You'll get it back!
That's not the point. What is this?
Think you can live on this?
Look, I'm working with a pro.
A pro?
A web marketer, for your information.
I've got a pro in my corner
and my subscriber base is rising.
Please, I need you to get behind me.
Are you OK?
What's wrong?
You alone?
Hold it!
A memory disorder?
The police brought her here.
She can't even say her name.
Is she a runaway?
Seems she was outside for a spell.
How are you feeling?
Did you sleep well?
Can you remember anything?
How about your parents?
Can you recall your name?
Don't worry.
For now, stay put and
things will come back bit by bit.
Okay?
Doctor, got a moment?
Yes.
These people are from
the Tamakita Crime Unit.
Detectives?
It's about the girl.
We need to talk.
Three!
Two!
One! Go!
This was Fantastic Kazuma!
Subscribe to my channel!
Views: 8,019.  89% down
Only 8,000 views.
Why is this?
They're getting bored.
Upload boring content
and they'll flee.
Come on.
Didn't you say
things were going well?
Don't rush it.
Make another viral video
and they'll be back.
You're going to school, right?
Weren't you editing all night?
I'm going.
Gotta find topics...
Popular videos are people doing
dumb things, gamers
sexy and titillating
or scary, urban experience videos.
Kazuma
are you aware of any scary places?
No.
Scary place, Tokyo, recent
Ten Scariest Spots in Tokyo
Tokyo's Top 20 Abandoned Buildings
"Exploring scary haunted places."
"Horrific places best not to visit."
"Ten scariest spots in Tokyo."
"Five killed in
apartment complex fire."
The arson case
in Numata Complex last month.
Five killed in fire
Suspect, a resident in the complex
The criminal is Sofue Hatsuko, 34.
The girl's mother.
What?
She set fire to the complex and died.
It appears to be suicide.
So, after the fire, the girl just...
All we know about her is
her relationship with Sofue
based on DNA analysis.
Beyond that, we know nothing.
At first
we didn't even know
of the child's existence.
Sofue has no child on paper.
Then, what does this mean?
Sofue delivered her
and raised her secretly.
She must not have gone to school.
No one even knows her name.
This building.
Do you remember it?
You lived here, didn't you?
Do you know who she is?
Right.
She's your mother, Sofue Hatsuko.
Now, can you recall your name?
What did she call you?
Sadako.
Sadako?
So, that's your name?
How about this?
Can you recall the fire?
Your home caught on fire.
Is there anything you recall?
Even something trivial.
Tell me anything you remember.
Was there anything unusual
about your mother?
Try to recall.
Weren't you always with her?
Mr Kida.
She must give us something.
Can't you remember anything?
This is important!
You must remember.
Maybe she had trouble
with the neighbours
and set the room on fire?
This is enough for today.
She's been through
a traumatic experience.
She needs time to recover.
Hello there!
Hello there.
- Here's the file.
- Thank you.
- I'm handing it over to you.
Hello.
How are you?
Sleep, sleep
Come in.
That new girl is creepy.
She hardly eats at all.
If I mention it, she gives me a look.
When I talk to her, she says nothing.
Thank you so much
for changing the flowers.
I see. It wasn't me.
Then who?
- Look here!
- Isn't it sick?
- For real.
- Look at mine.
That's so stupid.
- Mine's cool.
- Not stupid.
Not stupid at all.
- What?
- Look!
- Scary.
- Creepy.
- Real creepy.
- Weird.
- Let's get her.
- Let's do it!
Come on...
Don't you have a name?
Can you speak?
No name? Your parents must be nuts.
Totally nuts.
Come on, say something.
Okay, from today,
you're gonna be Jane Doe!
Good old Jane Doe!
Jane Doe, she has no name!
What happened?
Are you hurt? Stay right there.
Are you okay?
The doors are opening.
What are you doing here?
Are you okay?
Yo! It's Jahmes.
My video about
"Can I pick up chicks
even though I stink?"
was a hit
so I'm hitting on hot chicks again!
Can I pick up chicks
in my mini truck?
First Attempt
What are you doing there?
- Tommy here!
- Kanta here!
Jahmes got cocky before
so we thought to have
some fun with him this time.
He'll be by any moment.
Let's go eat.
- I parked there.
- You got a car?
I see.
This one.
Give me a minute.
Gotta feed the metre.
A truck?
What?
What's up?
What is that?
Everyone's in the playroom.
Won't you go?
May I stay here?
I hear you don't eat much.
If you don't eat,
you won't get better.
Surely you don't want more shots.
Is my mum...
dead?
Do you remember...
the fire?
No, I don't.
Well then
what do you remember
about your life
before you got here?
I was in a dark place
most of the time.
Mum would come and
bring me food.
A dark place?
The closet.
But she would let me out
when she came back home.
You, too?
What?
You were lonely, too.
What is it?
Hey...
wait!
- Are you okay?
- What happened?
- Call the doctor.
- Got it.
Check her vitals.
Are you okay?
Her pulse is fading.
She's losing energy.
Her anorexia is the issue now.
It's like she's refusing to live.
You too? Are you all right?
Yes.
Sorry for more bad news
Ms Kurahashi kept asking
for your number yesterday.
What?
She said you're avoiding her.
Didn't you tell her no?
I didn't say yes.
You must refuse.
Transference can happen
even between doctors and
patients of the same gender.
Sorry.
Incoming call: Unknown Number
Hello?
Is this Akikawa Mayu?
Yes.
I'm Ishida, a friend of Kazuma's.
It seems I'm unable to reach him.
What?
Here you are.
A Summary of Unusual Urban Legends
Do you know this site?
Fantastic Kazuma's
Scary Video Removed
It was an off-limits place.
The burnt complex?
It was creepy.
The cops got called.
Dumb trespasser!
Look closely,
there's something there.
- Dude got cursed.
- LOL
Is it still available?
The original was deleted.
See me sneak into the burnt complex!
This video has been deleted
What does this mean?
There was a case of arson at that
residential complex last month.
He went there to shoot
an urban exploration video.
I tried to stop him.
We can't run videos of crime scenes
involving death.
But he wouldn't listen.
As I figured, the police warned us
and made us delete it.
That fool.
We've had no contact since then.
Normally, I wouldn't care
but he was behaving oddly
the last time we met.
What are you up to?
If we don't go for broke,
we're not going to get any views.
But there are still lines
we shouldn't cross.
Afraid you'll get busted?
What?
I found it.
I'm going to do this alone
if I have to.
With this
I'll reach a whole new level.
I...
I saw it.
What are you saying?
The police...
Please leave.
It's been a week
and he's not returned my calls.
I've got to get back to work.
The video was deleted
but if you search hard enough,
you'll find it.
Hold it!
Why did you involve Kazuma?
Figured you could manipulate him?
- Not at all.
- Then why didn't you stop him?
I tried! But...
My brother...
he was proud to know you.
He thought he'd make it
with your help.
He quit school to do this.
What?
It might not have meant much to you
but, to him, it meant the world.
I haven't heard back from you
in a while.
I'm really worried.
Mr Ishida's worried too.
Please get back to me soon.
Fantastic Kazuma
deleted
Seems legit
Too spot on to be fake
Subliminal message?
- Look forward to more of your videos
- He was cursed
- This freaked me out.
- I'm fricking freaked out.
- Whoever saw it will die, right?
- Dead in a week
Three days, no?
He's marked for death
What's up!
What's popping, peeps?
Fantastic Kazuma here.
Today, I'll be doing something
with a touch of the mysterious.
Because today
I'll hit these digs!
Numata Apartment Complex
No question.
An arson case in which
five people met their fate.
Today, I am at
the scene of the crime.
Exploration of the Burnt Complex!
As for the fire, the reason
given by the media was
that trouble with the residents
caused the incident.
But the thing is, this Sofue person
was really freaky.
The suspect, Sofue
Bet you wanna know
how nuts she really was.
First of all, she was a psychic.
Sofue the Psychic
A psychic?
She did fortune telling,
folk remedies...
shady things like that.
This is why the other residents
harassed her.
They dumped garbage outside her unit
and even left a dead cat by her door.
She was badly harassed.
Everyone, are you aware of
the word "ostracism"?
Ninth floor.
I'm on the ninth floor.
I'm at the entrance and everything
is covered by blue sheets.
It's low!
Made it. I'll now start
my investigation of
the apartment of the suspect, Sofue.
Now, let's go inside.
Whoa.
Lots of graffiti here too.
This place got hit hard.
Look, this one says Sofue.
I'm sure it's her place.
It's time.
I'm going in.
Excuse me, I'm coming in.
Slowly...
Is this the hall?
I'm inside now.
It's dark.
Peeps, trust me when I say it stinks.
I'm not sure but...
it's like the smell of the fire
still lingers in the air.
Check out the wallpaper.
There's police tape
strung everywhere.
There's an iron grill door,
right here.
And then, another door behind it.
This room alone has two doors.
Can you see it?
I'm heading in.
Here we go.
Holy...
Incredible.
Hold it a second.
Is that where the...
The spots that are unburnt
show where the body was.
Wait.
Can't believe it, peeps!
Look what's still here!
It's a mirror and a CD player thingy.
Look, the air conditioner.
It's all melted.
This is bad, folks.
And look at this.
It's a shelf or a rack.
This is worse than I imagined.
It's like everything is still here.
This is too much.
What's that?
Hold on while I show it to you.
Look at the closet.
It's got a chain.
There's something.
Hold it.
A padlock and a key.
This is really crazy.
Who puts a chain on a closet?
Wait...
should I open the closet?
I'm gonna do it.
I'm opening it now.
Whoa!
Huh?
What? Holy moly! Hold on here!
They're talismans!
A shitload of talismans!
On the ceiling too!
And over here
some wired ornaments.
No way.
Wait. Hold on there.
I think these are dolls
and toys for kids.
They definitely are.
What the...
It's a rice bowl. A rice bowl.
I was in a dark place
most of the time.
Mum would come and
bring me food.
I'm sweating so much.
Peeps, this is...
You've seen it, so now you know.
I think
this is an incredible find and...
Elevator is going down.
That's it.
This was Fantastic Kazuma.
You've seen it, so now you know.
I think
this is an incredible find and...
What is that?
Missing Persons Report
Job: Self-employed
Name: Akikawa Kazuma
We can't do much now.
The man who saw him last
said he was acting odd.
It's not enough to suggest
he committed suicide.
It's not that...
We'll register your brother
as a runaway.
He's my only family.
He'd never run off
without telling me.
Yes.
Yes, right.
If Kazuma contacts you,
please let me know.
Yes.
Thank you. Bye.
There are lots of things in here
for someone to live.
This is really out there.
Especially all these talismans.
Well, I'm sweating so much.
Peeps, this is...
You've seen it, so now you know.
I think
this is an incredible find and...
Ms Kurahashi?
What are you doing?
Oh, doctor!
Sorry, I left something.
Ms Ohno gave me a key.
Well, you're working late.
Did you...
put those flowers
in my counselling room?
You noticed?
No one else bothers.
You like flowers, right?
I use this to cut the flowers.
Doctor?
Thank you.
I appreciate it but please don't
enter my office without permission.
Why?
Please stop!
That's not what I mean.
Then why are you backing away?
Why are you afraid of me?
That's not it!
What?
You're acting strange!
You kept me waiting.
Isn't it rude to keep me waiting?
Ms Kurahashi! Keep calm.
I'm not mad!
I don't mean
to overlook your kindness.
I said I'm not mad!
Why am I so mad at you?
Don't be conceited!
I was so kind to you.
Why do you make me feel like this?
Are you all right?
Come on!
Wake up.
Come on, please.
Sadako...
Come on! Hurry!
Akikawa!
What's the matter?
Wake up.
Are you okay?
Akikawa!
I'll take her to ICU!
Hey!
You okay?
- Hey!
- Ms Kurahashi!
Ms Kurahashi, what happened?
Ms Kurahashi,
I'd like to examine you.
Can you stand up?
Let's stand up.
What's wrong? Please calm down!
Get a wheelchair!
It's okay.
Got it, I won't touch you.
It's all right. Calm down.
Look, it's all right.
Let's get on the wheelchair.
Ms Kurahashi has been admitted.
Her condition was improving,
but now...
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
You need a break.
You need to take care of yourself
before you can take care
of your patients.
How's the girl?
She's still in ICU.
And still unconscious.
Honestly, it doesn't look good.
Mr Fujii.
I...
I saw something weird.
When Ms Kurahashi attacked me.
I saw a woman with long hair.
You are Sadako.
The reincarnation of Sadako.
You are a harbinger of misfortune.
You are destined to take life...
as did Sadako!
Sadako.
Dr Akikawa!
She can't talk now.
Doctor!
Please, don't. Doctor!
I'm here to talk about Sadako.
Please tell me.
My brother is missing.
He has probably seen her too.
Ms Kurahashi
you called that thing Sadako.
Please tell me! What is she?
When I was in high school
my friend died.
Not just her.
Many people did.
All of them...
got killed.
It was the curse of Sadako.
Curse?
A long time ago
a psychic killed herself.
She was clairvoyant.
Her reputation grew gradually.
One day, she was maligned
and labelled a fraud.
Because of that...
she killed herself.
Her daughter was...
Sadako.
With just a thought
Sadako could strike a person dead.
She was far more powerful
than her mother.
Alas, her life ended abruptly.
Fearful of her power
her father threw her...
down a well.
Sadako was tossed away and killed.
That's the origin of the curse.
All who come in contact
with her curse
were killed.
Including my friend.
Everyone.
A curse.
No way.
I have no doubt it was Sadako!
It's true, I tell you!
The curse exists. I've seen it!
It is not possible to save him.
Your brother
has been cursed.
That hurt!
Man, I could hear my back cracking.
Next time for sure! On to round two!
I'll try it backwards. Gently...
There! The Wrinkled Mug!
Where are you, Kazuma?
This was Fantastic Kazuma!
Subscribe to my channel!
Kazuma?
Hello?
It's Ishida. Sorry to call suddenly.
I found Kazuma.
He's in the video
we uploaded earlier.
I know.
I saw the video too.
Oshima?
Yes, Oshima Island in Izu.
I did an image search.
I think it's correct.
It's a place where
mountain ascetics trained.
Mysterious Spots in Tokyo, Izu Cave
Many priests lost their lives here.
The shrine was built
to appease their souls.
But a cave-in made it off-limits
for the past 20 years.
Do you recognise this talisman?
It's got a chain.
Should I open the closet?
Whoa! Huh?
They are talismans!
Like the complex?
Sofue was connected to this place.
What does that mean?
I don't know.
First of all,
how was the video uploaded?
I think
this is an incredible find and...
I first saw it here.
Do you know about the cursed video?
What?
It was all over the Internet.
I don't know who found it first
but at some point, it was mixed in
with other videos.
Then, a rumour started saying that
the video creators were cursed.
A curse...
It's just an urban legend.
"The psychic, Yamamura Shizuko
to be publicly tested."
Supernatural powers?
Is this the woman in the video?
The psychic
who killed herself was real.
What?
She was born on Oshima Island.
Sadako must have been too.
Sadako?
Kazuma is...
in Oshima.
Hello?
Hello, this is Fujii.
Don't be alarmed but...
Ms Kurahashi has died.
What?
When the nurse found her
this morning, she was already...
One, two, three!
What is it?
I must save Kazuma.
Wait, you mean...
Mayu!
I'll go with you.
I got Kazuma into this.
Aren't you cold?
Let's go inside.
What was it Kazuma saw?
The last time we met
he said he'd seen it.
Kazuma became cursed.
Do you really believe in curses?
I saw her too.
Sadako.
At the complex
he saw Sadako
in the room
where the girl was imprisoned.
A girl who shared
the same fate as Sadako
has resurrected the curse.
Let's go.
No large tents
are allowed in the area
Oshima Fisherman's Union
Keep Out
Please wait here.
Hold it there!
What are you doing?
Hold it! Can't you read?
My brother is in the cave shrine.
Please, we have to save him.
What?
Is someone in the cave?
This isn't a place for sightseeing.
You have no idea what this place is.
Many were swept away from
the banks of this sacred shore.
Those that are unwanted
are washed away by the sea.
Infanticide.
Unwanted babies
were put in the shrine and
carried out to sea.
Souls of children
killed by their parents
gather in the shrine.
Sadako thrives on them.
Sadako.
Do you know Yamamura Sadako?
It's impossible today.
It's the spring tide.
Spring tide?
Tonight is the full moon.
It will be high tide.
Go in there and
the sea will drag you down.
The full moon.
Of course.
Look.
The video is changing?
How?
Dangerous cave
Do not enter
We can't go in today.
The tide is getting too high.
Maybe tomorrow...
- It'll be too late!
- Why?
We must go now or he'll be...
It'd only be another disaster.
Please understand.
- Hold on...
- Don't be stupid!
- Calm down!
- Get off!
Calm down!
If the full moon rises
Kazuma will...
Don't be so ominous.
He was always there for me.
Kazuma and I...
grew up in an orphanage.
I was in grade school
when we were abandoned.
What's up, Sis? Not hungry?
Check out my new move!
The wrinkled mug!
Souls of children
killed by their parents
gather in the shrine.
Could it be that Kazuma and I...
have been summoned by Sadako?
Mayu!
Keep Out
Kazuma...
he's behind those rocks.
How did he get in?
Kazuma.
No!
Mayu...!
Dammit.
Kazuma.
Where are you, Kazuma?
Kazuma!
What happened?
Pull yourself together!
Kazuma.
Kazuma!
Hey!
No way...
Sadako.
I'm sorry, Sadako.
It is the only way.
Sadako's mother abandoned her.
But she didn't die. She survived.
That's how
she gained her fearsome powers.
You, too?
Abandoned by your mother?
Pulse: 53,
blood pressure 57/31.
SpO2: 93%.
Status?
Still in a coma.
Vital signs?
Temperature: 35C.
- Blood data?
- How much IV is left?
She's showing signs of cyanosis.
- Not good.
- Add more to the IV.
I will. Take this.
She's starting to asphyxiate.
- Doctor!
- Check SpO2!
Got it.
Legs up!
All right? Hang in there.
Fight!
Hold on. Please!
Stay with us!
No!
Don't give in!
You're not alone!
You have me!
I'll care for you!
I'll never let you die!
Doctor, she's conscious.
Vital signs?
Stabilised.
SpO2 is rising.
Blood pressure?
118/79. Stabilising.
Her colour has returned.
Mayu!
Are you all right?
Wait here.
Kazuma!
Hey, Kazuma!
Are you okay, Kazuma?
Kazuma! Snap out of it!
Kazuma! What's happened to you?
Hey, Kazuma!
Kazuma, what's wrong?
Come on!
Hey! Kazuma!
Snap out of it!
Kazuma!
Sis!
Run!
Get away!
Kazuma!
Sis! Stay back!
Mayu!
Get off!
Kazuma!
Yusuke, take her!
Sis...
Forgive me!
Kazuma!
No, Kazuma!
No!
Mayu!
Kazuma!
Kurokawa Memorial General Hospital
Dr Akikawa.
Before she leaves
she said she wanted to talk to you.
Your voice.
I heard it clearly.
I could come back
all thanks to you.
Thank you.
Translator: SPECTRA MEDIA