Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
Let me the fuck in!
Get... Get up!
Let me in!
Brother, are you seeing this?
There's a riot
on every fucking floor.
Look, you don't want
to feed them, fine.
Don't need to no more,
'cause I did it.
I found a buyer... 500K.
This is the time, man.
- Buyer won't wait.
- Oh, man.
This high...
Let's talk on the balcony.
You've done fine work, Roadie.
Is it real?
Yeah, sure as shit.
It all goes down tomorrow
at dawn, 18 hours.
Great.
Unload everything.
I'm gonna blow this town.
On it.
Did you follow me down here?
Is this what you want?
So?
Go on... if you really want it.
I'm not saying I condone
a militia mentality here
or anything like that,
but I'm saying people need to
take this into their own hands.
The cops can't do anything
anymore.
There's not enough of them.
They're taking care
of themselves.
They're killing each other.
We don't need to go in there
and do anything.
I'm not gonna risk my life.
I drive down the street,
yes, I see less homeless people.
Maybe there's more crime
around there,
but the crime's gonna be gone.
Baby's still running, huh?
Better than you are.
Whoa, man.
A little early for that,
ain't it?
Starting the day off right,
baby.
I guess so.
Let the good times roll, huh?
God!
It's depressing looking
at the old neighborhood, though.
It's depressing.
This used to be
almost a thriving place.
It's too bad it's going down.
It's turning into
a fucking war zone, man.
I'll tell you what it is.
It's all those goddamn drugs.
Say, about your truck, man...
It's old,
but it's still running, right?
At the moment.
Don't fucking...
Don't... Don't say anything.
It's old,
but it's still running, dude.
Just like us...
old but still running.
- See this?
- Yeah, I see it. What's...
There's a bunch of punks
who have been hanging out there.
Yeah.
I started noticing
about two weeks ago,
and there was just a couple
of them.
- And now there's more and more.
- Druggies?
I don't know what the fuck...
Yeah, I'd say
they're drug addicts, for sure.
There's a whole shitload
of them, too.
But as long as they keep
over there...
- Guess what, man.
- What?
Birthday boy!
- Fuck you.
- No, no. Birthday boy.
Don't say nothing
about it, all right?
I'm not the only one
who knows that.
You think the other guys
don't know that?
God! Shit!
Oh, great.
We're here.
I had a dream, Fred.
You hit every goddamn pothole
in town.
That was no dream.
Oh, it was delib'ate, wasn't it?
"Delib'ate"?
Where you from?
Walter, hit the lights.
Yep.
Got it.
There you go.
Son of a motherfucking whore.
Uh-huh.
This piece of shit's
on its last legs, Fred.
Hey, Walter.
Walter, settle down, huh?
Oh! Come on. Be gentle, man.
I brought this all the way
from Bloody Ridge.
Aw, one man and a big damn knife
holding back
the Communist regime, huh?
You used to like that story.
I used to be able to get hard
without the blue pills, too.
Read 'em and weep.
- Yes, sir.
- Geez.
- Lucky day. Come on.
- Do I need to ask?
- The man's horny.
- Pop it in, buddy.
The man's pathetic.
Look at this.
I'm looking. I'm looking.
Oh, Lord.
There we go.
- Hold on there. Hold...
- What?
You've been at this,
haven't you?
- I have.
- Uh-huh.
There's no telling
where his lips have been.
Yeah. I don't remember myself.
You'd better wipe that twice.
How about three times, will you?
Oh, there you go.
Here we go.
To us.
Still here.
- Still here.
- Still fuckin' here.
I thought
you had that fixed, man.
I thought I did, too, damn it.
Shh. Come on.
This is my favorite part.
- Standing in the way.
- You're blocking the man's view.
Two. Three. Take it down.
Come on. Reach!
Two. Three.
Gentlemen!
My heroes.
Whoo!
What a great day, huh?
Mm!
Look at Lou,
all spruced up, man.
Yeah.
Did the Better Business Bureau
close down Lou's Lemons?
No business today on account
of it's a very special day.
No, no. Not you too.
No way. No!
On account of this being
a very special day,
I need you to do me a favor.
Let me get you
out of that ancient,
rusted prehistoric truck.
I'll pass.
I'll give you 2%
off the sticker.
- Ooh.
- Oh, my God.
Two percent.
One, because I love you
and you're my pal.
Two, because it's your birthday.
It's got to be a cash deal,
though, because...
well, because
of your advanced age.
Lay off him, Lou,
especially today.
I can negotiate anything, huh?
I'm an animal.
Yeah.
Goddamn snake.
Ooh.
Hey, hey.
You know what, Lou?
You keep reminding me
it's my birthday...
and this goes
for all of youse...
I'll start reminding you
of your tabs.
- Now, come on, man.
- Sure, he will. Sure, he will.
Before you do, Zabriski's glass
looks a little light.
Yeah. Excuse me.
Glad somebody is looking out
for me.
- Thank you, Doug. Ooh.
- I got you, buddy.
Geez.
You run over a fuckin' skunk
on the way here?
- No. Upgraded, you know?
- Yeah?
Medical. Yeah.
It's California green.
What do you got,
some kind of condition?
Nurse at the VA.
Oh.
It's preexisting.
I hear they got scientists
making that shit now.
- Mm.
- Yeah.
Bring a man
to a whole other dimension.
I want some of that
science weed. Come on.
Not that. You lipped it.
Get out of here.
Yeah. I'll roll you a bone.
One for Freddy.
Maybe the old man
wants to join in, too.
No, no, no, no.
Only poison I'm going to put
into this wonderful body
is right here.
Maybe Freddy. Huh?
Roll one up for the occasion?
Come on.
You roll whatever you want,
but how many times
do I have to tell you
to take that shit outside, Doug?
Huh? What's wrong with you?
What, are you high?
Freddy.
Hey, Freddy, how about we close
the bar down early tonight?
What do you say?
What do you say
we got customers here, huh?
- I'll chase them off.
- You're the man for that.
What do you got going on?
The best birthday
that Freddy ever got.
Fuckin' idiots.
Fuckin' bunch of morons
is what you fuckin' are.
Boz, that's more
than double what it's worth.
Are you sure this is legit?
You know Roadie's fucked this up
before.
Jesus Christ.
Let me worry about my brother.
Clear these hypers out of here.
I don't want anything
fucking this up.
These are shitty cigarettes.
You know that?
You got shitty cigarettes.
How come you don't got no
organic True 100s or something?
I'll get right on it, Walter.
Mm!
All right, gentlemen.
Gather around the campfire,
because it's story time.
The year... 1969.
We're overseas.
And this is when Fred was,
you know, not this exactly.
I got a weekend of R&R
at some shitty fuel depot,
and I'm drunk as a payday skunk,
and I see this guy coming, okay?
Now, I hate the son of a bitch
'cause he used to pitch
for the Rockets,
which was two towns over,
and he beaned me in the skull
with a fastball senior year.
Boom! I go down, okay?
And I'm...
And... So I'm gonna take
this guy apart, but...
You know where you are, kid?
You're in the, uh, VFW post.
Want me to check his ID, man?
May be a situation
of stolen valor.
Come on. Check it.
Just check it, man.
No.
Be sure.
All right, Abe.
Uh-huh.
What are you drinking?
Beer, please.
You leading a parade?
Ha.
No.
Buddy of mine told me,
"If you wear your uniform
on the plane,
they'll bump you up
to first class."
Didn't happen.
Hey, Walter,
this will shut you up.
- Man just got home.
- Yes!
- Oh, hey!
- Yes, sir!
Don't think about reaching
for your wallet.
Nobody pays first day back.
Fred, gentlemen's preference
all around.
I'll contribute to the cause.
But not from that paint thinner
of the shelf.
Up there.
I was just getting
to the good part, guys.
Yeah. You must have been
taking the scenic route.
Hey, new fella.
- Shawn.
- Shane.
Shawn.
Whatever.
I don't even know you,
but I know you're gonna
fuckin' love this.
I knocked this motherfucker out
ice cold on the ground,
and I'm looking down at him,
and I go, "Oh, shit!"
'Cause I just realized
he is a fucking staff sergeant.
He's got like seven ranks on me.
I'm... I-I'm 19 years old.
I'm shitting myself.
"Oh, fuck, I am court-martialed.
I am so dead."
And what's the first words
out of your mouth?
Fred, you remember
what you said?
First words.
I said, uh...
"...Soldier...
you like American poontang?"
Yes!
That's right!
That's what he said.
I thought I knocked some marbles
loose.
But no, he's got tickets
in his pocket
for that night's USO show,
where Miss 1963 is shaking her
mm-mm-mm-mmm-mmm-mmm.
Oh, it was glorious.
It was.
Freddy says he's taking so much
high heat from the Viet Cong
that that little
red-white-and-blue right hook...
that felt like home.
He makes a couple
of phone calls,
and first thing I know,
I'm transferred into his unit.
And me and Lou over here
and Fred,
we finished out our tours,
and we all come home together,
and we...
we fart around in town.
We're painting houses and shit.
And then one day,
we say, "Fuck it,"
and we take the first plane
back into the shit, you know?
But that was...
And that was enough for me,
But... But Fred...
Holy cripes.
He's... He keeps going.
He goes like five tours of duty,
right?
That's enough, Walter.
All right.
You should have seen
this bastard over there.
- All right.
- Alive, I fuckin' tell you.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey. Hey, hey.
Let it go, huh?
I'm just getting
to the big twist here, okay?
Here comes the purple nurple.
Miss 1963.
Fred, you ever wonder
what happened to that girl?
She got married.
She had a couple of kids.
And one of them followed
in Mama's career path,
and that is why
I'm going to ask you
the same delicately phrased
question that you asked me
all those years ago...
Do you like American poontang?
What is this?
'Cause Miss 1963 had a kid
that's name is Crystal now,
and she's dancing on the pole
tonight at midnight
at the Deja Vu over on Lincoln.
- Aw, come on.
- And we're all going.
We're all going,
and you can't say no
'cause this is a celebration,
and we're not celebrating
in this shithole.
Watering hole.
Oh, geez.
Shitty watering hole.
And you, my young friend,
you are gonna get
a hero's homecoming.
That's how.
All right?
I'm serious.
So get your shit together.
We leave at 2300 hours
or whenever I finish urinating,
whichever comes first.
No, no, no.
That... That's it.
She got no pussy hairs.
Pardon?
I like pussy hairs.
What gives her the right
to cut off her pussy hairs?
It's her pussy.
I don't understand
how they get it so smooth,
like a goddamn ice luge.
Lasers.
Laser... Of course!
- The kid knows! Lasers!
- The kid knows. The kid knows.
Moonraker, blasting cunt hairs
from outer space.
Pew! Pew!
You don't get it.
Back in the day,
I used to buy toothpicks
by the gross.
Just in case.
You know what I'm saying?
- Wait a minute.
- Am I having a stroke?
If he says we need to move,
we need to move.
Is everything else ready?
Yeah, everything else
is ready to go.
We got a major problem here.
They're out of control.
All right.
This place is fucked.
Plan B.
I'll grab the stuff.
Do what you got to do.
Fuck!
Oh, for fuck's sake.
Who the fuck was in here?!
Hey!
Fuck.
Lizard!
They don't know
what they're missing.
This darkness...
...it's perfect.
It's peace.
God damn it.
I'm afraid
that's all she wrote, boys.
Party's over.
Time to call it a day.
Fred, I've been telling you
about this guy.
This guy Eddie Harris, he's
the best electrician in town.
He could rewire
this whole goddamn dump.
- Uh-huh.
- I mean, he'll have it humming.
Oh, yeah.
Or not.
Hell, you might even be able
to serve beer when it's cold.
Lou, if he's anything like the
plumber you sent over last time,
keep his number.
Don't say a fucking word.
What did you do?
Listen up.
A filthy,
filthy little reptile...
you all know her as Lizard...
has stolen your fix!
Hype... all you want,
enough to liquefy
your fucking tonsils...
to whoever brings me the girl.
Lizard's sister...
What purpose did that serve?
She won't get away.
The hypers will retrieve her.
Half of them can barely walk.
Don't underestimate them,
Gutter.
You see...
an army of brain-dead animals...
is still an army.
Freddy, this will cheer you up.
She's still dancing tonight.
- Aw...
- No. Come on.
No, Walt. I think I'm checking
out early and closing up.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Now, the taps,
they might be running, right?
Yeah.
All right.
One for the road.
- Ranger?
- Yes, sir.
Hey, soldier boy, don't you have
a baby's mama to go home to?
No. I have a wife.
You got any extra toothpicks?
- Ooh.
Lizard, get back here!
Lizard!
What the hell?
Guys?
- Hey!
- What?
Fred, there's
this fucking girl...
- Hey!
God damn it, Lizard!
What the hell did you do?
Hey!
Jesus Christ!
Christ!
Get down!
No!
Son of a bitch piece of trash.
Shit. Shit.
Doug, man.
What in the cocksucking fuck
just went on here?
Oh, Fred. Fred.
Oh, C-Christ!
F-Fred... I'm dead.
No, you're not dead.
You hang in there.
You hear me, brother?
You hang in there!
Here.
Help me out here, boys.
- Yeah. Yeah, I got it.
- All right.
Whoa, whoa. Go... No, no.
Go real easy. Real easy.
That shoulder looks like
it's hanging by a thread.
Oh, wonderful.
Sit him up.
All right. Here we go.
Lift. Lift. Here we go.
- Over to here.
- To the bar.
- Come on. Watch. Watch his head.
- I got him. I got him.
- I got... Don't worry.
- A little higher.
- Watch his head. Watch his head.
- Higher.
Good.
Kid, go shut the door,
will you?
We got you.
You got to get
a tourniquet on there, man.
All right.
Keep this open.
- You stay with us.
- Don't worry about me.
- Where did the kid...
- Hold that arm up.
Dougie, open your eyes.
Doug, you hear me?
I want your eyes open.
You're coming with me, bitch!
Hey, punk!
I got this, kid.
This is for Doug, you fuck!
Yeah!
That's right!
Fuck!
Fuckin' punk fuck!
Breathe.
It's like patching
a busted water main.
See?
This ain't working, huh?
- Yes, it is. Just breathe.
- Easy, Doug.
What the fuck is going on
out there?!
Hey, kid, check that side door.
Easy.
Easy, easy.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
Anybody else
want to come in my bar?!
Oh! God!
Hard line.
Other way out?
At the hall?
All right. All right.
Move your ass. Let's go!
- Okay.
- Come on.
Jesus Christ.
Where's your head at, Lou?
- I got blood all over me.
- We need a better tourniquet.
- Give me your belt.
- It's alligator skin.
Give me your fuckin' belt,
or I'll strangle you with it.
Jesus.
How's he doing?
Not good.
Well, you keep him breathing.
We're bugging out the back.
Yes, sir.
Easy.
Okay.
- A little tighter.
- Yeah, a little tighter.
What do we got out there?
Looks clear.
All right.
Fuck this.
I'll pull my car around.
We'll get Doug in,
and we all leave and eat.
Whoa!
- Shit!
- Holy shit!
Get in there!
Where's Z?
He's dead.
What the hell is going on here,
man?!
Easy, easy, easy, easy.
I mean, that trash
comes rushing in here,
and all of a sudden it's like
Khe Sanh all over again.
I mean, those animals outside,
don't they know we're
supposed to be at the titty bar?
We're supposed to be celebrating
Freddy's birthday!
Lou!
Shut your fuckin' yap!
There's nothing more we can do
for him here.
We got to get him to a hospital
now.
All right.
We're gonna.
Look, Abe.
Look, there's clean rags
behind the bar.
You keep pressure
on that shoulder.
Just... You keep him breathing.
The rest of you,
secure the doors.
What do we do, just sit here
with our thumbs up our asses?
Hey, Lou.
It's gonna be all right.
The smaller force acts while
the larger force regroups.
I'm gonna bring the truck
right up to the door.
We're gonna get him in it,
and we're gonna get ourselves
out of here alive.
- Roger that.
- All right. Let's move.
Time's on their side
not on ours.
It sure as shit
is not on Doug's.
Let's do it.
Get that pool table over here.
Barricade it, all right?
Come on!
Fred.
Hey.
Listen.
You and me both know
this ain't the only option.
We can push Miss Teen USA
right back out the front door
the way she came in.
Is that the man you want to be,
Walter?
Well...
All right. Look.
I got your six.
Get to your truck
and get your ass to
the police station ricky-ticky.
Hey, uh, you said something
a little while ago.
It was like, uh, "Oh, you should
have seen that bastard
when we were over there.
- He was alive."
- Yeah.
I'll tell you something,
brother.
I'm feeling pretty fucking alive
right now.
Yeah.
We're trying to stay that way.
God damn it.
Aah! Aah!
Give it back.
What?
Give... it... back.
I don't know
what you're talking about!
Then you die.
Come on, bitch!
Come on!
Fred.
Fred, you all right?
Yeah, yeah.
Hey.
- Appreciate it, Walter.
- Jesus.
Really appreciate it.
Shit. That was...
Oh, shit.
- All right.
- I got the one on the left.
Fred! Walter!
Come on!
These things are crawling
all over the place!
Come on!
Fuck.
Oh, Jesus.
Oh, my God.
You got a piece.
I do.
You're good with it.
75th Ranger Regiment, sir.
Some of the guys
took to calling me Dead Eye.
That is a clever moniker.
Well... Dead Eye, I'm...
...I'm glad you were in the mood
for a beer tonight.
That makes one of us.
Now what?
Now the girl talks.
Two hours and nothing.
Don't you think the police
would have heard something?
What? In this neighborhood?
Gunshots are like crickets.
It's like background noise.
Cavalry ain't coming, Lou.
It's Q&A time, kid.
Sit!
What's your name?
Elizabeth.
Call me Lizard.
Well, my name is Fred.
And see, the problem is
that me and my old friends
are probably gonna die tonight
unless you help us out
to understand
what's happening here.
Couple minutes ago,
some woman tried to kill me
in the parking lot.
But what really pissed me off
is that bitch trashed my truck,
and, Lizard,
I really, really love my truck.
She also said to me,
"Give it back."
What's that supposed to mean?
She didn't say, "Give her back,"
or, "Give Lizard back."
No, no.
She said, "Give it back."
So what is "it"?
Huh?
Hard case.
When she came in...
anybody see?...
was she carrying something
with her?
- Not that I saw.
- No, I didn't see shit, man.
I was busy focusing on this jerk
trying to cut off Doug's arm.
Why don't you quit
this true-grit bullshit
and just throw her out the door?
I mean, maybe you got this
merciful stuff still in you,
but I don't have it in my body
anymore.
Now, you...
- Hey. Whoa.
- ...you speak, honey,
or I'm gonna lace
right into you.
You're not gonna lace
into anybody.
- This is my joint, all right?
- Neither are you, man.
Fuck!
Shit!
All right. All right.
It's nothing.
All right?
Sorry.
Go on.
Clean yourself up.
Your own fault!
- It's his own fault.
- Yeah.
Give me some good news.
Eliminated one man.
Couldn't get inside.
Where's Roadie?
He's dead.
Bartender shot him.
Yeah.
That's when you used to be fine,
Fred.
Shit.
Well.
Hey.
Little Miss Bo Peep here,
she's been playing
hide-and-seek with us.
Oh.
Geez.
God.
How much is this?
That is a whole fuckin' lot.
That's what that is.
It's enough
to kill the kid over.
Hey.
Did you steal this?
Boz killed my sister, all right?
This, though, it's all he's got,
this whole fucking life.
Well, there it is...
We just give this back,
and the nightmare ends, and then
we can go to the titty bar,
- where we're supposed to be.
- It doesn't work like that.
That guy over there
with the exploded fucking head,
that's Roadie,
Boz's little brother.
"VFW."
What the fuck is that?
Veterans of Foreign Wars.
Soldiers?
Good.
Soldiers are good at dying.
You guys murdered
his little brother.
- Now, Boz won't stop until he...
- Killed every one of us, right?
Yeah, and your kids
and your grandkids
and... your great-grandkids.
Jesus Christ.
How fuckin' old are you guys?
Screw you, bitch.
Oh, pump the brakes
on the old-guy stuff, all right?
I don't know about this murder.
Could be manslaughter.
He came in with a big damn ax.
Jesus Christ, Walter!
What the hell is the difference?
I feel like I'm in
the twilight zone, okay?
Because this little girl here,
this little child,
she is dictating to us
what's gonna go down!
Maybe your sister,
maybe that little junkie
- deserved to fucking get it.
- Shut your fucking mouth!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Knock it off!
Hey!
This is my post, my rules.
You don't like it, then
walk the hell out of here, huh?
- Let's put her outside the...
- Crying out loud!
Shut up, Lou.
Hey.
Here.
You were a soldier.
You were a good soldier.
So were we all, weren't we?
So let's act like it.
We set a perimeter.
We make our stand.
Remember the Alamo.
Yeah, but they all died
at the Alamo.
- Yeah.
- Dumb shit.
All right.
I got nine rounds
for the 12-gauge.
- Ranger?
- I got three left in the .45.
I got a big damn fire ax,
and Doug can attest
to the effectiveness of that.
So, what do you think, kid?
It's not enough.
We'd better get to work.
Hey.
How are you with this?
No, I got this.
I got this.
You sure?
They didn't get
my trigger finger.
Huh.
Be good to me, Gordie.
Ooh, boy.
Right up his ass.
Bring 'em.
This little piggy went
to market.
I don't want to tell you
where that one's gonna go.
Here we go. Little more.
Little more. Little more.
See, the trick is to get
the snap and the flick
all in one very cool...
very fluid motion.
I used to be good at it,
but, uh, my fingers
are getting kind of stiff.
This place is kind of gross.
This place is our VFW Post 2494.
What's that mean?
It means it's... a home.
At least for me, it is.
And for the rest of these bums.
See, when we got back from Nam,
we just kind of gravitated,
you know, washed up here
like some kind of a tide.
There used to be more of us.
There used to be a lot more
of us, but...
What was it like over there?
- Nam?
- Yeah.
I remember the mud.
And the crawling in the mud.
A lot of men died in the mud.
I hated the fucking mud.
Now, uh, Abe, you know, he's...
Ow.
You know, he's the, uh,
old sourpuss
with all the charm
of a clawhammer.
He wasn't in Nam.
Nah.
He's Korea.
Different war, same shit.
Same mud?
Yeah.
Same mud, except his was frozen.
Yeah, and Old Ranger Rick...
you know, Shawn...
he just got back
from the desert.
No mud over there.
Just a whole shitload of sand.
Don't matter where you fought.
You make it back,
you got a home right here.
You ready?
Don't get killed
by those antlers.
They'll poke your eyeballs out.
Yeah. No problem.
No problem.
All right.
Don't kill them all at once,
now.
Fuck it.
Now I'm not gonna leave
any of them for you.
I like the sound of that,
Gordie.
Hey. Here.
I got something for you.
Ooh.
You know,
I think we're gonna be fine
as long as they come at us
on skates.
Well...
I imagine we're gonna have
some company any time now,
so why don't you get yourself
behind the bar
and look out for Doug?
No, no, no.
I can... I can help.
No doubt.
You'll be helping
by looking out for Doug.
And if shit goes sideways...
I'll kill them.
I knew you were a hard case.
Come on, motherfucker.
Ah.
Let 'em come.
Here we go.
- I got to help!
- Relax. Relax.
- T-They're my friends!
- They're gonna be all right.
You're good. Just relax.
Get to the grenades!
- Yeah. I got this.
- Get it out!
- Light that for me, will you?
- No. That's not good for you.
Oh, come on.
Are you fucking kidding me, kid?
It's medical.
- Are we winning?
- Yeah.
Your friends are kicking ass.
Aah!
Hey!
Come on, Lou!
Jesus Christ.
Sorry, Gordie.
A little... A little help here.
Fuckin' hippie.
Here.
You dropped this.
Aah!
Oh. Whoa. I got you.
I got you.
What, you're my fucking savior
now?
Now I got blood and pickled
pork shit on my jacket.
Well, you look good.
Thanks.
Hey.
You're gonna have
to walk it off.
- Yeah, yeah. Fuck you, man.
- Take a seat right there.
Everybody in one piece?
Well, let me check.
Yep.
Oh, shit.
Come on.
- Oh, God. Hey. Good j...
- You all right?
Oh, good job.
I'll tell you.
That son of bitch
stoved my chest in.
Any more of these
prehistoric creatures
coming through that door?
Get those doors barricaded.
Let's use those bodies
as sandbags, all right?
- Yes, sir.
- Come on.
It's taking too long.
The old men must have killed
Tank.
Fuck.
Sun's up soon.
If we don't get inside,
it's over.
Load up.
Heavy stuff.
Hard stuff.
I'm tired
of fucking playing games.
Thanks for saving my life,
Elizabeth.
I started this.
Let's finish it.
Hey. Hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey. Look at me.
You only winged him.
Are you losing your touch?
Don't... Don't make...
Don't make me laugh.
It... It hurts a lot.
Oh.
I think it's time to call
this game.
- No way, brother.
- One more for the road.
I'll give you one more,
but... it's not for the road.
It's for my birthday, remember?
It's my birthday.
Well, listen.
I'm older than you.
Y-You got to listen to me
right now, so...
- Happy birthday.
- Yes.
You're all right.
Hey, kid.
You know what I said, uh,
when you first came in?
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, when you get to be my age,
people don't really give a shit
what you say.
I'll just be ready.
I'd like the chance to get
to your age, old man.
- Lou.
- Yeah.
You know that bag she brought
in here full of shit?
Yeah.
What if you had all of that
in cash?
Cash.
Cold, hard cash.
What would you do with that?
- You know what I'd do...
- Mm?
...with all those funds
from that garbage?
Yeah.
I'd buy each one of us
a really nice casket...
gold trim, extra cushion,
Tempur-Pedic foam.
Uh-huh.
The best money could buy
so that we'd all be cozy,
like two little bears in a glen,
after we die.
You know what?
Your foxhole chitchat
needs work.
Jesus.
Fuck.
Lou's sliding off the deep end.
He's gonna be Section 8
any minute now.
We got to hold him.
No. No, no.
That ain't the way.
Look, those fuckers,
they got to be hurting, too.
I'm gonna go out there.
I'm gonna make a run for it.
- Fred. Oh, wait a minute.
- I'm gonna make a lot of noise.
I'm gonna draw them off,
and you get Doug to my truck
and get him
the hell out of here.
Fred, you ain't gonna make it
two blocks
without them being all over you.
Well, Walter, you telling me
you got a better idea?!
Dougie's dying on the bar!
You think I'm gonna let him
just bleed out there?
- That ain't gonna happen!
- Fred! Fred! Fred!
- Oh, shit.
- The fuck is this?
Fred!
You piece of shit!
What the fuck do you think
you're doing?
Give it back!
Hey! Hey! Knock it off.
Knock it off.
- What's going on? Stop it.
- Give it back!
What's going on?
I can negotiate us
out of this mess.
- No.
- I can.
I can do what you can't do.
Just... Just have a little faith
in me, okay?
- Lou.
- Just this once.
Lou, you, uh...
That bag is the only thing
that's keeping us alive, right?
You give that up,
they'll torch this place
like a matchbox.
You understand that, don't you?
Good man.
All right.
Whew!
What a day, huh?
Listen. Why don't you secure
the door and come on over here?
Let's have a...
Let's have a shot, huh?
I'm getting too old
for this shit.
I'll tell you that.
Hey! Hey! Lou!
Where the hell are you going,
man?
I'll be back.
After all...
we got a birthday to celebrate.
Lou!
Lou, wait!
He's out of his fucking mind.
He's a used-car salesman.
Yeah. He's got that goddamn
pussy party on his brain.
Let's make a deal.
Let's close a deal.
I mean... how can I get you
in this car today, huh?
Sure.
Hey.
I'm... I'm not armed.
I came to have a conversation
man-to-man.
So... what's your offer?
Easy exchange.
We'll give you back your, uh...
you know, your drugs.
You can go on your way and...
and we'll go on ours.
Intriguing.
Ultimately unacceptable
but intriguing.
There's only one
satisfactory solution,
and that is we get our product
back and each of you die.
Um... how about meet me halfway?
I mean, negotiate with me.
This is what I do.
Y-You know Lou's Used?
Maybe you've seen some of my,
um, my ads on TV.
The little blond girl saying,
"Want something ..."
"You need something new?
Call Lou."
I'm Lou.
That's me.
I'm not familiar.
Mind if we talk honestly
for a second?
Um...
A friend inside there
has, uh, has kind of lost it.
I mean, he thinks he's still
the... the platoon commander
back in the fuckin' jungles,
you know?
Ugh.
So he's in charge?
Well, not really.
I mean, he... he's kind of
in charge there, but...
but, I mean, I carry a lot
of weight, too, you know?
- But I'm here talking to you.
- Shh. Shh. Shh. Shh.
There's no negotiating.
However...
you may yet prove useful.
Fred!
Your friend likes to talk!
And you?
Will you now talk?
Send out the girl and the bag,
and I send him back!
Fred, what's up?
Give me the bag.
This is the last time
I talk to you!
Last time!
They're gonna kill both of you.
Fred, they're gonna
kill you both!
Your call, Fred!
This what you want?!
You let him go!
Shit, Lou.
Come on.
If you want this,
you let my friend go!
Fuck.
Fuck it.
Kill him.
Fred, on your left!
Lou!
Aah! Aah!
Fred!
Go!
- Oh, shit!
- Fred, come on.
Give me that leg.
Easy, easy, easy, easy.
All right.
Come on.
- All right. Oh, shit.
- Come on. Set him down.
- Set him down.
- All right. Let me go.
There you go.
Can we get a...
Hey, give me that.
Here. Make that.
Okay?
- There we go.
- Ow!
- Shit.
- It's all right.
Hey!
Fucking Lou.
Doug?
Doug, talk to me, man.
Oh, shit.
He's dead.
Call in the 92 Mikes.
Watch yourself. Watch yourself.
I'll tell you what.
If I'm gonna, uh,
go into the abyss...
...just as soon go out
on a buzz.
I'll see you down the road,
brother.
Fuckin' Lou.
Fuckin' moron.
What the fuck was that about?
It's done, man.
Ain't over till it's over.
Shit!
Fuck.
- Hey.
- This is bullshit.
You're bullshit.
I want to live.
We all want to fuckin' life.
We need you together, not drunk.
This is about as together
as I'm gonna get, all right?
Don't give up now.
- Look.
- Come on.
I'm sorry.
I... I don't know what to do.
We're done.
You had ways out.
You did.
But you chose to fight.
You asked for this fight.
And your friends,
they followed you
because they believed in you.
But now...
Now you're just a pussy.
Some mouth you got on you.
You know that?
Did you get that
from your dead sister, too? Huh?
You want to drink yourself
to death?
Go right a-fuckin'-head.
All right.
Fire it up.
We move without him.
I don't like it any more
than you do,
but getting home
is the priority.
"We"?
Who put you in charge?
If you don't have a better idea,
Walter, shut the fuck up.
Hey, assholes,
you're not helping anything.
Well, have you got an idea?
'Cause we could sure as hell use
a light-bulb moment
right about now, lady.
It's for you that we're doing
all of this.
Hey, I never asked
for your goddamn help, Gramps.
You didn't have to!
That's the point!
The second you walked through
that door,
we were duty-bound to help you!
Of course, you'd never get that
through your thick
fuckin' skull.
I'm supposed to be
at the titty bar right now.
You know, great big silicone
melons right in my fuckin' face!
Yeah. Sorry to ruin
your big fuckin' evening.
Well, sorry don't feed
the bulldog, boy.
Hey, ladies, I hate to interrupt
your party-planning session
right now,
but we got more urgent matters
to tend to.
Damn it! All the shit
I've been through in my life!
I'm gonna be put tits up
by a bunch of goddamn junkies!
Fuckin' chill out...
Oh, shut up, all of you!
Let's go.
Why not?
Oh, is that you, Mr. Fred?
Pleased to make
your acquaintance.
I know hindsight's 20/20,
but...
...you should have dealt
for him.
You know,
inside that little hole,
I can see just a small bit
of you.
But I know what's in there.
You regretting every single
decision you've made today.
You've got it all wrong, son.
I don't regret a thing.
I lost my friends.
Well, that's not right.
You took my friends.
But I guess they knew
what they signed up for now.
I don't regret a goddamn thing.
Matter of fact...
right about now,
I'm feeling real eager.
So whatever you're gonna do,
quit flapping your gums
and do it.
But when you come, boy,
you come sharp,
'cause you make a mistake...
...I'm gonna cut your heart out.
- Fred, that lamp propane.
- Yeah.
It's gonna blow.
We'd better hunker down.
Don't you think?
Yeah.
Hey, uh, Dead Eye.
You know how to waltz?
Waltz?
'Cause I'm gonna need you
to follow my lead.
He's back.
This ain't gonna be enough.
A victory is not a victory
if everybody dies.
Not in my mind.
It's been a real honor serving
with you men.
A real honor.
Hey!
- Jesus!
- Hey!
Holy Christ.
Come on.
Hunker down. Come on.
Hey. Hey, hey, hey, old man.
Look at me. Look at me.
Hey.
Move it, Fred.
I'm taking point this time.
Move it!
Come on, Fred.
Come on.
Let's see what all this rumblin'
is about.
Come on, ladies!
I got something for you.
Hello, friend.
Perhaps now we can finally
be civil.
You killed three of my friends.
That's not civil.
Oh. Well, that was just
a misunderstanding.
You're all... or were...
soldiers, right?
This whole place was built
on murder.
No.
Well, I suppose murder
is subjective.
Not really.
You enjoy it, don't you...
the killing?
Well, I got to admit...
I did get kind of a charge
out of...
...blowing your brother's
fucking head off.
Give me the bag now...
...and I promise you all...
a quick death.
Or we'll just take it from you,
and you'll all die
very, very slowly.
You last so you can watch
Lizard die.
Okay.
You win.
Get off me, you fuckin' animals!
Hey!
- Come on!
- Get out, Fred.
I can handle these assholes.
Nobody's gonna take this ridge!
- Look what I found.
- Jesus Christ.
Abe!
They're gonna feel the might
of the American military!
All right.
Hey! Look out, kid!
I got this!
Yeah!
So you're the bitch
that killed Z, right?
Oh, that's real scary shit.
Didn't your mother ever tell you
not to steal?!
Ow!
Fuck you!
Come on.
- Come on.
- I'm good.
I'm good. I'm good!
Go on!
Fred, come on!
- Hey, where's the girl?
- I'm coming. I'm coming.
God damn it.
She was here.
No!
You can't go back for her!
You look out for Walter.
- You empty?
- Yeah.
Okay. Take that.
I'm sick of the damn thing.
- All right!
- I'll catch up. I'll catch up.
Shit.
They slashed his tires.
Oh, shit.
The deuce-and-a-half.
Now.
- Will it run?
- It will if I tell it to.
No!
Let me go!
Oh, shit.
Are you ready to die...
old man?
Good shit.
Thanks. Thanks. Yeah.
I had the bitch, though.
Come on.
Hey, Walter?
- Huh?
- This thing got any ammo?
The .50-cal?
No.
- Walter, hurry up!
- Come on.
What's taking so long?
Goddamn impatient millennials!
You know something, Fred?
What's that?
I like this place.
I'm glad to hear that.
Turn around.
Give me that.
Fred!
Shit.
I'll be back.
Walter!
Hurry the fuck up!
Did you ever try to pee with
somebody watching you like that?
Come on, baby.
Aah!
Shawn!
Fuck!
Aah!
Aah! Aah!
- Hey, hey. Hey, hey.
- Oh, shit.
- Oh...
- Hey, you with me?
Yeah. I've had better days.
Oh, fuck.
That looks like it's gonna
do it, doesn't it?
No, sir. No, sir. Move over.
I'm getting us out of here.
Not on your life.
Where's Fred?
Oh.
Look at that son of a bitch.
He's slower than quail shit.
No! Fuck you!
Shoot.
Take peace in this, kid...
You and your sister
were only separated by...
I ain't gonna make it, kid.
I know that.
This is the end of the line.
You're a good kid,
and you're a good soldier.
Now, you go home and take care
of that wife of yours.
That's an order.
I got this.
We're not done.
No.
No, I suppose we're not.
Well, Mr. Fred...
...I believe we have
ourselves... a situation.
Come on, baby. Come on!
Yes!
Hey, Fred!
This is the last goddamn time
I'm gonna bail your ass out!
Hyah!
You in one piece?
Yeah, just about.
You two all right?
Walter?
One of those punks got him
real good.
He wasn't gonna make it.
God damn, Walter.
You old fool.
Hey, Fred?
Ranger, I think it's about time
we had one beer for the road.
You're a real bastard.
You know that?
You got it?
Yeah, I got it.
Abe!
Hey.
Hey, Abe.
Well, at least he died
doing something he liked to do.
Who the fuck said I was dead?
- Fuck!
- Jesus.
Don't do that.
Doug.
Z.
Lou.
Walter.
And Lucy.
And Abe.
Well, shit.
What do you figure
this is worth?
A whole lot.
Enough to fix the place up
and more.
Happy birthday, old man.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org