Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
[light dramatic music]
♪♪
[doorknob clicks]
[door buzzer sounding]
Oh, they, uh,
they put that system in
a few years ago
after a break-in.
Oh, don't worry.
Neighborhood's a lot
safer now.
[birds chirping]
[wind chimes sounding]
[gate door closing]
Enchantée!
Enchantée.
Are you okay?
Oh.
Are you alright,
Miss Stanhope?
Thank you, I'm fine,
I'm fine.
I just...
just a little wobbly.
Thank you, my dear.
Too kind.
Of course.
[crowd conversing]
We're not first-come,
first-serve.
Doesn't hurt
to take a look.
I'm Jerry.
I'm the manager.
Just give a shout
if you have a question.
Are there a lot of dogs
in the building?
Yeah, it's a pet-free,
smoke-free complex.
Alrighty.
Local contact?
Yeah, I just moved here.
I don't really know anyone.
Okay, that's no problem.
What brought you to LA?
I guess I'm trying
to start a new life.
That sounds ridiculous.
I don't know.
No, not at all.
It's a good city for that.
Oh, you, uh,
missed one here.
Any pets?
No.
Okay.
[cat purring]
Very helpful, Giles.
Mm.
[cat purring]
Okay.
[cellphone vibrating]
Hi.
[on phone]
There you are.
Haven't you been
getting my calls?
I've been busy.
When are you
coming home?
[on phone]
I'm staying.
I got a job.
[on phone]
Making costumes?
Already?
No, Dad, I'm...
I'm working as a temp.
At a law firm.
It's just for now.
[on phone] I'm gonna start taking
extension classes next quarter.
You know, I don't know if
you're trying to punish me
or punish Diane.
- But your mother certainly would not have wanted you...
- Don't.
Dad, please don't.
I just worry about you,
sweetie.
Do you really think you can
do this all by yourself?
I don't know.
I guess I'll find out.
[on phone]
Well, dammit, I'm...
Come on, you know
I didn't mean that...
Dad, I have to go.
I'll talk to you later,
okay? Bye.
[distant police siren]
[cat meowing]
[keyboard clicking]
Lisa.
Lisa, I asked you
to renumber the footnotes
for each section.
No, you didn't.
Are you calling me a liar?
You want me
to renumber them?
Just ask.
You don't have to pretend
I fucked up.
Give me half an hour.
Oh, and I'm leaving
at three.
I'm up for a sitcom.
Enjoy the show?
Sorry.
Sweetie,
I'm just fucking with you.
I'm Lisa.
You the new temp?
- Sarah.
- Good to meet you.
I'll introduce you
around later.
[whispers]
I know everyone.
[laughs]
Thanks.
[cellphone vibrating]
Hello?
Yes, this is she.
Really?
[light piano music]
♪♪
[cat meowing]
Shut up, okay?
We're almost there.
- [door closing]
- Hey!
You got it!
We're neighbors.
Oh, I'm...
I'm Brian.
I'm Sarah.
Um...
Let's do an elbow bump.
- [laughs] Good to meet you.
- Good to meet you.
Um, hey listen,
we're having a barbecue.
You should come.
Yeah, I'll try.
Um, I got a bunch
of stuff to bring in.
Hang on.
Hey, guys,
- you wanna give us a hand?
- Yeah, sure!
Um, yeah,
let me just run... I'll...
Give me a second, okay?
Okay.
How lovely our barbecue
has turned out to be
a welcome party for you.
Enchantée.
Here they are.
Our power couple.
[couple laughing]
Oliver is a big-time attorney,
and Esther is an even
bigger-time doctor.
This is Jessica.
She just moved in
on the second floor.
Sarah.
Oh.
I'm sorry, Sarah.
I just...
No, I'm terrible
with names, too.
It's nice
to meet you both.
Welcome.
We're so glad to have
you in the building.
Gettin' settled in okay?
- Sure you don't need anything?
- Leave her alone.
She doesn't need us
pestering her.
Sorry.
We'll stay out
of your hair.
Oh, no, it's okay.
Everyone's been really nice.
Good. Good.
We like to make this place
feel like a real neighborhood.
- Mm.
- It's great.
Yeah, it seems like
most places these days,
people don't even bother
to learn each other's names.
Oh, speaking of which,
our daughter Natalie...
Natalie!
I saw that.
What's the first rule?
Sorry.
- [exhales]
- Kids.
Medium rare?
You should read this.
I... what?
It changed my life.
Oh, um.
That's okay.
Thanks.
Hey.
Did you have a good time?
Yeah.
I still can't believe
I got it.
Out of all those people.
What?
I might have, uh, put in
a good word with Jerry.
All I did is tell him what
you did for Miss Stanhope.
Does she have family?
Just us.
We all kind of take care
of each other here.
I love that.
LA can be so...
Lonely.
I should go.
Unpacking.
Of course.
Well, um,
goodnight, neighbor.
Goodnight, neighbor.
Miss Stanhope?
- Can I walk you home?
- Oh.
Well, only if
you'll call me Edie.
We're friends, aren't we?
This is you?
You're beautiful.
Di... did you see it?
It was a terrible picture.
I was an awful actress.
I'm so much happier now.
I have such wonderful
neighbors.
You and me both.
[distant indistinct
conversation]
[distant gate banging]
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
[plumbing rattles]
[gasps]
[pipes rattling]
[water whirring]
Zoloft.
Fifty milligrams.
Well, when can
I get a refill?
Okay, thanks.
Hey, I got it,
I got it, I got it.
Oh, no, you don't...
you don't have to...
Moving is exhausting.
Yeah, I didn't sleep well.
Oh, yeah?
Does the plumbing
do that every night?
Do what?
Do you wanna
open the door?
Oh, no. No.
I... I got from here.
- Thanks.
- You... you sure?
Um, uh, okay.
Um, I'm just down the hall.
[sighs]
Giles, you are really
messing with my love life.
Stupid cat.
[plumbing pipes rattle]
[sighs]
Giles?
Giles, come on, buddy.
I need cuddles.
Giles?
[exhales]
[plumbing rattling]
[gasps]
[footsteps approaching]
Edie!
Edie?
Edie, what are you doing?
I... I'm okay.
[exhales]
Thank you.
[pill box clicking]
I'll refill this every week
so you don't have
to worry about it.
Are you sure
you don't mind?
I'm an expert.
I used to do this
for my mom.
Where can I put these so
you'll remember to take them?
Oh, just put 'em up
on the counter.
Did that guy
give you this?
Hmm?
What guy?
That creepy guy
with the weird glasses.
You know, he tried to
give me this at the party.
Oh, you mean Lester.
Oh, he's not creepy,
he's just a little bit sad.
He recently lost
his wife to cancer.
Just lovely, lovely lady.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know.
I didn't mean to...
I'm just tired is all.
Do you hear that noise
that the pipes make at night?
Oh, honey, I don't hear
anything very well anymore.
[laughs]
[pipes rattling]
Oh, you've gotta
be fucking kidding me.
[sighs]
[rattling intensifies]
[grunts]
[groans in pain]
[on phone message]
Sarah, it's Dad.
Give me a call back
when you get this.
Listen, I'm glad
you found a place.
I'm concerned, you don't
seem to have much of a plan
beyond these
extension classes.
Alright, listen,
I'm gonna find time,
I'll fly out...
[cat meows]
[eerie music builds]
♪♪
Hey.
Hey!
- [door closes]
- Hey!
I'm, uh,
glad I caught you.
You okay?
Just tired.
Uh, what's up?
Um, I'm having a dinner party
later tonight around seven.
Uh, you wanna join us?
I... I don't know.
Oh. Um, o-o-okay.
Uh, no pressure.
I... it was,
uh, short notice.
No, it sounds...
it sounds really great.
- I'll be there.
- Yeah?
Well, alright.
Then I'll see you
tonight then, neighbor.
[distant phone ringing]
[mouse clicking]
Sarah.
Check your e-mail.
I got two more reports
from accounting.
Uh, could I do them
first thing in the morning?
- I just...
- No, today.
But, clock out first.
We can't pay
overtime on this.
Mm-kay?
Sure.
Hey.
Fuck that
hatchet-faced bitch.
[laughs]
I don't know why
I can't just...
God, I'm so tired.
You do look like dog shit.
[laughs]
Thanks.
It's my fucking apartment.
I thought you
loved that place.
Hot neighbor guy?
You like Thai food?
Yeah, I...
Oh, shit.
I was supposed
to go to this.
Doesn't matter.
It's fine.
There you are.
Hey.
I'm sorry.
I forgot I already
had other plans.
Oh.
Uh, don't worry about it.
Uh, we're gonna be having
dessert a little later
if you wanna stop by.
Yeah.
Maybe.
Okay.
Is that the guy?
[chuckles]
He's cute.
[whispers]
Oh, Giles.
That's disgusting.
- You think I'm crazy.
- No.
[chuckles]
I don't know.
Maybe?
It looks kinda great.
No, I know.
- It's just normally the pipes would be...
- Did you do these?
They're really good.
Oh, shit.
What?
I was supposed to...
God, I completely forgot.
I... I missed the deadline
for the extension program.
I'm so fucking tired
all the time,
and I can't get
my prescription,
and I keep getting
these headaches, and...
and my neighbor is
gonna report my cat,
so then I'll have
no one left to talk to.
Hey, it's okay.
You can always pet my head.
[laughs]
Maybe fucking asshole
Dad is right,
and I should just go home.
No.
That's some horseshit.
I don't know.
I was always
such a daddy's girl.
You would've hated me.
Probably.
He bought you a Lexus.
[laughs]
Yeah, well,
I paid for it.
The shit he put me through.
Cheatin' on your mom?
[swallows] There was
more to it than that.
You know what?
Doesn't matter.
Fuck your dad.
He doesn't get to tell you
what you're capable of.
You just gotta sack up
and do whatever it takes
to make it.
Sack up?
Hashtag sexist.
Ovary up, whatever.
[chuckles]
Fallopian up.
Vag up.
You gotta fucking vag up,
okay?
[laughs]
You don't like this place?
Break the fucking lease.
Shit, you and I should
get a place together.
There's always gonna be
dads and Cristinas
who say "You can't do this"
and "You gotta do that."
- You just can't let them get...
- Hey, how do you do that with Cristina?
Stand up to her?
I would just...
I would be so afraid.
It's pretty simple.
I just remind myself
that it's my fucking life.
My fucking life.
Yeah, it is, girlfriend.
[faint metal squeaking]
[exhales]
[sniffing]
[grunts]
[groans in pain]
[smoke alarm beeping]
[exhales]
[tense music builds]
♪♪
[breathes quickly]
[gasps]
[whimpers]
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
[gasps]
[muffled screaming]
Help! Help!
- [shushes]
- Please stop!
[gasping]
[grunting]
[ties zipping]
No, no, no, no!
Lester?
Please.
Lester,
please don't do this.
[alarm stops]
Wait, what are you doing?
Help! Help!
Help!
[groans]
Help! Help!
[grunting]
[panting]
[sighs]
God damn it.
Fucking Ikea.
[grunts]
[groans in pain]
[grunting in effort]
Help!
I need help!
[gasping]
[yelling in fright]
- Sarah?
- Esther, please!
You have to... run.
Run!
- Brian, what the hell is going on?
- Nothing!
Everything's fine.
Oh, no don't let him
get close to you.
It's all under control.
She's not going anywhere.
[gasps]
[grunting]
[taser buzzing]
[groans in pain]
Help me!
Please!
Somebody help me!
This is why we do
the dinner party.
It's such a bad
way to start.
It's not my fault.
She said she would come.
- I told you we were rushing things.
- We had to.
- She was about to move out.
- That's enough.
No harm done.
Everything's fine.
Go back to bed.
What's happening?
Why won't anybody help me?
[gasps]
Oh.
We are helping you.
[distant metal squeaking]
[pipes thud]
[breathes heavily]
Help! Help!
[pipe rattle intensifies]
Hello?
Somebody please help!
[footsteps approaching]
[lock clicking]
[door squeaks open]
Save your voice.
Nobody can hear you.
Please,
please just let me go.
You can't do this.
You can't just keep me here.
Of course we can.
Yesterday,
you quit your job.
You closed your bank account,
your credit cards.
You cut ties
with the few people
who might care
that you're gone.
[on phone message]
Hey!
What's goin' on Sarah?
You know what?
I got your message
loud and clear.
And congratulations.
Whatever you said to Cristina
almost got me fired, too.
You want me
out of your business?
Stay the fuck out of mine,
you two-faced,
crazy ass bi...
Sarah,
no one's coming for you.
[inhales]
Why are you
doing this to me?
Let's get on with it.
Face the wall.
Put your hands on the wall.
Right there.
Oh, no.
No, no. Please.
Brian, please, no.
You don't have to do this.
Please. Please.
[gasps]
Wait.
Let me show you something.
This program's very simple.
You comply,
you get rewarded.
If you don't...
[pounding on door]
you get punished.
So, it's really up to you
how it goes.
Most people take to the
conditioning right away.
Lester, on the other hand,
was resistant.
That was for attacking me.
And that was for
trying to escape.
You get the idea.
You ready to do
what you're told?
Good.
Face the wall.
[inhales]
Put your hands
on the wall.
[inhales]
Step back.
Further.
Further!
Look at the wall.
This is a stress position.
It's designed to be painful.
In a few minutes
it'll start to hurt.
In an hour,
it'll seem unbearable.
When those lights are on,
you do not move,
no matter what.
When they turn off,
you can rest.
You see that?
Up there?
We'll be watching you.
This is for your own good.
- Someday you'll understand.
- [inhales]
And you'll thank me.
[door slams shut]
[shaky breathing]
Gonna get out.
My fucking life.
[exhales]
[whimpers]
[music over PA]
♪ There's a certain sound ♪
♪ Always follows me around ♪
♪ When you're close to me
You will hear it ♪
♪ It's the sound that lovers ♪
♪ It's my happy
heart you hear ♪
♪ Singing loud
and singing clear ♪
♪ And it's all because
you're near me, my love ♪
♪ Take my happy heart away ♪
♪ Let me love you night
and day In your arms ♪
♪ Music fills my soul now ♪
[distorted singing]
♪ I've lost all control now ♪
[exhales]
[breathes heavily]
[footsteps approaching]
[door hatch clicking]
[eerie music building]
♪♪
[buzzer sounds]
[door lock clicking]
[door creaks open]
How you holding up, dear?
What is this?
Jerry said that you
needed a friend.
His process
isn't a lot of fun.
But if I got through it,
anyone can.
[laughs]
You?
Well, of course.
Everyone here started exactly
where you are right now.
Edie, this is crazy.
No, it isn't, missy.
Crazy is hiding an animal
where it doesn't belong
with no regard
for your neighbors.
Crazy is poisoning yourself
with alcohol and pills
to forget your loneliness.
Crazy is throwing away
your only family
for a selfish fantasy.
It's not crazy.
It's science.
Jerry knows exactly how
to fix bad conditioning.
[buzzer sounds]
♪ It's my happy
heart you hear ♪
♪ Singing loud
and singing clear ♪
[lights buzzing] ♪ And it's all
because you're near me, my love ♪
[distorted singing]
[lights buzzing]
You've gotta stop fighting.
You're just making it worse.
It's science.
[buzzer sounds]
A selfish fantasy.
Selfish fantasy.
[buzzer sounds]
Jerry knows exactly
[echoes]
how to fix bad conditioning.
[buzzer sounds repeatedly]
Poor baby.
The sooner you give up,
[echoes]
the sooner you'll be free.
[thud]
[grunts]
The light is still on.
Oh, please, no.
I can't do this anymore.
Please.
I just want it to be over.
We can end it right now.
Oh.
Oh, no.
No, ple... please.
No.
I thought you
wanted it to be over.
[sobs]
[breathes heavily]
[eerie music pulsing]
♪♪
[breathing heavily]
Since you won't stay put
on your own,
we're gonna help you.
[gasps]
- Put your hand back.
- Oh, no.
Please!
I...
- Put it back.
- I promise I'll be good.
[inhales/exhales]
[screaming]
[gasping]
Oh, no.
Please.
I just wanna go home.
[cries]
[breathes heavily]
[dramatic music]
♪♪
[hammering]
[cries out]
[breathes heavily]
[groans in pain]
This is your home.
[door creaking open]
[door slams shut]
[whimpering]
[dramatic music]
♪♪
This program's very simple.
- Face the wall.
- It's really up to you how it goes.
It's designed
to be painful.
This is your home.
- You've gotta stop fighting.
- It's for your own good.
- How you holding up, dear?
- You comply...
- Face the wall.
- ...you get rewarded.
If you don't,
you get punished.
- His process is...
- ...designed to be painful.
- Sarah?
- Since you won't stay put on your own...
- Face the wall.
- Stop fighting.
- This is your home.
- It's designed...
- We're gonna help you.
- Sarah.
Sarah.
Dad?
- Is that...
- Shh.
- How are you...
- It's all right. Don't move.
I'm here.
I'm using the pipes.
I never believed their lies.
I'm taking you home,
honey.
All right, get ready.
Get ready...
get ready to run.
[footsteps approaching]
[door closing]
[distant banging]
Go!
Come on, sweetie,
you can do it!
- [grunts in pain]
- Yes.
Yes, that's it.
Come on, sweetheart.
I believe in you.
You're almost home!
[grunts in pain]
[breathes heavily]
[exhales]
[low eerie music]
♪♪
[buzzer sounds]
Stop.
Turn around.
Well done, Sarah.
I'm proud of you.
[shaky breathing]
♪♪
You were perfect.
Both hands clean
between the third
and fourth metacarpals.
She did do
a little tendon damage
when she pulled them out.
You'll be fine.
We'll take such good
care of you, my dear.
[birds chirping]
[slow dramatic music]
♪♪
Well?
Come on.
Come on in.
What's your sexual preference?
Um, men.
Heterosexual.
Tell us about your
first sexual experience.
Sarah.
Openness is one of the
foundations of our community.
We don't keep secrets.
So, tell us about your
first sexual experience.
[dramatic piano music]
♪♪
Pay attention.
Just observe.
See what we're all about.
You have to remember
what it's like out there.
Everybody in their own
separate world,
on their little devices.
Obsessed with themselves.
We have to be
better than that.
♪♪
We have to be there
for each other.
Our community has
to be strong enough,
powerful enough
to heal that world.
[door buzzer sounding]
[scoffs]
We can't change the world
without venturing into it.
Once we're ready
to handle it.
[piano music continues]
♪♪
Can you name the four
foundations for me?
Selflessness, openness,
acceptance, security.
Excellent.
Very good, Sarah.
Let's talk about
your father.
What happened
between you two?
You never talked or e-mailed
anybody about it.
Least not
that we could find.
I caught him cheating
on my mother
while she was dying.
Yes, we inferred that.
With her nurse.
I said I'd tell her
if they didn't stop.
And did they?
He knew I couldn't do it.
She was already so weak,
it would've...
[sighs]
She died thinking
he was a saint.
Sarah, do you want to be
a part of this community?
Yes.
Sarah.
No.
No, I'm sorry, Jerry.
I want to want it.
I... I'm trying.
I promise.
Please, pl...
It's alright.
You'll get there.
Let's move on.
[eerie music]
♪♪
[locks clicking]
[door creaks open]
[on monitor] It's time
to start contributing.
This way.
[on video]
Modern society is sick.
Greed, envy,
dishonesty, lust.
The vices that corrode society
all spring from one source.
Selfishness.
Well, isn't that just
human nature?
Of course it is.
But we have the technology
to change our nature.
We... we've had it
for decades.
Thorndike, Watson,
Pavlov, Skinner.
All we've lacked
is an understanding
of what to change to.
Until now.
Okay.
Uh, let's say I wanna
become this new,
improved human.
What do I do?
[chuckles]
You live by
four foundations.
First, and most importantly,
selflessness.
You always act in the best
interest of the community.
[dramatic piano music]
♪♪
Second, openness.
Secrets breed discord.
Third, acceptance.
Once an error
has been corrected...
it's already forgiven.
[piano music continues]
♪♪
Finally, security.
We're our best selves
when we know our
neighbors are watching.
♪♪
Well, fine,
but how is
the ordinary Joe
supposed to become
this perfect citizen?
It's not unlike childhood.
At first,
we only follow the rules
so we don't get spanked.
But soon enough,
living the foundations
becomes a habit.
Then it becomes
who we are.
And when that happens,
we will make of this world
a single, perfect community.
Free of loneliness,
free of poverty,
free of strife.
Why did you choose me?
Because you needed us.
I could tell
the moment we met.
And, we needed you.
Everybody here
has a role to play.
What's my role?
Let's see how far
we've come.
Do you want to be a part
of this community?
I...
I don't know.
I think you're ready
to take on
a little bit more
responsibility.
[door creaks open]
[door clicks shut]
[mouse clicking]
Who's watching us?
That's none
of our business.
Eyes back on your monitor.
[sighs]
Edie, she's...
[coughing]
[wheezing]
Esther.
How... how do we call Esther?
[phone dialing]
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, I agree.
Okay, I'll call you back.
I'm proud of you,
Sarah.
What you did for Edie,
that's what this
community's all about.
Edie, is this comfortable?
Can I get you anything?
Oh, no, dear.
I'm fine.
Hi, Edie.
How are you feeling?
Oh, I'm doing fine.
I'm so glad that you came.
Come on in,
my dears.
It's so good to see you.
Come on in, everybody.
Um, maybe I should go.
I feel like
I'm in the way here.
No, I want you
by my side for this, dear.
Edie asked me
to say a few words.
When I first arrived here
nine years ago,
Edie was the first person
to introduce herself.
As I know she was
for so many of you.
Of course, back then,
it wasn't Edie,
it was Miss Stanhope
until she told you otherwise.
[all laughing]
Edie,
you have been an essential
member of this community
for longer than most
of us have been here.
You have been a great friend,
and mother,
to all of us.
And we're gonna miss you.
So much.
[exhales]
[sniffs]
- You can't do this.
- [shushes]
She can't contribute
to the community anymore,
and we don't have
the resources
to take care of her.
I... I'll take care of her.
Just me.
That is not what
you're here for.
She knows this is what's
best for the community.
[gasps]
Don't ruin this.
[dramatic piano music]
♪♪
I'm so glad you're here.
Goodbye, my dears.
- Bye.
- Goodbye.
Goodbye, Edie.
[gas hissing]
[breathes heavily]
[dramatic music builds]
♪♪
When I got back from Iraq,
I was a mess.
At first,
I thought it was hell.
It took me years,
but I finally understood.
They saved my life.
When you let go
and embrace this community
with all your heart,
there is nothing we won't do
to make you happy.
You probably know
what I'm gonna ask next.
Sarah, do you want to be
a part of this community?
Yes.
[upbeat guitar music]
♪♪
♪ There'll be no strings
to bind your hands ♪
♪ Not if my love
can't bind your heart ♪
Kneel.
♪ And there's no need
to take a stand ♪
♪ For it was I
who chose to start ♪
♪ I see no reason
to take me home ♪
[torch hissing]
♪ I'm old enough
to face the dawn ♪
♪ Just call me angel
of the morning, angel ♪
[all cheering]
♪ Just touch my cheek
before you leave me, baby ♪
♪ Just call me angel
of the morning, angel ♪
I knew you'd make it.
[all]
Aw.
Welcome
to the community.
- Thank you.
- [laughs]
I told you you'd
thank me one day.
[laughs]
Come on,
let's party!
[all]
Yeah!
- [all cheering]
- Come on!
♪ Just call me angel ♪
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
We're so happy you're here.
It's just wonderful.
[laughs]
Everybody,
can I have your attention?
Sarah, I know you've
been anxious to know
how you're gonna
fit in here.
Six months ago,
we lost a beloved member
of our community to cancer.
You never got
to know Jessica,
but the minute Lester saw you,
he said to me
that you seemed, uh...
How'd you put it?
"S... smart and kind
like my Jessie."
Come here, you two.
Come on.
Sarah,
Lester is as selfless a person
as I have ever known.
He's gonna take
good care of you.
And Lester,
I know how hard it's been
on you losing Jessica.
But we all saw how devoted
Sarah was to Edie.
She's a perfect fit
for the community
and for you.
Y'all are gonna make
a great couple.
Great parents.
Well, go on.
Come on.
[all cheering]
[whispering]
Let's go home.
What... what about
my apartment?
It's not your apartment.
It's for new candidates.
Come here.
[dramatic music]
♪♪
Come here.
[rapid footsteps approach]
Sarah.
We have a problem.
Fourth foundation.
You know what
has to happen.
[cellphone vibrating]
Unless you can make him leave
and never come back.
[on phone] Sarah,
I need to talk to you.
[on phone]
I'm at work.
[phone disconnects]
Come back at six.
[dramatic music]
♪♪
[door closes]
Sarah.
He's here.
[knocking on door]
[knocking continues]
Sarah, you...
What happened to you?
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
What do you want?
I know, y-y-you
don't want to see me,
but I... [sighs]
Oh, dammit,
I don't want things
to be like this between us.
You think I care
what you want?
[laughs]
They're right,
you're such a narcissist.
- Who-who-who...
- You're just so sure this is all about you.
You're right.
I've been doing
a lot of thinking.
I wanna be a better father.
Fuck you.
You're a little
fucking late.
I've wasted my whole life
trying to be who
you wanted me to be.
Well, not anymore.
I have a real family now.
Go back to Diane.
- Honey, I flew across the...
- Go!
I don't ever want
to see you again.
[door opens]
Sarah.
I'm sorry.
I screwed up.
I know.
I never should've put you
in that spot with Mom.
I should have
been there for her.
And for you.
I...
and I will.
I promise.
Whatever you want,
whatever your dreams are,
I... I'm so proud of you.
Sarah?
Can you forgive me?
I can't lose you, too.
[cries]
[crying]
I love you.
- No! [gasps]
- What?
[inhales]
You really think Mom
didn't know?
You think
I wouldn't tell her?
I told her everything.
She knew exactly what
a pathetic coward you are.
But...
She died hating
your disgusting guts.
[smack]
Get the fuck out.
If I leave,
I'm never com...
The next time I want to
see you is at your funeral.
[door opens/closes]
[door buzzer sounding]
Okay.
Got it.
He's gone.
You did great.
- [exhales/crying]
- Hey, hey, hey.
It's okay.
- It's okay.
- [crying]
We were interrupted
last time.
[exhales]
Thank you.
This is strange
for me, too.
[sighs]
My first five years,
all I could think about
was trying to escape.
Or kill myself.
Jessie, she saved me.
She helped me finally
accept that this is my life.
This is our life.
Nothing can change that.
[dramatic piano music]
♪♪
But it could be a good life.
[birds chirping]
[indistinct conversations]
Hey, guys.
You're early.
Get outta here.
Natty misses you.
[chuckles]
Why risk letting them
all in like this?
Jerry has his system.
He must have seen
hundreds of candidates
before he found you.
I wish we could
help them all.
Someday.
[mouse clicking]
[door buzzer sounding]
Thank you so much!
I... sorry.
- Hey!
- You got it!
- Yeah, I did!
I just kept checking
the listings.
I figured after Sarah's
freak-out or whatever,
she'd eventually
run home to daddy.
[laughs]
Yeah, she, uh,
she didn't seem
too happy here.
Well... she was crazy.
[laughs]
Looking forward
to having your friend back?
Mm-hm.
Why'd you choose her?
Her personality profile
matches Edie's.
And, uh, we thought
that your connection
would help with her process.
We're gonna save her,
Sarah.
From an empty, selfish life.
First, we need to put her
in a receptive state.
[pipes creaking]
We need to learn
everything about her.
I need to cancel
my service.
Separate her cleanly
from her old life.
Prepare her to unlearn
her damaging conditioning.
She'll fight.
She's not like me.
She's...
strong.
Don't worry.
We can handle her.
[crying on monitor]
I said face the wall!
Put your hands
on the fucking wall.
Don't touch me,
I swear to God...
Hold her down!
[crying]
Let go!
You brought this
on yourself.
[crying]
Help me!
[sobs]
No!
No, get off...
[man screaming]
Hold on to her!
Stop her!
[taser buzzing]
[grunts in pain]
She bit my fucking ear!
[distant moans]
Go see Esther.
I'll handle this.
You were right.
She's extremely resistant.
This is gonna be
hard on her.
She needs a friend.
[door opening]
Not you, too.
I know you're scared.
I was too.
But everything's
gonna be okay.
We're gonna help you.
You can't keep me here.
Yeah, we can.
Did you come looking for me
when I disappeared?
It's okay.
I wanna help you.
We all do.
[inhales]
Jesus.
You let them brainwash you.
I didn't let...
I'm not brainwashed.
You're brainwashed.
[laughs]
You're a thirty-eight-year-old
office assistant.
You really think you're
gonna be a movie star?
They saved me.
Lisa,
they can save you, too.
I'd rather die
than end up like you.
Sooner or later,
everyone stops fighting.
You can only take
so much pain.
Don't worry.
Once you accept it,
you'll be happy.
You don't look happy.
- I am.
- You don't look happy, Sarah.
You look terrified!
They helped me.
I finally have a family
that cares about me.
[chuckles]
You don't have a family.
You just found a new daddy
to run your life for you.
- Shut up. Shut up.
- You pathetic, weak,
- spoiled little princess!
- Shut up.
Shut up. Shut up,
shut up!
[grunts]
Wait!
No, Lisa, wait!
- [thud]
- [grunts]
[ties zipping]
I'm sorry.
You need to finish
what you started.
[sobbing]
Hold her head.
Hold her head!
Come on!
- [grunts]
- Hold it.
[crying]
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- Hold her still, goddamn it!
Goddamn it!
- [thud]
- [grunts in pain]
[softly]
No.
Now.
[crying]
Please.
You don't have to do this.
- Shut up!
- Sarah!
Do as I tell you!
[softly]
Please, don't.
[gasps]
Sarah,
it's your fucking life.
[grunting in pain]
[choking]
[thud]
Sarah.
Sarah!
I can't move.
[alarm sounding]
We have to go.
Now.
Christ, Sarah,
you were right.
This building does suck.
[laughs]
- [gun shot]
- [gasps]
You can't leave.
- [battle cry]
- [grunting]
[gun shot]
Fuck you!
Fuck you! Fuck you!
[panting]
[alarm sounding]
[tense music]
♪♪
- Stay back!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Stay out of my way.
Whoa! Hey!
No, no, no, no!
Stay the fuck back!
[battle cry]
- [gun shot]
- [scream]
Throw it away.
Now.
[knife clinking]
How could you do this?
[crying]
How could you kill him?
He deserved it.
For what he did,
to all of us.
We can leave.
We're... we're free.
[indistinct murmuring]
Get back!
I just wanna go.
It's okay.
Sarah,
we can't let you leave.
You know that.
But he's dead.
Jerry didn't start this.
Who did?
I saw his hands,
his e... his ear.
Who did that to him?
Charles Ellerby.
But he... he's been dead
for thirty years.
He gave us
the four foundations
so we'd be self-sustaining
after he died.
It doesn't matter
who our leader is.
The community
is all of us.
Les, please,
look what they did to you.
You can leave.
Sarah, it's not too late.
You're still one of us.
No.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
No, get... get out of my way
or I'll...
Or you'll what?
- I'll...
- You can't even say it.
You're not gonna...
[gun shot]
[screaming]
[crowd murmuring]
[breathes heavily]j
[dramatic music]
♪♪
[door buzzer sounding]
No! No!
[grunting]
[breathing heavily]
Just do it.
Please!
Just shoot me.
[gun shot]
[crowd gasps]
[thud]
Go.
Go!
[crowd clamoring]
No.
[muffled gun shot]
[muffled screaming]
[breathes heavily]
[crowd clamoring]
[dramatic music]
♪♪
[panting]
[dramatic music builds]
♪♪
Who's watching us?
That's none
of our business.
[alarm sounding]
[shaky breathing]
[laughing]
[tense music]
♪♪
♪ There's a certain sound ♪
♪ Always follows me around ♪
♪ When you're close to me
you will hear it ♪
♪ It's the sound that lovers
hear when they discover ♪
♪ There could be no other
for their love ♪
♪ It's my happy heart
you hear ♪
♪ Singing loud
and singing clear ♪
♪ And it's all because
you're near me, my love ♪
♪ Take my happy heart away ♪
♪ Let me love you
night and day ♪
♪ In your arms I wanna stay,
oh my love ♪
♪♪
♪ Feeling more and more
like I've never felt before ♪
♪ You have changed my life
so completely ♪
♪ Music fills my soul now ♪
♪ I've lost all control now ♪
♪ I'm not half,
I'm whole now with your love ♪
♪ It's my happy heart
you hear ♪
♪ Singing loud
and singing clear ♪
♪ And it's all because
you're near me, my love ♪
♪ Take my happy heart away ♪
♪ Let me love you
night and day ♪
♪ In your arms I wanna stay,
oh my love ♪
♪ La la la,
la-la la la ♪
♪ La la la, la-la
la la ♪
♪ La la la,
la-la la la ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ La la la,
la-la la la ♪
♪ La la la, la-la
la la ♪
♪ La la la,
la-la la la ♪
♪ La la la ♪
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
[dramatic electronic music]
♪♪