(RHYTHMIC THUMPING IN DISTANCE)
(RHYTHMIC THUMPING CONTINUES)
(RHYTHMIC THUMPING GROWS LOUDER)
(THUMPING FADES)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(WATER BURBLING)
(MUFFLED SOUNDS
OF PEOPLE TALKING AND LAUGHING)
(MUFFLED MUSIC PLAYS)
(GASPS)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Shark got you.
Are you serious?
- Look what you did.
- I'll get you a new one.
Can we please do something? I'm so bored.
I don't know how you can
just lie in the sun all day.
No, I'm gonna go back to the room.
I told Stuart I'd give him a call.
(CHUCKLES)
Bring me a drink back. Thank you.
Yeah, you wish.
Nice ass.
(LAUGHS)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
I want to make a toast.
Come on!
Thank you so much
for bringing me on vacation.
It's gonna be the best time ever.
- Cheers.
Thanks for coming.
Stuart is missing out.
- I'm way more fun anyway.
- You are.
(LAUGHS): Yeah.
(CHIMING QUIETLY)
(INSECTS CHIRRING)
(WAVES CRASHING GENTLY)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
Lisa?
Sis?
(WAVES CRASHING)
Hey.
- What are you doing?
- (LISA CRYING QUIETLY)
What's wrong?
LISA: I lied.
What are you talking about?
I lied about why Stuart isn't on this trip.
- What?
- He's not working.
What do you mean?
He left me, Kate.
He broke up with me.
(SOFTLY): Oh, my God.
Why didn't you tell me?
'Cause I was embarrassed.
Do Mom and Dad know?
(SMACKS LIPS, SIGHS)
The one good thing in my life,
I managed to fuck up.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
What happened?
It's my fault.
He got bored.
He actually said that?
Yeah. (LAUGHS)
Kind of, more or less.
And then I thought if I came on
this trip and I came away with you,
and I had fun and I showed
that I could be fun,
somehow he would come back, but...
(DEEP BREATH)
(CRYING)
Come on.
- What?
- Come on, we have to get dressed.
- For what?
- You and I are going out.
Going out where? It's 1:00 in the morning.
(LAUGHS) Lisa, it's Mexico. You and I are
the only ones who aren't out. Come on.
I've been dying to do this all week.
("IT'S YOU" BY SYN COLE PLAYING)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
- (MUSIC PLAYING)
- (LAUGHTER, WHOOPING)
(LISA SCREAMS HAPPILY)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
This is the best night ever.
Oh, I could be here all night!
(WHOOPING)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(PHONE WHOOSHES)
(SIGHS)
LISA (LAUGHS): That is crazy.
You guys are insane.
LOUIS: Seriously, you have to try.
We do it almost every weekend.
- It's amazing.
- Yeah, yeah. Look.
25-foot great white sharks.
They come right up to your cage.
- 25 foot?
- You have never seen anything like it.
- KATE: How much does it cost?
- (MEN SPEAKING SPANISH)
What?
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(SPEAKS SPANISH)
Bueno. It's like $100 each.
We-we know Taylor.
He's like a friend of ours.
Great.
Uh, mmm... I don't know.
What are you gonna do...
sit by the pool all day long?
(LAUGHS)
- Seriously?
- I-I don't even know how to dive.
I will teach you everything
you need to know.
But I need one of those, like,
diving card certification.
You took that whole class!
Okay, okay, look, look.
This is Méjico, okay?
It's not even diving.
You're gonna be in a cage.
You're only down five minutes.
- It's totally safe.
- LOUIS: Exactly.
It's like you're going to the
zoo, except you're in the cage.
- Yeah, and-and underwater.
- Sí.
Come on, it sounds amazing.
Please?
I don't know.
You could just think of the photos.
I mean, they won't be the type of
photos that a boring person would take.
Just saying.
(LAUGHS)
- LOUIS: She's got a good point.
- BENJAMIN: Think of the photos.
LOUIS: Think of the photos.
Okay.
- (ALL CHEERING)
- (DRUMMING ON TABLE)
- All right.
- Okay.
- Cheers.
- Salud.
- (LISA LAUGHS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Well, good, I am pleased.
BENJAMIN: Okay.
(SPEAKS SPANISH)
Yeah, I just wanted to say I had
a really good night tonight.
Me, too.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Sorry.
(CHUCKLES)
Not... ready.
Thank you.
- No, it's okay. It's fine.
- See you tomorrow.
- Tomorrow for sure.
- Come on.
Oh.
- Good night!
- Buenas noches.
Adios.
(LAUGHING)
I'll see you tomorrow.
Sí.
Adios. Buenas noches.
- (LISA SCREAMS)
- (MEN LAUGHING)
They are so cute.
- Oh, cute. Hey.
- Hola.
(BOY SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY)
KATE: I am so looking forward to this.
It's gonna be amazing.
I can't believe you talked me into this.
I did not talk you into this.
Okay, you just wanted
to see the guys again.
I did not.
(LAUGHS) Do not lie to me.
LISA: Okay, he's kind of cute.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Kate, I don't know about this.
KATE: It'll be fun. I promise.
It... they're probably
not going to show anyway, so...
- BENJAMIN: Hola, chicas!
- LOUIS: Hey!
- Hey, hola!
- How's it going?
- Hola.
- Hi.
- Yeah. Hola.
- Hey, how are you?
(KISSING)
I'm so glad you came.
I wasn't sure you were going to.
(LAUGHS) Yep, here we are.
Okay, should we do it?
- Yeah, let's go see the boat.
- Okay.
Go ahead...
Oh, you lead the way.
Okay. (CHUCKLES)
So, uh, how did you sleep?
Uh, I slept all right.
- I had a really good time last night.
- KATE: Me, too. You guys are funny.
- How is your head?
- LISA: Uh, it hurts.
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
KATE: Okay. All right,
we're gonna go talk to the captain.
- Okay.
- Be back in a second.
Oye, Captain!
I... really, I feel
super uneasy about this.
Come on, it'll be fine.
I mean, is this even safe?
We don't know anything about these people.
Remember what the concierge said?
That we should book
all activities and tours...
Yeah, he works for the hotel.
He has to say that.
I've just heard horror stories about
tourists going on these shady trips.
And Stuart even told me that...
Stuart is a prick, Lisa.
It'll be fun. Come on.
LOUIS: Hey, come on over. Don't be shy.
- Come on.
- Okay.
This is, uh, Taylor, the captain.
- KATE: Hola. Hola.
- LISA: Hola.
Buenos días. ¡Cómo están?
- Bien.
You both know how to scuba dive, right?
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
All right, well, welcome aboard.
Okay.
Ah, gracias.
Oh.
KATE: I know you're clumsy,
so don't fall in, okay?
LOUIS: There she is.
Oye, Javi.
(BENJAMIN SPEAKING SPANISH)
(MEN SPEAKING SPANISH)
TAYLOR: Watch your step.
BENJAMIN: Here we are.
- LISA: Gracias.
- (BENJAMIN LAUGHS)
BENJAMIN: Okay.
(LOUIS SPEAKING SPANISH)
(METALLIC CREAKING)
LISA: Oh, no.
- TAYLOR: Here...
- Kate, have you seen the cage?
TAYLOR: Put those tanks in the back...
keep them out of the sun.
Relax.
You're gonna have the time
of your life, I promise.
It'll be fun!
(LAUGHING): I'm scared.
("DOWN IN THE WOODS"
BY RICHARD HAWLEY PLAYING)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(GRUNTING)
("DOWN IN THE WOODS" CONTINUES ON RADIO)
(ENGINE RUMBLING)
(WIND BLOWING)
(SPEAKS SPANISH)
BENJAMIN: This looks like the spot.
- BENJAMIN: All right.
- KATE: This is it?
- LOUIS: Yeah.
- This is totally it.
- KATE: Okay.
- LISA: Really?
(MAN WHOOPING, JAVIER SPEAKING SPANISH)
LOUIS: This is going to be amazing.
(JAVIER SPEAKING SPANISH)
It's feeding time.
- You hungry? Huh?
- Ugh, it's disgusting.
- No.
- Hmm? No?
- You hungry? Huh?
- KATE: Oh.
- (LAUGHS)
- LISA: Oh, my God, gross.
- Ah. (SPEAKS SPANISH)
- There we go, feeding time.
LISA: That's so gross.
LOUIS: That's... that reeks, huh?
I thought it was illegal
to chum the water.
JAVIER:
You think I should call the shark instead?
Mr. Shark!
Hello!
(MUFFLED): Mr. Shark, hello!
I don't think they hear
so good underwater.
(JAVIER SPEAKING SPANISH)
- (LAUGHTER)
- Yeah, they just put that down...
- What-what did he say?
- ...so the sharks will smell it.
- No, nothing.
- They should be here soon.
BENJAMIN: We should get this
party started.
KATE: Okay.
LOUIS: Here, fishy, fishy, fishy, fishy.
(LOUIS AND KATE LAUGH)
KATE: That works? Okay.
There! Look!
- LOUIS: Where?
- KATE: There, there...
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER, LAUGHTER)
(CHATTER CONTINUES)
- Oh, yeah.
- Oh, my God!
- Got to check this out. Javier.
- Javi.
Oh, my God, this is amazing.
(BENJAMIN WHOOPING)
- See, right over there.
- Lisa?
(BENJAMIN SPEAKING SPANISH)
LOUIS: Get ready?
BENJAMIN: Javi! (SPEAKS SPANISH)
(SIGHS)
KATE: Lisa, you in there? Come on.
There's a shark right by the boat.
The boys are in first, but we
got to get ready in a minute.
No.
I don't think I can do it. I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- What? No.
- No, no, please.
- Don't be mad at me.
- I can't, I ca-I can't.
- Come on, it'll be incredible.
- Please, please, please, please.
- (BREATHING HEAVILY)
You're not gonna make Stuart jealous
with photos inside the boat's bathroom.
- (CHUCKLING): Really?
- Well, I had to say it.
I did. Come on.
Please.
(SIGHS)
- Ah, yes.
- Okay, okay, okay.
Yes, I love you.
- Okay, come on.
- Oh, God, you owe me.
Yes, I will make you breakfast in bed.
- Yeah, you owe me big time.
- Scrambled eggs...
KATE: I will, I promise.
TAYLOR: That's it.
(GRUNTS): Okay.
(JAVIER SPEAKS SPANISH)
- LISA: Bye.
- KATE: Bye.
TAYLOR: Let's lower the cage.
- KATE: Be careful.
- (SPEAKING SPANISH)
(LOUD MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
- LISA: Oh, my God, that looks so scary.
KATE: Okay. Bye.
TAYLOR: Don't leave me hanging.
- (MECHANICAL WHIRRING CONTINUES)
- Bueno, Javi.
KATE: See, look, it's safe. It's fine.
- (WHIRRING STOPS)
- Have fun, boys.
Whoa, don't slip.
KATE: Bye.
(GRUNTS)
Okay.
(WHIRRING RESUMES)
(WHIRRING STOPS)
(SNAPPING FINGERS)
Come here.
There.
- Oh, my God.
- It's huge.
(LISA AND KATE CHUCKLING)
Oh, my God, Kate.
It's about 20 feet.
I've seen them get as big as 28.
- We're really gonna do that?
- Yes!
TAYLOR: Yeah, let's get you suited up now.
LISA: I'm really nervous.
- You are?
- Mm-hmm.
I'm shitting bricks.
- Really?
- Yes.
- You are?
Hey, help me. (SIGHS)
Does my butt at least look cute in this?
- Oye.
- (MAN WHOOPS, LAUGHS OVER RADIO)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(MEN SPEAKING SPANISH
AND WHOOPING OVER RADIO)
(SPEAKS SPANISH)
(KNOCKS ON DOOR)
You ladies ready?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Yup. Okay.
(SOFTLY): Oh, God.
(CHUCKLES)
- (NERVOUS CHUCKLE)
- TAYLOR: Relax.
- Okay. Okay.
- Okay? All right.
- Calm down.
- Okay.
- Yeah, I'm okay.
- Good.
- That's it.
- Okay.
Here, hold on to that.
There you go.
- Now...
- Put these down?
Uh-huh.
Check your air.
You should both have 200 bar.
Yeah, 200.
That's your air.
Okay.
TAYLOR: When it gets to 100,
you need to let me know.
When it gets to 50,
I'm gonna bring you back up.
50 is the orange.
- Yes.
- Yeah, okay.
Yeah, I know that, yeah.
- That's it.
- Right, okay.
All right, you're only gonna be
going down about five meters.
It's unlikely at that depth,
but... (GRUNTS)
if you get any pain in your ears,
you just need to equalize.
Tilt you head back and swallow.
- Equalize.
- Okay.
- Head back, swallow.
- Yeah.
- (EXHALES)
All right, now just remember,
the faster you breathe,
the faster you use up your air.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Relax.
Tranquilo, okay?
LISA: Okay.
Trust me, once you're down there,
you're not gonna want to come back up.
- Yeah.
- Right.
Great.
- Good?
- Okay.
Awesome, all right.
LISA (SOFTLY): Yeah, I can do this.
Okay. Okay.
(OXYGEN TANKS HISSES)
(MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
(BENJAMIN AND LOUIS WHOOPING)
(LAUGHING, WHOOPING)
LOUIS: It's great.
You're gonna love it down there.
Gracias. Gracias, Javi.
Next?
- That's it.
- Oh, I'm so scared.
Be careful.
Shark don't hear so good up
here, you know?
But underwater?
You're in his world.
Can hear your heartbeat
for up to five miles away.
Can sense if you're frightened or weak.
Track you down.
Good to go!
TAYLOR: Don't pay any attention
to that pendejo.
You're going to have a great time.
Can I borrow your camera?
Yeah, but...
if you drop it,
you got to go down and get it.
(BENJAMIN LAUGHS)
What are we doing, Kate?
- (BEEPING)
- Smile.
JAVIER: Adios, muchachas!
(WHIRRING RESUMES)
(LISA PANTING)
(WHIRRING STOPS)
- LISA: I'm really scared.
- KATE: I'm going to go first, okay?
Oh, I'm so excited.
Okay.
TAYLOR: All right. You're next.
(LISA GRUNTS)
That's it.
Right.
(MUFFLED CLANGING)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
LISA: Oh, Kate.
You can see for miles.
Kate, look at the fish.
Do you see all the fish?
KATE (LAUGHS): It's so much better
than sitting in a hotel room, right?
LISA: Oh, wow.
This is awesome.
I had no idea.
TAYLOR (OVER RADIO):
Can you girls hear me?
- Yeah.
- Yes.
TAYLOR: Lisa, how you doing?
I'm good, actually.
- TAYLOR: Kate, how about you?
- Yeah, I'm good.
I can't see any sharks, though.
All right, well, just be patient.
We're gonna add a little bit
more chum to the water now.
Okay.
(LAUGHTER)
Oh, wow.
It kind of takes your breath away.
How deep do you think it goes?
I have no idea.
(BEEP)
KATE: Wave to the camera.
LISA: Cheese!
Hi! (LAUGHS) Hi.
Oh, wow.
Can you take a picture of me?
- Yeah.
- Wait.
Oh!
Oh, shit. Sorry. Sorry.
Oh, my God, the guys
are going to be so pissed.
You've got to go and get that.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
(SCREAMS)
Oh, my God!
(LISA LAUGHING)
LISA: That is, like, the biggest shark.
(PANTING)
This is amazing.
- LISA (GASPS): There's another one.
- KATE: Oh, my God, he's huge.
LISA: Oh, my God, look at those teeth.
(LAUGHING)
I can't believe how close they are.
- KATE: I dare you to touch him.
- LISA: Are you crazy?
(METALLIC CREAKING)
Well, he definitely likes to look at you.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- (LOUD BANG)
- (SCREAMS)
Did you feel that? The cage just moved.
KATE: I thought we were
gonna drop for a moment.
TAYLOR: Are you girls okay?
No, I think the cage
just dropped a little bit.
TAYLOR: No, it's the winch mechanism.
It's-it's fine.
It just slipped a little bit.
Uh, no, I think we want
to come back up now.
No, no, no, no. We don't.
I'm sure it's nothing.
- We're fine, okay?
- Are you crazy?
No, we would like
to come back up now, please.
TAYLOR: All right, listen. Standby.
We're going to bring you girls back up.
- Come on!
- ¿Javi, están seguras?
- LISA: Sorry.
- KATE: Lisa, come on.
LISA: I just don't feel safe in this cage.
At least we got to see some sharks.
KATE: I mean, I guess so.
It's just so cool.
I could stay down here forever.
Hey, Taylor, once Lisa's out,
can I go back down again?
(MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
(LOUD METALLIC SNAPPING)
(MEN SHOUTING)
LISA: What...? Taylor, we're sinking!
KATE: We're sinking!
- Help us, guys!
- Taylor, help!
I have to get out of here!
Taylor, help us!
(SCREAMING)
Taylor!
(SHARP SNAPPING)
(BOOM)
(SCREAMING)
(METALLIC CREAKING)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(ECHOING BOOM)
(THUMP)
(METALLIC CREAKING)
(BURBLING)
(KATE GASPING FRANTICALLY)
(DISTANTLY): Lisa. Oh, my God.
Wake up. Wake up.
(GASPING)
Lisa, please wake up.
Please.
(BURBLING)
(NORMAL VOICE): Wake up, wake up.
Lisa, please, wake up.
Lis.
(GASPING)
(SCREAMING)
- No, no, no, no!
- No, no.
Taylor! Taylor, help us!
- We're stuck here at the bottom!
- Lisa, you need to calm down.
- We need to get out of here!
- If you do not calm down, we will die here!
- (SCREAMS)
- Look at me now!
Stop! Stop!
Kate, I can't breathe.
- Oh, I can't breathe.
- Slow your breathing.
- I can't breathe.
- Please, please, please.
- (GASPING)
- Slow your breathing.
In. Out.
In.
Out. Come on.
(LISA GASPING)
(BREATHING SLOWS)
Good, good.
The more you panic, the faster
you use up your air, okay?
I need you to slow down your breathing.
Okay, good.
- Good, good, good.
- (WHIMPERS SOFTLY)
LISA: How deep are we?
KATE: 47 meters.
It must've ripped the crane
right off the boat.
What are we gonna do?
- (RADIO STATIC)
- Listen!
Can you hear that?
(RADIO STATIC)
KATE: Taylor?
Taylor?
- Help us!
- Hello!
Taylor?
- Taylor! Taylor!
- Wait, wait, wait.
Stop.
(RADIO STATIC)
We must be just out of range
of transmission.
We've gotta try and get
back in contact with them.
How?
We-we can almost hear them, right?
So-so maybe we're just a bit too deep.
Maybe... maybe if I swim up a tiny bit,
then-then we'll be back in range, okay?
I could tell them that we're alive,
and they need to come and get us.
Yeah, but what about the sharks?
They can sense us down here, right?
I'll swim as close to the cage as I can.
I'll be okay.
No, no, no, please, Kate.
Promise me you won't leave me down here.
I won't leave you, I promise.
I promise.
(METALLIC CREAKING)
Oh, shit.
(GROANING)
(GASPING)
It's stuck.
KATE: No, it's not.
We can get it.
(GROANING)
We can do it!
Push!
(GRUNTS)
KATE: We're not gonna get out
through this side.
LISA: Yes, we are. Yes, we are.
(PANTING)
I can get it. Just give me a second. Okay.
I think I can get out through these bars.
I need to take my tank off, though.
LISA: Wait, what?
Is that even safe?
KATE: It's going to be okay.
You can pass it to me when I'm through.
LISA: That gap looks really small.
Do you think you could even make it?
KATE: Take my BCD, okay?
(PANTING)
Okay.
I need you to watch out for me.
LISA: Please, be careful.
KATE (GRUNTING): Okay.
I got this. Okay.
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
(BREATHLESSLY): Okay. I'm okay.
(GASPING)
Kate, come on, you can get this.
(KATE GRUNTING)
- (GRUNTS)
- Come on, push!
Push, Kate.
You got it.
(KATE GRUNTING)
(KATE PANTING)
What are we going to do, Kate?
What are we going to do?
I'm gonna have to take my mask off.
- Okay? It's fine.
- No. No, no, no. No, no, no.
Kate, Kate, Kate, Kate, there
has to be some other way.
- No, just stop, and think for a second.
- You have to calm down.
No, no. Kate, you can't take off your mask.
- Lisa, calm down! Stop.
- No, I can't.
- I can't. (EXHALES)
- Please.
I'm gonna take some deep breaths,
I'm gonna take it off... and go through and
you're gonna pass it right to me, okay?
What if you can't get it back on again?
You'll drown.
It's okay.
(DEEP BREATHING)
All right, you ready?
(BURBLING)
(MUFFLED): Here, take the mask!
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUFFLED, INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(EXHALES)
(GASPING)
Here, put this on, quick.
Come on, put it on quick. Hurry up.
(KATE PANTING)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Hurry. Hurry, hurry, hurry, please.
Before I make contact,
I'm gonna move the crane.
Just in case you need to get out
and I'm not here, okay?
Please don't say that, Kate.
We're going to get out of this together.
Just keep a look out, okay?
(STRAINED GRUNTING)
KATE: It's not moving.
(PANTING)
I'm going to go see
if it's stuck at the base.
Kate, I'm scared.
What if the sharks come?
It's caught against the rocks.
I think that I can move it.
LISA: Okay, but hurry, please.
Come on, Kate.
(KATE GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING)
I think I have it free.
- Oh, come on. Come on.
- Come on, Kate.
- (STRAINED GRUNTING)
- Push.
- You got it, you got it.
- (STRAINED GRUNTING)
- (METALLIC CREAKING)
- It's moving.
(KATE YELLS)
- (GRUNTING)
- Keep going.
Yes!
(METALLIC CLANGING)
We did it!
(LAUGHING)
(PANTING)
I'm gonna see if I can reach Taylor.
We're gonna get out of here, okay?
LISA: Hurry, please.
Taylor, can you hear me?
Is anybody there?
(PANTING)
Somebody please answer me!
TAYLOR (STATICKY): Hello! Kate!
- I can hear you!
- I said, can you hear me?
- I can hear you, Taylor, it's Kate, it's Kate!
- Say something.
- Hello?
- TAYLOR: I hear you.
- I read you loud and clear, Kate.
- Oh, thank God. Oh, you have to help us.
TAYLOR: Are you both okay?
Yes.
- Good.
- Yes.
- How much air do you have in your tank?
- Um...
I'm at 55 bar.
TAYLOR: What does your depth gauge say?
Um, the gauge is at 47 meters.
I had to come up to hear you...
I'm at 40 meters.
I'm am so freaking scared. What do I do?
TAYLOR: All right, listen, Kate.
I need you to get
back in the cage immediately.
It's the only safe place from the sharks.
Do you understand?
Javier's coming down to you now.
He's going to hook up the cage
to our spare winch
- and pull you up.
- Okay.
And remember, Kate,
whatever you and Lisa do,
don't try to race to the surface.
You'll get the bends.
I'm going back down now.
Promise me you'll come.
TAYLOR: Just stay in the cage
and reserve your air.
Okay.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(QUIETLY): Just keep calm.
Just keep breathing.
I made contact with them, Lisa.
(BREATHLESSLY): I made contact.
LISA: Yeah? Yeah?
What did the say?
Javier is coming down.
He's gonna connect the cage
- to a backup winch.
- He is?
Oh! Thank God, thank God, thank God.
Oh, okay. Oh, thank God.
- We need to conserve our air.
- Okay. Okay.
Oh, it's almost over.
I was so frightened, Kate,
waiting for you.
I thought that you were never coming back.
I'm so sorry I got us into this.
The other night at the hotel,
what did you mean when you said
that your relationship
was the only thing you were good at?
You're always doing such fun stuff, Kate.
Traveling around the world
doing crazy things,
guys always chasing after you.
I could never compete with that.
I was always just
your boring older sister, but...
my relationship with Stuart
was the one thing I had that you didn't.
We were never in competition.
Maybe you weren't.
What do you think Stuart would
say if he could see you now?
(LAUGHS)
(BOTH LAUGH)
What?
He would lose his mind.
- (LAUGHING)
- Yeah.
Listen.
(RUMBLING IN DISTANCE)
What is that?
Oh, my God, that's the boat's engine.
Oh, my God, they've left us!
They-they wouldn't have left us, okay?
- Oh, God.
- Maybe it's something else.
- Maybe it was a different boat.
- We would've heard it arrive.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Where are you going?
I've got to go and try
and get them on the radio again.
Kate, what are we gonna do
if they're not there?
KATE: They will not have left us, okay?
Taylor, can you hear me?
Hello, are you there?
Please answer me, someone!
Taylor, it's Kate. Can you hear me?
Hello, is anyone there?
Please, someone answer me!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
(SCREAMS)
Lisa, open the hatch!
Open the hatch! It was a shark!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
(SCREAMS)
I can't open it! It's caught on the chain!
It's coming! Oh, my God!
Hurry, hurry!
KATE (SHUDDERING): Oh, my God.
I thought it was g...
I thought it was gonna get me.
I thought it... I was dead.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
(BOTH SHRIEKING)
The cage is gonna break!
It's gonna get through!
(BARS CREAKING)
KATE: Be quiet! Quiet, be quiet.
LISA: It almost broke through the cage.
We're not safe here anymore.
Did you make contact with Taylor?
They weren't there.
Oh, my God, oh, my God,
oh, my God, oh, my God.
They're not just gonna leave us here.
They said they were sending someone down.
But we heard them leave, didn't we?
They also said they were gonna
come down here
and attach, like, a spare winch
to the top of the cage,
but did you even see one
on the boat? I didn't...
They are not gonna
leave us to die down here, okay?
- You need to calm down.
- So we have to get back up to the top.
No, Lisa, listen to me,
we cannot just swim up.
- We can swim fast.
- No, we can't.
- We can!
- We will get the bends.
Do you know what the bends is?
It's nitrogen bubbles in the brain.
The only way to go up is to ascend slowly
with a decompression stop
for five minutes.
Unprotected, in open water.
(WHIMPERING)
I'm so scared we're gonna die down here.
- I don't want to die down here, Kate.
- We are not gonna die.
We're not gonna die down here.
It's okay, they're gonna come and get us.
Read me your air.
Um... um...
it says 80 bar.
I don't know what that means.
At this depth, that means
we have about 20 minutes, tops,
before you run out.
What about you?
Kate.
30 bar.
LISA: Oh, my God.
KATE: I'm gonna be fine.
It's gonna be fine.
LISA: You're gonna run out of air.
(RADIO CRACKLES)
Listen.
Javier?
(PANTING): What is that?
I-Is that Javier?
LISA: There! There!
There, there, there! Hey! Hey!
Can you hear us?
We can see your flashlight.
(LAUGHS)
Javier!
Hey!
KATE: Why isn't he coming towards us?
LISA: May-Maybe he's out of range.
Hey! Javier!
KATE: We need to make sure
he knows where we are.
(CLANGING)
LISA: What's he doing?
KATE: I don't know.
LISA: Well, if he heard us,
why didn't he just signal?
We need to get that winch cable.
(BEEPING)
LISA: 17 bar. You're almost out of air.
Okay...
Okay, I'm gonna go out there and find him.
You just need to tell me
exactly what I need to do.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Okay.
Keep as close to
the ocean floor as you can.
Sharks attack from below, so if you
keep to the floor, you should be fine.
This button inflates your BCD.
Use it to go up.
This button deflates it.
Listen to me, this is so important.
No matter what happens,
no matter how panicked you get,
do not go straight up.
You will die. Do you understand?
I'll be right back.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Get down on the floor
as quick as you can, okay?
That's good. You're doing so good. Okay.
Keep your breathing slow.
Just focus on the flashlight.
Lisa, I can see the shark!
It's coming towards you!
Hide! Hide!
(SHRIEKS)
(PANTING)
KATE: Lisa? Lisa, can you hear me?
Are you safe?
- Lisa?
- I'm okay.
I'm okay. I'm in a cave.
The shark almost got me.
KATE: Where is it now?
I think it's gone.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
(SCREAMING)
KATE: Lisa? What's going on?
Lisa, are you okay?
Lisa? Answer me, please.
I'm okay.
(BEEPING)
I'm getting low on air.
I can see the flashlight.
I can see the beam. It's getting closer...
Oh! Oh, my God. Oh.
KATE: Lisa, what's wrong? What's wrong?
I'm at the edge of some sort of cliff.
I can't see the ocean floor.
KATE: We're running out of time.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Okay, I can do this. I can do this.
(RADIO STATIC)
KATE: Are you doing okay, Lisa?
I am so scared, Kate.
I can't even see what's below me.
(SIGHS)
(GROANS)
I see it! I see it!
I see it!
I found the flashlight.
(GROANS) Javier?
(PANTING AND GROANING)
He's not here, Kate. Javier?
I'm gonna come back, okay?
(PANTING)
Which way did I come from?
Oh. Oh.
Kate? Oh.
Uh-oh. Um...
Kate, can you hear me? Hello?
Kate? Kate, please answer me.
I'm really lost,
and I'm freaking out right now.
(PANTING AND GASPING)
Oh, my God.
(GROANING)
Stay calm. Stay calm and make a decision.
Kate!
(LOUD BREATHING)
(SIGHS)
(WHIMPERING)
Kate, I'm so lost.
(CRIES)
Kate, can you hear me?
(PANTING)
(WHIMPERS)
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
(SCREAMS)
(PANTING)
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- (SCREAMS)
- Get back into the cage!
(SCREAMS)
(GROANING)
(PANTING)
(GARBLED RADIO TRANSMISSION)
Kate? Kate, I can hear you!
Can you hear me?
You're breaking up!
(GARBLED RADIO TRANSMISSION)
(PANTING)
Kate?
I need you to bang a rock or something
when you see the flashlight,
so I know which way to go.
- (BANGING NEARBY)
- (GASPS)
I can hear you, Kate!
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
(SCREAMS)
(GARBLED RADIO TRANSMISSION)
(WHIMPERING)
He's got no air. Damn.
Okay, I have to...
I have to get the winch.
(PANTING)
Oh. Spear gun.
Oh, God.
(PANTING)
KATE: I can see the flashlight.
You're getting closer.
LISA: Oh. Okay. I can see the
lights on the cage. I'm coming.
I'm coming, Kate.
Lisa, I thought you were dead.
Where's Javier?
The shark ripped him to pieces.
I have the winch cable.
Oh, I was so lost I thought
I would never see you again.
Thread it through this end.
Hey, the cable looks really thin.
Do you think it will hold?
It has to. Give me the flashlight.
I'm gonna swim back up, and tell them
- that we have to come up now.
- Be careful!
I'll be right back.
(PANTING)
Taylor?
Taylor, can you hear me?
(PANTING)
Taylor, hello!
- TAYLOR: Kate?
- LISA: It's Lisa.
We managed to attach the cable
to the top of the cage.
We need to come up right now!
- TAYLOR: Is Javier with you?
- No!
- Javier is dead.
- What? Oh... Jesus.
Get back in the cage!
Get back in the cage now!
I'm bringing you back up!
They're bringing us up now.
- They are?
- Yeah. Yeah.
Oh. Thank God.
(PANTING)
(CREAKING)
Kate, do you hear that?
(WHIRRING)
(LAUGHING): Do you hear that?
Oh. Oh.
(LAUGHTER)
- Oh. See?
- Yeah.
Look. We're starting to move.
(CREAKING AND WHIRRING)
We're gonna go home!
Oh. Oh, thank God it's almost over!
Oh, we're gonna go home!
(PANTING)
It's working. Look. We're getting higher.
You did it, Lisa. You saved us.
The gauge is starting to move. Look, Kate.
Kate, it's at 46 meters.
45. (PANTING)
44.
We're gonna get out of here.
Yeah.
TAYLOR: Kate, Lisa, can you hear me?
Taylor, we can hear you.
We're at 36 meters.
35!
34!
33.
BOTH: 32!
(LAUGHING)
BOTH: 31!
TAYLOR: Good. Good. We're almost there.
BOTH: 30!
TAYLOR: Nice and slowly.
BOTH: 29!
- 28...
- (THUDDING)
- Taylor!
- Taylor, cable's breaking!
- TAYLOR: What?
- LISA: Taylor, help us!
TAYLOR: All right, listen, stay calm.
- Don't move! I'm gonna slow it down.
- (WHIMPERING)
Taylor, help.
Taylor? Taylor?
(SNAPPING)
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING)
(CRYING)
Get it off! Get it off!
Get it off, Kate!
Oh, my God! Okay.
(SCREAMS)
It's stuck, I can't move it!
(LISA MOANS)
(GASPING)
(BEEPING)
We're running out of time!
I've got to get ahold of Taylor.
Don't leave me, Kate.
I don't want to suffocate.
KATE (PANTING): No, it's going to be fine.
I'm going to come back.
Taylor, it's Kate.
- TAYLOR: Are you hurt?
- Lisa's trapped.
Her leg is stuck and we have no air!
My gauge is on five bar.
It's gonna run out any minute.
TAYLOR: I'm going to send down
extra air tanks.
But, Kate, there's a reason
that I didn't do this before.
Moving onto a second tank
is going to increase
your chance of nitrogen narcosis
dramatically.
You're going to need to watch
each other closely to make sure
that neither of you is behaving
strangely or hallucinating.
I've notified the Coast Guard.
They're sending a team that's fully
equipped for deep sea rescue.
They'll be here in less than an hour.
LISA: I'm so scared.
KATE: It's gonna be fine.
(BURBLING)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(INTERMITTENT BEEPING)
Look. (PANTING)
Over there.
It's the oxygen tanks.
(PANTING, GRUNTING)
LISA: Please, be careful.
I'll be right back.
(BEEPING)
Shit.
I'm almost out of air.
(INTERMITTENT BEEPING)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(GRUNTS)
LISA: Kate, did you find it?
(HISSING, KATE SIGHS)
Kate, are you okay?
KATE (GASPING): Yeah.
Okay.
They sent down some flares.
All we have to do is wait for
the Coast Guard to arrive.
I've got the spare tank.
Kate, get down.
Stay down.
Where is it, Lisa?
It's right above you, don't move.
(GASPING): Oh, God, I can't see it!
(CRYING)
I'm going to make a break for the cage.
No, Kate, no, no, no, don't move.
Stay down, please, stay down.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Open the hatch.
(LISA SCREAMS)
(SCREAMING): No, no, Kate!
(CRYING AND GASPING): No, no, no, Kate.
(CRYING): No.
(CRYING): No...
No, Kate, no, Kate.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(PANTING)
(PANTING CONTINUES)
I am not going to die down here.
(KNOCKING)
(GROANING)
(SCREAMING)
(WHIMPERING)
(BEEPING)
I'm going to run out of air.
(GASPING)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(METAL CLANKING)
Come on, come on.
God.
(GRUNTING)
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
(GROANING)
(SCREAMING)
(WHIMPERING)
(GROANING)
(GRUNTING)
(WHIMPERING)
(CRYING)
(ALARM BEEPING)
(BEEPING CONTINUES)
(GROANS)
(WHIMPERING)
(CRYING)
(GROANS)
(CLANKING METAL)
(PANTING)
(GROANING)
(LAUGHS)
(SCREAMS)
No!
(SOBBING)
(BEEPING)
(GRUNTING)
(WHIMPERING)
(AIR HISSES)
(CHOKING)
- (AIR HISSING)
- (SIGHS)
(DEEP BREATHING)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
KATE: Lisa?
- Kate?
- Lisa, are you there?
Oh, Kate, oh, Kate,
I thought that you were dead.
Oh, God.
I managed to escape.
(PANTING): Sharks, are circling me.
I'm hurt.
- How bad, how bad?
- Bad.
I'm bleeding a lot.
It's... it's attracting more sharks.
How much air do you have left?
30 bar.
The shark punctured my BCD.
My oxygen's escaping.
(CRYING): I'm scared, Lisa.
I know, I know.
Okay, I need you to listen to me.
You need to remain calm.
They are going to come down and get us.
I need you to concentrate
on your breathing, okay?
Breathe in and out,
like you told me, okay?
In and out.
- (SIGHS)
- In and out.
KATE: So cold.
Right, I'm gonna come and get you.
I'm gonna come and find you right now.
KATE: Tired...
(LISA GROANING)
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Stay with me, Kate.
Stay with me, okay?
Just keep talking to me.
KATE: I'm not going to make it.
(LISA GROANING)
Kate?
Kate, are you still there?
I'm so cold.
Kate, keep talking to me, please.
My BCD.
Oh, I'm gonna get us out of here.
(GRUNTING)
(AIR HISSING)
(METAL RUMBLING)
Please work.
Please, please.
(GROANING)
(PANTING)
(SCREAMING)
(CRYING)
(GROANING)
Oh, God.
- I'm gonna come and find you.
- I...
I'm gonna come and find you, Kate, okay?
...can't... breathe.
I'm coming, Kate.
Okay.
Kate?
Kate, can you see the beam
from my flashlight?
KATE (WEAKLY): Lisa... Lisa...
I'm so cold.
Kate, keep talking to me, please.
Can you see the beam from my flashlight?
KATE: I see you, I see the flashlight.
Yes! Yes, I can hear you!
Okay, I'm coming to find you.
Stay right where you are.
Kate?
Kate, can you see my flashlight?
KATE: Over here.
Kate!
Oh, God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God!
(PANTING)
Kate, you're bleeding to death.
Kate, we have to go up now.
I'm not gonna let you die.
Come on, we can do it.
- (SCREAMS)
- Come on.
(KATE GROANING)
Use the flare, Kate.
It'll help ward off the sharks.
Taylor?
Taylor, can you hear me?
(KATE GROANING)
Taylor?
Taylor, can you hear us?
Taylor!
TAYLOR: Hello?
- Can you hear me? Lisa?
- Taylor, can you hear us?
TAYLOR: Lisa, I can hear you.
Oh! Okay, um... we are heading up now.
TAYLOR: No, it's not safe.
You need to stay in the cage.
LISA: We don't have a choice.
Kate has been badly hurt.
We are coming up now.
TAYLOR: All right, but you
need to go very slowly.
Do you understand?
If you ascend too quickly,
you're going to get the bends.
LISA: Okay.
(KATE GROANING)
TAYLOR: Look at your gauge.
Tell me what your depth is.
LISA: Um, we're at 30 meters.
TAYLOR: You need to slow down.
If you get nitrogen bubbles in your brain,
you are dead, do you understand?
Yes, I understand!
We are coming.
(KATE GROANING)
We're getting there, Kate.
We're getting there.
Come on, you just need
to hang on a little bit longer.
(KATE PANTING)
(LISA GRUNTING)
LISA: We're at 20 meters.
TAYLOR: Okay, good.
Now you need to stay there for five
minutes and do a decompression stop.
LISA: Okay. Okay.
TAYLOR: You need to let
the nitrogen leave your bloodstream.
Four and a half minutes.
LISA: We need to light another one, hurry!
KATE: Okay.
I have two more.
(KATE GROANS)
I dropped it.
LISA: Here, take the flashlight.
Where is it? Where is it?
I can't find it, Kate.
Oh, got it!
Got it!
TAYLOR: Just three more minutes.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
(LISA SCREAMING)
Taylor, there are sharks everywhere!
And we're on our last flare.
(LISA SCREAMS)
We're gonna make it, Kate.
We're gonna make it,
just stay with me, okay?
(LISA SCREAMS)
We're out of flares!
What do we do?
TAYLOR: Break for the surface now!
Drop your BCD and swim!
Swim!
(BOTH GASPING, COUGHING)
LISA: Help.
Help!
(KATE COUGHS)
Help us!
- Help.
- TAYLOR: Kate!
- Lisa!
- Help us!
- Swim!
- Help!
TAYLOR: Swim!
TAYLOR: Grab it!
BENJAMIN:
Grab the lifesaver, we'll pull you in.
(LISA SOBBING)
(LISA SHRIEKS)
(KATE GASPS)
(SCREAMS)
(SHOUTS)
(GROANS)
BENJAMIN: Lisa!
Vamos!
(LOUIS YELLING IN SPANISH)
LISA: Pull us faster!
- (SPEAKS SPANISH)
- Grab her!
- LISA: I can't reach your hand.
- TAYLOR: Get them in the boat now!
- Pull us up!
- LISA: (SCREAMING) No!
(LISA SCREAMS)
LOUIS: Grab my hand!
LOUIS: Take my hand.
(LISA CRYING)
(LOUIS SPEAKING SPANISH)
(YELLING IN SPANISH)
(LISA CRYING)
Keep pressure on the wound.
(CRYING)
(LISA CRIES)
How strange.
(TAYLOR'S VOICE
FROM RADIO CUTTING IN AND OUT)
Your voice sounds funny.
(TAYLOR'S VOICE
FROM RADIO CUTTING IN AND OUT)
(GIGGLING)
(TAYLOR'S VOICE
CONTINUES TO CUT IN AND OUT)
TAYLOR (OVER RADIO): Can you hear me?
(VOICE CUTTING IN AND OUT)
(VOICE MUTED)
Ah, we made it.
(TAYLOR'S VOICE OVER RADIO CUTTING OUT)
We made it.
TAYLOR: Lis... hear me?
(LISA TAKES DEEP BREATH)
- (GIGGLING)
- Lisa? Lisa?
TAYLOR: Ans... my voice...
Do you un...
LISA: We made it, Kate. (GIGGLES)
- Lis...
- My BCD got me free.
(TAYLOR CONTINUES TO CUT IN AND OUT)
- You're hallu... nating.
- (LISA LAUGHING HYSTERICALLY)
We made it, Kate!
We made it! (LAUGHS)
We made it.
TAYLOR (CUTTING OUT):
Lisa, if you can hear me,
the Coast Guard are coming down right now.
They are going to bring you up.
The Coast Guard is here.
You are going to be fine.
We're going to get you home.
- (MUSIC PLAYING)
- (SOFT GASPING)
(PANTING)
Hey! Hey!
Kate!
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(DISTORTED SHOUT)
Oh, Kate!
(LAUGHS, EXHALES)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC FADES)
("DOWN IN THE WOODS"
BY RICHARD HAWLEY PLAYING)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(SONG ENDS)