Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Son of a bitch!
No, we can't touch the munis.
We'll use them as collateral for
a leveraged equity position in Cisco.
Then I want you to take everything out of
First National and move it over to Banyon.
Wait, you mean Delaware?
I thought that was dead.
That's resurrected.
We need to clean up the
Reynolds account...
in case those fucks at AML
decide to do their job.
Are you sure about this?
Nothing on email.
Move everything back on Monday.
You paying attention?
Yeah, yeah, I am.
- Tickets?
- I don't know if...
I'm sending the numbers through now.
What about Green?
Uh, stall him. I don't give a shit.
Call in sick if you have to.
Business or pleasure?
I don't know. I just...
Seriously?
Look, I don't know
if I feel comfortable...
Josh! Josh! Stop being such a pussy.
Just do what I tell you to do,
and call me when it's done.
To my fellow members of the board.
A man cannot unsee the truth.
He cannot willingly return to darkness...
or go blind once he has
the gift of sight...
any more than he can be unborn.
We are the only species
capable of self-reflection.
The only species
with the toxin of self-doubt
written into our genetic code.
Unequal to our gifts, we build,
we buy, we consume.
We wrap ourselves in the illusion
of material success.
We cheat and deceive as we claw our way...
to the pinnacle of what
we define as achievement.
Superiority to other men.
Corner office.
Who'd you have to blow?
I heard he closed the Reynolds account.
How exactly did you do that?
Just that good, I guess.
Don't forget about us little people.
Oh, how could I?
You know how I take my coffee.
Excuse me, but they wanna see you
upstairs in the partners boardroom.
Tell them I'll be right there.
Oh, and tomorrow
is your mother's birthday.
Get her something for me, would you?
Of course.
There is a sickness inside us.
Rising like the bile that leaves that
bitter taste at the back of our throats.
It's there in every one of you
seated around the table.
We deny its existence until one day
the body rebels against the mind...
and screams out,
"I am not a well man."
No doubt you will think
only of the merger.
That unclean melding of two
equally diseased institutions.
But the truth cannot be ignored.
For only when we know what ails us
can we hope to find the cure.
I will not return.
Do not attempt to contact me again.
Sincerely, Roland E. Pembroke.
Well, Mr. Lockhart...
what do you make of that?
Clearly, he's lost his mind.
Our thoughts exactly.
Man goes for a two-week spa vacation,
and has a complete mental breakdown.
Who the hell takes the waters
in the 21 st century anyway?
I trust you understand the sensitivity
of some of the information in that letter.
So it's true.
A merger of this kind will make us...
one of the biggest financial service firms
on the Eastern Seaboard.
Something that stands to
enrich everyone in this room.
Including you.
We hear good things.
Your work on the Reynolds
account was inspired.
Of course, the SEC will want
unfettered access to our books.
Any irregularities are sure to come out.
You didn't really think
we wouldn't find out?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You think there's a trick
you can pull we haven't tried?
This is amateur.
Can I ask you something, Mr. Lockhart?
You ever have a 12-inch
black dick in your ass?
Prison, Mr. Lockhart.
You're in a lot of trouble.
If that were the case,
you would have already turned me in.
So, my guess is the SEC
is after someone a little more senior.
Someone on the board, perhaps.
Or someone who's clearly unstable.
We'd like you to go to Switzerland
and bring Mr. Pembroke back to us.
You see...
the merger cannot go through
without Mr. Pembroke signing off...
on certain legal matters.
I don't have the relationship
with Mr. Pembroke that Morris had.
Fuck Morris.
Now, Morris was a good salesman,
dependable family man.
God rest his soul.
But he didn't have vision.
Someone has to take responsibility.
Josh, it's me again.
In an hour and a half, the Nikkei closes.
When it does, I want you to empty
Banyon and buy puts in Glenco.
I'm sending the details over now.
And fucking call me back.
I don't like leaving messages like this.
You're here for the cure?
No, I'm just visiting.
You mind?
Go ahead.
You're younger than most of my passengers.
Do a lot of driving for the sanitarium?
All the driving.
Every week, I pick up
rich people from the train...
and take them up the mountain.
Only rich people, huh?
Must be expensive.
Well, wealthy people
have wealthy problems.
Me, I'm happy with a simple life.
That's it? No ambition?
Just drive people
up and down the mountain?
Most people tend to stay.
Why's that?
I guess they like it there.
Oh, shit.
I don't go in for spas
and that kind of thing.
I work for a living,
like my father before me.
A son learns what it is to
be a man from his father.
Am I right?
I wouldn't know.
I didn't grow up with my father.
How long will you be gone?
Just a few days. It's business.
You don't look well.
I'm fine. I just haven't been
sleeping much.
You need to rest.
You know, I always
told your father to rest...
but he wouldn't listen.
He was weak.
You didn't know him.
And whose fault is that?
So, are you happy here?
Are they taking good care of you?
People come here to die.
Why would I be happy?
I'm getting a promotion.
So, when I get back
I'll be able to move you
to somewhere better.
Somewhere near the beach or something.
You won't come back.
Of course I will.
Another ballerina?
She's not like the others.
Why's that?
She lives in a dream.
But she's dancing.
That's because she doesn't
know she's dreaming.
Friendly bunch.
Yeah.
There's always been bad blood
between the villagers
and the people on the hill.
Why's that?
History.
How old is this place?
Foundations date back
to the time of the barons.
For centuries, all this land
and everyone in it...
belonged to one family.
The Von Reichmerls.
What happened to them?
Hmm. Interesting story.
Apparently, the last baron
was so obsessed with
the purity of his bloodline...
he decided only his sister
was clean enough to carry his child.
When the church forbade
the union, he renounced God.
That must have gone over well.
No shit.
So on his wedding night...
the villagers came up the hill...
chased the Baron and his bride
into the catacombs...
and made him watch
while they burned her alive.
Then they burned
the whole place to the ground.
That's a hell of a story.
Yeah.
But that was 200 years ago.
A lot's changed since then.
20 minutes max.
No hurry.
Welcome!
May I help you?
I'm here to see a guest.
Mr. Roland Pembroke.
I'm sorry, but visiting hours
are over for the day.
I've come a long way.
Maybe you could make an exception.
There are no exceptions.
Is there a manager I could speak to?
Sign here.
Please.
Thank you, Mr. Lockhart.
I'll see what I can do.
You won't get any service here.
Part of the treatment.
You get used to it.
What's a ten-letter word for amnesty?
No idea.
Exemption.
Nope. That's only nine.
Absolution.
Yes!
You like puzzles?
Not really.
You mind?
Thank you.
I believe the reception nurse explained...
that visiting hours end
at 3:00 p.m. precisely.
She did. But as I'm sure you're aware...
Mr. Pembroke remains the CEO
of a major financial institution.
Under the circumstances,
I was hoping you can make an...
exception.
Vitamins.
If we are to help the people
that come here...
we must keep up our strength.
May one ask what it is concerning?
It's a business matter.
I'm not at liberty to say
any more than that.
Of course. And I hope you understand
that we also have our rules.
Our treatments here are most effective...
when exposure to the stresses
of the modern world is strictly limited.
Director Volmer is quite firm on that.
Hydrotherapy?
That is correct.
That's a long way to come just for water.
The sanitarium is built
over an ancient aquifer...
that offers uniquely
rejuvenating qualities.
Rebuilt.
After the fire.
Yes.
History is full of darkness.
If you would like to leave a note...
I'd happily pass it along to Mr. Pembroke.
Mr. Pieterson?
I understand the work
you do here is important...
and you're obviously a very busy man.
But if you wouldn't mind
finding time between
administering aqua aerobics
and Jacuzzis...
to inform Mr. Pembroke he has a visitor...
with information of the utmost
urgency to him personally...
I'd be grateful.
On the other hand, if you
want me to write a note...
so you can slip it under his door
with his breakfast tray...
on the off-chance he notices it
before his morning rubdown...
I'm afraid that's not gonna cut it.
You see, I just traveled
4,000 miles to get here.
There's a red-eye going back
to New York tonight...
and I intend Mr. Pembroke
and I to be on it.
You plan to take Mr. Pembroke
back to New York with you?
Is that a problem?
Of course, it is entirely
up to Mr. Pembroke.
He's a patient, not a prisoner.
He'll be in treatment until after 7:00.
If you'd like to come back then,
I'll make sure he's available.
Thank you for your understanding.
Leaving already?
What a nice-looking young man.
Where's your friend?
What time's the last train to Zurich?
Not till 10:00.
Get me to a hotel. I gotta make a call.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Pretty girl.
What the fuck!
How long will you be gone?
Just a few days.
Are we waiting for someone else?
There is no one else.
Sleep well?
Uh...
I can't remember having slept better.
It's the mountain air.
Mr. Lockhart...
my name is Henrich Volmer.
I am the director of the sanitarium here.
How long have I been here?
Three days.
Oh, Jesus!
You can count yourself lucky.
It was a clean break.
Although I do feel partly responsible.
The locals tell me I should hunt
the deer on the property...
but I can't bring myself to harm
the innocent creatures.
After all, they were here long before us.
I need to call New York.
I took the liberty
of informing your office
of the accident, if that's your concern.
They agreed with me...
that business can wait
and your health cannot.
Hank Green said that?
Even the acting head
of a major Wall Street finance firm...
can't argue with the consequences
of a serious car accident.
We don't get many visitors here.
Most of my patients have done
extraordinary things.
Built vast fortunes...
commanded great empires...
but at a terrible cost.
They have no one who cares for them.
Mr. Pembroke is lucky.
He has you.
So, do your best to relax.
Enjoy yourself.
You are at the foot of the Swiss Alps...
one of the most
beautiful places in the world.
Think of it as an enforced vacation.
Although I know you Americans
are not so good at vacations, are you?
And remember, you're at altitude.
It can take a while to acclimatize...
so please make sure
you drink plenty of water.
Believe me, you're in good hands.
Are you lost?
Uh... Yeah.
I guess so.
Where is it you're supposed to be?
I don't know.
Name?
Pembroke.
Roland Pembroke.
Here it is.
Pembroke. Room 609. Steam bath.
Of course.
Mr. Pembroke...
the steam baths are in that direction.
You can't go in there.
Not like that.
Pembroke?
It is Mr. Pembroke, isn't it?
Do I know you?
My name is Lockhart. Mr. Green sent me.
I thought they'd send Morris.
Morris is dead.
Heart attack.
Mr. Pembroke, I've come to
bring you back to New York.
You want me to leave here?
Just for a few days.
I'm afraid I can't do that.
Why not?
I'm not well.
You look all right to me.
That's because you are blind.
As I was.
But soon you'll see.
Rest assured,
they'll take good care of you here.
I'm not a patient.
What happened to your leg?
Mr. Pembroke, the situation in New York
is really quite serious.
No longer my concern.
The director says
I must not involve myself
in business matters.
Have you met Director Volmer?
This morning.
He is a great man.
Kind man.
Not like other doctors.
Mr. Pembroke...
This obsession with blood.
You see, they have it all wrong.
Do you know the body is 65% water?
It's our fluids that must be purified.
Word that the merger
is in trouble has leaked.
The share price is in free fall.
Lockhart?
You're not any relation
to Henry Lockhart, are you?
My father.
You knew him?
We started out together.
Terrible, what happened to him.
They said there was a boy left in the car.
I don't remember much, to be honest.
He didn't deserve what we did to him.
What do you mean?
He was an honest man.
And we destroyed him for it.
Well, people get fucked over every day.
Either you have what it takes
to survive, or you don't.
And I suppose you do.
Is that why you came all this way?
Ambition?
Then you have it worse than any of us.
What's that?
The sickness.
Your father saw the truth
long before the rest of us.
The pointlessness of the entire endeavor.
We've all done terrible things.
So many terrible things.
What's it trading at?
What?
The stock! What's it trading at?
Eight and a half at close on Friday.
Parasites.
It'll be lower by now.
We're all concerned for your
well-being, Mr. Pembroke.
Mmm.
Just a few days.
There are certain irregularities
in some of the accounts...
that need to be clarified before
the merger can be completed.
And I suppose someone
has to take responsibility.
Something like that.
Then I better get my things.
I need a car to take me to the station.
Will you call one for me, please?
I'll see what I can do.
That's where the baron hung the priest.
- What's that?
- See?
The church would have been
right over there...
where that funny little building is now.
I'm sure of it.
People used to come from miles around...
for the miracles attributed
to the holy water.
Guess some things don't change.
How marvelous.
Terrible thing, though. Such violence.
That's what you get
for marrying your sister.
Sister?
Yeah, it was all about
a pure bloodline, wasn't it?
How fascinating!
I must look into that.
Glad to see you're back on your feet!
We heard about the accident.
You're American, aren't you, Mister...
Lockhart.
Frank Hill. Stockholm.
And this is Mr. Nair from London.
Bombay, originally.
I see you've met Mrs. Watkins,
our amateur historian.
Yes, of course. How rude.
Victoria Watkins. 40 years at Xerox.
Why don't you pull up a chair?
We need a fourth.
Careful. Like most Brahmins, he cheats.
Coming from a venture capitalist,
I take that as a compliment.
Actually, I was just on my way back
to New York with Mr. Pembroke.
Then he's...
He's feeling better?
Well enough.
I suppose that's wonderful news.
Isn't that right, Mr. Nair?
Wonderful news.
Mrs. Watkins...
time for your treatment.
Yes, of course.
Pleasure to meet you, Mr. Lockhart.
Safe travels.
Something in the water?
At the bottom.
I don't see anything.
Did it hurt?
Can't remember.
Better that way.
I saw you.
Before.
Are you a patient here?
It's just, you're so much younger
than everyone else.
Director Volmer says I'm a special case.
What about you?
Are you here for the cure?
No.
Actually, I was just leaving.
No one ever leaves.
What are you talking about?
Why would anyone want to?
Yeah, I see your point.
Did you get what you came for?
Well, I came to bring
someone back to New York.
So, yeah. I did.
Does he want to go?
Not really.
That song you were singing.
Where did you learn that?
I have to go now.
What's your name?
Hannah.
Mr. Pembroke?
Where's Pembroke?
The patient that was
in this room, where is he?
I thought you were Pembroke.
Do you know what they used to recommend
for the common stomach ailment?
The application of leeches.
Based on the diagnosis,
I always pitied the leech.
Mmm. Mr. Lockhart...
please, won't you join us?
The sturgeon is excellent,
unless of course you prefer the venison.
I couldn't let it go to waste.
Where's Pembroke?
Mr. Pembroke has unfortunately
taken a turn for the worse.
I fear your conversation
about business matters...
has set him back somewhat.
But, no matter. We have moved him on
to the next stage of treatment.
He looked all right to me.
But you're not a doctor.
Maybe it's time for a second opinion.
That, of course, is up to Mr. Pembroke.
And he's not available.
Ever since I got here...
you people have been
giving me the runaround.
I would ask you please
to keep your voice down.
We wouldn't wanna upset
the clientele, would we?
Mr. Lockhart, giving you the runaround
is the furthest thing from my mind.
My sole concern is for
the welfare of my patients.
It's bad for business if
people start getting better.
Am I right?
What are you implying, Mr. Lockhart?
Old people paying through
the teeth for what? Water?
What's your overhead anyway?
That is not your concern.
I don't wanna have to
get lawyers involved...
but I came to get Pembroke
back to New York...
and that's what I'm gonna do,
if I have to hit him over his head...
and drag him out by his hair.
Are you feeling all right,
Mr. Lockhart? You seem pale.
I'm fine.
You're bleeding.
What?
Perhaps you should sit down.
No signs of concussion.
Any headaches, hallucinations?
No.
You may dress.
Are you drinking the water?
Yes.
Good.
Make sure you do.
I took the liberty of running a few tests
after the accident.
Hannah.
Isn't it?
Yes.
She's a very special case.
What does that mean exactly?
She was exposed to serious trauma
when she was very young.
Her development was delayed.
Hannah did not utter a word
until she was 11 years old.
Please understand...
Mr. Lockhart...
she is like a daughter to me.
But we're here to discuss you.
An imbalance in your fluids.
Strain to the major organs.
Depleted immune system.
Many indicators that you have in common
with most of my patients...
but I will confess
I have never seen a case...
as advanced as this...
in someone so young.
Is that right?
Tell me, Mr. Lockhart...
when was the last time
that you actually felt well?
Before you came here,
when was the last time...
that you even slept through the night?
The mind may lie...
but the body cannot.
I should like to help you.
What we offer here...
is a simple process of purification.
Away from pressures of the modern world.
A return to a simpler time.
Mr. Pembroke will not be ready
to travel for a day or two.
And if you're willing...
I would like to recommend a treatment.
I can speak to the duty nurse...
and we may be able to start
as early as this evening.
If you think it's necessary.
Good.
Greta?
You're in luck, Mr. Lockhart.
We can get you in right away.
"VR."
Von Reichmerl.
It was found during the reconstruction.
Then it belong to the baron?
The baroness, actually.
Vanessa Von Reichmerl.
She was sickly.
The Baron was obsessed
with finding a cure.
It was he, in fact, who first discovered
the medicinal properties of our water.
He sacrificed everything.
He must have loved her very much.
Yes.
Like a sister.
History is right, of course,
to judge him on moral grounds.
But, as a man of science...
I can't help but admire him.
The duty nurse will escort you
to our isolation wing.
Thank you.
Mr. Lockhart...
If you wouldn't mind.
Just so we can keep an eye
on your progress.
Are you ready, Mr. Lockhart?
Then let us begin.
Life on this planet first came from water.
We spend the first nine months
of our existence submerged...
our bodies mostly liquid.
This sensory deprivation chamber
simulates a return...
to that embryonic state.
Think of it as a cleansing of the mind...
as much as the body.
Some patients experience
increased heart rate...
visions...
even primal memories.
But rest assured,
it's just the toxins leaving the system.
Give yourself over completely
to the process...
and you will see the results.
Keep a close eye on him.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Lockhart...
the treatment lasts 30 minutes.
I'll be monitoring you from here.
If you have any issues...
just tap on the side of the tank.
Get back!
In the last five days, a total collapse.
The Dow plunging over 508 points...
as panic spread throughout Wall Street...
wiping out more than
one-third of the gains...
from this rare, five-year bull market.
More than half of that
in a single trading day.
Chairman of New York
Stock Exchange, John Phelan...
tried to reassure investors.
Dad?
Dad!
Mr. Lockhart, are you all right?
Get off me.
Try to stay calm.
I'm terribly sorry.
Something must have
gone wrong with the machine.
There's something in the water.
There's something in the fucking water.
There is nothing in the water,
Mr. Lockhart.
But I saw them.
As the Director explained...
some patients experience visions
with this particular treatment.
Just the toxins leaving the body.
It's all part of the cure.
You need to rest now.
I will help you to your room.
Got you.
Morning, Lockhart.
Feeling better?
Joining us for breakfast?
The kedgeree is excellent.
I'm not hungry.
You must keep up your strength.
Mrs. Watkins?
That building where the church
used to be...
What's it used for now?
I couldn't say.
You were right about
the baron and his sister.
But that's not the reason
the villagers burned the place down.
It was on account of the experiments.
Some sort of medical experiments.
Apparently performed on his own peasants.
People went missing.
And then...
Im Jahre 1814...
farmers, tilling their fields,
stumbled on human bodies...
disfigured and emaciated.
Dried up like the mummies of Egypt.
He was looking for a cure.
- A cure?
- For the baroness.
She was sick.
Oh, I see.
I knew you liked puzzles.
Of course.
Mrs. Watkins...
time for your treatment.
Are you certain?
I just had one this morning.
I'm sure of it.
I have you on the schedule.
I must not be feeling myself today.
There is a terrible darkness here.
What is this place?
I'm sorry. I don't understand.
I thought I saw you with a patient.
No. Patient.
Okay.
Thank you.
Going for a swim?
I'm not supposed to.
Why's that?
On the account of my condition.
Thought the water made you better.
Told you. I'm a special case.
Right.
How far is it to town?
A few miles, I think.
Are you going to walk all the way?
Unless you wanna lend me your bike.
What will you give me?
It was my mother's.
Her eyes are closed.
Yeah, she's dreaming.
She just doesn't know it.
What happens if she wakes up?
I don't know.
My mother never finished the story.
So, we got a deal?
How will you ride it?
Maybe you could come along.
I'm not supposed to.
You always do what you're supposed to do?
It's okay.
Coming?
Want a beer or something?
I don't know. Do I?
I don't know what you want.
All right. If you're having one.
Still here?
Thought you were just visiting.
You've looked better.
Same to you.
How's the car?
That car was a piece of shit.
Sanitarium offered me enough
to buy a new one.
So, gracias a Dios.
Everything happens for a reason, right?
You drink too much.
I hope you're not driving.
You two are from up on the hill?
That's right.
We don't get many patients down here.
Good kids at heart.
Just weren't raised properly.
No respect for tradition.
Know if there's a doctor in town?
All the doctors are up on the hill.
A pharmacist?
Something like that?
There's Pieter. Over the road.
He a doctor?
Close enough.
Don't you like it?
No.
What, you never had a beer before?
How long have you been at the sanitarium?
Since I can remember.
What about your family?
My mother died in a fire when I was young.
Director Volmer says that
my father will come for me
when I'm better.
Does he visit?
He'll come when I'm better.
- Vitamins?
- Mmm-hmm.
Can I try?
Um...
Okay.
Ugh.
Tastes like sweaty seafood.
You get used to it. Eventually.
Will you be okay here for a few minutes?
I just have to go see about something.
But I won't be long.
Uh... Yeah. Okay.
Hello?
Do you know if there's a doctor here?
What's that you're drawing?
He won't talk to you.
Doesn't know how.
That's the castle...
when they burned it down.
My grandson, Wilmosh.
He likes ghost stories.
What can I do for you?
Could you take a look at this,
tell me what it says?
Human?
That's right.
Not my line.
I'll pay you.
How much is this?
Not much.
But enough.
Got a tampon?
My friend's time of the month.
Freak.
So is he fit to travel?
He's not a well man.
Some of those are
dental records, aren't they?
- That's right.
- What do they mean?
His teeth are falling out.
What could cause something like that?
Barring any pre-existing
condition, I'd say...
chronic dehydration.
Dehydration?
All they do up there is drink water.
I'm not a doctor.
Now, if you'll excuse me...
Wait a second.
The baron's experiments.
They found bodies in the fields, right?
Dried up like mummies.
Maybe there's some kind of connection.
The baron was burned alive
on his wedding night 200 years ago.
Yeah, but this is happening now.
People come here for the cure.
That's what the baron was looking for.
His wife was sick.
She wasn't sick.
She was infertile.
They tried for years.
But the baroness could not
carry a child to term.
They say her body rejected the fetuses
because they were deformed.
Now, you must excuse me.
I have to put this animal
out of its misery.
What's wrong with it?
Wandered off where
it wasn't supposed to be.
Broke its leg.
Like you.
Found it trapped in a drainage ditch...
drinking sewage water.
I need to make a phone call.
Long distance.
Your credit card.
Lockhart.
Mr. Green.
Where the hell have you been?
I have a question.
Did Pembroke have
any pre-existing conditions?
What are you talking about?
Before he got here.
Any medical conditions? Was he sick?
No. The guy is a fucking health nut.
Drank kale for Christ's sake.
Now what the fuck is going on?
You were supposed to be here
four days ago.
Yeah. But there was an accident.
What accident?
What?
I don't understand.
They said they called you.
Nobody called.
Are you sure about that?
Lockhart, do I have to reiterate to you...
the importance of what
you've been sent there to do?
Get Pembroke on a plane
within the next 24 hours...
or this whole place goes ass over tits.
And you with it. Understand me?
Lockhart?
Lockhart!
- I need to speak with you
- Hey, hey, hey.
You said no one ever leaves.
What does that mean?
You're hurting me.
- What happens to them?
- Please let me go.
Why won't they let me see Pembroke?
You know something, don't you?
No.
What is this stuff?
What makes you special?
Fuck off, Adolf!
Hey!
- Come on.
- No!
- I paid for this dance.
Let her go!
Go back to the sanitarium, cripple.
No!
No! Please, stop!
I am not a patient.
Hannah.
She may look like a woman...
but she's just a child.
Ignorance, Mr. Lockhart...
is the great enemy of science.
I wanna see Pembroke.
And you will.
Coming, Mr. Lockhart?
Nothing happened.
That's because I arrived when I did.
Lockhart was there.
With a knife to his throat.
Hannah...
Mr. Lockhart is not able
to look after himself,
let alone you.
He can't protect you the way I can.
I don't need protecting.
Of course you do.
We were just having fun.
He's not like the others.
He's young.
What?
- What is it?
- Nothing.
- Let me see.
- No.
I'm your doctor. Come here.
No! Don't touch me!
When will I be ready?
Soon.
When?
Patience.
Come here.
I said, come here.
Now, haven't I always looked after you?
Soon, I will make you better.
And you will thank me.
And my father will come?
Yes.
Get some rest, my little lamb.
Bitte?
I have a problem with my...
May I?
I'll just pop it in some milk, shall I?
There we are.
Mrs. Watkins?
Where's Pembroke?
You took him.
Back to New York.
What? No.
They moved him. He's down here somewhere.
You told me about
the experiments, remember?
Your puzzle?
I like puzzles.
Yeah.
I left it for you.
You'll see.
Listen to me.
The experiments...
I think they're happening again.
The baroness was infertile.
Not experiments.
A cure.
She was pregnant the night of the wedding.
Before they burned her...
the villagers cut out the fetus...
and threw it in the aquifer.
The child survived.
She doesn't know.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I'm sorry, I don't understand.
Take it easy.
Marcus!
It's all right.
Mr. Lockhart...
every time I turn around,
you're somewhere
you're not supposed to be.
I guess I'm lost.
I'm just trying to find
my way back to my room.
This is a restricted floor.
There are signs everywhere.
Surely you didn't just wander
down here by accident?
What is it exactly that
you are looking for?
I had a problem with my tooth.
Your tooth?
Actually, it's feeling much better.
If you could just point me
in the direction of my room.
Nonsense.
We can't let you get an infection.
You must let us take care of you.
After all...
that's why you're here.
Doctor Brennan takes care
of all our patients' dental needs.
I'm sorry.
Hmm?
About Hannah.
It won't happen again.
Hmm.
Tell me...
what were you doing in town?
Just having a beer.
Ah. Hmm.
What are you doing?
Get your hands off me!
It's all for your own safety,
Mr. Lockhart.
We don't believe in chemical
anesthesia at the institute.
The impurities inhibit the cure.
But, you will find that
with a proper focus...
the mind can overcome any amount of pain.
Trust, Mr. Lockhart. Hmm?
I mean, if we can't trust each other...
then how can I help you?
Mrs. Abramov...
so glad that you are here.
How long do we have you with us?
Just two weeks.
I probably overpacked.
Nonsense.
You'll be surprised
how time just slips away
here at the institute.
Drive!
What happened to your face?
Just drive!
They held me down and pulled my tooth out.
They threatened me.
Why would they do that?
Because I know what they've done.
There is a room full of bodies
floating in tanks like specimens.
These are very serious allegations.
No shit.
Director Volmer is a well-respected man.
The sanatorium is of great importance
for the local economy.
Take me up there,
and I'll show you what I saw.
Do you have any identification on you?
No, they have everything.
Well, then, is there someone
I could speak to...
who might confirm you are
who you say you are? Family?
I hope you understand the need
to verify your identity.
You can call my office.
All right.
Can I get you coffee or tea?
You got anything stronger?
Of course.
Rest assured...
we will get to the bottom of this.
Thank you.
Mr. Lockhart,
we've been worried about you.
Stay away from me!
Is this man a patient of yours?
Yes, that's right.
I'm not a patient. I was in an accident.
You signed the admission form.
I have it right here.
That's bullshit.
I did warn you about
possible delusions, remember?
A side effect of the toxins
leaving the body.
And my leg, is that a delusion?
Mr. Lockhart has been a disruptive element
since he arrived.
He stole confidential medical files...
assaulted a member of our Dental staff...
and threatened Mr. Pembroke.
I didn't threaten anybody!
I believe your exact words were...
"If I have to, I'll hit him over the head
"and drag him out by his hair."
I was sent here to bring
Pembroke back to New York!
According to your employer, a Mr. Green...
you're being investigated
by the Securities and Exchange Commission.
You're one of them.
Listen to yourself, Mr. Lockhart.
You're not a well man.
Stop saying that!
- Let us help you.
- Get back!
I know about the experiments.
The baron and his wife.
He has been spending time
with Mrs. Watkins.
Who is Watkins?
She was institutionalized
before she came to us.
The others humor her...
but clearly Mr. Lockhart's condition
has made him susceptible
to her conspiracies.
I know what you're
trying to do. All of you.
You're trying to make me think I'm insane.
I have seen this before.
It's not uncommon.
Some deep-seated childhood
trauma rises to the surface...
something a patient has been running from
their entire life.
In your case...
I would say misplaced guilt...
over the death of your father.
How do you know about that?
I never told you that.
You didn't have to.
That's why you came to us, isn't it?
I saw him.
Pembroke is dead.
That's what this is all about?
The evil doctor killing off his patients?
That's right.
All right. Perhaps we should
consult Mr. Pembroke.
Do you know this man?
He tried to take me back against my will.
Pembroke?
Please keep him away from me.
You were dead.
- Do you wish press charges?
- That won't be necessary.
Mr. Lockhart is not a criminal.
He is a patient.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
To the members of the board...
You sent me here for a purpose.
To retrieve a man against his will...
and bring him back to your world.
But I realize now...
that is not the reason I am here.
There is a sickness inside each of us.
We do our best to deny its existence...
dealing in lies...
and distraction.
Until one day the body
rebels against the mind
and screams out...
"I am not a well man."
A man cannot unsee the truth.
He cannot willingly return to darkness...
or go blind once he has
the gift of sight...
any more than he can be unborn.
Fuck.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hannah!
Stay away from me.
- Hannah.
- Stay away from me.
- We need to go.
- I said stay away!
There. Everything is all right.
Please enjoy your meal.
Hannah?
What have you done?
What's happening to me?
Here, here, here.
It's all right. You're safe now.
Leave her alone.
Haven't you upset her enough,
Mr. Lockhart?
Please, escort the patient
back to his room.
I am not a fucking patient!
Come on!
Had enough of cripples and old people?
Try it with me!
That's enough! Mr. Lockhart...
I can see you're extremely upset.
Why don't you come with me to my office...
and we can discuss
whatever's on your mind.
No.
We're gonna talk about it right here.
In front of everybody.
I don't think that's a good idea.
He's making you sick.
This place is making you sick!
It's in the water.
Mr. Lockhart.
I saw the bodies dried up like mummies!
Look at you people!
Your teeth are falling out!
You're dying, and you can't even see it.
But I'm here for the cure.
There is no cure!
Don't you see?
He's the one that is making you sick!
There's nothing wrong with you people!
I wouldn't do that, if I were you.
There's nothing wrong with you.
Yes.
Yes!
That's it!
Stand up!
Come on!
Yes!
Stand up!
He is making you sick!
Yes, that's it. Come on.
That's it!
There's nothing wrong with you!
I am not well.
What are you doing?
Get the fuck off me!
No. No, no!
Get off me.
Help me! Help!
Pembroke.
What have they done to you?
Done to me?
I've never felt better.
Relax, Mr. Lockhart.
It'll all be over soon.
Ah, yes. Remarkable creatures.
Anywhere else on the planet,
this species lives a dozen years, at most.
Here, in our aquifer...
they can live 300.
For the human physiology...
the effect of the water can be quite toxic
as you have discovered.
Unless, of course,
it is properly filtered.
The baron devised the process.
Using the bodies of peasants
that belonged to his land...
he managed to distill the water...
to its life-giving essence.
Of course, he paid
a terrible price for his ingenuity.
His only mistake...
was to use subjects who were unwilling.
Luckily, times have changed.
The last 200 years
have been the most
productive in human history.
Man rid himself of God...
of hierarchy, of everything
that gave him meaning...
until he was left worshiping
the empty altar of his own ambition.
That is why they come.
Men like you.
You're quite right, Mr. Lockhart.
No one ever leaves.
What you fail to understand
is that no one wants to.
Do you know what the cure
for the human condition is?
Disease.
Because only then
is there hope for a cure.
I don't understand.
For so many years,
I've tried to protect you...
from the impurities of the outside world.
But ironically, it is
your friend Mr. Lockhart
who we have to thank.
You're a woman now.
But I'm not well.
And I will always be here
to take care of you.
She's awake now.
You made me believe
I could leave here one day.
Why would anybody wanna leave?
What is it?
Come.
What is this place?
This is where you began.
I don't want to.
You know...
you look just like she did
on her wedding night.
The night they took her from me.
The villagers cut out the fetus
and threw it in the aquifer.
The child survived.
Please don't.
Don't be frightened.
Soon we'll be a family again.
The way we were always meant to be.
It's all right.
My sister was also
somewhat resistant, at first.
But after a while, she grew to like it.
We tried so many times
to make something pure.
That something was you, my love.
And now...
we can begin again.
I've waited so long.
So long.
He will have you. Yes?
Yes.
You can't keep her here forever.
No?
And what do you think would
become of her in your world?
People like you come to me in droves
with your disposable lives.
She's your daughter.
And what have you ever loved, hmm?
What have you ever sacrificed?
This is what the outside world has to offer.
You're right.
No.
Fire. Fire!
Everything I have built has been for her.
You think I would let someone
like you destroy that?
Dad?
Hannah.
Magnificent, isn't it?
Lockhart!
It's time to go.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Are you okay?
- Jesus Christ.
Easy, easy.
Lockhart?
My God.
What have you done?
Where's Pembroke?
He's gone.
What do you mean "gone"?
Get in the car.
You came here to perform a task, remember?
Now get in the car.
Did you hear what I said?
Have you lost your mind?
Actually...
I'm feeling much better.
Where the hell are you going?
Lockhart! Lockhart!