Subtitles by explosiveskull
Why are you laughing?
I am so scared.
- Why?
- I don't know.
Don't be scared.
When I was little and we used to move
all the time, I'd write these notes,
and I would fold them
up really small...
...and I would hide
them in different places,
so that if I ever wanted to go back,
there'd be a piece of me there waiting.
- Did you ever go back?
- No.
See? That's what I'm saying.
'Cause I didn't need to.
What'd they say?
They were just like,
old rhymes and poems.
Things I wanted to
remember about...
...living in that house
or what I liked about it.
Why did you leave?
Why'd you leave
all those houses?
'Cause I didn't have a choice.
Some weird noises in this house.
What are you doin'?
I was just trying to see how
heavy it was, if I could move it.
I just had it tuned.
That was like a year ago.
But it's still
- still in tune.
Should I try and find movers?
- For the piano?
- Yeah.
Mmm. Are we taking it with us?
She said we can if we want to.
Um... we can probably find
a better one if we just...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Is there something there?
What was that?
I don't know.
Maybe something
fell on the piano.
What time is it?
My heart's racing.
Can I have a minute?
- Wait.
- Yes?
Never mind.
Are you okay?
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
- I'll be just around the corner.
- Thank you.
No, no, it's not your fault.
Well, we were gonna be...
Are you gonna be
okay to drive home?
Yeah. Are you?
Thanks for taking me out.
Yeah.
It was fun.
Call me next week.
Okay.
Hey.
This shouldn't be so hard.
I really don't wanna talk about
this anymore tonight, okay?
Well,
can we talk about it tomorrow?
'Kay, maybe.
Here.
* Are you runnin' late? *
* Did you sleep too much? *
* All the awful dreams *
* Felt real enough *
* Is your lover there? *
* Is she wakin' up? *
* Did she die in the night? *
* And leave you alone? *
* Alone *
* Mirror, mirror *
* There's your crooked nose *
* What a stupid game *
* Getting nothing done *
* With your longest track *
* Your highest score *
* While you
crush your back *
* And lament the war *
* War *
* Am I runnin' late? *
* I get overwhelmed *
* All the awful dreams *
* All the bright screens *
* Is my lover there? *
* Are we breakin' up? *
* Did she find someone else?
*
* And leave me alone? *
* Alone *
Okay?
Carlos!
No, no, no, no. Si, no.
Okay?
Yasmina.
Mama.
* Breathe this moment like
it's gonna be my last one *
* Light it up, burn it down...
*
I don't know if you
believe in the spirit world.
- I do.
- You do?
Yeah, I totally do.
Well, then this next phenomenon
will really fascinate you.
I know it sounds strange,
but it does begin with,
"Pick a card, any card",
so pick one out.
And you got it?
- Burn the image into your mind.
- Yeah. Got it, got it.
I want you to watch
this very closely.
Because if the spirits are
with us in this haunted house...
...they may divine the card.
Holy shit.
I don't-I don't- I don't have a problem
with it if it's two people in love.
It's some sort of expression of,
you know, kind of...
It sounds like you don't
think women should do that.
If it's not gonna be that and it's not
gonna make us any money, then why...
And those are your
two polarities?
Polarities?
Priorities or whatever.
Money's just money.
You gotta take that out
of the equation. Now what?
Well, that's what I was saying.
It's not just...
No, no, you can find a reason.
And I wanna find out
what happens, too!
So, no money.
What have you got left?
You've got... other people.
You got Clara, you've got time.
Time's a big one.
But you've got about as much
as anyone else, give or take.
What about God?
Maybe you've got God.
Do you?
- What? Have God?
- Yes.
No.
Okay.
Well,
here's how I break it down.
A writer writes a novel.
A songwriter writes a song.
A symphonist writes a symphony,
which is maybe the best example
because all the best
ones were written for God.
So, tell me what happens if Beethoven's
writing his "Ninth Symphony"
and suddenly he wakes up one day
and realizes that God doesn't exist.
So, suddenly all of these
notes and chords and harmonies
that were intended to,
you know, supersede the flesh,
you realize, "Oh,
that's just physics."
So Beethoven says,
"Shoot, God doesn't exist,
so I guess I'm writing
this for other people.
It's just nuts and bolts now."
He didn't have any children,
that I can recall,
- but if he did...
- He had a nephew.
- He had a what?
- A nephew, he had a nephew.
Okay. Great.
So he-he writes it for him.
Or Immortal Beloved.
Yes.
Or for whoever that was.
But let's leave love out of this and
let's wrap this all up under the blanket
of someone thinking, "This is something
that they'll remember me for."
And they did. And we do.
And sure enough,
we do what we can to endure.
We build our legacy piece by piece, and
maybe the whole world will remember you,
or maybe just a
couple of people,
but you do what you can to make sure
you're still around after you're gone.
And so we're still
reading this book,
we're still singing the song,
and kids remember their
parents and their grandparents
and everyone's got their family tree,
and Beethoven's got his symphony,
and we've got it too.
And everyone will keep
listening to it f...
...for the foreseeable future.
But...
...that's where things start
breaking down, because your kids...
Do you have kids?
Wait, who here has kids?
You? Your kids are gonna die.
Yours too. Yours too.
Hey, just sayin'.
They're all gonna die,
and their kids will die,
and so on, and so on.
And then there's gonna be one
big-one big tectonic shift.
Yosemite will blow and the
Western plates will shift,
and the oceans will rise,
the mountains will fall,
and 90 percent of
humanity will be gone.
One fell swoop.
This is just science.
Whoever's left will...
...go to higher ground
and social order will fall away,
and we will revert to
scavengers and hunters
and gatherers,
but maybe there's someone...
...someone who one day hums
a melody they used to know.
And it gives everyone
a little bit of hope.
Mankind's on the verge
of being wiped out,
but it keeps going
a little bit longer
because someone hears someone
else hum a melody in a cave
and the physics
of it in their ear
make them feel something other
than fear or hunger or hate,
and mankind carries on
and civilization gets back on track.
And now you're thinking
you're gonna finish that book.
But it won't last.
'Cause by and by,
the planet's gonna die.
In a few billion years the
sun will become a red giant
and it'll, uh,
eventually swallow Earth whole.
This is a fact.
Now, maybe by that point,
we'll have set up shop on some
completely different planet.
Good for us.
Maybe we've figured out a way
of carrying with us all
these things that matter.
They've got a photocopy
of the Mona Lisa out there,
someone sees it, mixes a little
bit of alien dirt with some spit,
paints something new,
the whole thing keeps going.
But even that doesn't matter.
Because even if
some form of mankind
carries some recording of
Beethoven's "Ninth Symphony"
all the way into the future,
the future's gonna hit a brick wall.
The universe will
keep expanding,
and it'll eventually
take all matter with it.
Everything you've ever strived for,
everything that you and some stranger
on the other side of the planet
share with some future stranger
on some entirely different
planet without even knowing it,
everything that ever made
you feel big or stand up tall,
it'll all go.
Every atom in this dimension...
...will be pulled apart
by force as simple as...
And then all these shredded particles
will contract again...
...and the universe is gonna
suck itself back into a speck
too small for any of us to see.
So, you can write a book...
...but the pages will burn.
You can sing a song
and pass it down.
You can write a play and hope
that folks will remember it...
...keep performing it.
You can build your
dream house...
...but ultimately none
of that matters any more
than digging your fingers into
the ground to bury a fence post.
Or... or fucking.
Which I guess is just
about the same thing.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Thank you, O Lord,
for these, Thy blessings,
which we are about to
receive from Thy bounty.
Through Christ, our Lord. Amen.
This is good.
We'll have this house built.
Put it right there.
There. You see it?
I know you can see it.
A little house at first, but...
...I'll build you a bigger one.
Here we are.
Take a look around.
We've got two, uh, bedrooms
back there with a bathroom.
The kitchen's that way.
There's a study/den.
We, uh, haven't had any
tenants in a few months...
- ...so it's a little musty.
- Does it come with the piano?
Oh, it's... always...
It's always been here.
- It's... If you want...
- Does it come?
It's always been here.
- I can't hear you.
- I...
Yeah, if you keep playing...
- ...you can't here me.
- I'm just kidding.
Uh, it's always been here.
If you want,
I can have it removed.
No.
I-I gotta take this.
Um, make yourself at home.
Thank you, Linda.
Hello?
Hey.
Oh, no,
I'm showing a house right now.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
* Are you runnin' late? *
* Did you sleep too much? *
* All the awful dreams *
* Felt real enough *
* Is your lover there? *
* Is she wakin up? *
* Did she die in the night? *
* Leave you alone? *
* Alone *
* Mirror, mirror *
* There's your crooked nose *
* Boring hair *
* A dozen wrinkles *
- * No children *
- Come on.
* Just emptiness *
- * No place like home *
- Which is fine. I get it.
That's what people do. They leave, they
go away, and then they come home again.
I'm the one who's always here.
* Mess *
* 20 messages *
* Did you hurt your thumbs? *
What is it you like
about this house so much?
Seriously?
History?
What does that mean?
Honey, we've got history.
Not as much as you think.
This isn't how it's
supposed to work.
We're supposed to make
decisions together.
Can't you understand that?
Yes.
So why am I the only
one making them?
Because I don't
want what you want.
'Cause you want to stay here?
Mm-hmm.
Why?
Hey.
What?
It's okay. We can go.
We can go.
I don't understand.
Something fell on the piano.
What time is it?
Subtitles by explosiveskull