How was your day today?
How was it?
First tell me about yourself
Who do you think you are?
Do you know who this is?
Don't know?
It's your family
Want to see it again?
Fine then
Can you tell me
about that day?
About what happened?
You should be able
to remember it clearly
It's okay
From now on
tell me what happened
Aren't you getting out?
Su-yeon
Su-yeon!
It's so pretty
Give me your hand
The other one
Why?
Su-mi!
Welcome home!
It's been such a long time
You've changed
so much Su-yeon
You've gotten prettier
But you two
really disappointed me
I waited all day for you two
cooking and cleaning the house
but why didn't
you say hi first?
What did you do?
Were you at the wharf?
You should've changed first
before you went outside
Anyway
welcome back home
Is something wrong?
I see you've gotten better
I'm so glad
you feel better now
You're taking after your mom
You're feeling
a lot better too right?
Right
I bet you're both tired
Get some rest
and come down for dinner
I'm preparing a
special dinner
But you should
give me some time
There's a lot to prepare
We just got back
Things don't look
so good right now
It wouldn't help much
if you came
Yeah I know
Let's talk later
I should go
So you're doing okay right?
Did I tell you?
Sun-kyu and his wife
are coming over
lt'll be alright
I'll take care of it
Okay bye
Oh right!
I invited Sun-kyu and his wife over
for dinner this weekend
Really?
Lt'll be nice for them to
see the girls after so long
And to catch up on things
That was delicious
Sorry I have things to tend to
You must be tired
so clean it up tomorrow
Did you prepare
your father's undergarments?
Thanks but that's my job
Cleaning my room is my job too
Why'd you touch my stuff?
That's how it was before
So all of the same clothes
were hanging there before?
I'm not having
dinner with him
What?
I said I'm not having
dinner with that guy
He's not some guy
he's your uncle
It's the first day
so let's give it a rest
And you?
Yes?
Aren't you going to follow her?
You're supposed to follow your sister
What did that woman tell you?
If she ever gets on your case
then tell me
And don't ignore it like before
Okay?
Good night
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What's wrong?
Did you have a bad dream?
Was it the closet?
Then what's wrong?
I keep hearing
strange noises outside
It's because
you've been away too long
It's okay
Let's sleep
Somebody came into my room
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
He's asleep
I know
Then why are you trying to wake him?
Says who?
You were trying
to wake him just now
Have something to tell him?
It's none of your business
All I'm saying is
since his fast asleep
Don't wake him up
Don't you understand me?
I just came down for water
He's asleep so be quiet
Did you go to my room?
Yes
Who was it?
That woman
Stepmom?
Yeah
It's strange
What is?
That woman is strange
And so is this house
Are you scared?
Everything's alright
I'm here
Come here
Let's sleep
I'll always be with you
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Su-yeon Go away
Are you awake?
Yes
Can I come in?
No
Come down and eat
What are you doing?
Are you having your period?
No Su-yeon is
Su-yeon?
That's so funny
How could we both get our periods
on the same date?
Su-mi
It's okay come down
That's mom's favorite huh?
Do it like this
Shall we kill them?
Let's set them free
She'll have a cow
if we mess with her precious
I'd hate to see that
Su-mi
What are you doing
out in the cold?
Are you alright?
Why?
You don't look so good
Are you feeling sick?
No I'm okay
Tell me what's wrong?
I said I'm okay
Just get rid of
Su-yeon's closet
Su-mi
we agreed not to talk about
that closet
You promised right?
Su-mi
I know you're
very angry with me
And I know I'm a bad father
You're not even a bad father
It's cold so let's go inside
I will
What are you doing?
You scared me
When did you come in?
Did you go to the warehouse?
Yeah
Su-yeon look at this
Tada!
Wow
Cool
Pretty huh?
Is it mom's?
Yup and
There's more
It's mom!
Taritakoom taritakoom
What does that mean?
It's a spell to call mom
Who told you that?
Mom did
What?
Can I take this?
Huh? Sure
This and this
Wait!
What is this?
Who did this to you?
Tell me who did this?
It's okay tell me
She did this huh?
She did this didn't she?
Su-yeon
what's wrong with you?
I told you to
tell me everything!
She did this right?
She did this huh?
Did she do this?
Tell me! Tell me!
What?
How can you be so cruel?
It's retribution
If you disobey
you need to be punished
Does dad know what you did?
Think your father
can solve everything?
Then go get him
Want me to do it?
Sit down!
Where are your manners?
Were you like this
to your mom too?
Don't bring up my mom!
Listen carefully
I'm your mother got it?
As much as you hate it
I'm the only one in this world
you can call mother got it?
Crying over your mom's photos
won't change anything
Hard to handle huh?
That's too bad
But that's how the world is
The world isn't as sweet
as you picture it
Sometimes you have to bear the worst
and live on
Like the way
I'm bearing you two!
Tough isn't it?
I have beared you two brats
from the moment I came to this house
I have never met such ill-mannered
menaces like you two
What?
Why the hell did
you even come here?
I can't believe you
said that to me again
I see you still must be sick
Don't touch me
Let go!
What's wrong with you?
Are you that clueless?
Don't touch me
with those filthy hands!
Su-mi listen to me
I don't want to hear it
You're the same
That's not true
you've misunderstood
You're not even
accepting all this
Why is it always me?
Why are you asking only me
to understand?
Are you really clueless?
Yeah
Maybe I don't know
I don't have all the answers
I don't know so tell me
and let it off your chest
Tell me!
Will it change anything?
Will it?
Su-mi
Don't do this
Please don't
You'll get sick again
What?
Fine
From now on
anything that happens here
all the filthy things
you brought here
be responsible for it all
I have nothing more to say
so answer the phone
Do you remember?
My memory's a bit blurry
but I think it did happen
When was it?
Hey remember this?
You jumped into the rive
to catch some fish
Then you started to drown
and everyone had a fit
There was another funny story
What was it?
Oh yeah I remember
Remember that crazy guy?
The funny thing is
is that he was always normal
but whenever it rained
he went nuts
While plowing the field
he'd strip off his clothes
when it rained
and run out into the highway
The funniest time was
when it rained off and on
So he'd put on and take off
his clothes again and again
Then he got sick of it
and just went into his house
Everyone in the neighborhood
laughed so much back then
But when
But when he was little
he saw him doing that once
He saw him doing that once
and then he ran together
with that crazy guy
Our mom saw that
and she almost passed out
Do you remember?
You remember right?
Say something
Don't you remember?
You remember right?
No
I don't remember
What?
I said I don't remember
Why don't you remember?
Are you crazy?
Mi-hee!
Wait hold on to her
What's wrong?
Wake up!
Bring some water
Are you alright Mi-hee?
Water water
I'm sorry it's all my fault
Mi-hee!
It's okay
It's alright Mi-hee
It's alright
I'm sorry
I didn't want to come
but your father begged me to
so I had no choice
Honey
Yes?
I saw something strange
in that house
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What did you see?
There was a girl
under the sink
Just go in
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Can't you just stay here?
Why?
It's strange
What's strange?
After the girls came down
weird things have been
happening in this house
Don't say stupid things
Didn't you see it?
You're just having a hard time adjusting
You'll get better if you rest
No
There's something
in this house
I'll look around
so lie down
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Open the door!
Open it!
Open the god damn door!
I'll show you
Get up!
Get off the bed
Get off now!
I said now!
Come here right now!
You pest
Talk!
A person can't get any rest
around this household
Tell me
Who did it?
Who?
Better tell me the truth
Who did it!
Was it Su-mi?
You two need
to learn a lesson!
Was it your sister?
So do you feel better looking
at your dead mom's things?
Feel happy
after seeing the photos?
Say that you're sorry
Until you do don't even
think about coming out
There's no use in crying
Say that you're sorry
and beg for forgiveness!
I'm sorry
What?
Say it right
I'm sorry
I'll ask you once more
You're admitting
that you're sorry right?
Stop crying
I don't want to hear it
so stop it now!
Are you
Are you mad?
Is that why you're crying?
Fine let's see
how long you hold up
This will put some sense
into you two
Su-yeon
Su-yeon I'm sorry
I didn't hear you
I'm sorry Su-yeon
I'm sorry
This won't happen again
I promise
Don't cry it's okay
Tell me
What?
Why the hell
are you doing this?
Tell me why you've acted
so weird since you got here
You really don't know?
Don't know what? What is it?
I'm talking about
what that woman is doing to us!
So tell me what has she done?
She keeps harassing Su-yeon
What?
Didn't you hear me?
I said she keeps harassing Su-yeon!
She's vicious evil
and always locks Su-yeon up
in the closet!
Su-mi please stop it
Stop what?
You know that
Su-yeon is scared of her
Su-yeon you tell dad
Stop crying
and tell him now
Tell him!
Please stop it!
Su-yeon is dead
What?
No
Su-yeon is dead
So pull yourself together
How long will you keep this up?
It's not true Su-yeon
Su-yeon
Su-yeon No No
Come down tomorrow
I can't do it alone
Hmm
She's getting worse
I'll pick you up
call me when you get here
Su-yeon!
Su-mi!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Su-yeon!
I am fed up with your family
How did we come to this?
Don't you get it yet?
Remember what
I told you before?
Remember when I said
you'll regret it some day?
You
Know what's really scary?
You want to forget something
Totally wipe it off of your mind
But you never can
It can't go away you see
And
And it follows you around
like a ghost
Help me
Sure I'll help you
Let's end it here
Su-mi!
Where's Su-mi?
Where?
Please stop it
I'm sick of it now
Take this
you'll feel much better
Su-mi!
Don't you get it yet?
You're just having
a hard time adjusting
You still must be sick
You promised not to
bring up that closet
How could we both get our periods
on the same date?
Su-yeon is dead!
No I don't remember!
Su-mi are you okay?
It's all over now
You'll feel better here
Get some rest
I'll come and visit often
Take care of yourself
Bye
Su-mi what's wrong?
Let go
Let go Su-mi
Please stop it and let go
No I'll get it
Let me take one
Mom
Su-yeon!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Mom?
Mom? Mom mom!
Mom! Mom mom mom!
Mom!
Didn't you hear something?
Why'd you come up here?
Dad's not here
What do you mean by that?
Now you're trying
to act like mom
Do me a favor
Stay out of our lives
Can you get out of the way?
I have to go
You
You might regret this moment
Keep that in mind!
What can be worse
than standing here with you?
When you're here
I wanna be as far away
from you as I can
Understand?
Su-mi!
Help me Su-mi
Su-mi Su-mi
Su-mi
Subtitles ßy MühàmmáÐ Ü§mâñ