All right, kitty cats.
You ready to carve
the pumpkins or what?
- Hey, I was watching that.
- Sorry.
He wasn't watching that.
You weren't watching that.
Yes, I was.
All right then,
what was it?
A monster movie.
Fine, I'll put it back on.
Hey, Miss Witch, why don't you give
those fingers a rest...
and go wash your face.
I will.
What time are my parents coming home?
Uh, I don't know.
1:00? Hopefully sooner.
I get to stay up till one?
No, bedtime's at 11.
Stop eating all that candy.
You're gonna be up until tomorrow morning.
Very cute.
Your parents
owe me for this one.
You could slap him if you want.
I won't tell.
Oh, really?
I'll keep that in mind.
- What time is it?
- Oh, it's 10:50.
All right, seriously,
pumpkin carving in 10 minutes.
I wanna get this over with.
Yeah, come on, Timmy.
Get the hell up.
I'm not done
counting my candy, loser.
Can we just bury him
in the backyard...
and tell my parents
we lost him trick-or-treating?
Hey, look what I got.
What is that?
It's a videotape.
Where did
you get that?
Fell out of my bag.
Let me see it.
- Who gave this to you?
- I don't know.
You don't remember
who put it in your bag?
No.
It's creepy.
- What'd it say?
- It doesn't say anything.
Let's watch it.
Oh, absolutely not.
Why?
Why? Because God knows
what's on this, that's why.
Only one way
to find out.
- Timmy, you're not watching it.
- Yes I am.
Timmy, stop being
such an asshole.
Hey! I said no.
It's my tape, I can do
what I want with it.
Yeah, well, I'm in charge of you
and you have to listen to me.
Let your parents watch it.
If they say it's okay, you'll watch it tomorrow.
No, I wanna watch it now.
No, you're not watching it.
Fine.
Let's put it to a vote.
I vote we watch it right now.
Tia?
Put it to a vote?
What is this?
The town hall?
I vote we watch it, too.
Little traitor,
now you're on his side?
What? I just wanna see
what's on the tape.
Two against one.
We win, put it on.
Do you understand
this is creepy?
Some pervert could have
put it in your bag.
Who knows what's on this?
Probably it's
just a scary movie.
If it's that bad, you can turn it off.
We won't tell our parents.
It can't be worse than the stuff
we see on the Internet every day.
You're gracious 10 years old.
What do you watch on the Internet?
You know what?
I don't wanna know.
Please.
We won't make you
carve the pumpkin.
Fine, but you have to go
in the other room.
- I need to see what's on it first.
- Yes!
You too!
Ugh, this is retarded.
- Well, what is it?
- Well, give me a second!
Anything?
I don't see anything.
Looks like you
got hosed, Timmy.
Oh, wait a minute.
What is it?
Uh, I don't know.
This is stupid.
Come on.
Stop it! Excuse me. Who said the two of you
can come back in here?
See?
It's just a scary movie.
Let's watch it.
Wait for the gate agent to give
your boarding announcement.
Check your monitors.
Thanks you.
Fine, but if it gets out of control,
I'm turning it off.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, my God, it's great.
Um, girl.
Do you know when the train comes?
Uh, it should be about
10 minutes or so.
Uh, do you have
a cigarette? Heh!
No, sorry.
Yeah, thanks.
Well, happy Halloween.
Come on, let's go.
I need a fucking cigarette.
Come on.
- Passengers, slow down train is delayed.
- Please stand by for further information.
Please stop.
Ahh!
What are you doing?
Let me go. Help!
Help!
Ah-a-a!
No! No!
Help! Help!
Help!
Some help, would you please?
Come on!
Somebody answer me!
Please! Look!
Who's there?
Where am I?
What's happening?
Would someone
talk to me?
Please stop screaming.
- What's happening to us?
- This is where he keeps us.
There were three of us.
There was another girl.
What happened to her?
She was dragged down
into that tunnel.
They're pulling us down
by our chains one at a time.
Why are you two
just sitting there?
Why aren't you
trying to escape?
We've tried everything,
there's no way out.
Why is he keeping us here?
Why doesn't he just
kill us already?
Why are you doing this?
Let us go! Please!
Don't cry.
We're gonna die
down here.
Don't say that.
We're gonna get
out of here.
I don't want to die.
- Shut up! Just shut up!
- Kristen!
I can't take it anymore.
I can't... I can't keep listening to this.
She's just scared. Okay?
Help her realize...
I'm sorry.
We can't fall apart
on each other now.
We're all we've got.
What's your name?
Casey.
I'm Sara.
That's Kristen.
There has to be
a way out of here.
I told you, there isn't.
Then we have to go
down into that tunnel.
- What?
- We can't just stay here.
Going into that
tunnel is suicide.
Oh, and staying
here isn't?
What do you know?
You didn't see what happened to that girl.
We did. We watched her
getting dragged down into that tunnel...
and she was screaming
for her life,
and we were trying
to hold on to her...
but he just... He pulled her
right out of her hands.
We're not strong enough.
There's three of us now.
If we go together,
we might have a chance.
We don't even know
how many of them are down there.
What do you suppose we do?
The only thing we can do
is just wait here
and hope that
somebody finds us.
She's right, Kristen.
There's no other way.
No, Sara. Please.
You know I'm right.
Don't listen to her.
She's dead already.
Don't go!
I'm sorry.
There's no other choice.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Don't leave me here alone!
He's gonna kill you.
Kristen, we have to, we can't just
wait here to see who's gonna...
Oh-oh!
Oh! Oh!
Oh-o!
Oh, God.
It's got her.
Oh, my God.
Listen to me!
Kristen, we have to go now.
You hear me?
We have to go down there.
I... I can't,
I'm so scared.
I know you are,
and so am I,
but right now
I'm thinking about my family.
I'm gonna get out of here
and I'm gonna see them again...
and everything's gonna be
like it was before.
I know you feel the same,
but we're never gonna see them again
if we don't try to get out of here.
I can't stay here
anymore, Kristen.
I can't wait here to die.
I just can't.
We're gonna make it.
Do you understand me?
We're gonna be all right.
We stay close, and...
be quiet.
It's not further.
Stay right here.
Oh, God! Look, look, look!
You got it on the chains.
I think it's big enough.
Come on,
I think it's working.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Help!
No!
Oh, God!
All right!
Help me,
help me please.
There's something down there.
We have to get out of here.
Come on!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
No!
Please.
Please stop.
Don't hurt my baby.
That was sick!
Okay, that is enough
for tonight.
Hey, what're you doing?
I'm turning it off.
It's too violent
for the two of you.
No, it's not.
We've seen way worse.
Then you should be punished.
You're too young to be watching
a baby cut out of someone's stomach.
- Come on, let's go. It's bedtime.
- Bedtime?
Yes, bedtime.
Tia, go wash your face.
I want the both of you
to brush your teeth.
- Man, it was just getting good.
- Aw.
I know.
I liked the clown.
Yeah, he was great.
I liked when he honked his horn at the lady.
That was so funny.
Yeah, that was hysterical.
I'm gonna be up
to check on you guys in 10 minutes.
Hey, what's up?
Hey, this call is to be sure
you're not dead.
What is that
supposed to mean?
Baby sitting on the Halloween night,
that's just asking for trouble.
Yeah, tell me that it's already been
quite an eventful evening.
Why? What happened?
Some creep slipped a videotape into
Timmy's candy bag while they're trick or treating.
A videotape?
Hell, like a 1982 VHS.
That's very twisted.
Yeah, what you should see
with honest.
Oh, God! What did you
subject those kids to?
I got through.
Fucked up short film
with a clown...
and the devil
raping the woman.
Sounds like my kinda movie.
No, seriously, what
kind of sick bastard...
puts that in
a kid's candy bag?
- Probably some loser who still lives
in his parents' garage? - Probably.
Don't sweat it!
Look at the seemed way it was.
Yeah, that's what
Timmy and Tia said.
- Move away.
- I have to spit.
- I was here first.
- Get out!
You better move.
Now what?
That's it.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
Timmy, don't even!
Okay.
Timmy!
Hold on a minute, Dee.
What's going on up there?
Sarah, Timmy spit in my hair!
It was an accident!
Cut it out,
I'm calling your parents.
...reconsidering having children
at this point.
Can you think of anything
better to do tonight?
How did Barbara ever
talk you into this?
She never says right to anything.
What was I supposed to say? No?
You're a good friend.
Yes, I am.
Speak...
Speaking of good friends,
join me for a drink after this?
Yeah, I can totally do that.
All right, perfect.
I need one.
I'll text you
when I'm leaving.
- Cool! Oh, Sarah...
- Yeah?
Don't get killed.
Funny.
- Bye.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Little shit!
All right, let's go.
Is my tape in there?
- No.
- Where is it?
Downstairs.
Can I have it, please?
No.
I don't know why you're
making such a big deal out of this.
My parents are just
gonna give it to me in the morning.
All right, then,
the faster you get your little butt to bed,
the faster you'll
get your tape.
You suck, Sarah.
Goodnight.
Lights out, kiddo.
All right.
- You gotta come back.
- Are you gonna tell my parents...
that Timmy spit in my hair?
Well, it depends.
Is he gonna get in trouble?
Yeah.
Then absolutely.
Cool.
- Did you have a good Halloween?
- Yeah.
Did you get
enough candy?
I guess so.
You guess so?
Look at that bag, it looks like
you were trying to find the golden ticket.
Do you think
that clown was real?
See? Ugh, I knew this was gonna
come back to bite me.
No, it's just make-believe.
Demons, witches, monsters, that...
That doesn't exist.
But he wasn't really a monster,
if you think about it,
like a vampire or a werewolf.
He was just a man
in a costume.
Someone like that
could really exist, right?
Like a serial killer,
I mean.
What do you know
about serial killers?
See, you watch so much
stuff on that computer.
It's gonna
rot your brain.
I sound like my grandmother.
Listen to me,
the clown's only on
the video, right?
So if you don't watch it,
he can't hurt you.
And even if he could,
I wouldn't let him.
- You swear?
- I cross my heart.
Okay.
Time to go to bed.
Wait, Sarah.
Do you want me
to leave it on?
All right, sweetie.
If you need me,
I'll be downstairs.
- Okay.
- Okay. Sweet dreams.
- Goodnight.
- Goodnight, sweetie.
Sleep tight.
Does anyone up there know
why we're being attacked?
Whatever it is,
it isn't just happening here.
It's some kind of mass murder
that's going on everywhere.
- The radio said to stay inside...
- Radio?
Radio upstairs,
I heard the news from it.
There's a radio upstais,
and you boarded us in down here!
- I know what I'm doing.
- What did it say?
Nothing! Nothing!
They don't know anything yet.
But there's a mass murder everywhere,
and people are supposed to look for
a safe place to hide.
- Take the boards off that door.
- We are staying down here, Hellen.
Harry, that radio is at least
some kind of communication.
It is the authority to know
what happening with the friends.
People force that
they'll tell us what to do.
How we're going to know
what's going on...
if we lock ourselves
in this dungeon?....
Timmy?
What do you want?
Can I sleep in here
with you tonight?
Are you serious?
Why?
The clown scared you,
didn't he?
I thought he was so funny.
Fine.
Don't hog all the blanket,
all right?
It's my bed,
I'll hog it if I want.
First eyewitness accounts
of this grizzly development...
came from people who were
understandably frightened,
almost incoherent.
Officials and newsman
first discounted there...
You know what we saw
on our property this afternoon?
What?
- A deer.
- Get out of here!
I'm not kidding.
It was only ten feet away.
It's really beautiful.
Oh, that's so cute!
I know, isn't it?
That is a sign.
Deer symbolize peace...
in the beginning
of new adventure.
I think things are really gonna
work out great for you guys.
God, I hope so.
You know, the hardest part is just gonna be
adjusting to this new lifestyle.
It's just estrange not hearing an ambulance
or a bus every two minutes.
I'm standing by my window,
you know what I hear...
outside right now?
Listen...
- You hear that?
- No, what is it?
It's nothing.
It's absolutely nothing.
You could hear a pin drop,
that's how quiet it is here.
You know what 8:00
in the city sounds like?
Like stress?
Exactly.
And at least here
I can just clear my head...
and John can focus
on his work.
How is John, by the way?
He's good. He gotta have his first exhibition
coming up in a couple of weeks,
Found just talking article really well.
That's really pretty careline.
I'm gonna have to get my hands
on one of his paintings before he becomes too famous.
Ugh, I wish you'd buy
his latest painting...
so I can get it
the hell out of this house.
Thing gives me the creeps.
What is it?
It's a face.
Just a horrible face.
Honestly, I just...
I can't even be
in the same room with this thing.
That's the furor.
I didn't know
John painted things like that.
He doesn't.
According to him,
he doesn't even remember painting it.
He doesn't remember painting it?
No, he swears he was
in some sort of trance or something. And...
all he remembers is waking up
from this terrible nightmare...
with this image
in his head.
And the next morning,
there's this painting in the living room.
That's really strange.
Yeah, well,
you know how artists are.
As my chopstick feels,
and I still can't figure out
how his mind works.
The owner of the gallery thinks that
it's gonna be one of his best sellers.
Well, I hope everything
works out for you guys.
I'm really looking forward
to seeing the house.
Yeah, you know, when we get settle here,
maybe you and Bob could come up for a weekend.
- Sounds like friend!
- Okay, Marry, I'll talk to you later.
Bye.
All right, bye.
Shit.
Fuck!
We're sorry, your call cannot...
Oh, fuck!
Fuck this.
Well.
Are you kidding me?
You can't be fucking
kidding me, come on.
Start!
Fucking car, start!
What?
Are you fucking kill me?
Oh, my God.
It's okay.
It's just a meteor, right?
It's just a meteor.
Just like
the one in Russia....
It's fine.
It's totally fine.
The electricity goes out,
nothing works.
You're gonna be fine.
It's okay.
Calm down.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What the fuck is that?
God damn it.
- John!
- Hey, there you are.
- Where are you? - I'm headed back now.
I tried calling the house, but I couldn't get through.
- Is everything okay?
- No!
Something landed
by the house.
- What do you mean something landed?
- Something land to the house. I don't know,
It's just a few minutes ago. It was just so loud,
I thought it was gonna crash into the kitchen.
Was it a plane?
I don't know.
I thought it was a plane or...
or a helicopter,
- but before we.
- Before we?
You mean you can actually
see it from the house?
Yes. It was only a hundred feet away
from the house.
- Did you call the police?
- I couldn't.
My phone wasn't working
until you called me.
Call them. And whatever you do,
stay in the house.
Okay, I will.
John, I'm really,
really scared.
I think there's
somebody in the house.
Okay, calm down! There's no one in the house.
You're just getting spooked.
Listen, you'll be fine.
Call the police and then call me right back.
I don't want you to go.
You have to call them.
You'll feel 100 times better
knowing they're on your way.
No, no. What if
I get off the phone...
and then I can't get in touch
with you again?
Then don't call the police.
Worse case scenario,
just get in the car drive it to town.
You can stay at the Red Lion
until the power comes back on.
I can't. The car's dead.
What do you mean
the car's dead?
I told you,
nothing's working, John.
There's something really strange
going on around here.
John?
John, are you there?
God damn it!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Ah-a-a!
Help, help!
Ahhh!
Ah! Ah!
We're sorry, your call cannot be...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- John!
- Caroline, what's wrong?
- I don't know what.
- Caroline!
Caroline, listen to me!
- It's at the door. Help me, please!
- Caroline, hang on, hang on!
Caroline!
Caroline, can you hear me?
The police are coming.
Caroline!
- Caroline!
- No! John! Help me, John.
John! No!
No!
John, help me!
John, help!
Ahh-a-a-a!
Ahh-aa!
Help!
Help me, please, John!
Somebody help me!
Who makes this shit?
Why am I watching it?
Where are they?
Tia, Timmy, I told the both
of you to go to bed.
Don't pretend
like you're sleeping.
I told you to go to bed.
We are in bed.
Oh, really?
So it must have been someone else...
...whose own mischievous feet
running up the stairs.
What are you
doing in here?
She had a nightmare.
I didn't have a nightmare.
I heard a noise.
You heard a noise?
What kind of noise?
I don't know.
You can't describe
the noise?
Well, where did it come from?
My closet.
Your closet?
You always hear noise
that's coming from your closet?
Yes, she does.
This happens all the time.
Shut up, Timmy.
It was real.
There was
someone in there.
Maybe it's the clown.
Timmy, stop it!
Shh, listen!
I think I just heard his horn.
Stop it.
He's gonna drug you
and take you to the witches.
Timmy, knock it off.
Tia, listen to me,
we talked about this before.
There's nothing in your closet,
not a clown, not anyone.
And your parents
can be home any minute,
I want both of you to go to bed.
Maybe we could if you'd stop
checking in on us every five minutes.
What are you talking about?
I heard you creeping around
outside the door and turning the handle.
Just go to bed.
Hello?
Right, Sarah.
You're watching too many scary movies.
Oh! This is ridiculous.
It takes a little gonna be scared
when I can't even convince myself.
You're listening to
WORW 970.
It's one minute past
the witching hour.
Halloween is
officially here.
Lock your doors,
roll your windows.
...are nestled
safely in their beds.
It at last keep going.
Stay with me after the break
and I'll be joined by...
Perfect.
Hello?
Anybody there?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Need some gas.
Fuck guy, dammit!
You're out of your
fucking mind?
Jason, you think it's funny, the piss
all over the place and smear your shit on the walls?
What the fuck
is wrong with you?
I'm giving you 10 seconds
or I'm gonna call the cops.
Hey!
I mean it.
So, what can I get you?
Um, filled up.
Regular. Cash.
So that guy really just
did that to your bathroom?
Uh, not my bathroom.
And I don't care if they fire me.
I'm not picking up someone else's shit.
Why didn't you just
call the cops?
What's the point?
He's already gone.
I'm just gonna have to fill out paperwork.
Supposed to be off
in an hour.
Yeah, but what if
he comes back?
Uh, I've got enough blunt objects
I can bludgeon him with.
He's lucky I didn't
fucking break his legs.
God, you really were low, huh?
Yeah, good thing I saw
your sign when I did.
I'm actually kind of lost.
Oh. Well,
where are you headed?
Um, New York.
I'm just trying to get back
to the interstate.
Um, you got
a pen and paper?
I can give you directions.
It's not far.
Oh, yeah. Sure.
Where are you
coming from?
Um, Albrightsville.
I was up on
a movie shoot there.
Oh, you're in the movies?
Try to be, you know, independents, mostly.
Couple of commercials.
Is there anything
I would have seen you in?
Oh, I'm not an actress.
I'm a costume designer.
Oh, I've never met
a costume designer before.
Well, now you have.
All right. Uh...
- What you wanna do is
get back onto the 94.
You're gonna go
about six miles.
You're gonna see a bridge...
What was that?
Uh, hang on a second.
I'll be right back.
Hey, sir?
Hello?
Come on, you piece of shit!
Emergency.
What is the problem?
Yes. Please...
You have to help me.
There's been a murder.
Please hurry.
Emergency...
There's been a murder!
The old gas station
over on 94. Send help!
There's...
That's impossible.
That's fucking impossible!
Please! The killer's out here,
he's following me.
Hello?
Come on!
Oh, no.
Please, God.
Oh, shit!
This can't be real.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Ah-a-a!
Ahh!
This can't be happening!
Yes. Oh, my God.
Hello?
Please, you gotta help me.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hello!
Please, God! Help me!
Help it ringing.
Please.
- Hello?
- Nick!
Please, call the police!
Somebody is trying to kill me.
My phone's gonna die
any second.
I'm on Route 94, heading home.
Baby, I'm so scared.
Nick?
Nick!
Fuck!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Ahh!
Ah!
Stop.
Stop!
Please! Help me!
Help me!
Hey, are...
Are you okay?
- Have you been in an accident?
- Just drive!
Get out of here.
There's somebody after me.
Who's after you?
Some man.
He's in a clown costume.
He's trying to kill me.
This isn't some sort of
Halloween prank, is it?
I suppose not.
How bad are you hurt?
I don't know.
There's a police station
a few miles up ahead.
Just hang in there, okay?
Everything's
gonna be fine.
- Oh, God!
- What?
- That's him!
- What's wrong? What?
- Get out of here! Hurry!
- What's wrong? Why?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Hello?
- Now.
Please...
You have to help me.
There's been a murder.
- Please hurry.
- Who is this?
There's been a murder!
The old gas station
over on 94.
- Send help!
- Dee?
Is there the funny?
Who is the...?
Please! The killer's out here,
he's following me.
Who's following you?
Some man.
He's in a clown costume.
He's trying to kill me.
Fuck!
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
Do you think
that clown was real?
Someone like that
could really exist, right?
VictorR–11/03/2013.