Seoul, South Korea.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Happy Birthday!
Surprise!
Happy Birthday to you!
Happy Birthday! Happy Birthday!
What are you playing?
You scared me off.
Was it fun to fool me?
Vee, here you go.
Thank you.
Vee.
Vee is not even fat.
It isn't that. He has diabetes.
It's ok. Just a little bit.
Small bite. Ok?
Lucky.
You always keep things by yourself.
You should let it out of your chest sometimes.
This card says...
something that you lost will come back.
Was there something you lost...
it probably will return.
No.
Perhaps...
it may not be a thing,
Have you ever broke your promise with someone?
He's gonna take it back.
Don't listen to Ji-Ho so much.
She told me that I'll meet my soul mate.
But I'm still single until now.
Then stop being so picky.
I'm not pretty like you...
to get a good-looking guy like Vee.
Injection time.
Still scared of injection?
Won't take long.
All done.
I'll be back.
Ok.
Hello.
Hold on please.
Pim, it's your call.
Pim.
Is it an urgent matter?
She's not here.
Pardon?
What is it?
Pim.
The hospital in Thailand called...
Your mom had a stroke.
Go back now?
If I hadn't come here,
it wouldn't have happened.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Are you ok, Pim?
I don't want to go back there.
Since Ploy died,
I don't want to live in that house anymore.
Am I selfish for leaving
everything behind?
Don't say that!
If I hadn't wanted the operation,
maybe Ploy wouldn't have died.
Pim. We already talked, didn't we?
It's not your fault!
No one wants it to be this way.
The patient is now unable to move...
and also unable to talk.
because of the brain hemorrhage
affected the nerve's end.
we have to wait until
her condition gets better.
Then we can operate.
Mom.
Mom!
Excuse me, miss.
I think you should let her sleep.
Please go outside.
Oh! Pim.
That is Ploy's favorite song.
Ploy...
Miss Pim.
If you don't need me...
could I go home?
You didn't sleep here?
No, miss.
You can sleep here if you'd like
It's more convenient.
It's ok.
I'd better go home.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Vee! Vee!
What?
What's going on?
Vee!
Are you ok?
You're alright?
Mom.
How do you feel?
What is it, mom?
What did you say?
Excuse me, miss.
I'll give her a shot.
Noi.
What happened to mom on that day?
How did she collaspe?
I really don't know.
Since you've been here...
how is she so far?
Noi.
I...
I don't know what happened to her lately.
She always stayed in her room...
kept crying.
Sometimes I felt like...
she was afraid of something.
What was she afraid of?
How is mother's condition, doctor?
She's suddenly getting worse.
I think we have to operate her tonight.
Miss! Miss!
Are you ok?
Pim.
Are you tired?
You can go home if you'd like.
I'll stay here.
I'm ok.
Your mother is safe now.
She's still unconscious.
So when will she wake up?
I can't answer that.
It depends on the patient's condition.
Lucky.
What's the matter?
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Pim!
Pim! Open the door!
What's going on, Pim?
What happened?
It's done.
Pim.
What exactly happened to you?
Why did you hurt yourself?
Pim.
Why don't you tell me?
I see Ploy.
What do you mean?
I feel like she's still
near me all the time.
I don't understand.
How can you see her?
Ploy was dead.
Never mind.
I'm just anxious.
Pim.
You'd better go to the doctor.
Vee...
I'm okay.
How are you?
Oh! Good.
Long time no see.
You've changed a lot.
Really?
Coffee.
Thanks.
Ah! Pim.
This is Danai, my senior.
Hello.
We're very closed before I moved to Korea.
We haven't met more than ten years right?
Yup. More than 10 years.
It's been a long time.
How come you guys meet again?
Vee called me to visit this house.
How's your job so far?
Well, quite busy. I give a lecture...
and also have a lot patients.
So what are your specialized?
I am a psychaitrist.
Pim!
You think I'm insane?
Listen to me!
Pim!
Open the door, Pim!
Lucky!
Pim!
From the scan results,
your brain looks normal.
I'll show you some pictures.
Just tell me...
what do you see.
Okay?
Batman.
If I answer this, it means
I'm crazy, right?
I must say 'Butterfly', right?
That'll be normal.
Seeing a psychaitrist..
doesn't mean you're crazy.
Anyone can be like you.
It can be cured.
Vee's so worried about you.
He doesn't want to see you like this.
Can you tell me about Ploy?
We used to promise to live
with each other forever.
Then what made you seperate?
Alright, let's call for today.
I'll give you medicine.
It's no use, doctor.
You can't help me.
Apparently she is  mentally ill.
This's kind of sickness...
You can't tell between illusion and reality.
Plus the guilty from the past...
makes her see an illusion.
It can be cured?
Of course.
It can be cured.
You just take her back to korea.
She must be better.
We have to be here longer. I guess.
I don't know when her mom's gonna recover.
Then take her to a new place to relax.
That'll be good.
Go ahead! These are your favorite.
Eat a lot!
Here...delicious?
It looks yummy!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Try this!
Pim!
What's wrong?
What should I do?
She followed me.
Pim doesn't get any better.
I have to take her back as soon as I can.
It's probably a good idea.
You know...
it's not that I'm credulous.
Have you ever heard...
the story about the twins?
If one of them dies,
another one will die too.
Pim told me that
Ploy's gonna take her life.
It's just a belief, man.
It's possible that twins' mind
are linked.
But I think...
it's just a binding of...
the living that yearns for the dead.
Vee.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I think you went to the hospital.
Just stop by to bring you something to eat.
Go down to eat.
As for her condition,
I'm totally disagree about taking her to Korea.
It's risky.
We should observe her condition for a while.
Thank you.
Well then, excuse me.
Yes.
Mother.
What is it mother?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Pim!
Vee!
Vee! I'm scared.
I saw her again.
How can I make her disappear?
Miss Pim.
It's just your own imagination.
Like we talk about 'Mickey Mouse'...
we imagine about it but we don't really see it.
If our brain is malfunction,
the imagination in our mind...
will become...
as if it is real.
You still see your twin...
because your mind's still clinging on her.
You said you saw her in the mirror, right?
Look at the mirror.
Who do you see now?
Pim!
Ploy!
And that reason made
you both decided to seperate.
Even Chang and Eng twins still
wanted to be seperated.
Two persons whose their bodies
are joined together...
it is normally to have the conflict.
But we had furious fight.
Ploy didn't want the operation.
Did you ever think ploy is
unwanted thing in your life?
No, I never think that.
It isn't wrong that you want to have your own life.
But I...
I made her died.
If you stop blaming yourself,
you won't see shadow of your twin anymore.
Pim!
Are you ok?
Let's go.
No..
No..not true.
You bought him?
Lucky.
Lucky, come here.
Lucky!
Pim, he is not Lucky.
Noi!
Take him away.
Yes.
Oh, Pim.
Korean hospital already accepts.
We'll go back soon.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Pim.
Do you remember the painting I drew for you?
Ploy did it, right?
Don't Ploy!
Please Ploy!
It's because of me, right?
That made you two seperated.
I hate you!
Let's get disjoined operation.
Why didn't you tell me?
How can I tell you?
Tell you that I chose you
and let Ploy died?
Ploy...don't!
Mom!
You know? Vee.
Ploy loved you all along.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
I believe that you really saw her.
But medically, we can't say that
the thing you saw is really exist.
Human brain is very complex.
The thing that you saw...
is just an illusion.
- An illusion!
- Stop, doctor.
stop! How many time I tell you
she's still here.
She's not dead.
Miss Pim!
Where is Pim?
She wasn't be with you?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Pim.
Vee!
Vee! Help me!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Pim!
What's wrong, Pim?
It's me.
Vee.
It's all right.
Let's go back to Korea.
Let's go to the hospital.
Vee!
Don't worry, Pim.
I'll move your mother tonight.
Vee.
Where is doctor?
Can I help you?
I want to transfer the patient right now?
Please calm down sir.
Find the doctor for me.
Ok. I will find him.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What is it, mother?
Please take a good look.
Who do you see now?
In the mirror, I see Ploy in there.
Pim
You know, Vee?
Ploy loved you all along.
Vee.
Mom has passed away.
What did you do?
Why you get soaked?
How did she die?
The patient's condition is getting better.
About moving to Korea...
tell them to contact us.
I don't know either.
I never thought that she's
getting worse that fast.
Luckily, she talked to me before she died.
Why?
Afraid what she'll tell me?
This is yours, right?
Are you surprised?
Ploy.
What did you say, Vee?
Stop lying to me!
I went to the temple today.
What exactly happened to Pim?
How did she die? Tell me.
Let go!
Ploy's dead, Vee!
Ploy. Why you did that?
No...I'm Pim.
I'm Pim.
What happened to Pim?
Or you..
What did you do to her?
We can't live like this.
Let's apart.
No. I'll be with you until I die.
Why did you do that?
You know, you are unwanted.
No, I'm not!
No..No..
Let go, Ploy!
Pim!
Mom!
Mom! Help me!
Pim!
I did't mean it.
How did you do that?
She is your sister!
You've deceived me all along.
But why, Vee!
Pim and I are exactly the same.
Why can't you love me?
You're so pathetic!
What about time we've spent together?
There's no meaning to you?
Is it me that you love?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
It's not yours.
Vee!
[Lagu diputar]
I never thought this day will come.
Everyone loves only Pim.
After she died,
mom never talked to me again.
She treated me like disgusting thing.
I love you not less than Pim.
But you only have your eyes on her.
The letters that you wrote to her..
I pretended that they're for me.
The only way to make you love me...
is to become Pim.
all the letters that you received...
I wrote them all.
How could you say you love Pim?
It's me that you love!
Poor Pim.
I'm the one who get your love.
Is it hurt?
Just a second.
You hate it so much, right?
Why can't it replace the old one?
Why?
Even though it's all the same.
I'm sorry.
I forget my cell phone.
Where is it? I'll get it for you.
I'm not sure. Maybe in the kitchen.
Vee!
Where are you?
Come out now!
Or I'll burn you.
Come out!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Let me out!
Ploy and Pim
Translated Subtitles by Tennkp