Translation and subtitles by
PEPPER & LALASPAIN
*** SONG LIVES FOR EVER ***
We have six men that
were found last night,
in bed... shot and killed.
In 1965, Ronald DeFeo moved
his family from Brooklyn
into a beautiful three-storey home
in Amityville, Long Island.
Envisioning a better
life for themselves,
they even put a sign in front of
the house saying: "High Hopes".
Then things went terribly wrong.
Rumors have been circulating
that there is something dark
and evil about the house.
That the house somehow drove Ronny DeFeo
to commit this grisly act.
♪ Ain't it good? ♪
♪ Ain't it right? ♪
♪ That you are with me, ♪
♪ here tonight? ♪
♪ The music playing, ♪
♪ our bodies swaying in time. ♪
♪ In time, in time, in time. ♪
♪ Touching you, ♪
♪ So warm and tender... ♪
♪ Lord, I feel such a sweet surrender. ♪
♪ Beautiful is the dream ♪
♪ that makes you mine. ♪
♪ Rock me gently... ♪
♪ Rock me slowly... ♪
♪ Take it easy, ♪
♪ Don't you know? ♪
OK!
We're home!
Larry, old sicky bastard.
How did you even get in here?
Juliet?
Are you up here?
Hello?
Joan!
Hey!
Hi, you guys made it!
How was the ride?
We're worn out.
You know what? We're doing good.
I need to go back in town.
Thank you so much for
helping with all of...
What are sisters for?
Have you told them... about...?
No?
Oh, I just want us
to get settled in first, OK?
OK. Well, I have everything set up the way
you wanted if you wanna check it out.
I set up an emergency back-up
battery just in case.
You never know with these old houses.
And...
You know we're only
five minutes on the road,
so you say the word
if you need anything.
- We'll be there.
- Thank you.
We've pretty much
gotten to a routine now, so...
Oh, I'm glad you're here.
Everything's gonna be fine.
What did doctor Milton say?
The same as usual,
you know...
We're not gonna give up fighting.
Of course.
All right, everybody!
Dig in!
Aren't we gonna say grace?
You hate saying grace.
Never stopped you before.
Well, maybe I'm embracing a change.
I'll do it!
"Dear Lord, thank you for this food".
"And for this house".
"And for keeping James safe and happy".
"Amen".
Juls, how do you like your room?
Awesome! It's got pink,
purple, silver and gold.
All my favourite colors.
Do you have all your
paperwork done for tomorrow?
Yup.
Things do look good.
Yeah, it looks great.
Besides the fact that I have to
move to a completely new school
and start all over again
on my senior year...
We all have to make sacrifices.
Quiet, boy!
And what part of sacrifice
does this house fit into?
It's - It's three times
as big as our last one.
I told you.
We got a deal.
Save a few bucks?
That's good to know.
We moved here to be close
to my family, to Candice.
St. Alcuin has the best neurological
department in New York.
I want you to trust me, all right?
This house is gonna be good for James.
And that's all that matters.
Right now, yes,
that's all that matters.
We all need to rally round and that's
the only way he's gonna get through this.
Get through what, Mom?
I know James, OK?
I know him better than you do.
He's my twin!
I can feel it!
He's not there!
- And whose fault is that?
- James is gone, Mom!
That's enough!
Belle?
Larry, come on!
Yeah.
You still love me, don't you, Larry?
Even if you are stuck
with that dumb name.
Come on.
I miss talking to you.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Let's go, people!
OK, guys, this is Belle.
She just transferred here.
Have a seat and take notes.
We left off yesterday page 38.
1862. The Civil War.
Battlefield medicine.
Clara Barton.
Check out the lipstick on freaky girl.
She ended up starting
the American Red Cross.
What she did was, she talked
mothers and daughters
to come out to the battlefield
and take care of their sons... brothers.
It's not you.
It's the house.
What house?
Yeah, 112 Ocean Avenue.
Ugh! Who are you?
Some kind of stalker?
What? No!
How do you know
where I live?
- Everyone knows where you...
- Please, just...
Hey, hey, hey!
It's your first day.
You might wanna listen.
♪ Where were you when
the sun came down? ♪
♪ Chasing love
on the fountain grounds? ♪
♪ Where were you when the sun came...? ♪
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh, my God!
Juliet, you can't just...
... sneak up on people like that.
Sorry.
What are you doing up?
I just wanted to talk to James.
Doesn't James talk to you, Belle?
In a way, I guess.
Does he use bad words?
Why would you say that?
OK, party animal.
It's sleepy-time. Come here.
Tooty-hoi, yes, come on.
- Belle?
- Yes?
How come Mommy
doesn't love you anymore?
Who told you that?
Go to bed.
Go back to bed, girls.
You heard Mom,
let's go back to bed.
James?
It's his heart.
Sweetheart, stay with us, OK?
Belle is here,
Mom is here...
Good.
All right, sweetheart.
You're doing great.
Who's my brave boy?
It's gonna be OK.
All right baby.
Now, OK, sweetie.
Baby?
I don't understand.
What's happening?
Come on!
It goes too fast.
Come on,
don't do this.
Come on, baby!
Shit!
Come on, come on,
come on.
Come on, honey.
Come on!
Stay with me, James.
James...
- Come on!
- Mom.
- It's over.
- That's what you want, isn't it?
It's what God would want.
Honey.
We're never gonna stop fighting for you.
I'm so proud of you.
Come, sweetie.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Do you wanna give him a kiss?
I knew you'd come back.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Juliet?
Who fixed you breakfast?
- Shit!
- Language, honey.
D'you want some Granola?
(- Take care of yourself. Take it easy)
(- Oh, really?)
(Brenda, Leonie's looking for you! OK?)
In 1965, Ronald DeFeo moved
his family from Brooklyn
into a beautiful three-storey home
in Amityville, Long Island.
Then things went terribly wrong.
Are you still questioning
Ronald DeFeo?
No comment.
Where is Mister DeFeo?
What kind of a guy is Ron DeFeo?
Don't worry,
I'm just stalking you.
Yeah, erm, sorry about yesterday.
He didn't look for trouble.
And he was a happy fella.
You know, you're not the first girl to mistake
my basic human decency for perviness.
You really didn't know?
No idea.
Man, I can't believe
no one told you about that!
Sick shit, right?
Voices told him to do it.
Took out the whole family,
six people.
Wait, where are you going?
Well, I already missed
the last three periods
and I don't really
wanna transfer again.
Hey, wait, you ever see this?
Do you recognize that house?
We need to talk.
Good to see you, honey.
How was school?
Why didn't you tell me
about the house?
I'm just waiting
for the right time.
And when would that be?
You know it's just a ghost story, sweetie.
It's an urban legend.
Yeah, that everyone at my school
seems to know about.
You're right. I'm sorry.
I should have told you.
I just - I've really
had a lot on my mind.
Well, it would be nice if Juliet
and I could be on your mind too.
That's it.
It's the doctor.
Good talk!
But it's an improvement, right?
I mean, it has to be!
I know it may seem that way.
But remember, the last time we checked,
there was no brain activity at all.
But he opened his eyes!
I mean, who's to say
that he won't start speaking, or...
- Even sitting up or something?
- Joan.
You know there no
documented cases
of anyone with James'
injuries ever recovering.
Then James will be the first.
Is there any way to be sure
if there's any recovery?
It's highly unlikely.
But I suppose we'll get to another fMRI.
Great! How much more shit
do you wanna put him through?
Just leave him alone!
Hasn't he suffered enough?
Sorry about that.
[JULIET SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY]
Didi likes to chase
the ducks at the park.
- We ended to telling them...
- Are you talking to James again?
Yeah.
What does James have to say this time?
He says he misses talking to you too.
Hey, guys.
Hey, Juls, your Mom's gonna walk Larry.
D'you wanna go with her?
OK!
Come here, one, two, three,
oooh, yeah.
Huh, Belle, you know I don't
want any more tests either.
Then why did you suggest it?
Because this test is gonna show your Mom
what you and I already know.
Did you know about the house?
Please, just go.
Juliet!
You can't keep doing this.
Scroll over.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
♪ Happy Monday! ♪
Belle, this is Marissa.
She's my girlfriend.
You wish!
M, this is my friend Belle.
Wow! All kinds of love for
Terrence today. See how it is?
See you later, man!
These guys...
So, yeah... Marissa didn't believe
me when I said I knew you
so I thought you
guys should meet.
What's up?
God, I would kill my Mom if she does
something like that without telling me.
Yeah, all talk is early
and big at my house, so...
Yeah, well, thank God none of
this Amityville shit is real.
Whoa, whoa! That all depends
on your definition of real.
You know, when someone's
talking a lot about something,
your mind starts playing tricks on you,
makes you think it's real.
According to whom?
Science!
Well, I'm really over this
Amityville stuff anyway.
My family's got enough
demons to deal with,
I don't need fictional ones too.
I don't know, maybe that's
exactly what you need.
Hey, we should watch the movie.
No, thanks.
Come one, that's what
horror movies are about,
like escaping reality with your
friends for a little while. It's fun.
OK, it's fine.
Let's watch it at your house.
No. Your house.
Come on! How often do you get
to watch the Amityville Horror
at the actual Amityville house?
OK, sure.
Awesome! We have to watch it
at 3.15 AM though.
Why?
Cos that's when Ronny DeFeo
murdered his family.
And that's when the house comes alive.
Juliet.
Shit!
Larry.
What?
Come on, you see something?
What do you see?
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Oh, that was great.
Go, Larry.
- Oh, man.
- Look, I told him not to do that.
Oh, you should have seen her face.
You guys seriously have to be quiet.
We don't wanna wake up my Mom.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Wow! This place is amazing.
Is that a binding circle
in the backyard?
A bounding circle?
Yeah, like hundreds of years ago,
like colonial times,
there used to be all this weirdo cult shit
going on around here, so...
If they found an area was evil,
they would do a ring around with
like salt or fire, whatever...
to try to keep the
evil contained.
Yeah, or maybe the gardener just got a
little carried away with the weed killer.
All right! So, I thought we were here
to watch a movie.
Yes.
Yeah, I've seen the
movie a dozen times...
Shut up!
I've never been inside the actual house.
OK, I'm going to punch you
in the actual mouth if you don't shut up.
Oh, yeah? Is that a threat or a promise?
What's in there?
Nothing.
Let's go.
OK, so...
You got the original 1979
film starring James...
Psssst!
Starring James Brolin
and Margot Kidder, erm...
But just in case,
I brought Amityville II...
which is technically a prequel, so,
I don't know if you like that. All right.
Erm, then, of course,
there's the remake...
- No. - Yeah, right.
- Remakes totally blow.
Agreed! All right!
The original it is.
So, how would you girls like to be
the bread in a Terrence sandwich?
In your dreams!
This house is built on special ground.
Satan worship, demons.
You cannot destroy this evil.
It will always find a place to dwell.
Something or someone to latch on to.
What's going on?
Have you all gone mad??
George!
Come and go through here.
Find the well.
The passage to hell!
What?
Holy shit!
It's 3.15 on the dot.
- No, it's not.
- I swear, look.
- What did you do?
- What? Nothing.
I really hope not.
I gotta get the lights back on.
It's probably just a fuse.
Right?
No, we need to fix it or else
I'm gonna have to wake up my Mom.
OK, then, where's the fuse box?
I think it's under the stairs.
Oh, great. The basement of the
Amityville house, that's perfect.
Haven't been down there yet.
Hold on, I got this.
Who wants to go first?
Oh, God!
What's that smell?
Just try and find the fuse box.
Wow!
What?
Under the stairs.
It's where they discovered the red room.
Whatever is in there,
gets inside your head.
Wouldn't find much in your head.
They say this house
makes you see things.
Infects your dreams until you can't
tell what's real and what's nightmare.
And then, boom! Blood splatter
and brain matter everywhere.
Can we please just find the fuse box
so we can get out of here?
Hey, I think I found it.
My phone is dead.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What the hell are you doing down here?
I could have killed you.
We'll - We'll let ourselves out.
Very nice meeting you.
Since when do you carry a shotgun?
Jesus!
It was your father's for protection.
I really don't think I need protection
from my friends but thanks.
You're not allowed to have
friends over without asking me.
You know how easy it is
for James to get sick?
What are you talking about?
They weren't anywhere near him.
Someone was in his room.
The door was open when I came over
but I shut it.
Then who took his blanket off?
He's not some sideshow attraction.
Go to bed.
It's possible that he has something
called LIS. Locked-in syndrome.
- Does that mean he's conscious?
- I don't know.
That means he may have a
sort of consciousness,
but it's locked into
an inactive body.
So, he is getting better.
Well, looking at this fMRI scan and...
seeing the return of some limited
eye mobility, it would appear so.
And this thing will tell us for sure?
The EEG machine measures brainwaves,
the more activity on this monitor,
the stronger the emotional response.
You're ready to give a try?
All right.
Step into his line of sight.
Hi, Jimmy.
Hey.
Jimmy.
Oh.
That's a definite response.
Candice.
Belle, come closer.
Mom?
Are you OK?
Your brother's back.
It's just a fly, James,
don't worry about that.
What's going on?
I'm sorry, I...
I can't - I can't really
explain it but I...
I don't think I can do anymore for you.
Doctor Milton?
Come on, Jimmy.
You're doing great.
You're doing so great.
I love you so much.
Come on, let's try
to move that thumb up.
Do you want me to rub your feet?
You can blink once for "yes".
That's OK.
Once it first happened, Belle said:
"Jimmy will never give up".
OK. Out, out!
Go, now! Hey, hey, hey!
Out, Larry! Bad dog!
Don't worry,
I'll never let him hurt you.
I love you more than
anything in the world.
Translation and subtitles by
PEPPER & LALASPAIN
*** SONG LIVES FOR EVER ***
James?
Is that you?
What do you want?
Come here!
Where are you?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
James?
Juliet?
Juls, where are you?
Hey, sis!
- Start with "yes" or "no" questions.
- OK.
- Doctor Milton said that would be easiest for him.
Jimmy?
Sweetie?
Do you recognize me?
Belle?
James wants to talk to Didi.
Will you help me find him?
Belle?
Come say hi to your brother.
He's talking to us through the computer.
It's amazing. Come see!
It's called an AAC.
He can use his eyes to choose letters
so he can communicate.
You can talk to your brother again.
What do you wanna say to him?
I don't know.
Just talk to him slowly.
Is that really you in there?
Wow, it's so cool!
I miss you.
He misses me too.
I just never really told
anybody about this.
You don't have to tell me
if you don't want to.
No, erm...
I should.
I really think I need to.
I- I was having a lot of problems...
with my family and with school...
In and out of a lot of
different programs.
And I just started doing stupid shit.
I sent these pictures to some guy...
And then when I woke up the next morning,
they were all over the internet.
They were everywhere,
everyone had seen them.
Everyone at school and my Mom...
And my brother...
So, what happened?
James wanted to find the guy who did it,
and he lived in a three-storey
apartment building...
There was a really big fight and...
He went over the balcony.
Look, you didn't do anything wrong.
You know that, right?
You know, I -
I really wanna believe that.
And I keep telling myself...
it was his choice.
He would do it again in a heartbeat.
I know he would.
Because...
That's just who he was.
That was who he is.
Belle, he's still alive,
you've just talked to him.
You're reading the wrong book.
You know it.
Only saying, is it a little weird that
your brother is in a comma for two years,
and the minute you move into this new
house, he miraculously gets better?
I don't - I don't know.
Unless, of course,
it's not really him anymore.
What are you talking about?
He's talking about a possession.
In 1974, the house drives Ronny DeFeo
to kill his whole family.
A year later, it nearly drives the next
family to do the exact same thing.
And they blamed it on the red room,
that they discovered right there.
In the basement.
See? It's right under
your brother's bed.
So, you're saying...
this evil thing latched onto my brother?
OK, whoa, whoa, whoa, look, I hate to
bring everyone back down to Earth, but...
Other families have
lived in that house,
nothing scary has happened
there for 40 years.
40 years, that's a very
significant number in the Bible.
"And the land had peace 40 years".
So, maybe the evil only
latches on every 40 years.
- No, that's stupid.
- Dude, seriously? The Bible?
Belle, you're not actually
buying this shit, are you?
Well, you said he can talk now, right?
So, why don't you just ask him yourself?
Yeah, what's the worst
that could happen?
I need to ask you a question.
Are you OK with that?
Is someone else...
in there with you?
What can I do to stop it?
How can I help you?
No!
No, I can't do that.
I love you so much.
Are you sure you want to do this?
I'm gonna take this out.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
You're the one who's gonna fucking die!
Is he all right? Are you OK, honey?
What's going on?
Jimmy, are you OK?
- What did you do?
- I...
What did you do?
You've no right to do this!
He's breathing.
He's breathing on his own!
Jimmy wants to live.
He deserves to live.
Get out.
If you touch him again,
I swear...
It's bad enough that he's trapped
in his own body and now he's...
What? He's...
There's something in there with him?
What am I gonna do? I...
I have to help him!
Look, Belle, you have to help
your entire family, OK?
I mean, whatever is in there
with James, if it wins,
you know, if it takes over
completely, it will kill everyone.
Belle, you gotta get
your family out of there.
Or we have to prove it
to your Mom somehow.
Find a way to show her that
your brother is being controlled
by whatever is in that house.
Belle?
Why aren't you at school?
I wasn't feeling well.
I'm sorry.
I'm sure I'll be fine.
No, I'm sorry about last night.
For what?
If you hadn't pulled Jimmy
out of the respirator...
We wouldn't know that
he could breathe on his own.
I know you were doing
what you thought was right.
But now you know
how wrong it is.
Right?
Jimmy was always going to come back.
You do want us to be a family again,
do you, Belle?
Of course.
Good.
Get some rest, sweetie.
I love you.
Hey, James,
how you doing today?
Outside walk.
Those are your biggest words yet.
You're doing so great!
Yes, we can!
- Honey! Be careful by the water, OK?
- OK!
I don't know why it's so hard for
everyone to believe he's getting better.
Well, he's getting better
but don't you wanna know why?
Is it...?
I think a second opinion
would be good too.
We can do that.
A second opinion is OK.
Did you ask doctor Milton about this?
Hmm, I haven't been
in contact with him yet.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Juliet!
What happened? You're OK?
Come here, baby, come on!
What's wrong?
You tell me, what's wrong?
It's Larry.
Don't look at him.
Is that a binding circle out the back?
A bounding circle?
If they found an area was evil,
they would do a ring around
with like salt or fire...
to try to keep the
evil contained.
It's gonna be OK.
OK.
All right. That's great.
Thank you.
So, the vet can be here first thing
tomorrow morning to pick up the body.
Thank you for doing this.
Thanks for everything.
Of course!
Joan!
- Don't worry about it.
- I know.
- And Juliet is gonna be OK.
How about I come by and check on
everybody after my shift tonight?
- Is that all right?
- Yeah, it sounds great.
OK.
It can't leave the house.
Hey, Mom, I need to talk to you.
Mom! Stop!
Are you listening to me?
Look, I know you're gonna
think I'm crazy, OK? But I...
I got a really bad
feeling about this house.
I think it's doing
something to James, it's - it's...
It's like possessing him
or infecting him, I...
I don't know.
There's this room in
the basement, OK?
I've been down there,
I've seen it myself.
I swear, I think that's what's
making him all of a sudden better.
Please, say something.
I don't think you're crazy, sweetheart.
I know about the red room.
Come here.
Wait... what did you just say?
You know I always believed in God.
And then your father got sick.
We had to watch him rot away
from the inside from cancer.
Everyday I prayed.
And then James got sick.
And still I prayed.
Two years.
The doctors had
given up on him, right?
They said he'd never come back.
I won't accept that.
What are you talking about?
God gave up on us, sweetheart.
So, I gave up on God.
And I moved us here.
Because if...
if there is some power...
that can make your brother better...
Better? No, Mom, you don't understand.
This isn't better.
This house is evil,
this house is really bad.
It's gonna drive James
to kill our own family,
just like the DeFeo's...
You, me, Juliet...
Stop, stop, come here.
No, no, no...
James would never do that, OK?
He would never do that.
He's getting better.
Honey, come here.
- Belle? - Get up!
- I need you to put this on, OK?
I want you to hurry
and stay quiet. OK?
Where are we going?
I'll be right back. Shhh!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
♪ Ain't it good? ♪
♪ Ain't it right? ♪
♪ That you are with me here tonight? ♪
♪ The music playing, ♪
Hi, honey!
Come, sit down,
we're just about to start dinner.
Hey, guess what, Belle?
Chicken smells great, Mom...
Oh, hey, Belle!
How did you sleep?
I hope you're hungry.
Mom made all this great food.
Juliet, pass the chicken, please.
Hey, this looks great!
Where's your bed?
In his room.
It's about time we had
a proper dining-room.
Jimmy.
Of course.
Dad would be so happy
to see us all here together.
- Don't you think, Mom?
- Yes, I do.
Fuck!
Candice?
Candice!
Don't come in!
No, please!
Joan?
Are you awake?
Belle?
(INDISTINCT)
Juliet?
Belle?
Can't get out of my room!
Belle!
Belle, I can't get out of my room!
- Juliet?
- Belle!
- Pshh! be quiet!
- Tell me what's going on!
Belle?
What's wrong with Mommy?
Juliet?
Hi, Mom.
Hi, baby.
What are you doing with that?
Don't you recognize me, baby?
Oh, God, no.
God has nothing to do with this!
Damn you to hell!
Too late.
- I left Didi standing...
- Shhhh...!
Where are you going?
Is that Larry?
No, baby.
I want you to go in the next door
neighbor's house and wait for me, OK?
There you are, sweetie.
James?
I'm scared.
Shhhh!
Don't be scared.
Didi.
We'll play a little game, OK?
OK, Juls.
I don't want to.
Turn over and go to sleep.
Do it!
Stop!
Don't hurt her.
- You wouldn't hurt your brother, would you?
- You're not my brother.
My brother died two years ago
and you know it.
Because of what  you did!
Belle!
It hurts so bad.
I c-can't move.
T-t-that wasn't me, Bell.
You have to believe me.
I swear!
Please!
Help me.
I miss you!
Please!
I'm so sorry!
I'm sorry about everything.
I love you.
Help me.
Take me back inside.
It's - It's what Mom would have wanted.
You don't wanna disappoint her, do you?
Mom is dead, so is Juliet.
All we have is each other now.
Liar!
You're not James.
You're a liar!
No!
You're not James!
I don't wanna die!
(INDISTINCT)
It's me!
No!
Why?
No! No! No! No!
No!
Please!
Hey.
Thank you.
Belle?
- Belle?
- Juliet?
Belle!
Juliet?
Oh, my God!
Baby!
Hey, let me see you, are you all right?
Are you hurt?
What happened to James?
He was gonna hurt us, baby.
But he's in a - he's in better place now.
I promise.
OK, now, listen to me, Juliet,
the police are gonna be here really soon.
I'm gonna tell them
exactly what happened.
But I need you to do the same, OK?
James tried to hurt us
and I need you Te tell them that.
Right, baby?
- Yes.
- Yeah?
Do you think they'll believe us?
Tragedy has struck once again at
112 Ocean Avenue in Amityville, Long Island.
The infamous house where Ronny DeFeo
killed his entire family with a shotgun.
More than four decades ago.
Police are questioning 17-year old
Belle Walker as a person of interest
in the brutal murders
of her aunt Candice,
her mother Joan
and the death of her brother James.
Miss Walker claims that
her brother committed the crimes,
and her story is being corroborated
by her seven-year old sister, Juliet.
A spokesman for the
Amityville Police Department
said that forensic evidence does
point to James as the killer.
His fingerprints were found
on the murder weapon.
But doctor Ken Milton
refutes that claim,
stating that James Walker was
too weak to get out of bed.
Let alone stalk his entire
family with a shotgun.
But two years prior
to the murders,
James was in a comma,
a vegetative state.
Is this house a source of evil,
as legend suggests?
Did it awaken and possess
James Walker or his sister Belle?
For now the police are left
with a horrific unsolved crime.
And Amityville, Long Island, is once again,
the center of shock and horror.
Translation and subtitles by
PEPPER & LALASPAIN
*** SONG LIVES FOR EVER ***