Subtitle created by - Aorion -
"Annabelle: Creation (2017)" (Run time 01:48:58)
Find me
closer
Found you
Ah ha!
You think you could hide
from me, did you?
Did you read what it said?
It said found you.
- It didn't say tickle...
- Samuel. Bee.
That's enough.
- You don't want to get overheated.
- I'm not.
You're sure?
Good.
Because now it's my turn!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Dad, help!
- You need help?
Oh sure, I can
help tickle you.
I think the bottom of this feet
might be very ticklish.
Time for bed, Bee.
Thank you.
- I love you Mommy.
- I love you more.
Mommy?
- Just for a little while.
- Thanks.
- Mommy.
- Um-hm.
Can we play dollies
when we get home?
Well, I think if you help me
with the washing up
- I can play dollies with you all afternoon.
- Sam.
Yes!
Sam.
Good morning, Sam.
- Good morning, Esther.
- Morning.
Hey there, busy Bee.
Sam, just wondering...
if you got that order
of mine ready yet?
I got customers coming
into my store everyday
asking about your dolls.
You can send your son
over tomorrow, Vic.
They're ready.
Well, hallelujah.
I guess prayers do
get answered, don't they?
They do.
Oh right... well, thank you so much.
You all have a good Sunday.
- You have a good day too.
- You have a lovely day.
In you get.
Damn it!
Language.
There's a car coming,
why don't I wave it down
and see if we can
get some help.
No, no, no, no.
I got it.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I'll get it.
BEE!
No!
ANNABELLE
CREATION
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
12 YEARS LATER
St. Eustace Home for Girls
B-L-U-E
Okay.
Pick a number.
Linda?
Um.
Four.
Okay.
You'll soon make new friends.
Do my now.
What's wrong?
I just wish you and me
were going to a new home
instead of a new orphanage.
Sweet Sue thinks too.
It would be nice
to have a home.
Yeah, but...
only if you're there.
I don't want to go
anywhere you're not.
So, let's swear.
If someone wants one of us,
they get both of us.
Okay.
I swear.
Good.
Me too.
You know what I like most
about Sweet Sue?
What?
She looks just like you.
So, how much further
is it, father?
Jesus, Mary and Joseph.
You're worse than the children, sister.
The Mullins agreeing to take
us in was a gift from god.
What kind of person isn't
excited about getting a gift?
I should mention
don't be alarm if you...
don't see much of
Mrs Mullins at first.
She... has a condition.
You see, she was in
an accident years ago.
You girls would do well
to help her if need be.
Janice.
You need help?
No, thanks.
I can manage.
Sister.
She's one of the unfortunate ones
with that polio outbreak,
but she's getting stronger everyday.
She won't be a burden,
I promise you.
Um-hm.
Mr Mullins, why don't
you show the girls around?
I can unload their belongings.
We'll start inside.
Thank you, father.
Wow.
This is an amazing castle.
Which obviously makes us the princesses.
This is our new orphanage?
Which is fine if
we're never being adopted.
There's a TV.
The television no longer works,
the radio however does.
This goes on forever.
You're right. We're going to need
a map to find our way around.
Girls, this way.
As you can see, the dining room
is more than adequate
to accommodate all of us.
Wow.
What's in here?
Let's stay together.
Mrs Mullins and I stay in here.
Fell free to use the rest of the
downstairs as you see fit.
Your rooms are upstairs.
Mr Mullins.
Is there someway Janice and I
can maybe stay down here?
Me too.
I'll be fine.
I installed it years ago
for my wife.
Hasn't been used in ages,
it works fine.
Try it, Jan.
If you don't, I will.
Up is up
Down is down.
It won't work...
... unless you click the seat belt in.
Like this.
Simple.
Thank you.
I get to go next!
Wow.
Nice.
I guess this is ours.
Let's take that side.
Kate and Tierney can have these.
What about Linda and me?
Relax, Janice. This is a big house,
there are other bedrooms.
Why can't Linda and me
have those over there?
Okay, but then,
where would Kate and Tierney sleep?
Wow.
This is neat.
I got this one.
Locked.
And it stays that way too.
Hey, Jan.
In here.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hey.
You wanna bunk beds?
- Hey sister Charlotte, can we...
- Oh lord.
Please bless Nancy with the wisdom
to not give people their heart attacks.
Sorry.
What is your emergency?
Can we go exploring?
Help father Massey with
your things first and then...
But Mr Mullins insist that we go.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- But that doesn't mean you don't have to...
- You know how father Massey is.
We'll only get in the way.
- Fine.
- She said okay!
But look out for one another.
You coming, Jan?
Maybe in a little while.
Well.
Maybe I'll stay too.
Because you feel sorry for me?
Well...
You promised you wouldn't
treat me any differently.
Okay.
See ya!
Dear lord.
Thank you for bringing us all together.
Bless this food for our use,
and us to thy service.
Fill our hearts with grateful praise.
And help us give you
glory each day through
Jesus Christ our Lord.
Amen.
If you'd excuse me.
Carol.
Keep to your own business.
And if I die before I wake,
I pray the lord my soul to take.
Please, god.
Help Linda and me find a good home
and keeps us together.
- So we finally be real sisters.
- With good loving parents.
That hate homework
as much as we do.
But, even if they don't,
that's okay too.
Amen.
Find me
in here
Nancy.
Carol.
Are you guys in here?
Forgive me, Father,
for I am about to sin.
I bet this is where
Mr Mullins keeps his wife.
Does she really wear a mask?
Yeah, she look like a doll.
Mrs Mullins?
You down there?
Stop it.
I think he seems nice.
Why don't you go find Janice,
see what she's up to.
Why?
So you can talk about boys.
Well, do you want to
talk about boys?
Gross.
No.
I wanna play a game.
Okay.
Let's play hide and seek.
You go hide and
we'll come look for you.
Okay.
So, are we going to
look for her?
Maybe.
Bless you.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
I asked Mr Mullins if we could use
this room for our new classroom
and he graciously agreed.
Would you like to help?
What's wrong?
I have a sin to confess.
Forgive me, sister Charlotte,
for I have sinned.
-  It's been...
- At least 2 weeks.
... at least 2 weeks
since my last confession.
There's this room upstairs
I'm not suppose to go into.
But you did anyway.
How did you know?
Because otherwise why would
you be telling me about it.
Well, the door was already opened.
I don't know how because
Mr Mullins always keeps it locked.
When I went inside
there was this little doll.
- And it was really strange.
- Janice.
Weird things started to happen.
Janice, listen to yourself.
What do I always say?
A sin is a sin
no matter the context.
More importantly, you absolutely
cannot disobey the Mullins.
We only just got here and
they're doing a very generous thing
by allowing us
to stay with them.
If they decide to
no longer have us here
we'll all be split up.
So next time you're thinking
of breaking a rule,
think of how that could've affect
the other girls first.
Do you understand me?
Yes.
I'm sorry, sister, I wasn't thinking.
It's okay, love.
For your penance,
pray 1 Hail Mary
and unpack 3 of these boxes.
What are you guys doing?
Unpacking boxes.
Oh.
This place is so creepy.
What was that?
How dare you!
Oh, Mr Scarecrow.
Oh.
Found you.
You're not very good at hiding.
Years of neglect have
affected the counter balance.
There.
That should keep the draft out.
Thank you.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Those taken in Romania.
At a convent of cloistered nuns.
They have little contact
with the outside world
but I became very close
to these three.
That's sister Maria.
That's sister Anna.
And that's sister Lucia.
Who's this?
!! Valak !!
I... don't know.
I don't think I even met her.
Is there anything else you need?
No.
Thank you.
Good night.
Uuu.
I like him.
Which one would you marry?
Oh.
I don't know.
I guess I'll just have to date
all of them to find out.
This is Ira.
- His eye.
- He's very handsome.
Night time is when Mrs Mullins
gets her powers.
That's why she's in bed all day.
But at night...
she can go wherever she wants.
She needs to
so she can feed.
And if you look directly
at her you'll die.
And to get you to look,
she'll keep saying your name
over and over
till you can't stand it!
Nancy.
- Nancy...
- No. No.
Nancy.
Oh.
She's ready to feed.
Carol.
Hey, we're not suppose to be up.
- Well, you'll do it to.
- Hey.
Why isn't he answering her?
- It's her.
- Don't look at her.
No!
Please please please...
Please.
She's gone.
What's going on?
What on god's earth?
- Sister Charlotte.
- Mrs Mullins.
She was here.
We heard.
In this room,
she was sitting right over there.
Who?
Your wife apparently.
They said she was
just in here.
Oh, that's impossible.
My wife hasn't been
able to walk for years.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Girls.
Let's go back to our studies, okay?
You okay, Nance?
Did you really see Mrs Mullins
in your room last night?
Yes.
We swear we were under the cover and...
Nancy.
Stop it.
We just freaked ourselves out
last night, you know that.
Mrs Mullins?
Sister Charlotte.
Could I trouble you
for a glass of water?
Of course.
It's good to hear
some life again.
I've been cooped up here so long
I forgotten what that sounded like.
What a lovely picture.
She was taken from us
at an early age... unfortunately.
If you could turn away
for a moment, sister.
Yes, of course.
I'm very sorry to hear
about your daughter.
But we find comfort in knowing
she waits for you in heaven.
I wish that were true.
Oh my gosh.
You shouldn't be in here.
Well, neither should you.
Who's room is this anyways?
The Mullins had a daughter.
It was her's.
Had one?
I think she died.
And I think that was her
playing the music too.
Stop trying to scare me.
I'm not.
It's the truth.
Then why are we in here.
- We should leave.
- No.
Oh.
Linda.
What is it?
We shouldn't be in here.
Okay.
I'll leave in a minute.
Well, I'm going.
Dear Diary, today I came home
Who's doing that?
Hi.
You're the Mullins' daughter...
aren't you?
What happened to you?
Will you help me?
What do you need?
YOUR SOUL!
Charlotte!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Sister Charlotte!
No.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
How do you feel?
Give her some space.
Girls.
Janice is feeling
a little down right now.
So, we need to do
what we can to support her.
Time I think
is all she needs.
She'll walk again, right?
We'll have to see.
You need sleep.
That's going to help you
with the healing.
I can't stay here, sister Charlotte.
We can't stay here.
We need to leave.
Leave.
And go where?
There isn't anywhere else
for us to go.
I didn't fall down those stairs.
Something threw me.
What do you mean?
You always say that
even though we can't see god
we can...
we can feel his presence.
Well...
in this house I feel
a different kind of presence.
What kind?
An evil one.
It's coming after me.
Coming after my soul.
You soul.
Because I'm the weakest.
No, darling.
Listen.
The devil preys on
those weak in faith,
not weak of flesh and bone.
You are as strong
as any of us, Janice.
Stronger.
You're quiet, Samuel.
I think it was a mistake...
to bring the girls here.
Why?
The girl ...
The girl who fell.
Maybe she didn't fall.
Maybe...
It was an accident.
That's all it was.
Accidents happen.
It's been quiet for 12 years.
You should try embracing
the presence of the girls...
instead of frightening them away.
You'll be better soon.
I don't think so.
Not this time.
But you have too.
You said we'll find
a new home.
No one is going to
want me now.
I'll just be a burden.
But you swore we'll stay together.
I take it back.
Maybe I won't get adopted.
You will.
You know why?
Because you're special.
You're going to get adopted by
a nice family somewhere
and they're going to
spoil you so much.
You're going to have
so many dolls that...
you won't even be able to
name all of them.
Sure I can.
Janice one.
Janice Two.
Janice Three.
Linda.
Time for bed.
Won't you come upstairs?
I don't want to sleep alone.
Here.
Take Becca.
This way,
I'll always be with you.
Then, you should have Sweet Sue.
Thank you.
Remember before
all of this.
When we used to sneak around
the orphanage at night,
And ate all the chocolate
of the pantry.
Father Massey was convinced
that we had mice.
Oh lord, please cleanse
my soul of my sins
and cleanse our house of...
- these mice.
Whatever happens
I was thinking always
all those things we did together.
Good night, Linda.
Good night, Jan.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
A little sunlight will
do you some good.
I don't the sunlight can fix
what's wrong with me.
You mustn't give up hope.
Hope is a home onto itself.
Dwell in it and it will
protect and keep you.
What book of the bible
is that from?
The book of Charlotte.
But that doesn't
make it any less so.
Are you okay here?
The sunlight actually
feels kind of nice.
I told you.
Sister Charlotte?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
No, no, no!
GOD HELP ME!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Janice!
What's going on?
I couldn't get out.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm worry about Janice.
A few nights ago
she wanted to leave.
Why she want to leave?
Probably because this place
is off the wall.
She told me the Mullins's daughter
was coming for her.
The Mullins' had a daughter?
She died a long time ago.
So, she's seeing ghost?
Keep your voice down.
I guess.
Well...
You guys saw something.
That wasn't a ghost.
Ghost can only be
of dead people.
How does that explain
what you saw?
Unless it really was Mrs Mullins.
Or...
something was just trying to scare you.
You guys are doing a good job
with that on your own.
Janice is probably just looking for ways
to justify us treating her differently.
I don't think so.
Of course you don't.
You'll know what I mean
when you're older.
Now go get to bed.
What are you waiting for?
Nothing.
You like it?
It's nice.
It's not my finest work.
You seem troubled.
Maybe I can help.
I don't think so.
Talking about the things
that bothers us sometimes...
all the help we need.
Well.
It's Janice.
She's acting funny.
Acting funny?
She says...
she's seen your daughter.
My daughter...
has been dead for a
very very long time
I know, but...
You see,
Janice went into her bedroom.
She what?
She knows she wasn't suppose to
but...
- she found this doll and...
- What doll?
The one in the white dress.
That's impossible!
That doll was hidden away.
She mustn't go near that doll!
You understand me?
Found you
Janice, I told you
not to use that room.
Please don't take
my sunshine away...
Ahhh!
Stay here.
Mr Mullins.
Mr Mullins, are you okay?
Go get ready for bed, girls.
I need to speak to Mrs Mullins.
Linda.
What are you doing?
This doll.
It's hurting Janice
and it killed Mr Mullins.
I'm getting rid of it.
Linda, let's go back.
Linda?
No!
What is that?
Who cares!
Run!
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Janice. Janice.
I got rid of it.
I got rid of the doll.
Janice.
- What's going on?
- Where is Janice?
- I don't know.
- Go find her.
Hurry!
What's going on?
No!
Get that thing away from me!
It's back.
I know it was back.
What is it?
Evil.
The devil itself.
What are you talking about?
After Samuel and I...
lost our daughter
we prayed and promised
our devotion to
whatever power that
would allow us to
speak or see our
beloved girl again.
It started small,
the contact.
But it was her.
Our busy Bee.
We know it was her.
She wanted permission
to move into the doll
so she could be
with us forever.
please
We said yes.
And that's when it became stronger.
Soon we can actually see her.
Only in fleeting glimpses
but that was enough.
Our beloved Bee.
Our darling.
Annabelle?
Even though I couldn't hold her.
It was comforting to start
the past activity again.
But we soon realised
it wasn't our Annabelle at all.
You are my sunshine,
my only sunshine
You make me happy ...
when skies are gray
You'll never know dear,
how much I love you
Please don't take my sunshine away
Esther?
Esther.
My... eye...
It was a demonic presence.
And it was using our
Annabelle to manipulate us
into giving it soul
it couldn't have.
It tried to take mine.
Then Samuel reached out
to the church.
They saved my soul
but the evil was still
attached to that doll.
So we locked it away
where it could be surrounded
by the word of god.
It was quiet
for all these year.
I thought the evil was contained.
We thought helping the girls
could be our penance.
But we end up giving it
just what it wanted.
You are my sunshine,
my only sunshine
You make me happy
when skies are gray
- You'll never know dear,
- Janice.
how much I love you
Please don't take my sunshine away
She can walk.
It's just us, Janice.
Time to cease from sin, Carol.
Sister Charlotte!
It's-It's Janice.
- She's... She's...
- Look what she did!
- Carol, call for help.
- Okay.
- And stay together.
They're on their way.
Let get somewhere safe.
What do we do?
We can't just leave her here,
can we?
Mrs Mullins?
Girls.
Let's go.
Now.
Forgive me, sister,
for I have sinned.
- Sister Charlotte!
- Run. Come on!
Linda!
Go, Tierney!
Get help!
Or...
... you can help me.
The truck!
Come on.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Close the door! Close the door!
Come on!
Go!
Go.
No!
Okay.
I'm trying!
Guys!
- Guys! Guys!
- What? What?
The scarecrow.
What scarecrow?
Get out!
Come on!
Run!
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Carol?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Nancy, I can't Ge the door open.
Is it locked?
Can you get it from your side?
Girls.
Nancy?
No.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Lord, help me.
Lord, help.
Help...
Carol, it's me.
It's just me.
Now, come on.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
No.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
No!
Sister Charlotte?
You know what I like most
about Sweet Sue?
She looks just like you.
Linda?
Where are you, Linda?
Linda, I'm coming?
Found you!
You swore if I found a home
you'd come too.
You know what they say
about breaking a swear.
You go straight to hell.
Janice!
Forgive me.
No!
Let me out!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Let me out... !
Go!
- Sister Charlotte!
Anything?
I'm afraid not.
Still no sign of the girl.
But at her age...
how far could she'd gone?
Don't worry.
We'll find her.
This house is blessed.
Whatever evil was here
is no longer.
But...
The doll.
It was a conduit
for the evil.
That evil has moved on.
Now the doll
is just a doll.
So...
... which one of you gets this?
How are you holding up?
I'm okay.
You know, that wasn't Janice back there.
That was...
... something else.
I know.
ST. JOACHIM
ORPHANAGE
Hi there.
Welcome.
Let's go right inside, shall we?
She mostly keeps to herself,
that can be a bit quite.
but she's a lovely girl.
She's just been through a lot.
I think you will love her.
Hello.
There's someone here to see you, sweetie.
I want to introduce you to
Mr and Mrs Higgins.
And you must be...
- Annabelle.
What a lovely name.
We brought you a present.
I hope you like dolls.
12 YEARS LATER
- Did you hear that?
- Yeah.
What is it?
Stay here.
No, no, no!
No, wait.
It's okay.
It's alright, sweetheart.
I'm just going to
take a quick look.
Call the police.
- Annabelle?
- Hi, Mom.
John.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Subtitle created by - Aorion -