Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
It was a big mistake
acknowledging this doll.
And through that,
the inhuman spirit
tricked you.
You gave it permission
to infest your lives.
What's an inhuman spirit?
It's something
that's never
walked the earth
in human form.
It's something demonic.
So,
the doll was never possessed?
No,
it was used as a conduit.
It was moved around to give
the impression of possession.
Demonic spirits
don't possess things.
They possess people.
It wanted to
get inside of you.
And given
this unusual feature,
the doll will need to be
properly cared for.
- Cared for?
- Mmm-hmm.
It should be destroyed.
That would
only make things worse.
We think it best
the doll come with us.
We'll keep it somewhere safe.
That sounds like
a great idea.
She's all yours.
♪ Now that you're gone ♪
♪ All that's left
is a band of gold ♪
♪ All that's left of ♪
- ♪ The dreams I hold ♪
♪ Is a band of gold ♪
♪ And the memories ♪
♪ Of what love could be ♪
How much longer,
do you think?
Eh, about an hour.
Why don't you put your
head back? Get some rest.
No, you get lost coming home
from the supermarket.
If I do that,
we might end up in California.
Well, so you wake up
to the sound of the Pacific.
Nothing wrong with that.
I'll pick up Judy
on the way.
Ah, that actually sounds
so nice, Ed.
We should plan on it.
Uh-oh.
What's this?
You folks need to turn around.
Pretty bad accident up ahead.
Uh, anything we can do?
You a doctor or something?
Or something.
He just meant if you need
an extra set of hands.
Yeah.
We got it covered. Thanks.
Nice doll.
That's what you think.
All right, you're gonna head
three miles back to the last exit.
You'll hop on 26,
that'll loop you around.
- 26. Got it.
- Thank you, Officer.
A guy and his doll.
I think we missed our turn.
We didn't miss it.
Bridgewater's just up ahead.
Bridgewater?
Old Ridge Road.
Where did you get
Bridgewater from?
Well, you know what?
I think we missed our turn.
I'll keep my eye out
for the Pacific.
Ed?
- Ed?
- Hang on, hang on.
- Come on.
- What just happened?
Uh... I'll pop the hood
and find out.
Well, be careful.
There we go.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I like your doll.
I feel cold.
You were
just in an accident.
I was?
Sorry. Wires crossed.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
That should do it.
Honey, you okay?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Ed!
I'm okay.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I'm so sorry!
All of a sudden it was like
somebody took over my truck.
I had no control.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
It's the doll, Ed.
It's a beacon
for other spirits.
Over here.
Father, sooner the better.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Be not wise
in thine own eyes.
Fear the Lord
and depart from evil.
The curse of the Lord is
in the house of the wicked.
But He blesseth
the habitation of the just.
Surely,
He scorneth the scorners,
but He giveth grace
unto the lowly.
The wise shall inherit
the glory,
but shame shall be
the promotion of fools.
Amen.
We need another
barrier of protection.
A holy one.
I agree.
The blessing
will only do so much.
That chapel glass
we got from Trinity Church
before it was torn down,
where is that?
"Let us forgive those
who trespass against us
and lead us
not into temptation,
but deliver us from evil."
Amen.
Did it work?
Hmm. The evil is contained.
♪ Colorful, magical ♪
♪ Wonderful, wow! ♪
♪ The Captain is coming
Just look at him now ♪
♪ Super sensational, special
And new ♪
♪ The Captain is coming
With something for you ♪
♪ Here comes Captain Kangaroo ♪
Okay, Judy.
I just saw Mary Ellen pull up.
Go and get your things.
But first put
your cereal in the...
All right. Never mind.
I'll do it.
♪ Captain Kangaroo is who ♪
♪ Will make this day
So great with you ♪
♪ Colorful, magical
Wonderful, wow! ♪
♪ The Captain is coming Just look at him now ♪
♪ Super sensational, special
And new ♪
♪ The Captain is coming
And you're gonna love him ♪
What's that?
♪ Captain Kangaroo ♪
Oh.
Well?
You're my hero.
The pizza money
is on the counter
and numbers are by the phone.
Perfect.
And we'll be back
early tomorrow morning.
Well, and take your time,
we'll be fine. Right, Judy?
Yeah.
- So, you'll...
- Behave? Yes.
And you'll remember
to go to...
Remember to go to bed
on time.
Absolutely.
- All right, don't forget to...
- To have fun.
- I know.
- That, too.
Did you guys rehearse that,
or what?
Earth to Judy!
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm fine.
Well, it's just a couple more
hours until the weekend.
I'm gonna run to the market
for supplies
during my free period.
I'll pick you up after, okay?
Sounds super.
Bye, Judy!
Have a good day!
Mrs. Faley,
it's right over here.
Let me show you.
How could you not tell me
what the Warrens did
for a living?
Shouldn't you be
in math class?
Mary Ellen!
I babysat the Smiths
for over two years
and never told you
what they did.
Oh, what do they do?
They're podiatrists.
So not the same.
Well, obviously,
I'm coming over later.
We do have
that social studies project
- that we need to work on.
- Uh...
We don't have any project.
Okay, but how would
they know?
She's psychic.
Then, they're heroes.
I think
they're concerned parents
who wouldn't want
negative influences
around their child.
What negative influence?
'Cause I sometimes
stay out past curfew?
Among other things.
So, what's it like
inside the house?
Is it all creepy music
and cobwebs?
No. No, it's boring suburbia.
The inside
of your locker is scarier.
Wait. Whose party,
and why wasn't I invited?
Judy's birthday is coming up,
so we're gonna
celebrate early.
You really are the best
babysitter, you know that?
Compliments will
get you nowhere.
What about threats?
Did you, uh, happen to notice
who's working checkout?
- Have a good one.
- Will do.
- Thank you so much.
- See you soon.
You wouldn't.
You know what they call him,
right?
- Have a good one.
- What?
Bob's-Got-Balls.
How you doing?
Hi, Daniela.
Uh...
- Hi, Mary Ellen.
- Is this everything?
- I think so.
- Oh, cool.
You live near the Warrens,
don't you, Bob?
Uh...
Yeah, Mary Ellen's babysitting
for them tonight.
Yeah. Yeah, I live
right across the street.
Do you ever see
anything scary over there?
Like a ghost, maybe?
Bob...
Mrs. Faley went ahead
and dropped a can
of tomato sauce in aisle five,
and it looks like a crime
scene, so get the mop.
Ladies. Did you find
everything okay?
- Mmm-hmm.
- Yes, sir.
Bob here is not giving you
any trouble, is he?
- No.
- Yeah, I got it. Thanks, Dad.
- All right.
I'll do it right after.
So, what'd you see?
At the Warrens'?
Uh, nothing. Nothing.
Um, your total is $3.50, so...
Oh.
But you knew
what the Warrens did?
There were rumors,
I guess, but...
Rumors. Interesting.
Did you know there's a rumor
going around about you, Bob?
- Wait, really?
- What is it about?
Uh, it's about a girl
who has a...
Fine. You can come.
Stop.
- Oh. Sorry.
- Sorry.
- That's totally my fault.
- It's okay.
Um... So, what...
Bye, Bob. Thanks.
Bye.
Uh, she forgot her eggs, so...
Here.
She likes you.
There's been an accident.
Don't touch her.
You'll get obsessed.
- It's "possessed."
- That's what I said.
Anyways, if you know so much,
why don't you tell us
if you can catch cooties
from a ghost?
You can't.
Well, then how'd you get 'em?
Anthony Rios!
Don't make me
get your sister.
Please don't.
Then go. All of you.
Come on.
Come on. Let's go!
I'm sorry I can't come
to your birthday party, Judy.
You can't either?
My parents said
I'm not really prepared
to process death yet.
It's a birthday party.
I'm sorry.
Hey, how long
has that been happening?
Since everyone heard about
the article this week.
Please don't tell my parents.
I won't.
I won't as long as you do.
- I don't want them to worry.
- They're parents.
They're worried
about everything
whether they need to be
or not.
Are you sure the bullying is
the only thing
that's bothering you?
That isn't bothering me.
You know what I mean.
And remember our deal.
No secrets.
I know.
I don't have any.
What did you get
at the store?
A surprise.
- You said no secrets.
- A surprise isn't a secret.
- What is it then?
- It's a surprise.
♪ I remember
Finding out about you ♪
You're gonna make a mess.
Hey! Save some for the cake.
No.
I think
there's someone at the door.
I was knocking on the door
for, like, ten minutes.
How did you even get in?
Back door.
Is this a spirit bell?
What's a spirit bell?
It tells you if you're in
the presence of any spirits.
- So, it is one.
- No.
It's just a bell.
My mom collects them.
Oh.
Who are you?
She's Daniela,
and she leaves after cake.
Oh, good!
I love cake.
So, Judy.
Don't your parents, like, keep
any creepy stuff around?
No.
They keep it all locked away
in a room.
Well, can we at least
go in and look?
No!
It's not really good
for anyone to go in there.
How come?
Just isn't.
Wait.
Here.
Birthday present.
What is it?
Look inside.
How did you
even afford those?
They're my old ones.
But I only ever used them once
'cause I broke my arm
the first time I put them on.
You're kidding.
She looks
way more coordinated.
They're gonna ruin the floors.
Can we go around
the block, then?
- I don't think...
- Good idea.
You guys go.
I'll watch the cake
and make sure it doesn't burn.
Fine. But don't snoop.
Don't touch.
Don't do anything. Please?
Stay in the kitchen.
Promise me.
I promise.
Fuck it.
I am calling out to the
spirits on the other side.
Please unlock this door
and let me in.
Shit.
Please don't judge me.
Amen.
Whoa.
What'd you do
to get in there?
If there is a presence here
in this room,
please give me a sign.
Any sign at all.
Dad?
This is stupid.
Shit.
You burnt the cake? Daniela.
Only the top.
Just put frosting on it.
She'll never know.
How'd it go with the skates?
She loved them until she fell
on the way back
and skinned her knee.
Better than breaking her arm.
Where is she anyway?
She's out
feeding the chickens.
They have chickens?
Hey. How's your knee?
Oh.
Looks like your jeans will
at least need some stitches.
It's okay.
Accidents happen.
So, are you scared yet?
Scared? What? No.
Who says they're scared?
Kids in my class.
Anthony Rios started it.
I hate him.
Wait. Tony Rios started it?
Do you know him?
Yeah, he's my brother.
Anthony Rios is your brother?
Yeah, I know.
Don't hold it against me.
I don't like him either.
You know,
he still wets the bed.
You didn't hear it from me.
Or maybe you did,
I don't care.
Still, just...
go a little easy on him.
It's been a tough year.
You lost somebody,
didn't you?
My dad. Uh...
Did Mary Ellen tell you?
No.
I just knew.
Um, for delivery.
Could I do one large, please?
Um, it's gonna be
3506 Wayman Street.
Oh, perfect. Thank you.
Coming.
Hold your horses.
Who is it?
Hello?
Daniela?
Is Annabelle there?
Who?
Can Annabelle
come out to play?
I think you have
the wrong house.
There's no Annabelle here.
Yes, she is.
She's right behind you.
People are just...
They're really weird about death.
That's probably why the kids
pick on you at school.
It scares them.
They treat it like it's some
disease they don't wanna get,
even though
everyone already has it.
But here's the thing.
I used to think
it was fatal and whammo.
It's, like, out.
Like turning off a TV.
Then I learned
about your parents
and their whole exploration
into the afterlife
and stuff...
and they gave me hope.
That maybe
life goes on somehow.
Maybe...
my darling dad
is still out there somewhere.
"Darling dad"?
It was a thing.
He was darling dad,
and I was darling Daniela...
Stupid.
He's still out there,
you know.
You think so?
My parents
would say he is, too.
Where are you going?
Be right back.
Dad?
Daniela?
Daniela!
Where did she go?
What are you doing?
Daniela, you're not supposed
to go down there!
- What are you doing?
- I thought I saw something.
What did you see?
Forget it. It doesn't matter.
Judy?
In thee, O Lord,
do I put my trust.
Let me never be
put to confusion.
Deliver me into
Thy righteousness
and cause me to escape.
Incline Thine ear...
Hey! Hey, Judy! Judy.
What's going on? What's wrong?
What's going on?
What happened?
Nothing.
Judy...
I just got scared.
Scared of what?
Sometimes...
I see things.
Like how my mom sees things.
You mean like ghosts?
Where do you see them?
Everywhere I go.
Judy...
Ghosts used to be people.
And not every person
you meet is bad...
so maybe not all ghosts
are bad, either.
Daniela.
- You have to see this.
- What?
It's this case the Warrens
investigated about this girl
who was terrorized by
something called the Ferryman.
Here's a picture
of the girl he killed.
Look familiar?
I mean,
you two could be sisters.
Here's the rest of the file,
if you want to take a look.
Look at all this stuff.
How cool.
Okay, this is the file
on the Black Shuck.
The Black Shuck?
It was a case
the Warrens investigated
about a hellhound that
possessed a man in England.
He terrorized the shit
out of this town.
What's with the coins
over their eyes?
What?
Oh, I don't know.
I didn't get that far.
They used to put them
over the eyes of the dead
to pay the Ferryman,
so he could
take their souls
to the underworld.
It was his toll.
Okay, we should go.
It's okay. I sometimes
like to snoop, too.
Do you know
what this does, Judy?
I think it's called
a Mourner's Bracelet.
It helps you contact
your lost loved ones.
- What's that?
- Um...
It's a case my parents
investigated recently.
The wedding dress.
It haunts people.
And it makes them violent.
Where is the dress now?
Down the hall
in the artifact room.
I mean, that's where
all this stuff is.
Right, Judy?
- That's what you said earlier.
- Oh, um...
Yeah.
My dad says
that everything in there
is either haunted, cursed,
or used in some
ritualistic practice.
What about the doll
that's in there?
Because I read this interview
with your dad...
No.
Don't talk about her.
Why not?
She's in a case for a reason.
Okay, we should go.
I wonder what's on this.
No, Daniela! Wait!
I command you,
unclean spirit,
along with all your minions...
I command you
to obey me to the letter!
Okay, show's over.
Let's go do something else.
Do something that's
actually appropriate.
Come on,
don't you at least wanna hear
about the samurai?
What about this one?
I don't remember that one.
How do you play?
Let's find out.
Okay. Okay,
so you draw a card
and whatever picture
it has on it
is the object you try to find
by feeling around
inside the box.
If the object you pull out
matches the picture,
then you get a point.
You go first.
Okay.
You gonna get that?
Yeah.
Sorry, you guys keep playing.
Oh, got a point.
Nice.
Hello?
Hi, Mary Ellen.
Hi.
Remember how, at the store,
Daniela said that
you were babysitting here?
Yeah. Yeah.
Me, too.
Anyways, that's why I'm here.
Oh.
Bob, they don't really want me
having boys over.
No, that's not what I meant.
I don't wanna come in.
I just, uh...
I mean, I would, but...
Well...
I just knew you were
gonna be here,
and I just wanted to come by
and talk to you
without my stupid dad
or somebody interrupting.
Bob's-Got-Balls!
Nice.
You two sharing some pizza?
- I should get the money.
- Yeah.
Are you two, like...
I... I wish.
You know you need to, like,
woo her, right?
- Woo her?
- Yeah.
Guys like Mary Ellen,
they need to be wooed.
You mean
girls like Mary Ellen.
What did I say?
Guys.
So, how do I woo her?
There's only one way to woo.
It's obvious.
Rock and roll.
Here. Keep it.
Sweet.
Thanks, and that means
you can keep this.
Minus one slice.
I enjoyed that in the car.
See you later, Balls.
I would invite you in,
but like I said...
No, yeah, it's cool.
I thought I'd just stop by
and say hi, I guess, so...
I'm glad you did.
Me, too.
Hey, Bob, um...
How come they call you that?
Um...
Well, you know how
I'm the equipments manager
for the basketball team?
- Yeah.
- That's why.
There's not really, like,
a story or anything behind it.
Just like,
"Hey, I need balls."
I'm, like,
"I got it. Balls. Got 'em."
I'll see woo later.
You. You. I'll see you later.
I'm gonna go.
Bye, Bob.
Bye.
All right, Carolyn,
even a fortune teller
couldn't have predicted
the place we picked
for your date with Don.
Because who could ever have
dreamed up a place
as unbelievably fabulus as
Las Vegas, Nevada?
Yes, "amazing"
is the word for it.
You'll be flying off
for a fling
at the fabulous town
of Las Vegas,
to be guests of the fantastic
Flamingo Hotel,
a favorite spot
along the Vegas Strip.
And, Dawn, as a little
special gift for you...
Can you get your arms
around there?
Mary Ellen?
Daniela?
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, dear Judy ♪
Okay, Judy.
Ready for bed?
This is for you.
What's this?
It's an invitation
to my birthday party.
I don't think many people
are gonna come...
but will you?
You see what I got?
I got mine weeks ago.
So, you'll come?
I wouldn't miss it.
♪ You sheltered me from harm ♪
♪ You kept me warm ♪
What's that?
Oh, my God.
It isn't.
It is.
♪ You sheltered me from harm ♪
♪ You kept me warm ♪
♪ You kept me ♪
♪ warm ♪
- Bob!
- ♪ You gave my life... ♪
Uh... Um...
♪ Nobody else will ever know ♪
♪ The part of me
That can't let go ♪
♪ I would give
anything I own ♪
Uh...
Bob's got balls.
♪ Just to have you
back again ♪
How do I look?
Where's my inhaler?
Shit, no, it's in my car.
What am I supposed to do?
You will be fine.
It's only Bob.
♪ Just to touch you
once again ♪
Shit!
Fuck!
No!
Bob?
He left.
Hmm, hopefully he went home
to practice.
Okay. Back up to bed.
- Daniela.
- Yeah, yeah.
I'd feel better
if you let me stay.
I can wake up early.
We don't even
have to tell Judy.
No. No, it's fine.
Go home.
But...
But what?
Thank you for coming.
I actually think
it helped Judy a lot.
Sorry you didn't get to see
any cobwebs
or hear any creepy music.
Well, the Bob thing
was kind of creepy, at least.
But if Bob comes knocking
on this door late at night,
forget you're you for a minute
and let him in.
Call me tomorrow
and tell me the details.
There will be
no details to tell.
Shit.
How'd her dad die?
I don't know if that's
the best bedtime story.
Look who my parents are.
I'm used to it.
Well,
the short of it is that
he died in a car accident.
And the long of it is that...
Daniela was driving.
Was it her fault?
No.
There's only one person
who actually thinks
it was her fault.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Okay.
Let's try this again.
If there is
a presence here...
Dad?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
You did this to me!
It's all your fault!
Get back here!
You did this to me!
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
No, no, no. Please.
Please, no, no. Don't go.
Don't go.
No, no, no. No, come here.
Come here, come here.
No. No.
I'm sorry.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
♪ Day after day ♪
♪ Bring it home, baby
Make it soon ♪
♪ I give my love to you ♪
Judy?
Is that why he
picked her up from the closet?
Yes.
That must have been it.
He's not gonna pick
her up in a closet, is he?
You stay here
and don't make any noise.
What is happening?
Where's my coffee?
Good morning.
You've been
experiencing supernatural...
Good morning.
Where's my coffee?
Just a second.
He had
silver coins for his eyes.
She said his light shows you
the way
to the land of the dead.
I just wanna find my sister.
And when
did she first see him?
Not long
before he took her.
She said she'd wake up,
and he'd be in her room...
watching her sleep.
The night she went missing,
we both woke up to a noise.
It sounded like a coin
falling on the floor.
She told me
to wait in her room.
So I did.
She never came back.
I went to look for her and
ended up in a long hallway.
Filled with coffins.
Last night...
I woke up to a noise.
Another coin being dropped.
It was like he was...
Like he was calling me.
Have you ever seen
the Ferryman?
If you don't pay his toll,
he'll take your soul.
Shit! Shit! Shit! No.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Judy! Judy!
Judy!
Judy! Open the door, Judy!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
I like your dolls.
Judy! Judy!
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Go out the back!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
We're trapped.
- Hello?
- Oh, thank God. Mrs. Warren?
- Mom?
- Mary Ellen? Judy?
Is everything okay?
What's going on?
Judy's fine. Um...
Something is happening
inside your house
and I don't think
it's safe to go outside.
We're not really sure
what to do.
Can I speak to Annabelle?
I'm sorry?
You need to give her
a soul, dear.
- What?
- A soul. She wants her soul.
Give me her soul.
Wait! Don't!
I'm so sorry.
What are you doing here?
Annabelle.
The doll. She's the one
who's doing all of this.
A doll?
She wants a soul.
I just wanted
to see him again.
What did you do?
I wanted to tell him
I'm sorry.
I know it was my fault.
Daniela...
what did you do?
I let her out.
What else did you touch?
Everything.
Run! Run! Go!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Mary Ellen!
It's her asthma.
She's having an attack.
The inhaler's in her car.
I'll go get it.
No! Let me!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Judy! Run!
Mary Ellen!
Here.
Are you okay?
Where's Daniela?
She came after you.
Mary Ellen?
Judy? I'm up here.
No. That's not Daniela.
Something has a hold of her.
I can feel it.
What do we do?
We have to find Annabelle.
We have to put her back
in the case.
Do you know where she is?
No.
Wait, wait, Judy, don't.
Not all ghosts are bad.
Right?
What did you say?
Come on, let's go.
Come on.
I'll get her.
No, no, no.
No! Just stop!
Where do your parents
keep the key?
I don't know.
It's never locked.
I know where the key is.
- I'll get it.
- No! No, don't.
I'll do it.
Judy!
I got it.
Our Father, who art in heaven
hallowed be Thy name.
Oh, my God.
Give us this day
our daily bread,
and forgive us
for our trespasses
as we forgive those
who trespassed against us.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Mary Ellen?
Go!
Daniela.
Daniela, please!
Daniela, stop!
Stop!
I command you, unclean spirit,
along with all your minions,
now attacking
this servant of God.
- I command you to obey me to the letter.
- Judy, run!
In his name,
they will take up serpents...
...with his hands
and condemn all evil.
I command you,
unclean spirit,
along with all your minions,
- To obey me to the letter.
- No, no.
I, who am a servant of God...
I command you,
unclean spirit,
along with all your minions,
now attacking
this servant of God...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Judy!
Judy! Judy. Judy.
Get the doll!
- Close it!
- I'm trying!
Hurry!
Our Father who art in heaven,
hallowed be Thy name.
Thy kingdom come,
Thy will be done,
on earth as it is in heaven.
Put her in!
Give us this day
our daily bread,
and forgive us
for our trespasses,
as we forgive those
who trespassed against us,
lead us not into temptation,
but deliver us from evil...
Amen.
Is it over?
The evil has been contained.
Bob?
- Are you guys okay?
- Yeah. We're okay.
- Are you okay?
- No!
There was a werewolf outside!
You saw the werewolf?
Yeah.
He saved me from it.
You did?
Yeah. Yeah.
Kind of.
Maybe we should talk
about this somewhere else.
Good morning
from the staff
of WPKW-PV6
in Hartford, Connecticut.
This is Hartford, Connecticut,
the land of steady habits...
My parents.
Shit! You're not supposed
to have boys over.
I think that's the least of
our concerns right now, Bob.
Yeah, yeah. I should
probably still get going.
Hey, listen, um,
so Homecoming is coming up
- and I would really like...
- Yes. I'll... I'll go.
With me?
Yes, if the Warrens
don't kill me first.
We tell them everything.
Mom!
Judy! What are you
doing up so early?
Don't get mad...
What happened
to your car?
Here we go.
We'll have
our own party, huh?
- What?
- Can you please take that off?
It won't always be like this,
I promise.
You know,
and sooner or later,
you'll find people
who understand.
And as for young Anthony,
he better hope I don't
run into him anytime soon.
Ed.
Happy birthday, Judy.
Thank you.
Happy birthday.
I, uh, had a little talk
with my brother.
Thanks.
Come in.
Is it okay
if my boyfriend joins?
Sure.
Um...
- Hi, uh, thanks for having us.
- Hey.
Bob's-Got-Balls.
No kidding.
- Hi, Judy!
- Happy birthday, Judy!
- Happy birthday!
- Hello, Judy, happy birthday.
- Hey, guys, welcome.
Keep comin'.
Happy birthday, Judy.
- Anthony?
- I'm really sorry.
Am I still invited?
Sure.
Daniela?
I have something for you.
For me?
You found out the hard way
that there is a lot of evil
in this room.
But you know
what I actually like about it?
All the evil in here...
reminds me of all the good
that's out there.
Darling Daniela.
Did Judy tell you that?
No. Your dad did.
He also tells me
that he misses you.
And to stop being
so hard on yourself,
'cause it was
not your fault.
Thank you.
Um...
I'm sorry.
Oh.
It's okay.
You're young.
You know,
when I was about your age,
I once ran off with
a boyfriend for three days
without telling my parents.
I unleashed a demon.
So not the same thing.
Well, okay. True.
Does Mr. Warren know
about this boyfriend?
He was the boyfriend.
Anybody wanna
hear a song? Whoa!
Yeah!
All right, okay.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
♪ We get it almost
Every night ♪
♪ When that moon
Gets big and bright ♪
♪ It's a supernatural delight ♪
♪ Everybody was dancing
In the moonlight ♪
♪ Everybody here is
Out of sight ♪
♪ They don't bark
And they don't bite ♪
♪ They keep things loose
They keep it tight ♪
♪ Everybody was dancing
In the moonlight ♪
♪ Dancing in the moonlight ♪
♪ Everybody's feeling
Warm and bright ♪
♪ It's such a fine
And natural sight ♪
♪ Everybody's dancing
In the moonlight ♪
♪ We like our fun
And we never fight ♪
♪ You can't dance
And stay uptight ♪
♪ It's a supernatural delight ♪
♪ Everybody was dancing
In the moonlight ♪
♪ Dancing in the moonlight ♪
♪ Everybody's feeling
Warm and bright ♪
♪ It's such a fine
And natural sight ♪
♪ Everybody's dancing
In the moonlight ♪