Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Daddy, I heard something.
-Oh, yeah? What'd you hear?
-A noise.
It's just us working.
Why can't I come in with you?
'Cause I said so.
Ain't a place for kids.
We're almost done now.
Do not leave this truck.
Or drive off with it.
You hear me?
Go and put that in the glove box.
I'll be right back, bud.
Love you!
I'll finish up
and we'll go get your brother, Lucas.
All right, let's get outta here.
Hey, Frank, we still got plenty
to do one more batch if you want.
The fuck was that?
Listen.
You said they weren't gonna reopen this place
for another few weeks.
The fuck is that, Frank?
That's gotta be an animal.
Fuck me.
-The fuck you going, Frank?
-Come on.
Fuck.
The fuck is going on?
Where you going?
Frank.
Fuck.
Frank, let's get the fuck
outta here, all right?
Let's get the fuck outta here.
Something's on fucking fire, man.
Frank!
Let's get the fuck outta here, buddy.
Let's get the fuck outta here.
This is fucked up, man.
Where you going?
Let's get the fuck outta here.
Frank!
Run, Frank, run!
Oh, my God!
Frank!
Kenny!
Daddy?
I'll be right out.
It's obviously much more than just that.
Would anyone like to help him elaborate?
So, storytelling is a way for people
to explain their world...
their culture...
passing on customs and beliefs
from one generation to the next.
In America, and especially here in Oregon...
storytelling started with
our indigenous people.
Native Americans who were teaching
the younger people...
in their communities
about their culture and identities.
Can anyone give me an example
of a fable or a myth?
Or a fairy tale even.
Brody, give it a shot.
Evie, do you have any stories
you wanna share?
Lucas.
Give me an example of...
a fable or a myth.
Come on.
Anyone? Anyone?
Okay. Go ahead, Jasmine.
"Goldilocks."
"Goldilocks" is a fairy tale.
That's very good.
What's the story of "Goldilocks"?
Lucas.
While a family of bears are away...
Goldilocks enters their house
and eats their porridge.
Then the bears come home
and get angry with her.
That's right. Very good.
So, is there a moral or a lesson
in that story?
Yes.
Don't eat bears' food without permission.
That's right.
Don't take something that's not yours.
Hey, everyone, be prepared to discuss
and write about...
a fairy tale or a myth when you come back.
Guys, let's go.
Here you go, ma'am. Nice to see ya.
That'll be $3.
Is that everything?
That'll be $4.50, please.
...have already begun rolling back
environmental regulations.
Today, an EPA spokesman
announced a comprehensive plan...
to revive the coal industry by promoting
what is known as mountaintop mining.
In remote Cispus Falls, Oregon...
the Greymouth Mine is one of a handful
his administration is reopening...
ending what they say
is a war on American energy.
Hey, sis.
How was school?
It's about the same.
Just give it time.
They'll warm to you.
I'm not sure it's about warming.
It's just not... what I hoped it would be.
You want me to move that out of here?
All right, I'm gonna try
and get some sleep. Good night.
Good night.
Boy.
Opioid epidemic persists in rural Oregon.
The basket by the phone.
Can you not move my stuff, please?
I have it all where it is,
so I know where it is.
Sorry. Yeah.
I was just trying to give us more space.
I'm gonna move out as soon as I can.
Jules, I didn't say anything
about moving out.
I'm sorry.
I'm just getting ready to go evict...
another family with kids.
Give 'em 10, 15 minutes...
to grab what they can carry,
throw it in their car...
if they have a car, and then...
I wish you wouldn't have run, Paul.
You didn't have to.
There weren't exactly too many people...
banging down the doors for the position
after Warren Stokes retired.
I barely recognize this place anymore.
Yeah, well, a lot can change in 20 years.
It's our own little slice of paradise here.
Who's next?
Lucas.
You wanna read us your story?
He can't read, Ms. Meadows.
-Clint.
-Yes, he can.
I know you've been working on a story.
Will you read us a little bit?
Once, there were three bears...
that lived in a dark and wet cave...
up above a small town.
Big Bear, Little Bear, and Baby Bear.
Big Bear used to take care
of the little bears.
But Big Bear got sick.
Lost his job.
And his insides turned black.
One day, Little Bear came home...
and Big Bear and Baby Bear were different.
Big Bear's sickness had gotten worse.
Big Bear has become
more angrier and meaner...
because they had no food.
No meat.
It's very good, Lucas.
But they had each other.
You know he belongs there, right?
Oh, my God! Is that dog shit?
God, dude. That smells like ass. God.
What kind of a person
would put that in there?
You motherfucker!
You think this is funny? Eat it!
Fight! Fight! Fight!
-Clint! Hey! Clint, stop!
-Eat it!
Does that hurt?
Okay.
Okay, you put your shirt back on.
I'll be right out.
Hey. I was just about to go in there.
You wanna join me?
That's not why I invited you in.
I invited you in to have ice cream...
because I wanted to know
if ice cream is your favorite vegetable.
Because it's mine.
Ice cream isn't a vegetable.
Yeah, it is.
It's a dessert.
To most people, yeah.
But to me?
Totally a vegetable.
So, if ice cream is a vegetable,
what's your favorite fruit?
Come on.
Donuts?
Mine too. Chocolate, obviously.
I also like cheeseburgers as a fruit.
What about your brother?
Does he like ice cream?
How do you know I have a brother?
Teachers know everything.
So where is he?
At home.
With your mom?
If you knew everything,
then you would know my mom's dead.
I'm sorry to hear that.
But that's something we have in common.
My mom died too.
Really?
When I was 12.
I'm 12.
I know.
So tell me about your brother.
What's his name?
Aiden.
How old's Aiden?
Seven.
Oh, so he's... Is he in our school?
Not anymore.
He's always with my dad.
Does your dad teach him at home?
What's your dad do?
I gotta go.
And don't follow me this time.
Move!
Shoo.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hello?
-What... What?
-Jesus! Jesus!
I thought you heard me.
No.
The fuck is this?
Is that the kind of thing
you taught in California?
'Cause I don't think that's gonna fly here.
Paul.
You have every right to resent me.
I don't blame you for that.
I know you couldn't have understood then...
but I couldn't stay in this house anymore.
Just know that I have spent my life...
trying to deal with leaving you.
And resolve my issues.
And it has not been easy.
Yeah, and I've spent my entire life
praying you'd come back.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Go!
Here.
I got this for you.
I'll come back after he's eaten.
He'll be tired.
Daddy, no.
No. Daddy.
Please. You're hurting me.
Hey, Jules. What? What?
-Jesus!
-Sorry.
You okay?
-Jesus.
-Sorry.
I was just...
I wanted to clear the air and talk.
-You sure you're okay?
-Yeah.
Well, no. I'm...
So many...
Hey... do you know Frank Weaver?
Of course.
I've cited him...
and revived him with Narcan
more times than I can count.
Why?
His son is a student of mine.
That was his drawing.
I pulled it from the trash.
That makes sense, yeah.
Every time I see him...
I expect to find Frank dead
with a needle in his arm.
So why isn't he in jail?
I don't know. I've tried many times...
but he goes away,
who takes care of the boys?
After their mother died...
Protective Services felt he was somehow
fit enough to be their guardian.
And what can I say to that?
Something is going on there.
First of all,
it looks like no one even lives there.
And when I got close...
You went to his house?
I thought I heard something
that did not sound normal.
You can't do that.
You can't go to Frank Weaver's house...
-without telling me.
-I heard something, and it was not normal.
Do you understand? You can't do that.
Everyone thinks these problems
are just gonna go away...
and we know that they don't.
Lucas?
Lucas... I'm hungry.
-Where did you get this?
-His desk.
It's textbook, Ellen.
Emotional, physical...
Hold on.
Neither of us are experts
in diagnosing abuse, but I hear you.
This is very disturbing.
But sadly, Lucas is not the only one
not getting the attention he needs.
But he's here. In a safe space.
What is that supposed to mean?
His younger brother, why isn't he enrolled?
We've had plenty of students
that are homeschooled.
And they're kept out
so they can move product for their parents.
Or so we don't smell methamphetamine
on their clothes, and turn their parents in.
Okay, but regardless, that is a cry for help.
Take it from someone who can diagnose abuse.
I tell you what, next chance I get,
I will reach out to his father.
Here you go.
What can I do for ya?
Sorry.
Hey.
I don't know, Paul.
It was just...
The bottom half was all chewed to hell.
Damnedest thing I ever saw.
All right, well...
We'll go take a look.
Thank you, Warren.
Thanks, Sheriff.
What's going on?
He found a part of a man
in the woods today.
Part of a man?
Who is that?
You don't remember Sheriff Stokes?
-When we were kids?
-Yeah, I do.
Yeah, he said he was
hiking up near Greymouth...
when a stench led him...
to a man half buried in the woods.
I guess the other half was found in the mine,
near a meth lab.
It was probably
a bear or a cougar, something.
Jesus.
Well, from what he just told me...
I don't think Jesus was anywhere to be found.
All right.
We gotta get out there and meet the coroner.
See you later.
Ready?
-Hi.
Are you okay?
Is God really dead?
What?
Daddy said God is dead.
Just remember what Mama told us.
Me and you...
we was born under the lucky star.
Here. I brought you these.
Determining cause was virtually impossible.
This has got to be an animal, right?
No animal that I've ever seen.
What's more troubling are the teeth marks...
on the radial bone.
They seem human.
I don't quite know what to tell you, Paul.
I'm sorry.
She false with Cassio!
Did you say with Cassio?
With Cassio, mistress.
Go to, charm your tongue.
I will not charm my tongue,
I am bound to speak.
My mistress here lies murdered in her bed.
Heavens forfend!
Nay, stare not, masters, it is true, indeed.
Nay, lay thee down and roar.
For thou hast killed the sweetest innocent
that e'er did lift up eye.
Oh, she was foul!
Iago knows that she with Cassio
hath the act of shame...
a thousand times committed.
Oh, heavens!
Cassio confessed it.
And she did gratify his amorous works
with that same handkerchief.
-Handkerchief.
-Alas!
'Twill out, 'twill out.
-Hold your peace.
-I peace?
-No, I will speak as liberal as the north.
-Be wise.
Let heaven and men and devils...
let them all, all, all...
Hello?
Mr. Weaver, it's Ellen Booth, from school.
Will you, I pray, demand that demi-devil.
Why he hath thus ensnared my soul and body?
Demand me nothing.
What you know, you know.
Are there no stones in heaven...
but what serve for the thunder?
Mr. Weaver!
Hello?
Oh, my God.
You must be starving.
What has he done to you?
Here's where we found
the other half of Kenny Glass, right here.
What are these?
Medicine bags. Wards, for defense.
But why would these be hanging in here?
What about this?
Is that from a buck?
Nope.
Nothing like anything I've seen before.
How far back does this go?
Far. But I wouldn't go any further.
Go for Paul.
Say again.
10-9.
...missing person.
Shit.
All right. Let's go.
Headed to your house
full of drugged-out freaks?
Teacher can't step in
to save your ass out here, faggot.
I said I was sorry.
I don't take apologies from pussies.
Hey! Don't walk away from me
when I'm talking to you.
Lucas!
When was the last time
you heard from Ellen?
Ellen Booth?
Yesterday. Why?
Her husband called in
a missing person's report.
Said she hadn't returned his calls...
or been home all day.
Really?
What are you doing about it?
Filed a report.
Issued an APB, searched the hospitals...
but aside from that,
just hope it's all a misunderstanding.
I asked her to talk to Frank Weaver.
About Lucas.
You smell that?
Yeah.
Frank, it's Sheriff Meadows.
Fucking place smells like death.
Yeah, there's something wrong here.
Frank!
Let's get outta here.
We'll get a warrant tomorrow.
...small town of Cispus Falls, Oregon.
Rumors of another round
of gruesome attacks...
...processing evidence
and provide forensic expertise.
Our attempts to contact
local law enforcement have gone unanswered...
Have you spoken with Clint's parents
this morning?
Yes. They wanted to know
if he had been in school yesterday.
And he was here
till the end of the day, right?
Look, I know this has...
been difficult on all of us.
But right now, we have to work
under the assumption...
that this is just some kind of a coincidence.
We'll find him.
Excuse me.
-What?
-A coincidence?
That my student is now missing, too?
What the fuck, Paul?
What else would you like me to do, Jules?
The warrant is being processed right now.
It takes time.
-It doesn't just happen overnight.
-This is all related.
-What would you like me to fucking do?
-You cannot tell me that it isn't.
God almighty.
These Frank Weaver's footprints?
Some.
There's also a child's.
What the fuck is this?
Jesus Christ.
It's charred.
It's burnt.
And flayed.
It's gotta be Frank Weaver.
Yeah, the teeth will tell us.
Looks like something just burst out of him.
Lucas. Lucas, listen to me.
Listen, I don't want you to go in there.
-No. No. Let me go!
-Listen, I know. It's okay.
What's going on here?
Well, needless to say, I'm concerned.
He's severely dehydrated,
suffers from chronic malnourishment.
I recommend keeping him overnight,
possibly longer...
but I don't have to tell you
that he is a deeply damaged boy.
Could be the circumstances
or his genetic disposition...
but there are definite signs
of a psychiatric crisis here.
Anti-anxiety, anti-psychotics
will be our friend...
but given what he's just experienced...
When do you think
I'll be able to interview him?
Well, not tonight, certainly.
What do you plan on doing with him?
Well, we're discussing that.
But it's complicated.
Oh, I'm sure.
The little fella's
got a long road ahead of him.
I'd be remiss if I didn't mention...
but it's clear that he has been
subjected to abuse.
And for some time.
Thank you, Alan.
We can't. No.
He has no one.
We don't know where the brother is.
So where's he gonna go?
I have no idea right now,
but he is not your responsibility.
He doesn't have a family.
And he's my student.
So he is my responsibility.
Jules...
This is not about you.
This is about him,
and getting him the help...
What did you just say to me?
Don't put our past on him.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Did he snap your arm in two?
Did he force you
to hide under the floor of that kitchen...
-praying he would never come home?
-You have no idea what he...
Did you have to meet
his every fucking need?
Because I don't remember that.
You have no idea what he did to me.
Let us in!
Daddy!
-Dad, please!
-Open the door, Daddy!
Guys, you have to give me a second.
Daddy's just sick.
Daddy! Daddy, please!
Daddy, what's happening to you?
-Open the door!
-No!
Daddy!
Look at me. Daddy is very, very sick.
You lock that fucking door.
No matter what I do,
you don't open that door.
You hear me?
Lock it!
Lock the door!
Daddy, Aiden's very sick.
If you wouldn't mind, just telling me
what you make of these.
Where did you find this?
Belongs to a student.
Is the student Native?
No.
How can that be?
I don't know. He isn't.
This is what was in the mine.
This... is what was in the mine.
It's the wendigo.
Translates to...
a diabolical wickedness that devours mankind.
According to legend,
during a brutally cold winter...
a lost hunter's severe hunger
drove him to cannibalism.
And after feasting on human flesh...
he became crazed...
and transformed into an amorphous spirit
that could take many forms.
And roamed the forest for fresh victims.
His insatiable appetite was never satisfied.
Excuse me.
This is a myth you're talking about.
For you, yeah.
But a cautionary tale
to the indigenous people who believe in it.
They're elusive.
And known to be eternally starving,
but feasting only makes them hungrier.
And weaker.
Those who are unfortunate enough
to encounter one...
can only kill it
when it's in its weakened state.
And only by extinguishing
its beating heart...
forcing it to search for another host.
But it all makes sense, you see.
I mean, our ancestral spirits never died.
They were here long before we were...
and they'll be here
long after we are gone.
But now, they're angry.
Paul.
Go for Paul.
Pumphouse Road.
You gotta come by the tracks.
What? What happened?
We got a body out here.
It's bad, Paul. It's real bad.
ID?
Yeah. It's Clint Owens.
I don't know where to start, Paul.
Let me see it.
Tell me this was a train, Jake.
That boy was eaten in half.
The fuck is going on here?
I don't know, Dan.
We've...
Let's get back to the station...
and we'll figure it out.
I'll call the mayor...
and we'll get out in front of it.
I'm sorry.
I'm not inclined to believe anybody...
about some mythological nature beast.
Things like that don't exist, Jules.
Regardless of what Stokes said.
There's a logical, reasonable explanation
for this.
So Ellen Booth...
and that... husk that you pulled out
of the Weavers'.
And what about Lucas's brother, where is he?
I don't know.
Take me to the hospital.
I'm outside your house.
Good. I'm wrapping up with the mayor,
then headed over.
Just take a look around.
Can I get you anything else?
No, thank you.
Lucas, do you remember
when we were talking about our moms?
And how they died?
Well, what I didn't tell you...
was that my dad died, too.
How did he die?
Well, he kind of did it to himself.
When did he die?
Not too long ago.
Were you here when he died?
No.
Why?
Didn't you love your father?
Well, I moved back here
to be with my brother.
We actually, we grew up in this house.
And I missed him.
Lucas, did they tell you at the hospital?
Tell me what?
Your dad died.
He's not dead.
Yeah, he is, Lucas.
My brother, Paul...
he found him in your house.
No. That was my old dad.
The one who was sick and mean.
My new dad is with Aiden,
but Aiden doesn't understand.
And he needs me.
I just have to feed him,
and he'll love me.
What?
See? I told you.
He'll come for me,
and take me to the mine to be with Aiden.
He's here.
Hey, Paul?
Yeah, Dan, what is it?
There's something here.
I think it's in the shed.
Come on. Let's go.
Where are you taking me?
I wanna see my brother.
Dan?
Dan, do you read me?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
There's a little kid in here.
What, Lucas?
Lucas is at the house.
Dan!
Dan, come in!
Oh, shit.
They all have locks.
Goddamn it.
Fuck.
Paul.
Lucas, stay. Don't move.
Paul, no.
No. Lucas!
Dan.
It's okay.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Paul?
Lucas?
Oh, my God!
Paul! Oh, my God. Paul!
Oh, God.
Paul...
Paul, I have to move you. Paul.
I'm gonna move you.
To where?
Come on.
Is Lucas dead?
Be still. Be still.
He went to the mine.
I'm gonna go after him.
What?
He thinks that's where Aiden is.
No, you can't do that.
You can't...
I have to. I have to go find him.
Not by yourself.
You need a doctor.
I'm coming with you.
Get my gun.
You're not leaving me.
This is Julia Meadows.
Paul and I are at Greymouth Mine.
He needs an ambulance.
Lucas?
Lucas.
He's...
What?
Go back.
Go.
He's gonna be okay.
He's just sick.
Lucas, listen to me.
He is never gonna get better.
Yes, he is.
Lucas, he's not.
It's too late for him.
He's sick...
but he'll be better, I promise.
Lucas, listen to me.
You know he's not gonna get any better.
I need to know that you understand.
Look away. Look away, Lucas!
It's okay.
I'm so sorry.
What are we gonna do with him?
Keep him. For now.
We have no choice.
It's like living with a tiger cub.
You know what he's going to grow into.
Do you think you could kill
something you love?
There.
Come on, let's go.
-You okay?
-Yeah, I'll catch up to you.