Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
Now, if I mention something,
do you promise
to be civil about it?
When you say things like that,
I notice I grip
the handle of the pan
just a little tighter.
It's not that
I don't appreciate
everything that you do for me,
and the family too.
Out with it.
The hem is a bit short
on one side.
You're blind.
Are you keeping an eye
on the time?
I'm paying attention.
But look. Look here.
They were the same
when I did them.
Yeah, but that's all
well and good,
but I'll be at the office
and I'll be looking like
I'm some kind of rapper guy.
I highly doubt that
anybody is ever going to
mistake you for a rapper guy.
What time is it?
Henry, she's there.
Come on, Henry.
She's early.
Be careful. Watch your steps.
Shh. Quiet.
Watch the baby.
I can't. I can't get...
Get her off of me.
Got it. Come on!
No, no, no!
Shh. Keep quiet.
Shh.
Shh. Shh.
Mmm. Mmm. Mmm.
"Aloha" means "hello"
and "goodbye."
She's up.
Hmm?
Oh.
Hello. My name is Audrey.
And this is my husband...
Oh. Well, he'll be along.
The stairs just take
a few extra seconds.
Mmm, mmm!
There.
Uh, as I was saying,
my name is Audrey,
and this is my husband Henry.
First and foremost, Shannon,
we would like to apologize
for scaring you this morning,
but after much deliberation,
we feel this would be
the best way
for you to go missing.
By now, you've recognized
my husband Henry,
or Dr. Walsh
as you would better know him.
Hello, Miss Shannon.
Dr. Walsh will continue
your care from our home.
You should know
that we mean you
or your unborn child no harm.
While we apologize
for what we must do,
please make no mistake.
We must do it,
and we will not waver
no matter how much you beg.
So, please do not try,
as we all have feelings.
Do you understand?
Mm-hmm.
Do you know
that we don't want to hurt you
or your baby?
Can you nod?
I guess that's out of the way,
then.
Maybe we should get the tests
over with.
Now?
Give me a minute.
Okay. I'm ready.
Shh.
Shh, shh, shh.
Help!
Please, someone!
Please!
Nothing.
Help!
Someone, please!
Now, nothing
or nothing at all?
We're good.
Please!
Shh.
No one can hear you.
We've soundproofed the room.
Shh.
Now, don't make this
any more unpleasant
than it already is.
We want you
to be comfortable here.
For you,
and for the sake of the baby.
You know, I don't want to
have to gag you again,
but I will.
Do you understand?
Why are you doing this?
We need to bring
our grandson back,
and this is
the only way.
I can't eat it in the car.
Ta-da.
Him?
What do you see?
Finished.
You see him?
Oh! He knows.
He knows you're here
to save him.
I don't know what you're saying.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Jackson, dear.
He's dead.
Let's make him
a little bit higher.
Oh, Jesus.
Oh, no. We don't use
that name in this house.
All right. You rest,
and I'll bring you some lunch
in a little while.
Jackie loves music.
See?
Someone, please!
Please help me.
Have you seen my keys?
I thought they were in
my pocket.
They're not in my coat.
What?
He showed himself to her.
No.
Mm-hmm.
That's good, right?
Yeah.
The, um...
...appearing.
Appearing to the host
is a good thing, right?
Mm-hmm.
He's coming back to us.
You know,
I think I'm going to
stay at home today.
I'll call
and I'll reschedule my app...
No.
No. Keep up appearances.
No changes in our routine.
You're right.
I always am.
Hmm.
Have a great day.
Well, there's something
I didn't think
I'd see in this lifetime.
What?
You. You're still here.
I shovel your snow.
Oh. Ray, right?
- Rory.
If you give me two minutes,
I'll clear you a path here
right quick.
Uh, Mrs. Walsh is pretty sick.
Everything's all right, I hope?
Oh, yeah, yeah. She's just
come down with something,
which is why
I'm a little late today.
So, I think we should
let her rest this morning.
Of course.
Now, if you want,
I can get my shovel.
Whisper quiet.
She'll never even know
I was here.
Thank you, but I think
we should let her rest.
Okay, okay.
I'll come back
in a couple of days
when she's feeling better.
Now, if you could just
move your truck
so I could get out,
I'm a tad late for work.
Ah. Look at me,
screwing with your day.
You wish Mrs. Walsh
a speedy recovery,
and you drop me a line
anytime you're ready.
I'll fix you up.
Thank you.
You have a good day, now.
You, too.
Hello.
Time for our morning vitamins.
Oh, we can't have Mommy
missing out, now, can we?
Oop. There.
Okay. There you go.
No, don't worry.
They're just vitamins.
You see?
There.
All right. I get it.
It's been a big morning.
I will back off.
Hey.
Don't worry.
Oh, oh.
You brought your own pills.
Are these pre-natals?
Gosh. I can't read that.
Don't get old.
I need to get my glasses.
I will be right back.
Okey-dokey?
Yes.
No. No!
- Give me the phone.
- No.
No extra stress, now. Come on.
Thank you.
There you go.
Let's see.
5-0-2-9.
Stop it.
No, no. It's all right.
It's all just part of it.
Give me my fucking phone!
Oh, no.
Swearing is bad for our baby.
There we go.
Oh, I'm sorry to paint you
as a woman
who would do this sort of thing,
but it's just a little extra
insurance at our end.
No. You don't have to do this.
You don't have to do this!
Please.
All right. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I can't do two things at once.
Shh. Shh.
All right. Okay.
Um, let me see.
Um... All right.
That's good.
Would you say "Taking a me day"?
Henry and I went back and forth
on that.
I said,
"Mommy needs some alone time,"
but you know, sometimes
you just have to let them win.
Well, aren't you popular.
Oh.
"DTF"?
What in world
does that mean?
DT... Down to...
Oh, my goodness.
Well, no wonder
he didn't spell it out.
You know,
if you can't even say it,
you shouldn't be doing it.
That's a good rule of thumb,
I think.
Okay.
Um, "Meet me at Fairy Lake,
2:00."
Send.
All right.
There we go.
There.
Hi, dear. Yeah.
I just wanted to let you know
that the plan worked.
I made the call
and got the prize.
Wonderful.
You're a full-blown techie now.
Have a good day, my love.
Bye-bye.
Believe me when I say
we have thought of everything.
No one has more time
than a grieving family.
No one.
Dr. Walsh, the hospital called.
They're just asking
if you can do a review for them.
Yes, of course.
Um, good.
Could you make sure
you forward that, please?
Already sent.
Dr. Walsh.
- Colin.
- Hi.
To what do we owe the pleasure?
First off, I know
what you're going to say.
Yeah. It is entirely possible
that I don't have HPV.
I'm sorry for my rudeness.
I'm really stressed out
right now, okay?
All righty.
And if I could go ahead
of you guys,
that would be
really appreciated.
Let's go into the back room
now...
You have Ms. Becker right now.
No, no.
She's not until Friday morning.
No. She rescheduled. She had
a couple of questions for you.
No, no. He's got to help me now.
Wait, wait. Uh, no. She said...
- Help me!
- Send an e-mail.
No, no.
I still don't see anything.
Did she e-mail you directly,
or...
No. That's right.
I saw her this morning.
She was out for a walk...
I could be done by now.
I could be done!
And she said that
she couldn't make it today.
Okay. Well, Dr. Walsh,
she's 37 weeks.
So, is she coming in
later today?
Because the hospital
keeps asking.
I have no idea. Could
you just help me here, please?
Dr. Walsh, I swear I have it.
Yes. Let's go on at the back.
Thank you.
Uh...
I'm so sorry.
Here it is.
What am I looking at?
I found it here this morning.
Okay.
Dead, right?
Well, I'm not going to touch it,
but yes, it looks dead.
Yeah.
What are you doing?
You can't be carrying that
around.
It's a thousand years old.
I know.
Just hold it here.
Let me open it.
Oh.
There. Hold that. All right.
Just watch.
You ready?
All right.
Ut aosoth meum sanguinem,
dedi sanguinem commutant,
ut suus reddet
animam pro animam
pulmonis apud.
How did you do that?
I found it in the book.
I needed to test it to see
if it was real.
I wasn't sure I believed it.
We can't be bringing dead things
to life.
Well, I can.
I've been doing it all morning.
All morning?
Henry, yes.
Do you know what this means?
It works. The book is real.
We can do this.
We're getting him back, my love.
Henry?
You seem nervous.
Maybe it's because
we have a pregnant woman
locked up in our house.
We have to keep up appearances.
Got it.
Hey there, Ian.
Henry, Audrey.
Oh.
Thank you so much
for the book, Ian.
It was a fascinating read.
I'm glad you liked it.
You can still keep it
if you want.
No, no. I read it, dear.
I know.
Let's not be late, hmm?
Okay.
Uh, Henry? Henry?
Remember the Beur book
you were looking for?
Oh, yes.
Uh, that was just curiosity.
Yeah. Most subs I'm in
don't think it exists.
Well, I appreciate you looking.
Well, I did have a lead.
I had a lead, but the guy said
he sold it.
And to be honest with you,
I think he's full of dog shit.
You asked him about it?
That was before I found it.
We were desperate.
What if he tells somebody?
What if it gets out?
Well, it won't get out,
so stop talking about it.
I have to eat, you know?
I mean, everyone has to eat.
We're human.
Looks like we're all here.
I trust everyone had
a good week?
- Yep.
- Had a horrible week.
My boyfriend graciously
made snacks for everyone,
but if you don't mind,
I'd like to wait until after
to enjoy them.
Excellent.
Let us begin.
Glory be to Satan,
the Father of the Earth,
and to Lucifer,
our guiding light.
As it was in the void
of the beginning,
is now, and ever shall be,
Satan's kingdom without end.
And so it is done.
Hail Satan.
Hail Satan. Hail Satan.
Well, Miss Becker,
I think it's safe
to rule out any chance
of a tapeworm.
Yes. That just leaves me
being pregnant.
It certainly does.
Oh, my God. I was kidding.
I'm so sorry.
I... I thought this would
come as welcome news.
Thank you.
You know, there are options.
Out of state, unfortunately.
But also, I could talk to
the father if you wished.
Long gone.
Didn't even give me
a real name.
Plus I don't really believe in
the, uh... option.
I see.
I promise, I usually
make good decisions.
Of course.
Um...
What about family or friends?
I'm sorry. This really is
none of my business.
Um,
my mom lives in Florida.
She might, uh...
Oh, I really don't want
to give her another reason
to call me a failure.
This does not make you
a failure.
Right.
I guess I'm having a baby.
Uh...
Oh, yes. You are.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Sometimes I can be
a little emotional, too.
It's refreshing.
It's nice to know
I'll be in good hands.
Ah.
Uh, I guess I have
some planning to do.
Uh...
Um, would you mind if I took
a photo of you?
- A photo?
- Yeah. Just for the records.
To match a face to the names.
Sadly, at my age,
my memory needs
a bit of a reminder.
Sure.
I'm sure I look my best.
Um, should I say "cheese"?
Say "miracle."
Miracle.
No, no!
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
You won't find him here,
sweetie.
No, no!
You don't have to do this.
Please don't do this.
No, no.
Just a little bit.
- It'll only take a minute.
- Please don't do this.
Please don't do this.
All right.
There you go.
You don't have to do this.
The worst... The worst is over.
It's all right. All right.
We ask for an audience.
We wish to invite our dark lord
to a seat
at the head of our home.
We welcome you.
Please don't do this.
My blood is your blood.
Don't hurt my baby.
Please don't hurt my baby.
Please don't hurt
my baby, no!
Start reading.
Nos invite Surgot
in domum nostram.
Placere reserare
fores condemnabitur.
Keep going.
Rogamus autem
vos recludam haec processerat.
Hoc reserare in domum suam.
I see you!
Oh, Jackson.
Oh, he's here.
Jackson,
come and take the baby.
Go on, Jackie. You can do it.
Go on. Keep reading.
Nos invite mortuis.
Nos invitare in domum nostram.
Are you all right?
Yeah. I'm fine.
Henry...
She's okay.
Let me hear.
Here.
It's him.
Audrey...
I know my grandson's heartbeat.
Yes, yes. Of course you do.
I'm sorry.
We did it.
I'll put on some tea.
Aud?
Had a hell of a time
sleeping last night.
I guess side effects
are to be expected.
Sorry. Bad joke.
It's all going to work out.
I had my doubts,
but you were right.
Hello?
Henry, can you give me
a hand with the groceries?
You're not still in bed,
are you?
Audrey?
Get away.
Keep...
Audrey!
What's wrong?
What?
I, I... You...
No. I'm right here. What?
- What?
- All those things.
Well, you just... What?
Look. There's nothing there.
Hello?
Excuse me, Dr. Walsh.
There's an officer here
to see you.
An officer?
Yes. She said
she'd like to speak with you.
I'll be right there.
Okay.
Dr. Walsh?
- Yes?
- Detective Bellows.
Is something wrong?
I'm looking into
a missing persons case.
Do you know
a Miss Shannon Becker?
Oh, yes. Of course.
- She's a patient.
- Yeah?
Well, unfortunately,
she hasn't been to work
in a couple of days,
and she has
quite a few people worried.
Oh. Well, that's just awful.
Um, do you have any leads?
Well, we're retracing her steps.
Miss Becker
had an appointment to see you
on the same day
that she went missing.
What time did she come in?
Ah. Well, actually, um,
she cancelled that day.
Do you know when she called?
Do you keep phone records,
by chance?
I'd love to have a listen.
Actually, she didn't call.
Really?
Well, remember,
I asked you if she called,
and then you said that
you saw her earlier in the day.
Right, doctor?
Oh, right.
Thank you, Talia. My mistake.
Yes.
I saw her walking.
- Walking?
- Uh-huh.
And where was this?
Um...
Do you remember what street?
Time of day?
Anything would be helpful.
Um, yeah.
I was on my way to work.
She walked by my house.
It would've been
about 9:00, 9:30.
Sorry.
I should've remembered.
Oh, no, no, no. It's okay.
Which street was this?
My street. Hibiscus Avenue.
Thank you.
This has been very helpful.
Both of you.
Well, please keep us posted.
You're panicking.
She was in my office.
Well, we knew this.
It's not a shock, Henry.
We planned for it.
They came in,
and you told them that she'd
cancelled her appointment.
And then they'll look at
her updates and her dating app
and see that she met
a stranger.
We've been all through this.
Well, there was some confusion.
I had to tell the police
that I saw her walk...
What?
Well, it's fine.
Nothing changes.
I just said that
I saw her walking
and she cancelled.
What reason did she give
for cancelling?
Well, we didn't...
Did she go left or right
at the bottom of the hill?
- I mean...
- I know what you're doing.
Why were you watching her
all the way down
to the bottom of the hill?
Are you attracted to
younger girls, Henry?
It's not a plan
if you don't stick to it.
All right, now.
I'm sorry. I made a mistake.
But we'll go
over all this tonight.
Okay, Audrey?
- Damn it.
- What's the matter?
Well, it's probably the police
at the door.
I'm coming.
Trick or treat?
What?
That's not very funny.
I don't like games.
Whoever put you up to this
is just cruel.
Please don't knock again.
Trick or treat?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
No!
Trick or treat?
Please?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hello?
Henry? Henry, I need help.
What's wrong?
She's trying to get me.
Trick or treat?
Get out!
Maybe you should give her
your soul.
What?
Trick or treat?
- Trick or treat?
- What?
Trick or treat?
What?
Trick or treat? Trick or treat?
Trick or treat?
Oh. Oh, God.
No.
Why were you screaming?
Screaming?
Earlier. I heard you screaming.
My daughter just came to see me.
She used to dress as a ghost
every year for Halloween.
I tried to get her into
a princess costume
or a ballerina,
anything other than
that darn ghost.
But they like what they like.
I can't believe
I tried to change that.
Seems so silly now,
when I look back.
Where's your daughter now?
I love my Jackson.
And Jackson loves
his gammy's cookies.
I'm going to make some
right now.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Whoa, whoa!
I can't get the door open.
Aud?
What the hell is going on?
She's all stitched up.
No real damage.
I'm so sorry.
No.
Whatever this is,
we both did it.
You know,
I think we're in over our heads.
Well, we can't Google this.
Do you think we made a mistake?
Let's get some sleep.
Good morning.
Right on schedule.
If I don't do it in the morning,
I don't do it.
And someone seems to crave
the consistency.
Better get used to it.
Pretty soon, that little person
will be calling all the shots.
I am.
Sorry?
Um, getting used it, I mean.
I know I was apprehensive.
But, uh, I was laying in bed
the other day
worrying about bills
and formula.
And all of a sudden, this
little mush starts squirming.
Yeah, right.
It made all my worries go away.
I finally found my family.
They do have a way of
getting into your heart,
don't they?
They really do.
Well, I'm glad
that you're excited to be a mom.
You have no idea.
Um, I'll see you Thursday?
Wouldn't miss it.
Are there more?
Yes.
How can you tell?
I tend to notice a murder
of crows in my backyard.
It's because of what we did?
Yep.
It's because of what we did.
Oh, no.
What's he doing here?
Go on upstairs. Keep her quiet.
Dr. Walsh? Morning.
I'm here to clean your drive.
Uh, yeah. I thought we talked
about this. We're still okay.
Pretty sure you and I got a
different meaning of "okay."
Yes, but I called, though.
What's that?
Um, after last time,
uh, I called your wife,
and I explained that I wouldn't
need you for a month or two.
We're not firing you
or anything.
We just don't need you.
Oh, boy.
Full disclosure here, doc.
I haven't been home in a while.
Is that right?
The number you called is Jenny.
On account of taxes,
everything's in her name,
and she's gone and chucked me.
I mean, I get it.
I made a mistake.
A stupid, stupid mistake.
And now, will you look
at all this, huh?
I'm going to lose my business,
my home.
Cripes. She won't even
let me see my two girls.
How the hell is that fair?
I'm sorry to hear that, Rory.
But maybe you could, um,
send her some flowers
or something.
Oh! What am I doing?
This isn't on you.
No. Uh...
That's it. It's over. No more.
Well, that's good to know.
Um, I'll be seeing you, then,
Rory.
No, no, no. I'm not leaving.
You're getting a freebie.
No, no. Everything's okay.
No. It's settled.
You need it. I need it.
Done-zo. I am hooking you up.
Henry?
What the hell was that?
Don't yell at me.
I am not a doctor.
I thought you told me
you cancelled him?
I did! He wouldn't take
no for an answer.
Hey!
Oh...
Hey, Mrs. Walsh!
Wave.
Hi!
Smile.
Glad you're feeling better!
Thank you, Rory.
Hey. Hey...
What's wrong?
I just...
I don't know what
the other ghosts are.
I don't know why they're here.
What if we did it all wrong?
What if...
What if Jackson's not...
No. In a few days,
we'll have Jackson back,
we'll head to Mexico...
Okay.
And I'll burn
this house down,
ghosts and all. I promise.
Hey!
You did it right.
Jackson's in there.
He's coming back to you.
Stay the hell away from me.
No, I-I'm just here to
clean you, nothing else.
All right.
There we go.
Oh...
Wrists are just not getting
any blood circulation.
Please don't move.
There.
Okay.
This will just
make it a lot...
softer for you. Okay?
I hope this works.
You ready?
There. How does that feel?
Are you gonna kill me?
When this is over
and you have your
grandson back?
You're not saying anything.
There's...
a... lot of words in silence.
Does that mean yes?
Shannon, the first rule
we set for ourselves
was that you cannot get hurt.
You know, you remind me of her.
Your daughter?
She was such a good girl.
She was always so much
smarter than the other kids.
She always knew
what she wanted.
Did you try
and bring her back?
I don't think she can come back.
She was in the car, but...
we didn't lose her right away.
We... We renovated this house
to give her
everything she needed.
Henry and I tried to make her
as comfortable as possible,
so that she could...
try to move on.
But...
I didn't realize how impossible
it is to move on
after losing a child...
until I lost mine.
But you know,
I know that she would be happy
knowing that you're helping
bring our Jackson back.
Oh, God damn it.
Yes. Hello?
Dr. Walsh?
It is.
This is Detective Bellows.
We met a few days
ago at your office.
Uh-huh.
Sorry to disturb you.
I'm just following up
on a few notes.
I remembered you saying you saw
Miss Becker walking
the morning she went missing.
I wondered if I could come
see you for a quick chat?
Uh, yes, of course.
Always happy to help.
Have you had any luck
in finding Miss Becker?
Um... I saw on the news that
you might have got a suspect.
I'm not at liberty
to discuss that with you.
No, of course. I was just,
uh, concerned about her.
You know that, um, she... she's
due to give birth any day now.
Uh-huh.
Can I come by your house?
Well, actually,
I'm out right now.
But how about
we meet at the clinic
tomorrow morning first thing?
Aww, Doctor,
time is of the essence
in these circumstances,
you understand.
Well, of course.
Um... Yes.
You know, I... actually,
I could be there in... in...
in an hour.
I'm actually
in your neighbourhood.
Let's meet at your house.
Ahh!
I would help.
What do you mean?
Be Jackson's mom...
with you and Dr. Walsh.
You're just saying that.
Yeah, Henry told me that...
that you would try and use
my emotions against me.
Shame on you.
I'm not... I...
I...
I don't... agree with this,
but...
I understand it.
Doing anything for him.
I'm just trying to
do the same for my baby.
I don't know.
You and Dr. Walsh aren't young.
You're gonna need someone
to look after Jackson.
You can lock me up in a room.
I don't care. I just...
I just... I just want to be
a part of the baby's life.
Do you really think
you could do that?
Like, if I talk to Henry,
you're not just saying it?
I do.
I'll do whatever you want.
Please.
I'm sorry.
I'll come back and take
that off in a minute.
Henry Walsh!
Henry, I tried to stop her!
Place your hands on your head
and get on your knees.
Are you okay, my love?
Henry, I'm so sorry!
Henry Walsh, get down
on your knees now.
- Let me go!
- I'm sorry.
No, it's all me,
Officer. Please.
My... my wife had nothing
to do with this. Please.
Please, let her go.
Let me up, please.
You have to help my baby.
Dr. Walsh, I am placing
you under arrest
for the kidnapping
of Miss Shannon Becker.
Please!
Please, no!
Just let me out of here.
Miss Becker, calm down.
You have to let me out.
I know you're afraid,
but it's all over now.
I just have to
do this one thing.
Oh, Henry...
It can't be...
Can you help me? Henry...
There we go.
Oh my God.
Don't look.
Did she call for backup?
I don't know.
- The cop.
- What?
Did she call for backup?
- No, no.
- No?
No, she heard Becker.
I tried to get
rid of her, Henry.
I tried to get rid of her.
I know. Let's...
let's get her away from here.
- What?
- Come on.
Oh my God.
I'll get an arm,
you get an arm.
Get her arm. Come on.
Where are we gonna take her?
Back side, just right
in the corner.
All right.
Good.
Will you please stop that?
I'm nervous.
I'm aware.
We need to talk about Becker.
She and I were chatting.
I-I know I'm always the one
yelling about plans,
but just hear me out.
Later, okay?
Do you actually have it?
Like, actually have it?
Come inside.
Where did you find this?
I went to a museum.
Talked to some historians.
One of them sent me to
another guy, and another guy.
Eventually, I flew to Jerusalem
and bought it off a very
shady-looking individual,
who seemed only too pleased
to be rid of it.
How much did it cost?
Well, we don't have
a retirement plan left.
Can you read it, Ian?
Of course I can read it.
Some of it, not all of it.
It looks like it was written...
over a bunch of years.
There's different languages,
there's different dialects
and religions.
This might be the
oldest book in the world.
Ian?
We're friends, right?
I don't have friends.
But we're bound to
each other with the church.
Of course.
So...
could you show what
you make of this here,
where it says "the invoking",
where you can invite a
spirit into a new vessel?
Well, first of all,
you can't invite a specific...
Did you guys do this?
Wh-wh-what if we did?
Then, I'd be an
idiot for standing here. So...
It's okay.
Okay.
You guys...
need to tell exactly, exactly...
Uh-huh.
...what you did right now.
Um... okay, well,
we, uh... yeah,
we asked this one
to bring our grandson back.
You asked Surgat
to bring him back?
The book said he could.
No. Henry...
your translations
are so far off.
Yes, this is Surgat,
the demon who unlocks the gate
between us and tormented souls.
And, yes,
technically,
he is the first step
in bringing... someone back,
but it's not a private
goddamn VIP invitation.
Okay, once that gate is open,
every ghost in purgatory
is gonna be crawling
to find a host.
What host did you use?
Is she alive?
Yes. Uh, sedated.
When did you...
when did you do it?
A few days ago.
This is hers?
No. That's... someone else's.
Is Jackson in there?
Who's Jackson?
Um, our grandson...
the reason that
we're doing this.
Oh. Um...
No.
But he can be. He can be.
You guys only did
half the ceremony.
I'm not gonna...
praise you for your choices,
but... you actually
did the right thing.
Now, you need to follow up.
Trade the life,
invite him in.
Trade?
The mother trades her life,
so the tormented can come back.
You... you think
that you can perform this?
Of course I can.
I studied my
whole life for this.
I just can't believe it's real.
I get to keep the book
when we're done.
Of course.
And $10,000 as well.
I don't have a
lot of money and...
you seem to have more.
No problem.
When do you
think that you could do this?
How quickly?
ASAP. As soon as possible.
Tomorrow work for you guys?
I'm gonna have get some stuff.
I'm assuming you've
seen some ghosts, huh?
Mm-hmm.
You're gonna need salt,
rock salt, kosher only.
Spread it all
around this... woman here.
That unborn baby's literally
a free ticket back
to life for those things.
Salt keeps them away?
I don't fucking know, Henry.
But I've read it helps,
so do it. Okay?
And put it around
yourselves, too.
You aren't ideal,
but they're not picky.
I think I'm gonna... go.
I don't really feel
safe being here...
until we do this.
He says
you have to kill me.
Mm-hmm.
Mrs. Walsh said that
I could be the mom to Jackson.
Did she talk to you about that?
How many more people have to die
just to bring
your grandson back?
All of them.
Whatever it takes.
Rory, the cop, you, me.
You can't win a moral
argument with me.
I've made a deal with the devil.
You haven't made the deal yet.
I made that deal
the day we lost Jackson.
I know you love him.
Her.
When it happened,
she couldn't remember a thing,
but I know that she
was distracted.
She didn't resist
fussing over Jackson,
especially on car rides.
She was driving a car?
I realize that she couldn't
accept what happened
and I couldn't expect her to...
come back up.
So...
I joined her,
going back down.
You're doing all this for her?
I do everything for her.
I'm sorry.
People say "sorry"
instead of fixing things.
You could fix this,
but you choose not to.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
So... you aren't.
What if...
I hope that happens
for the rest of your life.
Ian, come to supper please.
Not hungry.
I'll keep it warm
in the oven for you.
Are you sure you don't want
something? Just a little?
Sweetie, I really don't mind.
I'll bring down to you.
Not fucking hungry!
Henry?
Audrey?
Guys?
She's been doing that all night.
Don't step on the salt.
Okay.
Turn to the page with
the bookmark, read it.
"Hoc autem..."
"Hoc au-tem".
"Hoc autem satanas
in domum suam,
"invenit eum coram te relinquo."
What does it mean?
The salt slows them down...
The sacrifice
keeps them away.
This will help keep them out...
until...
we're ready... to do this.
Don't disturb it, please.
One of you starts with...
this.
I know it's in here...
somewhere.
One of you starts with this.
The other, come with me.
One, two,
three, four, five, six.
Here. Here.
You know when it comes time,
you're gonna have to be
the one to kill her, Henry.
I can't do that for you.
You don't have to
worry about that.
I'll take care of it.
You can't hesitate.
Okay? If he senses
that you're not ready,
Henry...
Henry!
...we'll all die. We'll all die.
I'm not saying this to be mean,
but this is your deal.
I'm just here to broker it.
I told you,
I'll take care of it.
Ian, this will work, right?
He's listening,
Henry.
He actually wants to hear you.
Please don't ever
doubt him in my presence again.
Three more to go.
Is it today?
It is.
And you spoke to Dr. Walsh?
About me coming with you?
Raising Jackson with you?
We did.
He thinks it's a great idea.
So, when this is over
and you have Jackson,
with the ceremony...
...you're gonna
let me out of these?
We are.
We're... we're even gonna
have a room for you,
with a crib and everything.
I was thinking, uh,
maybe we could
send my mom a picture
of the baby when he's born?
We're not close, but, uh...
She'll still be really
excited to be a grandma.
Well, that's a great idea.
Let's do that.
I'm kind of hungry.
I...
I just want to make sure
I have my strength for this.
Okay.
Let me fix you something.
Shannon?
Mrs. Walsh!
- Mrs. Walsh!
- What?
My water broke.
Oh my goodness.
Henry! Henry!
She never starts
meetings with a blessing,
she never acknowledges
the work that I do
to make those meetings
even fucking happen.
You think that twat
could help you with this?
No, no.
You're certainly the one
that should be running it.
Yeah. She doesn't
even care about the church.
She's a stupid...
stupid skank.
Speak of the devil.
Henry!
All right. Let's get this off.
How much time
between contractions?
It's hard to tell. I...
Ahh!
What are you waiting for?
Okay.
"Nos obsecro in auditorium.
"Rogamus autem satanas
iungere nobis ad mensam."
What if Jackson's not in there?
"Nos obsecro
in auditorium..."
He'll be in there.
Just focus on her.
"...iungere nobis ad mensam."
"Satanas animas..."
Wretched thing.
It's working.
"Satanas animas
"tibi offerimus pro vase.
"Veni nobis, accipe solio tuo.
"Nos obsecro in auditorium..."
Henry...
Say it.
I've been trying
to get a hold of you.
What's wrong?
It's Ian.
He fucking snapped, man.
He killed his mother last night,
drew a bunch of fucking
symbols on the wall.
The police are
asking me about the church.
I don't even believe
in this shit, you know?
Henry?
Hello?
Henry!
Fuck.
Something's wrong with Ian.
Just don't say anything.
Everything all right, Henry?
Fine. Just, uh...
Just keep going.
"Nos obsecro in auditorium.
"Rogamus autem satanas esum.
"Iungere nobis
"requium ad mensam.
"Satanas iungere nobis tibi..."
- Ian?
- "...offerimus pro vase."
How do we know
when Jackson's inside?
"Veni nobis..."
When it's finished!
You want to see
your fucking grandson?
Shut up! I know what
I'm fucking doing!
"Solio tuo..."
Ahh! Ahh!
Don't hurt her!
- Henry...
- Undo my legs.
Don't.
No! Don't do it.
Henry, please don't do it.
Undo my legs or, I swear,
I'll cut her throat!
No! No!
"Satanas..." don't! Don't! Don't!
Give me the keys!
No!
I know you won't
let me hurt her. Do it!
"Veni nobis, accipe..."
- Give to me!
- Don't fucking do it!
Henry, don't do it.
You dumb fucking shit!
We need her! Okay?!
This is bigger than your
stupid fucking bitch wife!
No! No!
Ahh!
Henry...
Fucking idiot.
You fucking idiot.
Ian, please, I just
want my Jackson back, please.
I just want my Jackson.
Oh!
Mother's a mother.
Henry...
It's all right.
It's okay.
What are you doing?
Stop! It's okay.
I'm giving him a home!
Take whichever one you want!
Cleanse the earth
of these fucking sheep!
Vas, tuum est!
I'm cold.
Take mulieri!
Just need a blanket.
Veni nobis Vanth!
I love you, Audrey.
He's coming.
He's coming!
And you,
you can't fucking stop him!
Ahh! Fuck!
Fucking bitch!
Shh...
Henry! Henry!
Henry! Henry! Henry!
Get him off me!
Help me!
Audrey...
Ahh! Ahh!
Go.
Shannon... forgive us.
Audrey?
Dr. Walsh, come on!
Ahh...
Trick or treat.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Miss Becker,
your safe now.
Come with me.
Miss Becker,
what are you running from?!
I can help you!
You gotta let me
see my kids, Jenny!
How's this fair to me?!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
You're not taking my
motherfucking kids, Jenny!
You're the one that cheated!
You're the one
who ruined this family!
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org