Produced by
Omega Project, Inc.
Creators Company Connection
AFDF KOREA
Body Sonic, Inc.
Dear Mom,
Get well soon.
- Tell the head nurse to stand by.
- Yes.
Ryoko.
Hello.
I'm so sorry.
5:28 p.m.
I brought this for Mom.
Seven years later
Hey!
Let's go home.
The waves are too high.
Dad!
No luck again?
You don't understand.
I'm only after the big ones.
I prefer real-life girls
to imaginary big fish.
Well...
When you grow up
you'll understand.
It's called being romantic.
Hello?
Yes. The proposal is ready.
I'll bring it tomorrow.
Yes.
Hello?
I gotta go. See you tomorrow.
This is too big for us.
We'll share it with Rie.
You haven't brought friends home lately.
Is everything okay?
Did you know all
black sea bream are born male?
What?
When they reach 15cm long,
they become hermaphrodites.
Then some become female.
I see.
What about this one?
Didn't you see the ovaries
when we cut it?
That's right.
I don't know much about ovaries.
Have you been feeling down
or something recently?
Why?
You look dispirited.
Gang.
Hey, Dad...
why don't you get remarried?
Why do you say that?
I just think you should.
Thanks for dinner.
It's your turn to wash the dishes.
Well...
It's like a ceremony for worshippers.
They're pretty much the same...
lonely people.
Happy people wouldn’t go
to that kind of concert.
All Japanese are lonely.
Are you?
You too?
Boss.
Ueno wants to change
tomorrow's meeting from 1:00 to 3:30.
Okay.
It doesn't matter to me.
I'll be here.
I'll drop in at Starts,
then meet Yoshikawa tonight.
I won't be back at the office.
If there are any changes,
I'll call you on your cell phone, then.
Okay.
- Excuse me.
- What?
I'm going to get married soon.
Really?
Congratulations.
To whom?
Someone you don't know.
Anyway, congratulations.
You're a busy man!
It's been all right,
but the profit margins are shrinking.
- How about you?
- Well...
Didn't you know?
The movie industry
is recession-proof.
- Really?
- I'm lying.
It's a survival game,
or a test of endurance.
What's your outlook?
Seems like there is
a bright future ahead.
But I don't know
how long we should wait.
Yoshikawa...
didn't you say the same thing
a year ago?
Did I?
Awful girls.
No class and stuck up.
Stupid as well.
Where are all the attractive girls?
Japan is finished.
Give me another one.
Well...
I'm thinking about getting remarried.
What made you decide to do that?
- To whom?
- I haven't got a girl yet.
My son told me...
that I looked dispirited
and I should get remarried.
That's the story.
Look dispirited, huh?
So, how are you going to look for one?
An arranged marriage?
No, that's not my style.
I wish there was a very nice woman
hiding somewhere.
What kind of girl are you looking for?
Preferably young?
Not too young.
Possibly she has a job
and has some skills.
Skills?
For example,
playing the piano, singing,
or Japanese dance.
Your wife Ryoko was like that.
I believe that confidence comes
only from having decent skills.
Lack of confidence
makes you dependent on someone,
and that brings unhappiness.
Pianist, huh?
lt'll cost you a lot.
She doesn't have to be
a successful professional.
I don't want to fail
at marriage at my age.
I'd like to have enough time
to get to know her.
I want to meet
as many girls as possible
and choose my ideal one.
What are you laughing at?
Am I expecting too much?
I probably am.
No. Just leave it to me.
I have a good idea.
Conduct an audition.
"Looking for Love"
lt'll be a romantic story.
Remember the documentary
we made before?
It was about a former dancer,
a patron, and an autistic boy.
The one where we teamed up
with the German TV station?
It's based on the story.
Any problems?
Well... but...
Well...
Are we really going
to hold an audition?
Trust me.
Have I ever disappointed you?
But...
The heroine is supposed to be
in her early 20s to early 30s.
One of the requirements is
that she is skillful at something.
Any objections?
But don't you think
that would be fraudulent?
This audition is not only
for finding you a wife.
It's part of making a movie.
If we can find funding,
we can make the movie.
The story isn't bad.
Well...
Am I going to marry
the lead girl of this movie?
No.
Any girl who could get the lead
wouldn’t marry you.
They aren't the marrying type.
Really good ones pass
the preliminary screening
and fail the second screening.
Really?
Those are about 10
of the 1,000 applicants.
They are quite attractive.
Smart and well-bred.
Obedient and well-trained.
The kind you'd want
your son to marry.
I don't get it.
Why can't she get the lead, then?
Because she won't be unhappy.
Unhappy people can act well.
One more thing.
I have a plan to work
with an FM station, so I'll combine this.
It's a program called
Tomorrow's Heroine.
Trust me.
I am a pro at auditions.
This is Yoshikawa.
I'm in room number two.
- Coffee?
- Yeah.
Is coffee okay for you?
Bring two coffees, please.
I'm in a middle of a traffic jam.
I might be late...
Can you hand that tape
to Mr. Kaneda? Yes.
Okay. Thanks.
Tomorrow's heroine,
I'm just wondering
where you are now.
Sometimes
unbelievable things do happen.
All you need to do
is gather your courage.
Every star has her defining moment,
even Hepburn and Julia Roberts.
They lived normal lives
before they became stars.
Tomorrow's heroines
are living just like you.
Tomorrow's heroine could be you.
I'm home.
- You're home early today.
- Yeah.
I have to work at home tonight.
Please heat up your dinner.
The bigger dish is for Shigehiko.
Okay.
I'll see you on Monday, then.
My daughter's going to visit me
with her children.
I have to go shopping.
- That's exciting.
- Hey, Gang.
Please put the laundry
in the hamper.
- I got to go.
- Okay.
- Thanks.
- Bye.
Hello. This is Aoyama.
It's me.
Oh, Yoshikawa.
I'm checking out the applications.
They're all good, aren't they?
Right.
I don't know what to do.
It's like buying my first car.
Don't confuse your car with your wife.
I'd like to have the audition
late next week.
Can you choose about 30 applicants?
Thirty applicants?
Okay. I'll let you know.
And... don't trust pictures.
An essay can be more useful.
- Okay. I got it.
- Bye.
Bye.
Choose 30, huh?
Oh, you're here.
Why don't you knock?
Did you just come home?
Are you ready for dinner?
I'll eat later.
Why don't you eat now?
Okay.
Well...
I have a friend of mine here.
A girl?
You guys can eat mine too.
Thanks.
Asami Yamazaki.
Piano, classical ballet for 12 years.
"I'm not sure
I can become an actress,
"and you probably won't choose me.
"I'm simply attracted to this story.
"I studied ballet for a long time,
"then damaged my hips
when I was 18.
"It happened when I was planning
to study ballet in London.
"I was devastated.
"Ballet was my top priority,
"so my dream died.
"It might sound like I'm exaggerating,
"but it's like accepting death.
"Living is another way of
reaching death.
"I think I know these things very well.
That's why I want
to audition for the role."
When did this dinosaur live?
The latter part
of the Cretaceous period.
The latter part of
the Cretaceous period means...
Well...
That's the period
for the parasaurolophus.
Good.
What about the dinosaur
that has a Syracuse model?
- I don't know.
- Do you want to see it?
Yes, I do.
- Hi! Good evening.
- Good evening.
I am his father.
Nice to meet you.
- My name is Misuzu Takagi.
- Nice to meet you.
I often see her on the train.
I thought she was pretty.
Then I tried to talk to her.
Good job.
Since I'm interested in biology too,
- I wanted to see his books.
- I see.
- We ate your dinner.
- Fine.
What? Was that his?
What should I do? I ate it.
I'm sorry.
I can cook something for you.
Don't worry about it.
Take it easy.
Thank you.
Gang.
Come here.
Good boy. Let's go for a walk.
Shigehiko, make sure
she gets home all right.
Of course.
Come on, Gang.
Let's go.
Ready?
You know, I feel like a criminal.
I'm ready.
Let's start.
Pleased to meet you.
Please sit.
My name is Yu Tanaka.
Nice to meet you.
Please have a seat.
- Are you nervous?
- Yes. A little bit.
- Sorry you're the first.
- That's okay.
We're going to film this,
but just be natural.
Do you mind if I ask
what your father does?
My father's job is... well...
What can I say?
Next one.
- I'm going to ask you frankly.
- Yes.
What made you decide
to audition for this role?
Have you ever had sex
with someone you didn't like?
Are you interested in drugs?
Did you play any interesting roles?
Can you act a little bit for us?
- Sure.
- Go ahead.
What kind of music do you like?
- Which actresses do you like?
- I like Mitsuko Mori.
Next.
I used to like sports.
In high school, I played...
Have you thought about working
in the sex industry?
I have a friend who is working
in the industry, however...
Next.
How do you view men?
Have you ever seen
any Tarkovsky movies?
Ren Osugi.
There are some sex scenes.
Can you handle that?
No problem.
Do you have a sixth sense?
Okay. Next.
May I ask you a question?
Can you smile?
What kind of men do you not like?
I'm Yoko Sugimura.
Nice to meet you.
If I didn't have confidence,
I wouldn’t be an actress.
Excuse me.
When I was two, my mother decided
that I would be an actress.
Can you walk around the chair?
Turn around.
Next, please.
It was nice meeting you.
It's time for a break,
according to our schedule.
We're 30 minutes behind.
- Let's take a 10-minute break.
- Sure.
Why are you making me
ask all these questions?
Don't tell me you're
not interested anymore.
It's not like that.
Then what?
I'm kind of nervous.
I gotta go to the restroom.
I lived in Paris for three years.
Then I came back to Tokyo,
and I was working as a designer.
I can't think about anything else
except being an actress.
I realized my agent
specialized in porn.
Can you keep this one
for another job?
I'm not satisfied with
just being called a cover girl.
This scar is from the first attempt,
and this one is from the second.
I was sent to a mental hospital
three times.
Next one.
Emi Kitani. Nice to meet you.
Didn't we finish your interview?
Right. But I haven't finished
what I have to say.
You have a great career.
Why do you want to audition for this role?
Well... It's so difficult for me, and...
I tried hard, but...
I'm sorry.
I am a pediatric nurse.
My work is very tough, but...
Next, please.
The next one is Asami Yamazaki.
Please.
- Asami Yamazaki.
- Have a seat.
Sorry for the delay.
Have you done any movies or TV jobs?
There were some opportunities,
but they all fell through.
Do you belong to any agency?
Not really.
A guy from a record company
is supposed to represent me,
but we haven't contacted
each other for a long time.
Which record company?
Ace Records.
Could you tell me his name?
Director Shibata,
in the Japanese music department.
It says you've been unemployed
since you quit your previous job.
How do you manage
your daily expenses?
If you don't mind, can you tell us?
I work at my friend's place
three times a week.
What kind of place?
It's a small bar located in Ginza.
The owner used to be my classmate
in a voice training class.
If I keep my expenses low,
I have no money problems.
Don't you want
to live a luxurious life?
Being too poor isn't good.
But if I can afford books and CDs,
I'm pretty happy.
May I ask you about ballet?
Certainly.
- You damaged your hips.
- That's correct.
It must've been awful to quit
what you had been doing.
Yes.
I must sound a bit rude, but...
Your essay says
that your dream died,
and it was like accepting death.
I was highly impressed.
I think everyone
has similar experiences.
There is always something
beyond our control in our lives.
You just have to accept it.
I think that's life.
I mean...
I was amazed a young girl
like you understands that.
I think you've been taking
your life very seriously.
That's what I thought.
Thank you very much.
Are you finished?
Thank you. We may contact you later.
Yes.
Excuse me.
May I call the next one?
- Let's have a 15-minute break.
- Fine.
Please call Mr. Ito
and tell him I will be late.
What do you think about her?
She made me very nervous.
She made me want
to smoke a cigarette.
You knew you would like her
before the audition.
I've been thinking about her
since I read her essay.
I like her much more
after meeting her in person.
You said, "I think you've been
taking your life seriously."
That's not a comment an interviewer
says in an audition. I was stunned.
Don’t joke about that.
She really impressed me.
I'm sure she's a serious girl.
She looks better than her photo,
and may also be goodhearted.
But there's something
I don't like about her.
What?
I don't know what it is.
I can't explain exactly what's wrong.
Something bothers me.
The girl you brought
the other night looked nice.
Misuzu?
- She looks nice, but...
- What?
One of those girl things.
- I don't understand girls.
- Come on.
Thanks.
Hey, Dad, about your remarriage.
Preferably someone
who cooks better than Rie does.
Why are you in such a hurry?
Another dinosaur was discovered
at Moon Valley in Argentina.
That one could be older than eoraptor.
- Really?
- I'll be busy collecting information.
Take a bath.
Yes, hello.
Sorry for calling so late.
This is Aoyama, one of the producers
who interviewed you today.
Thank you for your time today.
Not at all.
Well...
I would like to talk to you more.
I wonder if you might have some time.
Of course. I'd love to see you.
What time would be good for you?
Anytime during the day
would be fine.
Really. Let me see.
How about...
Good night.
This is Aoyama.
It's me.
What's up?
Well...
Regarding the girl, Yamasaki?
I called Ace Records
just to make sure.
It's not a big deal.
But something didn't seem right.
- What is it?
- Well...
There is no Director Shibata
in the Japanese music department.
To be precise,
he isn't there anymore.
This guy, Shibata...
has been missing
for a year and a half.
He just disappeared.
I'm nervous.
I won't ask you
any special questions,
so please relax.
Do you only want me to enjoy
this nice food and talk to you?
That's correct.
That's the best request
I've ever had.
Just one question.
The guy from the record company.
Mr. Shibata?
I'm sorry.
I said so at the audition,
but, in fact, I've never met him.
I was advised to say so,
since it would be too difficult
without an agency.
I see.
I didn't mean to lie.
It's okay.
I've clarified that question.
That means there is no problem.
Here is your food.
It looks delicious.
Go ahead.
Delicious.
Good.
I hope I'm not asking
too much of you...
but if you have some free time,
I'd like to talk to you more.
That would be wonderful.
I don't have any adult men
to be frank with.
If I'm good enough, I'd love to.
Really?
I'm very happy about that.
I'll try not to bother you.
Anywhere is fine.
Even just on the telephone
would be fine.
I wrote down my cell phone number
on the business card I gave you.
Please call me anytime.
Thank you very much.
Thanks for the meal too.
I've decided.
I don't care about the movie.
I'm interested only in her.
Don't worry about the movie.
I'll handle that.
I'm not worried about that.
But don't be too hasty.
You said you wanted to have
enough time to get to know her.
Why are you so negative about her?
What's wrong with her?
I only think that life isn't so easy.
She's beautiful, classy, and obedient.
And she doesn't have any boyfriends.
And she fell into our trap.
Isn't it too good to be true?
I checked her references,
but none are accessible.
The bar she said she was working at
is also unknown.
We can't reach anybody
who knows her.
I wasn't born yesterday.
I won't be fooled this easily.
I trust myself
more than the opinions of others.
If there's any trouble,
I will handle it.
Right.
As you said before, I found
my ideal woman from an audition.
I appreciate it, Yoshikawa.
Hey, Aoyama.
Promise me one thing.
Don't call her for a while.
I hope I'm wrong.
It's going to affect your whole life.
You had better not be hasty.
Cool down a bit.
All right. I promise you.
You're not sick, are you?
It's rare for you to take a day off.
This is the first time
since I started working for you.
Oh, well...
It's good to have a break.
You might be a little tired.
Since your wife passed away,
you've raised your son by yourself.
You started your own company,
which is doing quite well.
You've been working too hard.
I wish my husband was like you.
My life would be easier.
You must have a nice girlfriend.
I'm sure you do.
A man can't function
without a woman's help.
I'm done. I'm going home now.
Bye.
I'm leaving.
See you.
What? Do you have
anything to tell me?
Not really. See you tomorrow.
Bye.
This is Aoyama.
Really? Good.
I thought you
wouldn't call me anymore.
You might think I'm desperate
if I tell you this...
but I was longing for your call.
I'm sorry.
So, how are you?
What?
What's so funny?
I didn't think I would see you again,
so I'm pretty excited.
Here's your drink.
I didn't ask you about your family
at the audition.
Are they fine?
Yes. They're fine.
You're from Tokyo, right?
They moved to Chiba last month.
My father loves golfing, and living
in Chiba is more convenient.
- I see.
- We're not that close,
but not that distant either...
quite an average family.
Do you still work at the bar?
- Yes.
- Is that in Ginza?
The Stone Fish on 4th Street.
Isn't it a funny name?
The Stone Fish?
Shall I come for a drink?
I would love to have you come over,
but my boss tries to...
interfere with my private life.
She is a good person, though.
If you don't want me to come,
of course I won't.
I just want to know you better.
I won't lie to you. Definitely not.
I promise.
I have to tell you this...
It's about the movie.
Did someone else get the part?
It's not like that.
The movie...
Actually, the sponsor
didn't like the story.
It looks like the production
is going to be on hold.
The movie production might...
fall through.
Oh, really?
You might be hurt.
Not me. But you might be.
You read my essay, didn't you?
I never thought about getting
the main role.
It's okay.
The good thing is that I met you.
I felt wonderful...
Seeing myself in the mirror,
picturing myself
among beautiful things.
That's incredible.
I trained myself hard to release pain.
That's why I could go through
the difficult lessons.
But, after all, I lost ballet too.
It's hard to overcome
that experience...
but someday you'll feel
life is wonderful.
That's life, isn't it?
Thank you.
Living alone is a hassle.
I have nobody to talk to.
There were some guys
who approached me,
but you're the first one
who is really warmhearted
and tries to accept
and understand who I really am.
Let's have dinner soon.
When will that be?
Sorry, am I pushing you?
I'll call you.
Yes. I'll look forward to it.
You can stop here.
Please stop the car.
She's getting out.
Thank you very much for today.
See you.
- Good night.
Take me to Okusawa.
Yes.
Can I talk to you for a moment?
What?
The curtain is dirty.
- Well...
- You found a girlfriend.
Right?
Bingo.
You're acting strange lately.
Sometimes you smile to yourself.
She is just 24 years old.
She's closer to my age.
She must be very beautiful.
I'm the same as you.
I like pretty girls.
Don't get fooled.
I'm much smarter than you.
Have you proposed to her?
Not yet.
We're going away this weekend.
I'm going to propose to her then.
Good luck!
I'll introduce her to you soon.
If I think she's all right
it will be fine...
because you're in love now,
and love is blind.
Well...
What can we do before dinner?
The chef here is very skilled.
He prepares very good food.
You can look forward to it.
Not only is he a good chef,
he also has a bad mouth.
There is a small museum close by.
If we leave now,
we can still make it.
It's about 20 minutes away by car.
After that, we can go to the harbor.
It's a little harbor,
but there is a great coffee shop.
And they serve delicious cheesecake.
The desserts are...
Come to me.
Please.
No. Don't take off your clothes yet.
Please...
look at my body.
I burnt myself when I was little.
I want you to know all about me.
You're very beautiful.
Please love me. Only me.
I will.
Everybody says so.
But I hope you're different
from other guys.
Only me. Okay?
Only me.
Please love me. Only me.
- Yes.
- Is this Mr. Aoyama?
This is the front desk.
Yes.
I'm terribly sorry.
You must be in bed.
We called a few times,
but no one answered.
Since your partner left,
we wanted to know if you're staying.
I'm sorry to call you so late.
Left?
What do you mean
she disappeared?
She doesn't answer the phone.
There is no way to contact her.
When I send her home by taxi,
she usually gets out on a nearby street,
not in front of her place.
What happened at the hotel?
I just told you everything.
People don't just disappear like that.
We might have
misunderstood each other.
I just want to talk to her face-to-face.
Yoshikawa, can you
find out her address?
Listen to me.
All we got is her résumé.
It's impossible.
Aoyama...
Why don't you forget about her?
I can't do that.
I know I can't convince you, but...
Anyway, I think
you should forget about her.
You're saying...
that I got too crazy...
about a young girl.
Are you saying...
I'm a pathetic, lonely,
middle-aged man?
Yes, you are.
What's the matter with you?
Didn't you say,
"I wasn't born yesterday"?
Whatever problems come up,
you can fix them, right?
What?
It's okay.
What's okay?
It's okay now.
I won't ask for your help anymore.
I'll look for her by myself.
- I'll find her by myself!
- Aoyama!
Shimada Ballet Studio
Excuse me.
Are you...
Mr. Shimada?
I am...
the one who called you
this afternoon.
Hello?
- Regarding Miss Asami Yamazaki.
- Go home.
Well...
Let me be frank with you.
Did you have any problems...
with Asami before?
I just want to know
how to contact her.
Do you know her whereabouts?
So...
did you see her?
Yes.
Did you hear her voice?
What do you mean by that?
Did you touch her body?
Did you hold her in your arms?
How was that?
Was it good?
Did you smell her?
Asami.
Go home.
4th Street. The Stone Fish.
The Stone Fish
No one is there.
Is it closed today?
That bar has been closed
for more than a year.
What?
The owner was murdered.
That was a huge mess.
Do you know an Asami
who used to work here?
Asami?
I don't recall.
Normally the owner worked here alone.
Asami was supposed to work here
three times a week.
I don't think so.
Excuse me.
Why was the owner killed?
I'm not sure, but...
people say it was about
some sort of man problem.
She was having an affair
with a music industry guy.
She used drugs too.
Did she get murdered here?
The body was chopped up completely.
It's a 28-year-old building.
The whole building is tilted.
We saw her blood flowing
through the gap under the door.
The other mystery was...
The police collected all the body parts
and tried to put it together.
They found three extra fingers
and an extra ear...
and an extra tongue as well.
Isn't it a terrible world?
Mealtime, Gang.
Bye.
Hi, this is Shigehiko.
I'm going to stay at
my friend's house tonight.
It's none of my business,
but eat properly.
There's some yogurt.
You can eat it if you want.
And Gang was hiding
underneath the house,
so please feed him
when he comes out.
Talk to you later.
I'm sorry.
So, how are you?
I didn't think
I would see you again,
so I'm pretty excited.
I didn't ask you about your family.
Are they fine?
When I was little,
my parents got a divorce.
I was sent to my uncle's house.
That was a terrible place.
I only remember being abused.
My uncle's wife
was that kind of woman.
I used to have many scars.
If it's too painful,
you don't have to talk about that.
No, I want you to know
everything about me.
I was forced into cold baths
in winter, and I got pneumonia.
She pushed me down the stairs,
and I broke my shoulder bones.
The doctor got worried about me.
He sent me back
to my mother's house.
How old were you?
I was seven years old.
I see.
My mother got remarried.
I didn't get any more scars...
but my stepfather...
hated me so much.
He had bad legs.
He used to stay home all the time.
I did nothing...
in a dark room every day...
until my mother came home.
I'm sorry.
It's not an easy story, is it?
If you dislike me...
please say so.
Strange.
I never imagined
you'd had such a painful past.
Because ballet helped me get through.
You had talent.
I'm not sure,
but only when I danced it...
purified the dark side of me.
That might be the reason
why I didn't kill myself.
I think you're wonderful.
I've been looking
for someone like you.
Darling.
Ryoko.
This is a good opportunity
to introduce you.
This is Asami Yamazaki.
She isn't good for you. No!
She is a very fine woman.
No...
No!
Darling.
I want you right now.
Asami.
It was just a mistake, right?
You made love to me.
Only once.
I expected something from you.
Was I stupid?
Sorry.
Forgive me.
I'll do anything
to give you pleasure.
I like doing this.
What are you doing? Stop it.
Look, you've got a hard-on.
Stop it!
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Meal...
Three extra fingers, an extra ear...
and an extra tongue as well.
Yummy!
You'll love only me, right?
Only me.
Asami.
Dance for me.
Dance.
Dance, you bitch!
Dance for me, or...
I'll torture you as usual.
Dance. Please dance for me.
Dance!
Asami.
Good girl.
Asami!
This wire...
can cut flesh and bones easily.
You're wonderful.
I never felt unhappy...
because I have been unhappy
all the time.
Asami.
Please stop! No!
A man can't function...
without a woman's help.
Aoyama.
Conduct an audition.
My son told me that...
I looked dispirited,
so I should get remarried.
That's why I decided.
Asami.
Asami...
You...
You can't move anymore.
You'll be paralyzed,
but your nerves will still have feeling.
That way your skin gets sensitive
and you can enjoy the pain.
You guys auditioned many girls...
and you didn't pick me...
but you called me afterward.
You just wanted
to have sex with me.
All guys are the same.
Deeper, deeper...
Painful?
Words create lies.
Pain can be trusted.
Right?
You can feel pain.
You can study
the human body as well.
Deeper, deeper...
That's the most painful spot
around the belly.
How about...
here too?
Here as well.
Right?
Deeper, deeper...
See?
Underneath the eyes
is also very painful.
You only realize who you are
by going through pain
and suffering.
Only when you feel pain
can you know
the shape of your heart.
Your son's name is Shigehiko, right?
Your son has to feel pain.
Then you'll understand more.
Stop that.
Stay away from my son.
You love your son too?
You are a liar.
You only love me, right?
I've got only you.
But you have many others.
I don't want to be
just one of those.
Even if I give you everything I have,
you won't be mine completely.
Everybody is the same.
Everybody.
You can't escape without your feet.
This wire can cut flesh
and bones so easily.
Stop.
Stop it!
Right foot, please.
I'm home.
Dad, are you still awake?
My friend got sick all of sudden.
Then we called an ambulance.
Are you sleeping?
What happened, Dad?
What's going on?
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Yes. Yes.
Well...
I...
I will respond to your proposal.
What?
Your proposal...
I accept.
Proposal?
It's like a dream.
I'm so happy.
Among the girls
who auditioned for the role...
I am...
the luckiest one.
Because I became the real heroine...
not in the movie.
Deeper, deeper...
What happened, Dad?
Who the hell are you?
What do you want?
What?
Dad!
Are you all right, Dad?
Call the police...
Is this the police?
This is the Aoyama residence
in Okusawa.
Please send an ambulance right now.
My father has been seriously injured.
And a woman too.
I don't know the details.
His left leg has been chopped off
and is bleeding badly.
Yes. Yes.
The address is Setagaya-ku,
Okusawa, 6-20-4.
I thought you were a busy man.
I don't know what you do very well.
You may think I am desperate.
I was longing for your call.
I didn't think I would see you again.
Sorry, I'm pretty excited.
Living alone was a hassle.
I have nobody to talk to.
You are the first one...
who is really warmhearted...
and tries to accept me
and tries to understand
who I really am.
It's hard to overcome that experience,
but someday you'll feel
that life is wonderful.
That's life, isn't it?
Ryo Ishibashi
Eihi Shiina
Miyuki Matshuda
Toshie Negishi
Tetsu Sawaki
Ken Mitsuishi
Shigeru Saiki
Ren Osugi
Executive Producer
Toyoyuki Yokohama
Planner
Junichi Shindo
Produced by Satoshi Fukushima
and Akemi Suyama
Original Story by
Ryu Murakami
Screenplay by
Daisuke Tengan
Directed by
Takashi Miike
Cinematography by
Hideo Yamamoto
Sound Effects by
Kenji Sibazaki
Music by
Koji Endo
Special Makeup Effects by
Yuichi Matsui