Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
It won't work, Ashley.
I want my present.
Your birthday's tomorrow.
I want Barella now.
There Barella, you're
almost as pretty as me.
You left Todd behind the sofa.
You're special.
I don't like him any more.
That's no way to treat your old
bear.
Leave me alone!
Barella wants her dream house.
I saw you wrap it.
You're special.
Special.
Todd tried to get me, Mummy.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What have I told you
about getting out of bed.
But, Mummy, Todd.
Todd what?
No, Mummy, don't.
Leave him alone.
Scream again, and you'll get a
smack.
Now turn the light off.
Can I leave the light on,
please?
Not another peep, I mean it.
Special.
Special!
I said, shut it!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
If you want him so badly, have
him.
Noooo, Mummy!
Not another word.
You're special.
Special, special,
special, special, special.
Caught you, you little shit.
You're special.
I was never one of the lucky
kids,
the ones locked in a
cupboard under the stairs,
cigarettes stubbed out
on them in the dark.
Now I know that doesn't seem
very lucky.
But those kids, they had nothing
to lose.
No happy family, no toys and
games.
They certainly didn't
have a bear like Benny.
My story begins when I turned
35,
the year Toy Box sold record
units
of the state-of-the-art Rosko.
Its creator made designer of the
year.
But neither were mine.
Ushering in a new era in Toy
Box's future,
give it up for Richard.
That's my competition
for creative director,
brown-nosing Ron, my
boss, who has a stutter,
but only on F words.
These fakes pretend to like him,
but we all know he's a galactic
tit.
It's Reshard, actually.
Reshard.
Tit.
Deep underground.
A new breed of machine.
Uncompromising.
Devastating.
Disco.
Dancing disco AIDS.
♪ Aids ♪
Yeah, okay, that's my toy,
but in fairness.
It's meant to say RAID,
Robot Artificial Intelligent
Disco System.
Now I bet we're all wondering,
who wants to give their
children AIDS for Christmas?
I had a date
with the stunningly bland Tara.
Just you wait, babes.
Shut up!
Babes, who was that?
Sorry, Mum.
You live with your
fucking parents, babes.
Ah, I forget to mention,
I still live with my fucking
parents.
Open your card, it's funny.
You laughed at ET.
Well only the ending.
I don't wanna a huge number
reminding me of how old I am.
Aww. Have a cupper, love.
40? I'm only 35.
And now you feel better about
it.
Oi, how would you like to be put
on spin with dad's skid marks?
Benny loves you.
Why don't you help me
put the shelf up today?
Because it's not your birthday.
You're gonna have to learn this
stuff
if you're getting your own
place.
Who said anything about that?
Oh I did think about getting
my only place, but, cake?
Every year, Mum and Dad
would plan a special
birthday surprise party,
which by the time you're 35,
isn't much of a surprise
anymore.
Ohhhh.
Mum, could I have a?
Mum?
Dad?
Mum say something.
My 35th birthday,
the day I finally got my own
place.
Jack.
The company
want foreclosure on the loan,
repossess your house.
No you can't, I'll get on top of
this.
Ah, ah, I managed to talk
them out of that, just.
I've convinced them to
restructure the loan,
into smaller payments.
Good.
This says I'll pay back three
times as much.
Four.
You should be thanking me.
Your ads says
the best rates in town.
Oh they are.
Just not this town.
I just need time.
That promotion-
Has nothing to do with the loan.
Listen, if I were you, I would
sell the house, problem solved.
This is my home.
Not if you don't sign.
That is my favourite
pen, if you don't mind.
Scum.
Excellent, now I do have to
inform you
that if we don't receive
payment by the end of the week,
the company will have to start
the repossession procedure.
Biscuit.
Oh yes, don't mind if I do.
I wish I could put in the hours.
But with a family, it's just not
possible.
Then why are you here?
Told the wife I was working
late.
Working late.
But really, I'm off
to the Prince concert.
Fuck off.
No, really, Prince is back.
No, really, fuck off, I'm
working.
I'm celebrating.
Come on lets bury
the hatchet.
No one's going to get promoted,
by being wasted Richard.
God I hate people who
pronounce it Richard.
You're not even French.
So, no one calls Ralph Feinnes,
Ralf.
Because he's Welsh.
God I'd hate to be Welsh.
Just go, I have to get this
finished.
Lots of people are saying
you're already finished.
Who's saying that?
People.
Lots of them.
Jack?
I suppose you're wondering
why Ron's here so late?
He's here to tell you the good
news.
Good news.
About the promotion.
No?
Mmm.
About the promotion.
Jack.
Jack?
Hmmm.
Precious!
Jack!
Sweetums.
Come to daddy.
Who's a good boy?
Jack?
Come on!
Who's a good doggy?
Doors opening.
Jesus!
Prince actually.
But close enough.
Hmmm.
Here's the thing.
I'm letting you go.
What?
I can't send my creative
director
to New York in a Goonies
T-shirt.
I don't have a Goonies
T-shirt, I have a Gremlins one.
I don't give a fuck about the
Goonies.
Me neither, you keep
going on about them.
Or Gremlins!
Young people today
aren't playing Simon Says
in f-f-f-fucking fingerless
f-f-f-fucking gloves
and shoulder pads, it's all
smart phones
and blue movie players.
Blu-Ray, sir, look, my designs...
You haven't evolved.
Richard's edgy, stands up for
himself.
Okay, I am not gonna stand
here...
Sit.
It's just business, sorry.
Please, sir.
Hmmm.
There is a junior design
position,
two-thirds your salary.
Best I can do.
Sir, I can't afford a pay cut.
I'm offering to help.
Do you want my help or not?
Yes sir.
Great, welcome to the team.
You're on probation, so
I want something fresh
by Friday or you're out, again.
Oh, and smile.
You always look so bloody
miserable,
plodding around like someone
died.
Sir?
I just gave you a job.
Give me a smile.
Come on!
Good boy.
Are you a loser or a winner?
If you bought this tape, you're
a loser.
Look in the mirror and tell
yourself.
You're a fucking winner.
Yes, I'm in the area
with a buyer on Monday.
Should be able to swing by then.
It's quite big isn't it?
Must get quite lonely.
It's more of a family home.
Do not fear change, embrace it.
Take your failed,
pathetic life and bin it.
Become someone greater.
Cheeky, we'll find you a new
home.
One by one, you'll feel the old
you dissolve
away, leaving an uncompromising
winner in its wake.
Benny loves you.
More. Weeeee.
Goodnight, my special boy.
Jaaaaaaack.
Jaaaaaaaaaaaaack.
Mum, mum!
Jack!
Mum!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Leave the light on, please.
Wait there.
Cuddle Benny.
Ta-da.
I was gonna save him for you,
but this, this is Benny.
Made just for you.
With one mission, to keep you
safe.
As long as you have him by your
side,
nothing can ever hurt you.
Not even the demons in the
hallway?
Apart from them!
No, silly, not even the
demons in the hallway.
Benny loves you.
Come on, boy.
Oh wow, cuddle Benny, more.
We'll be friends forever and
ever.
Benny loves you.
Play with Benny.
It's time to let go of the
past.
Weeeeeeee.
Cleanse yourself.
You are not defined by
your former mistakes.
But prepared by them to tackle
the future.
Your life cannot change until
you do.
Play with Benny.
Press my tummy to make me laugh.
Press my tummy to make meeee
laaaaaaugh.
Cuddle me.
Play with Benny.
Cheeeeekyyyyyy.
999, please state the emergency
service you require.
Oh, God, someone
murdered all my teddies.
Sorry?
Calm down, sir, there's no harm
done.
All the doors were locked.
Suggesting the intruder had a
key.
It's normally someone you know.
It's Benny.
Someone jealous.
Do you have an ex-wife?
No.
Anyone staying with you?
Relatives?
No.
A girlfriend?
Friends?
A pet?
No. No. Ok, there's no one else.
I'm a complete loner all right.
Good!
Complete. Loser.
Loner!
Yes, of course, sorry.
What about biscuits?
For DNA?
No.
For my tea.
Custard creams.
I love custard creams.
Ohhhhh.
How many teddies were involved
in this massacre then?
I don't know.
All their heads are gone.
They're still here, just
gotta match them up like socks.
Don't I get some protection?
Where's Benny?
Who's Benny?
My teddy bear.
What, two megabytes of
level two cache memory?
No, that's not good enough,
Rupert.
It's caché memory.
Say it.
I just wanna give it a little,
uh,
just a little je ne sais quoi,
you know.
Boo!
Joie de vivre.
Some bon viveur.
Crème de la crme.
Ok, you know what, Bon Voyage.
The Secret to Award-Winning
Success.
For Losers.
Well, they ran out of Dummies.
You've left the price tag on
your suit.
Hey, uh.
You're not gonna win
any awards for this.
It's F-Friday.
Yeah.
The thing is, sir, I haven't...
I took his designs home to
cost spec, so it's my fault.
Already have our new tech lady
on it.
First thing Monday.
Senior Product Engineer please.
If you need voice control,
motion sensors,
proximity triggers, or even
level two cache, I'm your lady.
Well, I'm no lady.
You provide the toys,
I provide the back end.
Dawn.
Now, finally,
you're on the road to success.
Hey, this is David from Bay...
Message deleted.
Hey, this is David again.
Deleted.
Jack, we still haven't
received the first payment.
Deleted.
Hey, this is David again.
Come on, Jack.
Deleted.
Jackster.
Jackie, Jackie.
Deleted.
Now, Jack, this is your final...
Play with me.
Come on.
You can do this.
[Piss]
Benny loves you.
Cuddle me.
Ta-da.
Weeeeeee.
Officers.
Can we come in?
We left our camera.
Wait there, I'll just get it.
No, uh, actually, we've
got a few more questions
to ask about the break-in,
if you don't mind, sir.
Just let me change.
Shit.
Mr Hunt.
What is he doing?
Come on, Jack, we know you're in
there.
Why would he run away?
There's a door there.
Let's go round the back.
He just shut the door.
Mr. Hunt, just, Mr. Hunt, open
the door.
What's that?
Come in.
Oh, come on.
That's new.
I like it.
Modern art, exploding from
the boundaries of the canvas.
Do you recognise this man?
He's
unrecognisable.
Your account manager at
Bayvista?
Oh, I recognise him.
I just thought you meant,
you know, recently.
He was booked to visit you
yesterday.
He's not here.
Maybe he's ill.
That was our thoughts,
until we found his car parked
at the end of your road.
How odd.
Can I borrow a pen?
I'll give it back.
Am I under any suspicion here?
We thought there could be
a connection to the break-in.
You're fine.
Unless we find his body.
Is there something you wanna
tell us?
No.
Just, just hope he's okay,
that's all.
It's probably nothing.
Hang on.
It's not the same.
Without custard creams.
Now which cupboard are they?
No, no biscuits.
Really?
They were cheap ones anyway.
Leave it, Sarge.
It's not worth it.
Oh, you found your bear then?
Oh my God.
Benny loves you.
Fuck!
Benny?
I'm not gonna hurt you, okay?
Cuddle me.
Weeeeeeeee.
Benny loves you.
Okay.
Play with Benny.
Oh wow.
All right.
More, more, more.
Okay.
Oh wow.
Okay, enough.
More, more.
Weeeeeeeeeee!
No way.
It's Benny.
Play with Benny.
Oh fuck, I need a beer.
Okey dokey.
Benny loves you, Benny
loves you.
Play with Benny.
Why did you kill him?
Benny loves you.
Okay, for the moment, you can
stay here.
Weeeeeeeeee!
Under the conditions no one else
dies,
stay completely out of sight,
no one can know you're here.
Just until I figure out what to
do.
Okey dokey.
My house, my rules.
Look, we can't just kill
people we don't like, okay?
You have to promise.
Are you listening?
Say okey dokey.
Okey dokey.
Cuddle Benny.
Later.
Weeeeeeeeeeee!
Shit!
Calm down, Benny.
Oi.
Look, it's really nice to
have you around and that,
but, sit.
And put that knife down.
Good boy.
Cuddly robotic killers.
A whole universe.
They've got different
personalities, weapons, outfits.
They can talk to each other,
interact.
They can even fight.
This could be huge.
Huge.
Have you had a brain
haemorrhage?
Think young adults, collectors,
teenagers, horror fans, comic
fans.
Losers, virgins, chumps.
There's a huge market out there.
Let me create toys for a new
demographic.
Loser.
As the new creative director,
I'm not gonna allow this project
to...
Sorry, did I say that you
were the new creative director?
Yeah, well, you fired
him, so, here I am.
Did I say that you were
the new creative director?
99%, yeah.
Did I say
that you
were the new
creative
director?
99%.
Well you didn't use that
exact specific sentence,
but just juggle some of
the words around, and, yes.
Yes.
No.
Let's see where this goes, shall
we?
Hold it there. Hold. Hold.
Aren't you beautiful, yes-
No!
High-five.
You're good.
I've got thousands of
motion-capture files,
and I can upload them all with
this.
Milk, milk, lemonade,
round the corner, chocolate's
made.
How about tonight we go
shoot some pool and grab
some burgers and mow some
old ladies down on the pier?
Grand Theft Auto.
I'd love to, but I've got
market research, profit ratios.
What are you afraid of?
Benny loves you.
Don't ring me at work.
Mmm.
I want you to pitch that to
the New York team next week.
Oh, and I'm taking me grandkids
to the theatre Saturday night.
So can you look after me lovely
Precious?
Oh, that's really not...
Fine, Richard said he could...
Not really a problem, sir.
I'll drop her off at 7:30.
Saturday, your place.
You cook.
I knew it.
I've been here before.
I had a date with this creep,
babes.
Oh you mean, um, Jack.
Yeah, well don't worry,
you're with me now.
There's nothing to be afraid of
here.
Oh dear.
Cheap.
This, um,
airing cupboard is lovely and
cosy.
Cosy?
I'm not getting in it, babes.
No, of course not.
Right.
[Get out babes]
See here, he's transformed
this seemingly blank canvas
into a rather stunning feature
wall,
which I'm sure you'll agree
really brings the room together.
Can I just. Get out of my way.
Please.
Anythink you'd like.
Everything's for sale!
Benny loves you.
It's Benny.
Weeeeeeeeee!
Huh?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Benny loves you.
What the fuck?
Play with Benny.
Ta-da.
Cuddle me.
I'm tired.
Night, Benny.
Benny loves-
[Get out]
It's gonna be great down here.
You've got your favourite comic.
Promise to be quiet, okay?
Cuddle me.
Say okey dokey.
Okey dokey.
Good boy, in.
Voila.
Wow.
Chips and beans.
Those are oven chips, crinkle
cut.
No microwave shit round here.
Aw, the beans are cold.
I can microwave them.
We could get Chinese.
Weeeeeeee!
Oh.
Oooh.
Oooooohhhhhh.
Meh.
Play with Benny.
It's your birthday next week.
Wanna do something fun?
I'm not big on birthdays
anymore.
What about yours?
We'll celebrate that.
Hmmm?
I'm not really that big
into birthdays either.
Right.
Give her these vitamin tablets
at 9.
She only drinks mineral water.
And don't feed her after
10, even if she begs.
She won't get a thing.
Good boy.
Keep this up, and I'm looking
at the new creative director.
Bye-bye, my little Precious you.
Say bye-bye to Precious.
Bye, Precious, bye.
Bye-bye.
And that's how you
apply the psychology
of winning to your loser,
no-hope life.
It's a personal journey of...
Who the fuck still listens to
cassettes?
My mum.
Well, she did.
I know what happened to your
parents.
Is that why you've been
keeping me away from you,
from this place?
I lost my parents when I was
young.
It's not easy, is it?
Everywhere I look, there's
a reminder of them.
Cheer up, have some chicken
satay.
I bought my mum that mug.
[Every Day a Bonus]
Oh wow.
I couldn't have
done this without you.
I know.
Or without being Ron's bitch.
You don't even like dogs, do
you?
What?
No,
I love dogs.
What happened with your parents?
I had this doll, Amy.
♪ Little girl who counts her
sheep. ♪
I was 10, I used to play
with her all the time.
My dad thought it was weird.
Two days before my
birthday, she went missing.
Dad said I'd lost her,
but I knew it was him.
I threw a strop and
refused to talk to him.
The night before my
birthday, I couldn't sleep.
I heard something, a clatter.
And then my mum screamed.
He'd tripped at the top of the
stairs.
♪ Little girl don't make a peep. ♪
Tripped on Amy.
He'd broken his neck.
I wanted to rip Amy apart.
But I never saw her again.
That's why I hate birthdays.
Jack?
Where did you go?
Just, um,
checking on dessert?
Oh, what are we having?
Nothing.
Are you okay?
Maybe we could do this another
night.
Don't be silly, we're
celebrating, remember?
Got to celebrate.
Oh wow, it's the prototype.
God, he's cute, yes you are.
Put him down.
Why don't I rip out his insides
and we can...
No, no.
I don't love you.
I'm not saying I don't like you.
No, I'm totally saying that,
I don't even like you.
Something's up.
Tired. It's been a busy week.
You're burning up.
I just need to lie down.
Let's get you upstairs.
No.
Yeah, yeah yeah yeah.
I'm fine, I'm fine.
We need to get you into bed.
You don't look very well,
come on, down you go.
Look at you.
It's probably a virus, I
don't wanna give it to you.
Oh, I just need the bathroom.
Benny?
Fuck. Fuck.
Shit.
Oh shit.
Shit, shit.
Oh fuck.
Okay, Precious, that's not too
bad.
Sir,
I am so sorry.
She must have passed away
peacefully in her sleep.
Oh Christ.
Oh, hello, um, do you have any
fat dogs
in stock?
♪ Daddy wouldn't buy me a
bow-wow ♪
♪ Bow-Wow ♪
♪ Daddy wouldn't buy me a
bow-wow ♪
♪ Bow-Wow ♪
I don't know, it's a
scrunchy wrinkly thing.
Ugly, you know the ones,
a face like the back end of a
bus.
♪ I've got a little cat and I'm
very fond of that ♪
Hello?
Benny?
♪ But I'd rather have a
bow-wow-wow. ♪
About time.
I have something you're gonna
wanna see.
Nooooo!
Get away from her, you bitch.
Oh my God
fuck!
♪ Daddy wouldn't buy me a
bow-wow ♪
♪ Bow-Wow ♪
Jesus!
Jack, no!
Now,
I bet you're wondering
why your dog is dead.
Before you go,
I just wanted to say,
I'm so glad I didn't take her.
Word is, you ripped our her
spine
and twisted it round your head.
I heard Rosko got canned.
Rosko is so last year.
I'll be taking over Skare Bears
now.
Ahh, we got you a little
something.
Had to whip round, didn't
get much, but here you go.
♪ AIDS ♪
Happy birthday, Jack.
Have you seen this?
Aw, poor little thing.
I know.
This one's not much better,
look.
I know.
Shit.
Open it.
We found these on the camera we
left.
Care to explain them?
Benny!
Come on, Benny.
Daddy's home.
What is going on in your head?
Cuddle me.
All you wanna do is cuddle
me and kill everyone else.
What the fuck is your problem?
Ron fired me because of you.
Benny loves you.
Yeah? Then do one thing for me.
Go back to the way you were.
A stuffed, lifeless toy.
Ta-da.
Forget it.
Play with me.
Fuck off, Benny.
Shitbag.
Benny, come on.
Ta-da.
Ron!
Are you insane?
I'm so sorry sir, it wasn't me.
Then who was it?
How did you even get...
Someone hit me over the head.
Then I woke, tied to this
f-fucking chair.
You've lost it.
This is the end of you, the end.
But it wasn't me.
You wait till the police
hear about this, you maniac.
Look. Let's not do anything we
might regret.
Let's just think about this.
Untie me, you f-f-fucking idiot.
Yes, sir, I'm sorry sir.
There's a good boy.
What?
I said, hurry up, come on.
No, you said good boy.
So what?
What are you playing at?
You've never really understood
what I'm capable of.
After my Precious, I'm very well
aware.
Precious got it easy,
and you're in no position to
negotiate.
What do you want?
Hmm, let's say I hang on to this
photo,
you give me that promotion.
Double my salary.
And we never speak of this
again.
It's just business.
You're joking?
Am I?
Nothing to lose.
Okay, whatever
you want, just untie me.
Then give me a smile.
What?
Give
me
a smile.
Good boy.
Now tell me I'm a fucking
fabulous first-rate designer.
Look, this isn't necessary.
Say it, bitch.
You're a f-f-f-f-f-fucking
f-f-f-f-fabulous
f-f-first rate f-f-f-f-fucking
designer.
Now tell me you love being my
bitch.
I love being your bitch.
No.
No!
Ta-da.
This
is not
a present.
Benny loves you.
Yeah?
Well Jack hates you.
Cuddle me.
Benny loves you.
You're a winner.
You're a loser.
Listen, I've just...
You're wearing a party hat.
It's my birthday.
Was.
I'm cleaning.
Okay, weird.
I've come to pick up the
prototype.
Otherwise, they're gonna fire me
too.
It's not what you think it was.
I don't wanna talk about it.
I protected you.
From a pug?
I think it had rabies.
In everything that's happened,
the one thing I don't
regret is meeting you.
Whatever anyone says,
whatever you hear about me,
I'm not Norman Bates, okay?
Good.
I can't bear cross-dressers.
Friends?
I should go.
Stay.
And do what?
Cleaning up dog remains.
This is not Grand Theft Auto.
You really know how to treat a
lady.
You're not a lady.
Dawn?
Shit.
Cuddle Benny.
Good job.
How did you convince him?
I didn't.
Benny loves you.
Play with Benny.
Let's cut it open.
Get away from him!
She's not my type.
The bear, he'll kill you all.
Poor Jack.
He's just a teddy.
He's alive.
Ah.
Come on, Benny, Jack's here.
He's playing dead.
Come on Benny.
He's upset because I buried him
alive.
Well you deserved that.
Now I bet we're all wondering.
Richard, have I ever told you
how much I love you?
Aw, well, thanks, Jack.
Benny loves you.
If you want her, you've
gotta go through me.
Or Richard.
What?
It's Benny.
Cuddle me.
My car.
Two-seaters are fucking death
traps.
Give me the keys, you can't
drive.
Mirror, signal...
Manoeuvre, Jack, fucking
manoeuvre.
I can't drive.
Move!
Be careful with her.
She's the most beautiful
girl in the world.
Let's go.
Cuddle me.
Weeeee.
Ta-da.
Could it be a midget in a
costume?
Toys don't come to life
when you treat them like shit.
They don't come to life at all,
in fact.
We should go to the police.
The staff were witnesses.
All dead.
I should know, I've got three
bodies in my back garden.
Three?
Five.
If you count pets.
Look, he can't be bargained
with.
He doesn't feel pity or remorse.
He does get scared sometimes,
but he absolutely will not stop
until you are dead.
What's this got to do with me?
I know.
Do you want another cuppa?
Go on then.
So why the hell am I here?
Because I'm the only
person he won't kill.
I mean, go if you want.
Laters.
But he'll kill you anyway.
And why is that?
Because you're a tit, Richard.
Right, well, I'm calling the
police.
That had all my Prince photos on
it.
Leave, and you'll end up like
Ron.
He's one of the five.
Why Ron?
He loved being my bitch.
What is wrong with you?
Why didn't you put him in the
fire or stab him, shoot him?
Because he's my best friend.
Don't be ridiculous, he's
trying to kill all your friends.
I don't have any other friends.
You've got me.
Yeah, and you keep slapping me.
Why don't we,
talk to,
an Indian spirit chief
or a a voodoo priest?
It's a two-foot teddy bear,
right?
One and a half.
Oh We are so fucked, ow!
This is jeux terminer man, jeux
terminer
We need to lock this place,
get anything we can to defend
ourselves.
Okay, all right, I've got
some water pistols in the car.
What are you gonna do?
I'll make the tea.
♪ AIDS ♪
Oh wow.
It's Benny.
Are you still angry at me?
Of course.
Why does he wanna kill me?
Is it because you think I'm a
tit?
It's because he's jealous.
He thinks I love you more than
him.
Don't worry, he's like that with
everyone.
You're nothing special.
You're gonna have to kill him,
you know?
Don't come out until I say.
I can look after myself.
Jack?
Be careful.
Ouch!
I've gotta make him think
I don't love you, okay?
Bastard.
Play with Benny.
Are we gonna die?
We're gonna die.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Look, in a situation like this,
just ask yourself, what would
Prince do?
He'd shit himself.
Cuddle me.
I mean people don't realise, you
know,
he's not just a musician.
He's, he's, like he's
multi-talented.
He writes all his own songs.
He writes a lot of other
people's songs actually.
Oh wow.
♪ Little girl who counts her
sheep. ♪
♪ Little girl don't make a peep. ♪
Amy?
He's directed like
8 films, some of them
full-length feature
films, which are amazing.
He's so good.
♪ Little girl don't worry dear. ♪
♪ Go to sleep cos Amy's here. ♪
Jack!
Just on another planet.
He's an actor.
Where have you gone?
Benny loves you.
Richard!
It's Reshard.
The blades!
Okay, it's just you and me now
buddy.
Play with Benny.
AIDS.
Cuddle Benny.
Play with Benny.
Benny loves you.
Rosko is so last year.
Oh God noooooo!
Purple Rain. Purple Rain.
Jack!
For he's a jolly good fellow.
Okay, no more Mister Nice Guy.
Okay, okay, I'll be nice.
I'll. Be. Nice.
Play with me.
More.
Come on, Benny.
Come for Jack.
Come to Daddy.
There's a good boy.
I'm not a little girl anymore,
you cheap piece of shit.
No more Mr. Nice Guy.
I hate people who say Reshard.
La la laaaaaa. La la laaaaaa.
Bon voyage.
It's Benny.
Benny loves you.
Rosko.
Benny?
Play with me.
Brain haemorrhage.
You're finished.
Ta-da.
Owwwww.
We know you're in there Jack.
Surrender.
Richard you tit.
Tit.
You're surrounded.
Surrounded? Idiot.
Then call it in.
We don't need armed response.
We need, these.
Pellet guns?
Thank God, we're saved.
These will take down anyone at
10 paces.
You go in, I'll cover you.
No, you go in, I'll cover you.
With what?
My batton.
Take this, take it.
Fine.
But, you go in first.
What? Oh fuck, all right.
After three.
One.
Two.
Three.
What?
It's not her you're angry with,
it's me.
I threw you out, I ignored you.
I fucked up, and I'm
a dick, and I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for treating you,
like a toy.
Where they're gonna take me,
you won't be able to come this
time.
It's over.
Cuddle me.
Make a wish.
We'll be friends
forever and ever.
Jack loves you too.
Benny, no!
Play with me.
Benny?
Benny looovvvees
yooooou.
What the fuck was that?
Call it in.
Right, you call it in.
Jack.
Are you okay?
We need an ambulance at 415 Elm
Way.
One suspect down.
Male, 40, shot and wounded.
I'm 36.
The sight of the
massacre where
Reshard Williams killed his
co-workers over a lost promotion
will be a place of gathering for
family...
Last lot.
They're all coming with us.
Oi, Jack, come
here, you filthy sod.
My special boy.
Locked all the doors?
Check.
Key under the mat?
Disposed of all the evidence?
Oh.
Check.
Then we're golden.
Get out of here, before
we change our minds.
There goes an accessory to
murder.
Go ahead, tell the truth,
I'll be right behind you.
Pulling this face.
Now, I bet you're all wondering
how the hell we got away with
it.
But, the real lesson is,
we've all got that one special
bear,
someone we've cherished for
years,
someone that once meant the
world to us.
Maybe he's tattered from
years of gathering dust.
Maybe you've found
something else to play with.
But whatever you do,
under any circumstances,
Don't.
Throw.
Him.
Out.
Or the next time you curl up to
sleep,
he might just come back for a
cuddle.
You're special.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull