What, what?
Captain?
- What was that?
- A whale?
- Whales don't sound like that.
- What, you get a lotta whales
on the Lower East Side, Bigelow?
- Listen.
It's a ship.
- A ship?
We're saved?
- Faraday, give your life
vest to Miss Prescott.
- Oh, for heaven sake,
the man has a broken arm.
Ahoy, over here!
- Oi, sit down you fat
head, you'll capsize us.
- Don't you touch me.
- Look.
- Great.
Fuckin' Nazis.
- I don't care if it's Hitler's
personal pleasure cruiser.
This is the only ship
that we've come across
the last two--
- Keep your voice down.
- And what are they
gonna do, shoot us?
We're dead anyways.
- He's right, Captain.
The Russian's are done.
- Chances are they'll
shoot me on sight,
but I guess that's better
than starvin' to death.
We got to get off this raft,
simple as that Captain.
- What about her?
What do you think those sons
of bitches will do to her?
- I'll not have any of
your deaths on my hands.
We'll live to fight
another day, hm?
All of us.
- Perhaps we could consider
some of the other options.
I simply mustn't be allowed
to fall into enemy hands.
- What makes you
so bloody special?
- Surely there's something
more we can do besides--
- Can it, Specks.
We'll hitch a ride
with the krauts.
Brace yourselves!
Hey!
- Captain Malone
and Sinclair: Hey!
Hey!
- Down here!
- Hey!
- Hello!
You dirty bastards!
- I can't see anyone on deck.
- Hello!
- Hey!
Ahoy!
- Hello?
- Hey!
- What are you doin'?
- Need a tow-line.
Shit!
Everybody hold still.
Oh!
- How many bullets left?
- Wait a God damn minute.
You speak English?
- I never said I could not.
Well,
this is just perfect.
- How many bullets?
- One.
- Sniper?
- Nah, we're not gonna give
our only rifle to the Russian.
- Yeah, especially
to a guy who's
been spyin' on
us the whole time.
You can't trust this guy.
- What's he gonna
do with one bullet?
- Hopefully not miss.
- You buyin' it
or firing it Ivan?
- The Enfield, Mark One.
Old action rifle.
Shoots to left if not
properly re-calibrated.
- I swear to God,
Ivan if you miss--
- Look, would you just shut up
and let the man concentrate?
- Gentlemen, we're
running out of ship.
He got it!
Grab it.
Grab it!
Pull.
Pull!
- Heave!
- Pull!
Get up there Teplov.
Captain, hold on.
Come on, come on, pull, pull.
- Ivan!
- Come on, come on climb.
- Climb.
- Who up now?
Miss Prescott, Miss
Prescott my hand.
- You got her?
- Thank you.
Bigelow?
- Come on.
- Come on Bigelow.
- Jackson?
Faraday, come on.
- I couldn't
possibly, it's my arm.
- Mr. Faraday, come on.
- Captain, come on!
- Come on Mr. Faraday.
Give me your hand.
Mr. Faraday, Sir?
- Come on.
- Come here.
- We don't have all day mate!
- Come on.
- No!
- Grab a hold.
- No, no.
- Come on.
- Get on.
Get up here.
Come on here, here.
Get on Faraday.
Up you go, come on.
Grab him, grab him.
Come on.
- All right, move, move, move.
Here we go.
- All right.
Oh, damn.
Come on Captain.
- Captain!
Grab him Jackson.
Come on Cap.
There we go.
- Pull him up!
- Come on!
- Come on Captain!
- Come on Captain.
You're a damn fool Captain.
Captain!
- Jesus Christ!
- Hey, hey.
- What?
Captain!
- Jackson, I'm sorry he's gone.
He's gone.
Yeah, he's gone.
Come on, everyone.
- How's that hand Mr. Faraday?
- No, no, no.
Gerard...
I, look, I...
- The Englishman
has many secrets.
- You're one to talk.
- You limey weasel.
- You were gonna
let us starve to death
so you could live
a few more days.
- You'd have done the same if
you had the
brains to think of it.
The work I do affects
the lives of millions.
You're just meat
for the grinder.
- Oh!
Leave him alone.
He's harmless.
- He's a coward is what he is.
- Who's to say that fuckin' arm
ain't even broken?
- Hey, hey, hey.
- Yeah, why don't we
just throw him overboard?
- Hey!
- Oh, enough!
In case you'd
forgotten we're all
on the same side,
now act like it.
- You know what
I think is strange?
- Oh, what?
- All this, this
fighting and shouting.
No one comes to see, hm?
- It's one bloody thing
after another isn't it?
- Let's take shelter.
- Amen to that toots.
Mr. Sinclair,
perhaps you could help.
Come on.
- Engine's runnin' but--
- Nobody's home.
It seems that way.
- We can't stay out here.
- Well, if you wanna
go stumbling around
in the dark go
knock yourself out.
After you ladybird.
- Oi.
What have you and uh, Ivan--
Teplov.
- What?
- Junior Sergeant
Alexander Teplov.
With the four keeps--
- Okay, yeah, yeah.
Sniper.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, got it.
Why don't you and Bigelow
head up to the bridge?
See who's steerin'
the thing, huh?
- I'm not goin' anywhere
with the fascist.
- Communist, dickhead.
- What's the difference?
- Hey look, why don't you just
do what the man says Bigelow?
- And since when did you
start givin' me orders?
- Come, I do not bite.
- Gosh he's smug.
- You know you're
gonna get frostbite?
- Yeah, I've been through worse.
- All you Cossacks
are a bit loony.
- And you Americans
talk too much.
- I preferred when
you didn't talk at all.
- We need to get his
arm back into a sling.
- Hm.
- Yes, Ma'am.
- Thank you Mr. Sinclair.
- Fuck, it's mouldy.
You wanna point that
outta my fuckin' face?
Jesus man.
Fuck.
Oh.
- Here you go.
Courtesy of the Fuhrer.
- It's not exactly my colour.
- A sling, your majesty.
- Colonist.
- Imperialist.
- Convict.
- Wanker.
Over here.
- You go.
- Okay.
You gonna be all
right Miss Prescott?
- We're fine.
- It was a cowardly
thing I did, I know.
- I've seen men do
far worse in this war.
Sinclair!
- Hey.
- You ought to know.
- Blimey.
The life boats have
been sabotaged too.
- Oh, you're kidding me man?
- You ever seen
anything like this before?
- I have seen gas
turn a man inside out,
but nothing like this.
- Whatever it is it's startin'
to give me the creeps all right?
There's somethin' wrong here.
- I knew farmers who
took up arms against
the Wehrmacht with more
courage than you.
- Hey, what do you want from me?
I'm a God damn cook, all right?
Three years in that
fuckin' war and then
I get torpedoed my way
home and then I get stuck
on that God forsaken raft
with no food and no water
and now you're tellin' me
that my only fuckin' chance
of hope is on some God
forsaken ghost ship?
On top of it you
forgot to mention
I got stuck with you, you
cloak and dagger asshole
and that limey prick
and you, Australia.
I ain't even know you
people were in the war.
- Pull your head in mate.
- Hey, I ain't your mate, okay?
I don't owe you people nothin'.
We got stuck in the same war
and now get stuck
in the same boat.
- Yeah, we did and
we're still breathin'.
- I just want lady luck to
smile on me just this once.
- It ain't about luck mate.
It ain't.
It's about how you play
the hand you're dealt.
Look, keep this to
ourselves for now.
- All right.
Okay.
No shoes.
- What's your excuse?
- I was in bunk
when torpedo hit.
- Oh, you poor thing.
We'll get you out of
the retched weather.
We'll find a sickbay, okay?
- So you're British
Intelligence?
- Something like that.
Oh, oh.
- How'd you get here?
- He needs rest Mr. Jackson,
not an interrogation.
Watch your step.
- You guys find anything?
- Uh, no just a busted
compass and uh,
someone chained
the wheel, no Jerries?
- Yeah, just don't jinx it, huh?
- Yeah.
- Bet this tug's still
crawlin' with krauts.
- What's that?
- It's a doll.
- It's really old.
- Spooky.
It's an antique.
- Oh, you're some
kind of expert are ya?
- An antique dealer actually
in another life before the war.
- Of course you were, Gerard.
- May I?
Oh.
Pierre-Francois Jumeau,
finest doll makers in Paris.
Hm, 1780 - 1830 I'd say.
- Is it worth anything?
- A thousand pounds.
Perhaps more at auction.
- Well that's a whole lotta
clams for a kid's toy.
- What the hell's it doin' here?
- Jackson?
How do you feel
about switchin' sides?
- Hey, if it means us gettin'
out of these wet
drawers sign me up.
All
there is I'm afraid.
- Man, how many
times you been shot?
- Not all bullets.
Some is knife,
some is cigarette.
This one wild pig.
It's long story.
- Oh my...
Sorry.
- Don't be.
Just a scratch.
- Where'd you get those?
- Tobruk.
Panzer division.
Blasted us to buggery.
- All that time of the life boat
and you didn't say anything.
- Three years as a POW.
Not much to tell.
Shelly, my wife.
They told her I was killed
in action, so she remarried.
She's happy.
She's had a baby.
Few months old now.
I wanna see her
just one last time.
Don't blame her for movin' on.
Life's too short.
It's too bloody short.
- You'll see her again.
- What about you tough guy?
You got family?
- Not anymore.
I'm
sorry to hear that.
- Such small feet these Nazis.
- Boiler room, ammunitions,
galley, radio room.
Let's see if we can reach
anyone on the shortwave.
- All right.
I wanna take a
look at the engine
and see what's
keepin' her runnin'.
- No offence Jackson
but you're a cook.
- Oh yeah, he's a real demon
with the ladle this guy.
- I worked in a
shipyard before the war
and the mechanics before that.
- Okay then.
- Remind me, what did you do
- Okay.
- before slingin'
last week Bigelow?
- Two groups.
Jackson, Bigelow
with uh, Teplov.
Miss Prescott and
Faraday with me.
Meet back in the
galley when we're done.
- All right then.
- Bloody Yanks.
- German.
- Do you know
what they're saying?
- Bits and pieces.
- I think they're
looking for this ship.
- Don't be daft, say something.
Just speak, go on.
- We're on a German ship
without any Germans on it
and you wanna just
invite some along.
Go on genius.
- Mm, brilliant.
- Must be someone else.
- Oh, not good.
This is not good.
- You care to uh, humour me
with specifics Mr. Jackson?
- Uh, the boiler
must be runnin' dry.
Engine pressure's
through the roof.
- So, who gives a shit?
- Look, if the boiler
runs dry and the engine
is still running it could
set off a chain reaction.
If it reaches the
munitions room,
it can blow this
whole ship to pieces.
This tub's a ticking time bomb.
- So turn it off.
- That's exactly
what I'm gonna do.
- No, hold the fuck up.
You're not shuttin'
this ship down.
- Look we don't know how
much fuel we got left.
A day, maybe less.
We can always
turn it back on once
we realise where
the hell we're goin'.
Teplov, grab that other wheel.
- Don't fuckin' touch
that wheel, okay?
Listen to me, listen to me.
If you shut it off
how do we know
we're gonna turn it back on?
- I'd rather be
dead in the water
then literally
dead in the water.
Wouldn't you?
Teplov, grab that wheel.
- Fuck that, no.
- God damn it.
Listen, I have been
smiling through
your bullshit for
two and a half years.
Do you see me smilin' now?
Look, you're not
my boss anymore.
Down here what I say goes.
You can try to stop me but
I wouldn't recommend it.
Do we have ourselves
an understanding?
You gravy?
- Gravy.
- Three, two, one.
- Jackson.
- What the?
All right, that's it.
Fuck this thing.
I want off this God damn ride.
- Sweet mother of mercy.
Not again.
- What?
What do you mean not again?
What, is there somethin'
you're not tellin' me Bigelow?
- German sailor on bridge.
- And you didn't say anything?
- It was Sinclair's
idea all right?
He told us not to say anything
until we knew what it meant.
- It meant somethin'
bad Bigelow.
Damn, I mean dead bodies
usually mean somethin' bad.
- That's two weeks old at least.
- I've had worse.
- Ah.
- Oi, Jackson?
Why'd you turn the engines off?
- Had to.
The boiler was about to blow.
- We could've
discussed it first, mate.
- That's what I said.
- I made the call.
I made the call
just like you did
about the dead
body on the bridge.
- What?
- Decapitated, right?
With all the funky veins
runnin' through it?
Well there's more down in
the engine room burned alive.
- I didn't wanna cause
a panic, Jackson.
- We need to be able to
trust each other, Sinclair.
- Yeah we do, Jackson.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Stop.
While I appreciate your
decision making Mr. Jackson,
and your discretion,
Mr. Sinclair,
right now we have food,
clothing and shelter
and it appears we have this
entire boat to ourselves.
Our present predicament is
far better than yesterday's.
Who knows what
tomorrow may bring, hey?
So for now let's eat.
"An army marches
on its stomach."
- Hang on.
Did you just make that up?
- I think you'll find
that's Napoleon Bonaparte.
- You need to eat too Mr.
Faraday, keep your strength up.
- You are an absolute
angel Miss Prescott.
- Yeah, and don't choke on it.
- Sorry Miss Prescott.
- I'm sorry too.
- Can I at least buy you dinner?
Wehrmacht's finest.
Thank you Mr. Sinclair.
- Look, there's no um...
- You don't like fish mate?
- There's no ring.
- That's all you're
getting mate.
Could you
possibly open this?
Yes mate.
- What was it?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Some kind of
child or somethin'.
- A child?
Yeah, a child who
scared the shit out of me.
Okay come
on, come on guys.
Oh.
Someone hacked
the lifeboats to bits.
- Excuse me?
Why would he do that?
- So nobody could leave.
- Hey, please don't
think about it Ivan.
- Gasoline.
- He's right.
It smells like fuel.
Marvellous.
So, so, mad captain
loses his marbles,
gets a bit axe
happy with his men,
sets them on fire
and then sabotages
their only means of escape.
Not to mention ours.
- Shut up Faraday.
- Yeah.
- But then who did this to him?
- Rats.
Big rats.
Miss Prescott?
- Hello darling.
Is this yours?
Don't be scared.
It's all right.
Ow.
Did she bite you?
It's fine.
Just a scratch.
- Little monster.
- Who knows how long she's
been here on her own,
or what she's been
through poor thing.
It's okay.
We're scared too.
We're
not gonna hurt you.
- That's family.
- What's that?
- Uh, sounds Italian.
Somethin' about family.
Family is.
- Okay, so she's
speakin' Italian?
- No, no, no, no it just,
not it's not Italian.
It just sounds similar.
- Romanian.
I recognise it.
- Hey, once bitten...
- It's okay.
Oh.
Hm.
- What is that?
That looks old.
Looks like it's worth somethin'.
What?
Well, clearly he
doesn't need it.
Now we're talkin'.
Oh.
- Nothing broken
and nothing bruised?
Nasty.
Any bullets?
- About half a dozen maybe.
- Wanna trade?
- Nice try.
- You're okay, hm?
Jane.
Yes, that's me, Jane.
- Mya.
- I'm sorry, what is happening?
- She wants us to follow her.
- You're honestly gonna go
following some
little brat around?
What on earth's she doing
here you bloody fools?
- That's what we're
going to find out.
Come on Gerard.
- Something
happened on this ship,
the ship that you forced me onto
and now despite
all logic and reason
you're gonna go
casually exploring.
No.
I'll have none of this.
I mean, look at him.
He loves casual exploring.
- Yeah.
Well uh, why don't you
hang out with old skipper?
Looks like he uh,
loves antiques mate.
- You want us to go down there?
Faraday?
- Wait for me.
- What's Romanian for how
many Nazis are down there?
- Bigelow, why don't you
stay up here with Faraday?
- I like this idea.
- I agree.
- Hey.
- No wait, Mya?
Mya?
Mya, you can't just run off
like that, it's dangerous.
Don't shit yourself.
- Oh I won't.
- God damn.
- Wait.
Yeah, I wouldn't
touch it if I were you.
Gasoline.
- Hey, what is it?
What is it?
- Come down and
see for yourself.
- I'll be damned.
- Jerry! It's a goddamn Kraut!
- We gotta open it.
- Eh, naw.
No we don't.
- I think they're gonna open it.
- Blithering idiots.
Are you barking mad?
You've got no
idea what's in there.
It could be a trap.
- You know, I'm
startin' to think
that shortbread
here has got a point.
- Look, put a lid on it Bigelow.
This man knows what
happened on this ship.
I'd like to know as
well, wouldn't you?
Americana?
- Yeah, yeah Americana, yeah.
- You are Australian.
- He doesn't know
the difference mate.
- We're going to open the door.
Do you understand?
- I can't say.
Yeah.
Sure you wanna do this?
- Yeah.
Yeah I do.
- You want me to take gun?
- I got it.
- If you have to
shoot, don't miss.
- If it comes to it, I won't.
- Relax.
Okay.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait!
- Put it down.
What's happening?
Shut up.
- Okay, look at me.
- What?
What?
- Yeah.
Relax.
Hey, yeah look at me.
Put the gun down.
Jackson?
- Shit.
- Yeah?
Calm down, calm down.
Jackson, relax.
- We wanna talk, yeah?
Calm down, calm down.
- Kind tricks?
- Kind, kind tricks.
No tricks.
Yeah.
Okay.
Looks like we're
gettin' somewhere.
- That beast!
That beast!
- Huh?
- Put it down!
- Shoot him.
- What's he sayin' Sinclair?
- He's spooked.
- Well no shit.
- Do it!
- Sinclair!
- It's jammed.
Well, I'd
better get out of the way.
- Where you goin'?
- Shoot him!
Shoot him!
- Jackson?
- Bloody Jesus, is
anybody alive down there?
Oh man.
- Oh.
- Anything else up your sleeve?
Here.
Bigelow?
- You're shot.
- I'm fine.
Bigelow?
- Gravy buddy.
Gravy.
- Not safe.
Just wait.
What was he so afraid of?
- Hey ho, can I have a gun?
- You can have the knife.
- Actually, I'm okay.
Suit yourself.
Well, it looks like Fritz was
plannin' on stayin' awhile.
- Yeah.
Home sweet home.
We need
to apply pressure.
I've had
worse.
This'll work.
Here you go.
- Sweet mother Mary.
Hey Sinclair?
We're gonna be rich.
- Why?
No we won't.
You gotta hold off on
the celebrations mate.
- Yeah, but this is
what I'm talkin' about.
This is what I've
been talkin' about man.
This is it.
This is lady luck is
finally smilin' down on us.
- Ain't worth Buckley's
if we don't make it home.
What in the devil?
We maybe wanna
keep this to ourselves?
- Oh yeah, 'cause that
worked so well last time.
Actually, you know what?
I'm actually okay with that.
We can keep this to ourselves.
- It's just a little bit of
blood Mya, he'll be fine.
- Teplov, big enough?
Here you go.
Thank you.
- No, no sorry.
No one.
- Yeah uh, just a
couple of old boxes.
- Yeah.
Looks like Fritz
was all on his own.
- Well, that's good yes?
- Yeah.
Except we still don't know why.
- Oh, well first thing's first.
I need to get
Alexander to a sickbay.
Mya, stop dawdling, hm?
Once I get that bullet out
you'll need just a few stitches.
- What I need is a drink.
- You and me both.
- Ought to take the sting off.
- Did you see where Gerard went?
- Screw him.
He's a deserter.
- Wouldn't want
us to look for you?
- I wouldn't go runnin'
off in the first place.
- I'm gonna head back to
the captain's quarters.
I'll keep an eye
out for Faraday.
Got one left, if you need it.
Come on Bigelow.
- I never liked these things.
Now, this may sting a little.
- You think that
buckle head down there
just locked himself in there
just to get away
from his captain?
- Don't know.
- You know, I heard flyboys
talkin' about gremlins
causing all kinds of
trouble for the aircrafts.
It's givin' me the heebie
jeebies just thinkin' about it.
- Gremlins?
- Yeah, gremlins.
- There you go.
That's the worst part over.
- You know, whatever
happened on this ship,
it wasn't gremlins.
It was somethin' far more real.
And ever strange.
- Please, please, please.
Come on, come on,
come on, come on.
- Man look.
Fritz from downstairs.
I've seen this before.
What's this insignia?
- That's some Nazi
voodoo shit right there.
That thing's huge.
What is that?
That some kind of safe?
- These bastards were makin' off
with a fortune and
artwork and artefacts.
- Maybe that was in
those crates downstairs.
Maybe that was...
Maybe there's gold and jewels.
Yeah, nice little Nazi nest egg.
Seemed like it.
- Do you think her family's
here on this vessel?
- I don't know.
If there's one thing this war's
good for it's making orphans.
- Surely?
Wait.
Yes.
Come on.
Mayday.
Can anyone hear me?
Is anybody there?
Mayday.
You said
you had a family?
- Yeah.
The Nazis, they
come for my village.
They shoot the old, the weak.
They killed my
father in front of me.
They uh, take my
mother and sister.
I knew I would not
be seeing them again.
- I'm so sorry.
All done.
Let's see how this is going.
- Your daughter?
How old was she?
- She would've been 12
this year but the blitz.
It's impossible not
to be reminded of her.
You know, part of me's scared of
this war ending
because then I'll go home.
And she won't be
there waiting for me.
My husband, he's lost in Africa.
I know he won't be coming back.
This bloody war,
takes everything from
you, gives you nothing back.
- What were they up to?
What the hell is this?
Hey Bigelow, look.
Oi?
Bigelow?
- Sorry Mr. Jackson but to
the victor go the spoils.
Oh.
Lady luck, you are
one beautiful minx.
I hustled my way out of a war
and I'm still gonna
come out on top.
- Bigelow?
Bigelow?
- Get fucked.
Bigelow!
- Yes Mya, we'll keep
looking I promise you.
Mya?
- Miss Prescott?
Hey, hey, hey.
You okay?
- Mya, she--
Hey?
- She...
- I know.
I need to show you somethin'.
- Mayday.
Um, mayday.
Can anyone hear me?
Mayday.
Yes, yes, yes I can hear you.
- Um, English, English.
Uh...
Speak the English better.
English?
- Yes.
Yes.
I'm English.
I'm, I'm on one of your vessels.
Anyone else on board?
- Everybody's dead.
The captain went
mad I'm telling you.
What is your position?
- Oh, um...
Somewhere...
It's somewhere in
the North Atlantic.
I don't know.
I'm not a navigator.
Come in English.
- My name is Gerard Faraday,
and I am a code breaker
with British Intelligence.
If you help me,
if you rescue me,
I can provide you
with vital information,
classified information.
Listen my name is Gerard--
- We will send help English.
Stay on the radio.
We will attempt to
triangulate your position.
- Thank God.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- My guess is uh, they
brought these caskets onboard.
One of these things got
out, slaughtered the crew.
Mya.
- Yeah, she was the
only one on the ship.
The captain must've figured
out what was goin' on.
Killed as many as he could.
Wrecked the life boats,
turned the ship off course.
It's these monsters.
This is what killed Bigelow.
This ugly bastard.
- Please, please.
It's, it's not possible.
Strigoi.
- What?
- Strigoi.
Fairytales.
Something my
grandfather used to tell us.
- This isn't exactly
a fairytale Alexander.
- Strigoi is the living dead.
Shape shifters.
They, they, they
move by night, hunting.
Changing shape and appearance.
They command armies of
animals and insects.
That's what bedtime stories
to, to frighten children.
- Alexander?
Alex?
Hey?
Did these bedtime stories,
did they tell you how
to kill the bastards?
Yeah?
- These uh, holy weapons.
Relics and stuff.
- There's a box of this
stuff down in the cargo hold.
It's locked in there with
the one that killed Bigelow.
- Okay.
So, only little girl
we have to worry about.
- And Faraday.
He's still out there on his own.
- Let's hope he's as
smart as he thinks he is.
- Faraday?
Faraday?
- Gerard?
Gerard?
- Faraday?
- Gerard?
- Hey?
Gerard?
- Gerard?
- You know nothing of death.
We must show you what it
means to embrace death.
To welcome it,
with open arms.
- It is your nature to fear
what you do not understand.
- Gerard, stop.
- Faraday?
- It is not Faraday.
Strigoi.
- Wait!
Wait!
Wait.
- Teplov.
- Do it!
Do it.
- You are already dead.
You simply do not know it yet.
- Do it!
- Why?
- You stabbed me.
- Just breathe Gerard, breathe.
I'll get you to sickbay.
You'll be right as rain.
Where are we?
- You're going home Gerard.
- It's autumn there now.
- You did what you had to do.
What is this?
- It's a big fucker.
- All of this because
of one little girl.
What if this big one gets out?
We
can't let it happen.
- Let's end this.
Mya?
Mya, where are you?
- Mommy?
- Milly?
- Mommy, I'm scared.
Mommy, please?
- That's my
daughter, that's her.
- You can save me this time.
- Milly?
It's not her.
- No!
- Mommy let me out please!
- Let me in!
- You can save me this
time mommy, please!
- Let go of me!
- It's not her!
It's not your daughter.
Do it.
Do it!
- Miss Prescott?
I'll meet you at the
captain's quarters.
- Right, that'll do.
Sinclair?
- Miss Prescott?
Miss Prescott?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Strigoi.
Nathan?
- Jane?
- Nathan?
I'm waiting for you.
Come to me my darling.
I've been waiting so long.
So long.
- Shelly?
- Come back to me husband.
Come.
Come back to me husband.
We'll be together again.
- But that other fella?
I thought I lost you.
- I'm right here.
- I've been waiting a long time.
- Sinclair!
Sinclair?
- Wait for me.
What are you doing?
Why?
- They are not
so easy to kill, no?
- Not so easy to kill, no.
- You hurt?
I've been through worse.
Miss Prescott?
Ship.
- The flare.
Teplov, again.
Signal the ship.
- No, that was last one.
What if it is German, hm?
- Better for the Nazis.
Piece of piss mate.
Strigoi.
We can't let the
Strigoi off the ship.
We won't.
- We gotta find Miss Prescott.
- Find Miss Prescott,
signal ship, kill Strigoi.
- What's your plan?
- We blow it up.
We blow up ship.
- We find Miss Prescott.
- Jackson, he said chain
reaction could blow up ship.
We get to munitions room,
we detonate shell,
blow up boiler, boom.
- You're right, boom.
- Yeah?
- You're as mad as a cut snake.
- Piece of piss mate.
- That looks promising.
Got another plan?
- Open door.
- Teplov and
Sinclair: Kill Strigoi.
- All right, well I've been
killin' monsters for years.
A few more won't hurt.
Can't promise you're not
gonna get anymore scars.
- Yeah, more
scars, more stories.
- That's the spirit.
Wanna trade?
- No.
- Hey.
Now we know what happened
to the crew.
- And what we will happen to me.
- What?
- Bite marks like this.
- No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, naw.
- I think when Strigoi attack,
what doesn't kill you
makes you one of them.
So--
- So no, come on.
- No, no, no, no,
- Come on!
- no, no, no, no.
You go all right?
You find Miss Prescott.
I will set off explosion.
- No, no.
- Yes.
- No.
Please.
- Mate.
- I hope you see
your wife again.
No.
I hope she's happy.
You tell her baby,
there are not so many
monsters in the world today,
as there were yesterday.
Okay?
You tell her.
- Whoa!
Jane?
Come on, come on, come on!
- No, Nathan!
- Come on.
What?
- No.
- What?
- Oh, are you all right?
- It's not my blood.
Come on, come on, come on.
- No, Nathan?
What?
What's wrong?
Come on.
We're not beat yet.
We ain't beat yet.
Come on!
We gotta find the ship.
Come on.
- Jane come on.
Come on, Teplov's
gonna blow the ship.
- What?
- Come on.
We don't have time.
Come on!
I can see it!
We have to jump.
- No, I can't.
We
don't have a choice.
- You have to leave me.
- What are you talking about?
- No!
- Miss Prescott?
Miss Prescott?
Miss?
Look, look a ship!
It's a ship.
Miss Prescott?
It's British.
Hey, hey!
Hey!
You okay?
Let the
medic through.
Stand aside
gentlemen, give her a hand.
- There.
- Bring this there.
- You're safe now Miss.
Did anybody else
make it off alive?
- No.
Only me.
This bloody war.