Subtitles by explosiveskull
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- What the hell happened?
- It was a rabbit.
You nearly killed us
for a rabbit?
Well, you wouldn't want me
to kill it, would ya?
Oh, babe, I don't care about
the stupid little bunny,
you nearly killed us.
What was that?
Pigs. Lots of pigs.
Oh, look, there's another one,
still trotting along.
What are they doing?
I don't know,
maybe something startled them.
Yeah, babe, like what?
Maybe there's a hunter
out there.
What the FUCK was that?
OK, let's get out of here!
- Ah, how's it going, mate?
- Not bad at all, mate.
Did you hear about Bernie?
Bank's trying to foreclose
on the poor bastard.
I heard. Bunch of snot-nosed
assholes, if you ask me.
- Too right.
- They just don't get it.
I mean, if they'd get out
of their fancy city offices
and come down here,
they'd understand we're in
the middle of a bloody drought.
Hey, mate, the ah, Genny.
The lid.
Anyway, what about yourself,
mate? Knocking a few over?
Not even trying, mate.
I've been doing
a bit of fencing.
Something's been
tearing the fences down there
at old Patterson's farm there.
- Oh, yeah.
- Keeping me busy though, eh?
Hey, hang on, what's that?
Is that Bob?
Yeah, that's him.
Look at the old bastard.
Get a fucking job,
youse poofters.
Jesus.
That old bloody pisspot,
I mean, he shouldn't be
driving around anymore.
He reckons the same thing's
happening up at his farm too.
- Yeah? What's that?
- Ah, knocked down fences.
He's down a few sheep too.
- Yeah?
- Something's killed them, yeah.
What, all nine of them?
He's probably stewed 'em up
and forgotten about it.
I mean, look at him...
he's a hundred mile
of bad bloody road.
Hey, Gail's daughter works
for the quack.
She reckons he's been
diagnosed with dementia,
so I wouldn't be
at all surprised.
I couldn't give a fuck because
I've got things to do, alright,
I've got places to go,
I've got to go to work.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- I've got a fair drive ahead.
Alright, alright.
See you in the pub though?
Ah, yeah, ah, maybe.
I don't know.
Ah, bastard.
Brucey!
Sure you don't want me
to drive, Bruce?
No, no, I'm fine,
I'm fine.
- You sure?
- Yeah, oh, yeah.
Come on, Bruce, just let Robbie
drive for a while.
Yeah, maybe that's
a good idea.
We'll get in the back
and we'll make out.
Well, that sounds good.
I'll pull over for that.
Mum, that's gross.
You are not doing that
while I'm in the car.
Well, actually, sweetheart,
Bruce and I make out all
the time, even in the car.
- Mm-hm!
- Blah!
Yeahhh!
Come on, let your parents
have some fun.
We can have the front
to ourselves.
Remember when you did that thing
when I was driving to Sydney?
Um, you'd better not
be doing that.
It's called a blowjob, Mum.
I don't care what it's called,
you don't do that while
you're driving, it's dangerous.
I was actually talking about
this other thing that she does.
Kind of tickles.
- She does it with her tongue.
- She does.
You are such an asshole, Bart!
Takes one to know one.
Ow! Fucking dick!
I wasn't talking about blowjobs,
you little shit.
- Oh, guys, stop it!
- Oh, sorry, babe.
OK, cabin fever has officially
set in.
I don't know about you guys
but I'm hungry enough to eat the
crotch out of a low-flying duck.
What? What the fuck
did he just say?
It's the ass
out of a low-flying duck.
Robbie!
It sounds so shit
when he says it.
Well, hey, look,
I'm doing the best I can here.
You're trying.
I suggest the next town
we pull over and get some grub.
- Good idea.
- Sounds great, Bruce.
You want to stop so you can give
Robbie a little tongue tickle.
Hey, Bart. Bart.
- WHAT?
- You a virgin?
Robert, stop it, OK.
He's saving himself for the
right woman, aren't you, baby?
Hey, Bart, you can't be a virgin
because your face is fucked.
OK, we're pulling over.
- Thank fuck for that.
- Robbie.
Sorry, Deb.
- Morning, possum.
- Morning.
Hey, Dad, those folks look
familiar to you?
Oh, look at the ass on that,
would ya, eh?
Like two possums fighting
in a paper bag.
Dad!
Which reminds me,
are those jeans tight enough
on you, do you reckon?
Ha, ha, ha.
Bugger me.
Can you put a leash on it,
old man?
She's way too young for you.
Here.
If you can still raise
your sword,
you're still in the fight.
Yeah, well, stop your perving
and come give me a hand,
it's almost 10 o'clock.
- Get a room, you two.
- Ha, ha, I would if I could.
Hi.
Young lady, you wouldn't have
a smoke on you, would you?
Sorry, I don't smoke.
Vape then. You look like a lady
who does vapour.
No smokes, no vapes.
I tell you what, though.
Here.
This ought to buy you
a pack of smokes.
Oi! Here ya, boss.
Cheers, mate.
Ernie's the name.
Robert. Nice to meet ya.
Well, that was
a waste of 20 bucks.
And he owns a drilling company.
Got to be fucking joking.
That was really sweet of you,
baby.
You just gave $20 to probably
the richest man in town.
Are you mocking me?
Maybe he'll give it to charity
or something.
- Well, I'll be fucked.
- Will you rein it in?
No, no, no, they're familiar.
It's been years
but we do know them.
Oh, yeah, well, who are they?
Don't keep me in suspense.
Yeah, well, see that blonde
sheila walking with that bloke?
Yeah, well, that's Debbie
Monroe, Bernie's sister,
so they'd have to be her kids,
Ella and, ah...
- Oh, um, Bart.
- Bart!
- Holy shit, haven't they grown!
- Yeah, well, they don't shrink.
I don't know
who the two blokes are.
Hey, didn't Debbie's first
husband leave her or something?
Yeah, something like that.
So they're obviously going over
to see Bernie.
Maybe Debbie's here to help him
keep the farm.
How'd you know about the farm?
Dad, I own a pub,
I know everyone's business.
Point taken.
Hey, look, I'd like to stay here
and chat to you for hours
but I've got work to do. Mwah.
- Oh.
- See you, possum.
Thanks for your help.
I'd be fucked without ya!
Watch out!
What the hell, Bruce!
- What was that?
- What a fucking idiot!
- Oh, Jesus.
- Where's my chocolate?
Oh.
10-second rule?
OK.
- Can I have some KitKat?
- No.
Oh, my God, look at you!
Oh, my God!
Oh, I've missed you so much.
Are you taller?
Fuck me, you weren't kidding.
He's a giant.
- Your mum's a walking headjob.
- Shh.
That's my mother
you're talking about.
Yeah, but look at her.
Little Ella bo Bella!
Yeah, Uncle Bernie, it's me.
Oh, my little buddy!
I've missed you so much.
- Hey, it's a nice place.
- Yeah.
Look at the lambs.
Do you reckon he eats them?
- Yeah, probably.
- And who's this?
Uncle Bernie, this is
my boyfriend, Robert.
Be nice.
Hey.
I can crush skulls
with my bare hands.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too, mate.
Just mucking with you.
Yeah.
Good to see you're still around,
Bruce.
What can I say? Deb makes a mean
sponge cake.
Good to see you, Bernie.
Alright.
- Good to see you too.
- Yes.
Come on,
let's go and get some grub.
Are you guys coming?
Oh, yeah.
He's a great guy but you
don't want to piss him off.
- He can be a mean bastard.
- Got that from the handshake.
Yeah. Welcome to the family.
You'd better not be shagging
the old labrador at Patto's.
Whisky!
Come here, boy!
Where you at, boy?
Whisky!
WHISKY!
Come on, boy.
Come here, boy!
Whisky, come here, boy.
Leave him alone, you bastard!
Leave him alone!
Whisky, come here, boy!
Come here!
Ken, mate,
are you there?
Barely. It's as hot as a tomcat
with four balls out here.
What do you want?
Oh, look, mate,
I'm going a bit soft.
I thought I'd come out and give
you a hand, if you like.
Ah, you just want my body.
Well, grab your swag and some
ice and a few beers, eh?
OK.
I'll stop at the pub and I'll
put them on your account, huh?
Oh, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Hey, tell Sasha I won't be back
till late morning,
something like that, alright?
Not a problem, bud.
See you soon, matey.
Yeah, I can hardly wait.
- Asshole.
- Roger that.
Fuck was that?
There you go.
- Oh, yes, you have.
- No, no.
- There you go, darling.
- Good on you.
What time do you call this?
- What did I tell you?
- What?
No, I've got no tab.
I thought you had the tab.
Nah, nah, nah. Nah.
I'm not paying for it.
I'm not paying for it either.
Hey, Sash, when's that
spunky father of yours
gonna ask me out on a date?
You ask me that same
bloody question every week
and I give you the same answer.
You're way too much
for my old man to handle.
She's right. He wouldn't last
five minutes with you.
That's way too much information.
Yeah, you're right.
I need a virile man
who can handle a cougar like me.
Kind of makes me wish
I wasn't camping out tonight.
- G'day, Bluey.
- G'day, how are you going?
Whoa, Blue, don't encourage her.
Let me guess. Dad sent you in
here for beer and food, right?
Well, he didn't say food,
but now that you mention it.
Mm-hm. Well, you know where
the cold room is.
I'm not your bloody slave.
Off you go.
Alright, alright. God.
And whose account
am I putting this on?
- Do you really have to ask?
- Put it on Dad's tab, right?
Rack one up for me
on there too, eh?
- You can bloody pay for yours.
- Well, you can put it on ours.
No, you two can bloody shut up.
Don't let Dad get too pissed
and make sure he eats
something this time.
- Is that enough food?
- We'll eat every last crust.
Here, you'd better take these
too.
Dad likes a treat after dinner.
I could give him
an after-dinner treat.
You're such a bloody tart!
Well, on that note,
I'm out of here
but I'll catch you tomorrow.
Be safe.
Don't get too pissed.
Ah, we will and we will.
Yeah, I know you bloody will,
you pair of old drunks.
I swear the worst thing I did
was buy a pub.
See ya.
Do you think this is
a good idea?
Mm-hm. Best idea I've had,
like, ever, maybe.
I don't want Matt and Sheri
to hear us.
Then be quiet.
Mmm.
- Oh, I tell you what.
- Mm?
You go and get me a drink
and make sure that Matt
and Sheri are not outside
and I might let you have
a quickie.
Promise?
After all, we don't want
your balls exploding.
- Could get really messy.
- Yes.
Ah! I'm alright.
So graceful!
Oh. Oh, bugger.
I was bloody enjoying that.
Jesus Christ.
It's just dropping everywhere.
Sasha's a good cook, eh?
She's just like her mother.
She's JUST like her mother.
Yeah. She was amazing,
wasn't she, Maryanne?
Mm.
How long since she's gone, mate?
15 years.
15 long years since I buried
my fucking heart.
What's that?
What do you see?
Is that a spot fire?
A camp fire, I think.
I can just make out a few tents.
Oh!
Jesus, how much of that bloody
carton did you drink, mate?
A lot more than you, mate.
You've been drinking
like a fucking woman.
That Wendy and Anna
could drink you under the table
tonight, I reckon.
Ah, bullshit.
What the bloody hell
do you think they're doing
camping out here?
I don't reckon they got
permission.
What do you reckon
they're up to then?
Oh, what do you reckon
we go and find out, eh?
Oh, bullshit, mate, I mean it's
nice and warm and cosy here.
Jesus Christ.
Oh, mate, mate. OK, we'll take
the truck, we'll drive.
- I'm too drunk to drive, mate.
- Yeah, bullshit.
You're too drunk to drive,
you're not too drunk to sling a
bloody rifle over your shoulder.
Oh, for fuck's sake.
Oh, you fucking prick,
wait a minute,
I'll get some bloody piss
to take with us.
You carry on like an old fucking
woman, you do.
Hang about, mate,
where's the bloody sandwiches?
- Oh, for fuck's sake.
- What about a torch, mate?
Hurry up, princess.
You'll end up bringing the whole
camp, the way you're going on.
Mate, it'll take us
a bloody hour to walk.
We're just going
for a little walk.
It's not going to kill you.
Come on.
For Christ's sake!
Girl Guide.
Ryan, is that you?
Ryan, don't be an ass.
It isn't funny.
Oh, you're such an asshole.
Screw cutting you off
for tonight,
I'm cutting you off
for the entire month!
Oh, Ryan, where are you?
Please tell me it's you
out there.
Please.
Ryan?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Is it just me
or does that campfire
seem to be getting
further and further away?
We're past halfway, old mate.
Stop your bellyaching.
I'm not as young
as I used to be, mate.
The furthest I walk these days
is from the bar to the shitter.
Which reminds me,
I was in the pub today
and I saw Anna and Wendy.
They wanted to come out camping
with us.
Oh, Christ.
Young Sasha put a stop to it,
though.
Well, thank fuck for that
because I wouldn't touch
either of them
if they were the last living
pussy on the planet.
You'd end up with a crutch
full of herpes
or fucking dick rot.
Come on, let's get going.
What, you reckon
they've got a dose?
I'd bet my left lung on it,
mate.
Shit! Hope you're bloody joking,
matey.
I'm not joking.
Ah, Christ.
Come on, poxy balls, hurry up.
Hey, hey, did you hear that?
That was a scream, wasn't it?
Yeah, definitely a scream, mate.
What do you see?
What do you see, mate?
What the fuck is that?
Either I'm pissed off my chest,
mate,
or that's the biggest
fucking boar I've ever seen.
Here, you're a better shot
than me. You take a look.
Holy Mary, Mother of God!
That is a monster!
Well, shoot the fucking thing!
- Please tell me you got it.
- No, mate.
- No, it's... it's... it's gone.
- Oh, shit.
Mate, we've got to get back to
the bloody truck and get help.
No, mate, we're much closer to
them than we are to the truck.
We've got to find them and
we'll take one of their cars.
Mate, whoever was down there
before
is not there any bloody more!
Mate, we have got to try,
you know,
we've got to go and fucking
find out, for Christ's sake!
Oh, Jesus.
Jesus Christ!
Ohhhhh.
Jesus Christ.
Ken, look, mate, look.
Oh, mate, I'm not fucking blind.
I can see, alright?
What the fuck is happening here?
Oh, Jesus, look at that.
She's...
Blue, she's...
They're... they're
just kids, mate.
Ahh... there's more of them.
- How do you know?
- There's two tents, right?
I mean, they're not going to
come out here and go camping
and sleep in separate tents,
are they, you know?
So, ah, well, judging by this,
um...
..this, ah, this girl, mate,
..I-I reckon that they would've
been sleeping in that tent
and the other kids must've
took off
when that bloody big pig
attacked.
Now, give me that, give me that.
Here.
Oh, Christ.
We don't have any bullets, mate.
- What?
- I haven't loaded the mag.
Oh, shit. Why didn't you bloody
check it, you stupid bastard?
- Well, because...
- No fucking bullets!
How was I to know we were
going to find a fucking pig
the size of a fucking rhino?
Jesus Christ.
Blue, you're going to have to go
back to the truck, mate.
I-I got bullets in the glovebox
and-and I'll stay here and see
if I can find these kids.
No, no. Fuck that, mate.
I'm not leaving you on your own
and I'm not walking back there
by myself either.
Blue, I got no bullets.
We are sitting ducks if that
monster fucking comes back here.
You've gotta go back
to the truck, you know.
I am not leaving those kids
out in the bush by themselves.
You know, they'll be scared
fucking shitless.
So you've got to get going.
Well, what are you waiting for?
Blue, look, you can do this.
You'll be back in half the time.
When was the last time
you went for a jog?
Alright, I'll go back
to the bloody truck, mate.
But you look around, see if
there's a bloody car here,
get in the bastard
and pick me up
because, mate, we're both
dead men without a bloody rifle.
So it's weapons first, then we
look for the bloody kids, right?
Righto, mate, I'll-I'll do my
best, I'll look around, OK,
but you just get going, OK?
- Take the bloody torch.
- No, you-you...
No, I don't need
the fucking torch, you know.
I can build the fire up.
You take it.
- Go on, go on, get going.
- I'm gone, bloody piss off.
- Oh, Blue. Blue!
- What?
Mate, go as fast as you can
but find a big
motherfucking stick
and grab it just in case,
alright?
Got it!
Jesus H. Christ.
Oh, oh, Jesus.
What's that?
Hey! Are you the kids
from the camp back there?
You fucking dingoes!
Oh, Jesus! Fuck!
Oh, Jesus.
Oh, shit!
What the...?
Ohh.
Holy Jesus Christ.
Oh, Jesus.
I know you're out there.
I know you're out there!
I know you're there.
Oh, Jesus.
Come and get me!
Oh, you feral fuck.
Oh, Jesus!
Oh, oh!
You asshole, where are you?
Come on!
Come on. Come on.
Come and get me.
Come and get me, you bastard.
Where's your bloody car?
Matthew.
Where are you, Matthew?
I hope you know
how to get back to camp.
Yeah, it's just up here a bit.
Don't panic, it's probably just
Ryan and Hanna mucking around.
That is something Ryan would do.
I want to tell you about this
Yara-ma-yha-who.
Come sit down here for a bit.
So, the Yara-ma-yha-who, right,
he's like a little red man,
alright,
and he kind of looks a bit like
a demon, yeah?
And he doesn't have any teeth,
which is weird for a vampire.
And his skin's all glossy,
like... like silk.
Anyway, he climbs up high
into the trees
to stalk his victims.
You know, he moves like a monkey
in the trees, ooh, ooh, ooh.
But he doesn't make a sound.
He watches them closely,
sizing them up.
And then he stalks them
and stands right above them,
right above his next meal.
Then, when he's ready,
he jumps,
wrapping these octopus-like
tentacles around his victims,
sucking all the blood
out of them.
Now he can dislocate his jaw,
too, like a snake,
so he can swallow his victims
whole.
Then, when he's finished
his meal, he rests,
lets it all settles down
in his stomach.
And then when he wakes up,
he immediately regurgitates
everything back up
onto the floor
and there in a pile
of muck and goo
is a baby newborn
Yara-ma-yha-who.
Firstly, that is disgusting.
Did you hear that?
I'm not going to sleep or eat
for a week now.
- Secondly...
- Seriously, shh for a second.
I heard something.
Hand me the torch.
I'm not handing you the torch.
I think there's a wild pig
out here.
Of course there is.
There was drop bears,
drop possums
and some ridiculous
outback vampire
and now wild pigs
are stalking us!
I'm serious.
Give me the bloody torch!
Your story doesn't make sense.
What do you mean?
Your drop vampire yeti story,
it doesn't make any sense.
It's not my story.
It's an Aboriginal legend.
Ryan. Is that you?
Sheridan, we have to be quiet
for a sec.
- Why?
- Just sh-sh-sh.
Well, I was always told that
drop bears hang from the trees
and when their claws come down,
they hook into your head
and reef you off the ground.
I am serious! Shut the fuck up!
Calm down, babe.
That was really rude.
I'm sorry. I just need you to be
quiet for a sec, OK?
I'm going to turn the light out.
What?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Fuck me!
Sheri!
SHERI!
Help me!
Somebody help!
Let her go!
What the fuck?!
What the fuck?
Oh, shit!
Hey, honey,
you breathing over there?
Come on, one of you be OK.
Oh, Jesus.
Oh, Jesus, Jesus.
Ah. So sorry, sweetheart.
Oh, shhhhh, it's all right,
it's all right, it's all right.
- You don't have to talk.
- It's not a drop bear.
No, yeah, I know.
What's-what's your name?
Sh... Sheridan.
Yeah? My name's Ken, hey?
Now, just try and relax.
You're in shock, sweetheart,
hey?
Now, I just need you
to stay calm
to help me, alright. Hey?
OK?
Is Matt OK?
No, no, not really, he's not.
It's you that we've got to worry
about now, though, eh?
Sheridan, Sheridan,
you've got to be still, OK,
and very, very quiet.
I need you to be as quiet
as possible, OK?
I know it hurts.
But...
..I need you to be...
..nice and still.
And I'll lead him
away from here.
- No! No!
- No, no, it's-it's... it's OK.
It's OK. I've been doing this
since I was a kid.
Yeah?
I've been doing this
since I was a little kid.
Hey!
Come on, come on, you mongrel!
You're the pig, I'm the big bad
fucking wolf!
That's right, ugly guts,
come on, follow me!
Jesus!
Sheridan, Sheridan,
you've got to stand up.
You've got to stand, OK?
I've got to get you out.
Ohhhh.
Oh, Jesus.
Oh. I'm so sorry, little one.
I'm sor... I'm so sorry.
I'm coming, Maryanne.
Come on, you piece of shit!
Sashaaaa!
Mum, I don't think I could eat
another bite.
I'm ready to explode.
You're going to explode,
are you?
It's not for you, honey,
it's for Uncle Bernie.
He's already had three servings!
Elli, I'm a growing boy.
Yeah, 'boy's about right,
the way you chased Bart
to the bathroom this morning.
So, what's the plan for today,
Bernie?
I've been thinking we can take
a drive out to Patto's farm,
we can take a picnic lunch,
have a swim in the river,
when the sun starts to go down
we can do a bit of spotting.
- Yeah, let's go swimming.
- You want to go swimming?
Hey, Uncle Bernie, do you reckon
we could take some guns out?
- Maybe just...
- Deb.
Bart wants to know
if we can take some guns.
Bernie, you know how I feel
about guns.
I would think that out there
at least one for safety.
Not a bad idea, Bruce.
What do you say?
Just for safety, Debs?
You guys are full of it.
You just want to sneak about
in the bush like commandos
and shoot shit.
Well, I've seen Charlie's Farm.
I know there's creeps out there
ready to cut you up, rape you.
- Robbie!
- I can tell you right now,
all those hillbillies out there
will shoot you
before you step foot
on their property.
Well, I reckon I can shoot a can
at 50 meters.
- Probably 25. I don't know.
- Is that right?
And at the fair last year,
with the ducks,
you didn't shoot a single one
and they were two meters away?
Yeah, well, that game
was rigged.
Yet Bart hit three of them.
Three of them.
But the way you kept trying
to win me that teddy bear,
that was sweet.
I wasn't trying to win you shit,
I was trying to prove a point,
that the game was rigged.
Whatever.
And if I remember correctly,
you were the winner
at the end of the night.
That's right.
I was the winner, wasn't I?
Are you right?
So, how are we all going to get
out there, Bernie?
- The troopy, my friend.
- And what's a troopy?
Aw, what's a troopy!
Why the bloody hell did you
have to go and marry a Yank?
Bruce, it's the car we took
to the pub last night.
- I knew that!
- Yes, I know you did.
Thank you, sweetie.
What a knob.
I'm going to go
and put my swimmers on.
I'm going to join you. You guys
want to load up the car?
Ah, Mum, about the gun...
Alright, one gun.
Bernie, I mean it, just one.
Fine, fine, one gun.
Got it.
- Oh, fuck!
- Bernie!
Did I scare you, Bruiser?
You need to relax, city boy.
Too much pent-up tension.
Come on, Robbie.
Let's go and fill up
the cruiser.
- It's Robert.
- Nah, I like Robbie better.
Hey. Let him call you Robbie.
It's easier that way.
Come on, Bruiser.
Fill up the troopy.
The troopy!
Yeah, you like that, don't ya?
Seem like the kind of girl
who loves a good spanking.
Why don't you bend over and let
me stick my foot up your ass
and see how much you like that?
- Sounds kinky. I like it kinky.
- Damo!
Control your fucking mutt!
He's got a point.
You're being a fucking idiot.
I get it.
Let me make myself
very fucking clear
because I've just about had
enough of your fucking shit.
If you fucking touch me again
I'll rip off your arm and I'll
beat you to death with it.
How about I give you a free pass
for my indiscretion?
I'll let you hit me.
I won't try and stop you.
Come on, babe. Just let go
of some of that tension.
You stupid fuck!
Get the fuck out of my bar!
Go on! You're leaking
all over my floor, you asshole!
Fucking slut!
Who do you think you are?
You show her some fucking
respect, you little shit.
Get that sack of shit
out of here, Bernie.
He's stinking up my bar.
Yahoo!
What's he doing?
I think
he knocked him out.
- Did you see that? Holy shit!
- Ouch!
And that, Robert, is why
you let him call you Robbie.
Got it.
You alright, Sash?
- Yeah. What a dickhead.
- Yeah.
Hey, I had it under control,
you know.
I know you did. I was just
finishing it for you.
Ah, what a shot, big fella!
You shut up.
Thanks, love.
What can I get you?
I'm taking the family out
to Patto's for a swim.
I just might clean out
your fridge.
No worries.
What are you after?
Some of those doughnuts please,
Sash.
- And some chockies for Bart.
- Yeah, yeah. Of course, love.
How about drinks?
Yep. Just soft drinks.
That'd be wonderful.
- Can I get some ice too, there?
- Yeah, love, no worries.
Thank you.
Just give me $20, love,
that's fine.
Hey, if you see Dad out there,
can you get him to give me
a call?
He was out there with Blue
last night
and he was supposed to be back
this morning
but I haven't heard from them.
Sure. Was he working at Patto's
yesterday?
Yeah. I tried calling
his mobile phone
but I just got his
answering machine
but maybe they've got
no reception.
No worries, then.
If I see a pair of old drunks,
I'll send them home
with their tails
between their legs.
Thanks, darling.
- See you later, big fella.
- See you, mate.
- See you, Bernie.
Come on, tackle!
Hey, Bernie, be careful, dammit.
He's not going to hurt Bart.
He's too protective of him.
Yeah, I know but he doesn't know
his own strength.
If he's not careful,
Bart's going to end up
in one of those trees.
- Bernie, I mean it!
- Relax, sis.
Your mother's gone soft.
- Oh, hey!
- Yeah, that's mature.
Oh. I'll be taking off
for about half an hour.
What for?
Sasha said Ken and Blue
are out there somewhere.
She's a bit worried because
they didn't come home
when they said they would.
Well, how are you
going to find them?
Isn't this property
over 2 million acres?
I was talking to Ken
the other day.
He told me he was working down
the west fence.
That's only a few klicks
that way
so I'll take a quick run on the
fence line and check it out.
Want to go with him?
You want Bruce to go with you?
Nah.
Bruiser can stay here
and protect the family, mate.
No worries, mate.
I will stay here
and protect the family, Bern.
It's Bernie, mate. Not Bern.
Bernie.
Rightio, then.
- He scares me.
- Yep.
He scares everybody, that one.
Yo, VIP
Let's kick it
Ice, ice, baby
Alright, stop
Collaborate and listen
Ice is back
with my brand-new invention
Something grabs a hold of me
tightly
Flow like a harpoon
daily and nightly
Will it ever stop
yo, I don't know
Turn off the lights
and I glow
To the extreme
I rock a mic like a vandal...
Now that the party is jumping
With the bass kicked in
and the Vegas are pumping
Quick to the point
to the point no faking
I'm cooking MCs
like a pound of bacon
Burning them
we ain't quick and nimble
I go crazy
when I hear that cymbal
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
A hi-hat
with a souped-up tempo
I'm on a roll
Time to go...
Did you guys hear that?
I didn't hear anything.
Are you deaf? Yeah, I heard it.
It sounded like an explosion
or something.
- Didn't you hear it?
- No.
Yeah, yeah, it did.
I think I'm going to go
check it out.
Why?
I just want to.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Yeah, alright, well, take
one of the boys with you.
- I don't want to go.
- I'm not going that far.
It's just for safety, hon.
Take Robert.
Go on, baby.
You can finally play soldier.
Yeah, you'd love that,
wouldn't you, huh? Huh?
Give me a kiss. Another one.
- Hon, wait for Robert.
- Stop it.
Look after my boy, Bruce.
Hon, forgot your binoculars!
Fuck me!
I'm going to ask Elli
to marry me.
What?
How long have you guys been
going out, like 7, 8 months?
She's the one, Bruce.
When you know it, you know it.
Life's too short for what-ifs.
Did you tell Debbie?
No. Not yet.
I reckon she'll be pretty happy
though, don't you think?
Well, she likes you
so I should think so, yeah.
I mean, my only piece of advice
is make sure that's what
you guys want to do.
It is, mate.
A lot of times people jump in
when they're in that starry-eyed
phase and...
Yeah, well, we're adults, Bruce.
Well, you know, marriage is not
all fun and games.
You've got to be in it
for the long haul.
I am.
You know, I've been helping
to raise Elli for so long
I feel like her real father
and I just want you to know
that if you hurt her...
..I will hurt you back.
I wouldn't have it
any other way, Bruce.
You know, I don't want to get
all heavy here,
I don't want to piss
in your pocket
but, you know,
I don't know much about you,
I don't know about your
childhood or your parents.
What the hell does that have
to do with anything?
Well, it has everything
to do with it
because I want to make sure
that Elli is happy.
My parents were real good,
Bruce.
They were real good.
Well, that's good because
marriage is permanent.
Remind me, Bruce,
how many times
have you been married now?
Three times.
Yeah. Yeah, that's my point.
I'm the poster child
for what not to do.
Yeah.
Look... I'm sorry
if I pissed you off.
Don't worry about it.
Let's check up around that band
and then we'll go back, alright?
Yeah.
You right there, bub?
You look a bit out of sorts.
Ah, look, it's probably nothing,
Ernie,
but Dad and Blue camped out
last night
and Dad said he'd be back
first thing in the morning
and I haven't heard from him
all day.
I can't even get him
on the bloody phone.
You tried Blue's mobile?
I got his number here somewhere.
I tried them like 20, 30 times.
- The usual, love?
- Yes, please.
That's not like your dad.
I mean, he's alright, though.
He'll be alright.
There's nothing out there
except dust and roos.
That's a load of shit, Ernie,
and you know it!
There's something out there
that's been knocking down fences
and killing the livestock
for months now.
You mean that monster wild boar
you claim to have seen?
Not claimed to have seen,
I saw it!
- Ah, you were drunk.
- I know what I saw.
What exactly did you see, Jack,
'cause all I've heard is
second-hand rumours
and they get more
bloody ridiculous
every time they're told.
Well, you remember that smash
up on the highway
coming into town, right,
about 12 months ago?
You remember they couldn't find
the couple?
All the police found
was the wrecked car, right?
Yeah.
Well, I was coming back
from Bob's place in me truck
and I'm looking out the window
and I spot something
in this paddock
about 300 or 400 metres out
so I gets the spotty on it...
fuck me drunk, it's a boar!
It looks like a boar
and it's about the size
of a fucking kombi van!
Yeah, so I follow it along
with a spotlight
and I'm driving along
and it starts getting closer,
right,
and it's about 100 metres off.
And I can see that
this bastard's
got a person hanging
in its mouth.
Well, it's a female,
to be precise,
and she's got long hair,
you know,
and she's just hanging there
like a rag doll
and I shat meself
and then I accidentally lost
control of the spotty handle.
Come on.
You're shitting me, right?
Pigs don't grow that bloody big
and they don't eat people.
I know what I saw.
I might have been drunk,
yeah, I shouldn't have been
driving or something.
Well, it could've been anything,
eh, eh?
Maybe it was a cow eating grass,
eh?
Well, whatever it was when I hit
the spotty back
it was long gone.
How do you know it wasn't
a hairy bloke, Jack?
I saw her tits, they were
hanging out the top like that.
Mate, if there was something
out there
as big as what you say
it is,
knocking over fences
and terrorising livestock,
it'll take more than a rifle
and a slug to slow it down.
Yeah. Yeah.
What, you believe him?
Yeah, well, I've heard
stranger stories.
You believe that I saw a monster
pig with a kid in its mouth?
Hey?
When I said to... I spoke
to the cops
they just laughed at me.
Yeah.
Well, you know how it is,
everyone here thinks I've got
a few roos loose
in the top paddock,
if you know what I mean.
Mate, your drunken antics
have gained you quite
a reputation around here.
Ain't that the truth?
I still remember you doing
the nudie run
- up and down the street.
- Yeah!
That's something
I would like to un-see, Jack!
Well, mate,
if there's anything out there
as big as what you reckon
I reckon a lot more people
would've seen it
than crazy old Jack.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
thanks, mate.
See?
Well, you know, whatever it is,
even if it's not a monster pig,
something is wiping out
the livestock
and smashing the fences.
Still nothing?
No. Hey, you know what?
Bernie's out there,
swimming with his family.
I'm going to give him a go.
If I had a phone,
if I had a phone
with one of them cameras,
I woulda taken a picture,
but I don't have a phone.
I don't have a phone.
Nup.
- Ern, can you do me a favour?
- Sure.
Can you watch the pub
for a couple of hours?
You know what, I'm gonna
bloody drive out there.
What if they've broken down
and they've got no reception?
It's a three-hour drive
out there.
You're gonna hike it
all the way out there
for a couple of old pissheads?
Maybe they're just sleeping off
a hangover.
Then that way I'll kick
both their asses
to Timbuk-fucking-tu.
So can you watch the pub for me?
Yep, I'll look after
the bar for you, honey.
I've got this, mate.
Fuck no, I want stock
when I get back.
Everything's here in the folder
but Tina's gonna be in
in a couple of hours anyway.
She knows where everything is.
Alright, thank you so much,
darling.
You want me to come with ya?
No, I want you to stay here
and keep drinking, right?
I've got rent due
at the end of the week
and that goes
for the lot of you.
Yeah, well, all the drinks
are on Ernie!
Free drinks if you're black.
You white fellas
are paying double.
I'm going outside
for a quick suntan.
What the fuck is that?
Whoa! What the fuck?!
It's a fucking pig.
Shit! Oh, my God!
That's insane!
- Fuck this, I'm out of here!
- Argh!
Fucking coward!
Run!
Mum.
Mum! Something's wrong.
Run!
- Run!
- What's that, hon?
- I can see Robert.
- Run away!
- He's alone and he's running.
He looks scared.
What the fuck?
- Run away!
- Where's Bruce?
Run!
- I think he wants us to run.
- Where's Bruce?
I don't like this.
Something's wrong.
No, hang on.
There's a wild fucking pig!
Poor bugger's scared
of a wild pig.
Where's Bruce, Mum?
Where is Bruce?
He's dead.
What did you say?
He's full of shit.
- Did he say 'dead'?
- Watch out!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Come on, let's go!
- Robbie!
- Let's go!
Robbie!
Come on, baby, we've got to go!
We've got to go now.
You have to come.
- Come on, Elli!
- Get up!
Get up!
Come on, take this!
Come on, Elli. Get up!
Robbie!
Come on! Give me that.
Get to the other side!
Don't look back!
Fucking go!
Come on!
Come on.
Come on, Elli!
I don't want to die.
Get up!
Come on, Bart, hurry up.
Come on!
Fucking hell!
Bart!
Mum!
Don't move, baby.
Don't move!
Mum!
Mum! Mum!
- No!
Come on! Go!
Come on! Come on!
Oh, God, no.
Come on! We just need to get up
there. We'll be safe.
Where?
Go. Go, go!
- Help me!
- I'm trying!
Come on.
Fuck! Fuck!
Fuck, fuck, fuck!
I'm OK. I'm OK.
It's OK. I'm OK.
Take care of your mum.
Why did you let my son die?
Why, Bernie, why didn't you try
to save him?
I'm sorry, sis.
Why didn't you save
my son?
Why didn't you fucking try?
- Why? Why?
- I'm so sorry.
Why, Bernie?
It's OK, Mum.
Bart might be OK.
We have to stay positive.
No. He's gone.
They're all gone.
They're all dead.
They're all dead!
There's only one way we're gonna
make it through this.
We need to kill that overgrown
diseased fucker.
How do we... how do we kill it?
We don't have a gun.
How did it get so big?
- That's not normal, is it?
- No.
It's definitely not normal,
Ell.
I've never seen a boar
that size.
How are we
going to kill it, Bernie?
We don't have a gun!
It's OK.
It's not OK!
It... it took my boy.
- It took my baby boy.
- It's OK, Mum.
I'm so sorry, Deb. I'm sorry.
Bernie.
My baby.
Is she asleep?
Yeah. It's really cold.
Do you think we could use some
of this wood in here
to start a fire and keep warm?
Don't see why not.
So we have a lighter
but no gun.
I thought you were asleep.
Could you sleep?
I'm going to go outside,
grab more wood and kindling.
It'll make it easier
to start a fire.
- No, don't do that. It's OK.
- It's alright.
It's just out there.
You guys keep an eye out the
window for me while I'm outside.
Bernie, don't... don't go.
Please don't go, no.
It's alright, I've got my knife.
Ready?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
No.
Bernie, get it!
Come on, behind me.
Slowly. Slowly, slowly.
Take it easy, big fella.
Now, when I say run,
you fucking run, OK?
- Where do we run?
- That way.
Right behind the barn.
Don't you hurt me, big fella.
OK.
Run!
Go! Go, Elli, go, go.
Let's do this, you ugly fuck!
Bring that shit!
We've been walking for ages,
Mum.
I think we should set up a heap
of spot fires and get warm.
What about the pig?
What if it comes back?
Bart told me about a documentary
he watched on grizzly bears.
He said they're scared of fire.
Maybe it scares off pigs too.
It's worth a shot, Mum.
He's a good boy, my Bart.
OK, baby, yeah. Let's... let's
build Bart's fires, eh?
Maybe he'll find us that way.
What are you doing?
I'm making hand-held torches.
Like the ones Bart and Bruce
made on that camping trip
a few years back.
That's a good idea.
I'll make one too.
He taught me so much.
Do you think Uncle Bernie
killed it?
If anyone could kill it
it would be Uncle Bernie, OK?
Mum, just grab one of mine
and light it.
Oh, it works.
Get back.
OK. OK, OK.
Get away!
Fuck! Fuck!
Is she OK?
It's OK.
It's OK. I'm alright,
I'm alright.
Jack was right.
Debbie, go and get the rifle
out of the back seat of the car,
quick.
Just breathe!
Kill it, Mum!
- Is he dead?
- Yeah. It's dead.
Come on. Let's go.
You've got to be kidding me.
It's them.
Oh, God!
Bart!
Bernie.
Oh, come on, let's go.
You right?
Takes more than a monster boy
to keep you down, hey, Bernie?
You've got no idea!
We're going to the city
tomorrow.
Bernie, you're coming with us.
I think I might fucking join ya.
Subtitles by explosiveskull