I really need to...
Hold it.
Don't look!
I love you.
You don't have to say it back.
I'm sorry. I just...
I love you.
They're not as nihilistic
as they look on the internet.
That's just, like,
what they want you to think.
So, David thinks
you're a childhood friend.
Mmm-hmm. Yeah,
he actually was, um,
my preschool boyfriend.
Of course, before I realized
that I was a raging dyke.
Wow.
They all look so impressive.
You're impressive.
Yeah, sure.
I'm serious.
Jordan is going
to be obsessed with you.
So...
Who is that?
My mom.
You little freak.
I'm... I'm not. I just...
She's gonna be fine, all right?
It's okay to be nervous.
That's part of the fun.
Ugh, this fucking window.
It's gonna be so fun!
You coming?
Yeah. Um...
I forgot something in the car.
Okay...
Don't take too long.
Your game.
Oh, my God!
Surprise, bitches!
You fucking whore!
What the fuck?
It's Sophie.
Bitch!
Oh...
What is she doing here?
- I don't know.
- Oh, oh...
Hello!
You got me soaking
wet, you bad little girl.
- Come here...
- Whoo, boy!
Hey, did I win?
Yes, Greg.
I told you guys.
I got really big lungs!
I know.
Oh, my God.
I can't believe
you're here, like,
last time I saw you,
you were coked out
on the subway,
pissing on the floor
like a little hyena.
I thought you
were an NYU student.
Oh, my God.
And that is why we do not let
the Henny monster out anymore.
No, no!
Okay, but, seriously,
how are you?
I'm good. Yeah.
Yeah?
Yeah, I'm, like, really good.
Good. Good.
You look so good.
I miss you!
I miss you too.
Also, I have to say,
love the podcast.
Okay, we have a fan of the pod.
We love the podcast.
A fan of the pod.
Oh, my God!
It's so good to see you!
I can't believe that
you're here! It's, like, what?
Hi. Hi, I'm Emma.
Hi.
Oh, my God. I'm so sorry.
That was so rude of me.
I'm Alice.
You guys, this is Bee.
Bee, this is everyone.
That's David, my best friend
in the whole, whole,
whole wide world.
That's Emma.
That's Jordan, and...
'Sup! I'm Greg.
'Sup, player! I'm Sophie.
Oh!
Whoa. You're Sophie?
Real nice of you
to make it, Soph.
Ooh, spicy, spicy, Jordan.
What is that supposed to mean?
Just means that
we have all been here
and nobody had any fucking
clue that you were coming.
Let alone, an hour before
the storm is supposed
to start, so...
What? I totally
told you guys
that I was coming.
And I texted you.
In the group chat?
Yeah.
No, you didn't.
Whatever,
you guys know that I'm
useless with text, right?
Also, we meant
to come up yesterday,
but then Bee got scheduled
for a shift at work, so...
Oh, where do you work?
- Game Hut.
- Oh, nice.
Why are you guys being so weird?
Are you talking about me?
What are you doing with that champagne?
- Guys!
You know you're not supposed
to touch my dad's shit.
Sophie is here.
Okay, it's Sophie.
It's a once in a
millennium sighting.
- We're doing it.
- No.
Yes, come on.
- Who wants to pop it?
- I'll do it.
Greg, you'll help me pop it?
Yeah, I'll pop it.
Okay.
Yeah.
I, um...
I brought something.
Oh! What, uh... What is it?
It's, uh, zucchini. A bread.
- It's zucchini bread.
- Thank you.
Yum.
- Hey, nerds.
- That's sweet.
Oh, my, God! Oh, my God!
How did you do that?
Did you see that?
All right.
It's not that cool.
That was crazy.
Oh, my God!
Wow.
That was so sick. I can't
believe we didn't video that.
Give me my dad's Gurkha sword.
Gimme that.
Here, man.
Fuck, that was so good.
I just found it on the wall.
Yeah, don't grab
shit off my wall.
Whoa! Eh, careful
with that pour,
the shits expensive.
All right, all right.
There we go. There we go.
Thanks.
Really impressive.
Nice pouring.
Soph, you want?
I'm sober.
Yay!
No, thanks.
Congrats.
- Cheers.
To hurricanes!
To hurricane parties!
- Yeah.
- To hurricanes.
To hurricanes.
Deep.
Guys it's starting!
Party time!
Starting.
Shit. Fuck.
Okay, what's going on with Max?
Nothing.
Where is he?
He's just taking a break.
He'll be back.
What does that mean?
Is that all you got,
motherfucker!
Let's go!
Hey, fuck face!
Can we talk for a second?
Can you knock?
No, it's my house.
Sure. What's up?
In private.
Oh!
Sure.
I'm sorry. He'll learn.
I'll be right back.
Yeah, that's what
Tom Hanks said in Castaway.
She's actually really cute.
In like a school shooter
type of way.
"Brought you
zucchini bread, Dave."
She's mine. Hands off.
Hey.
Oh, hi... I...
Uh, I was just...
No, no, I know.
It's beautiful. The house.
Sophie's parents have one
that's even bigger.
Just be careful, okay?
With Sophie. Just...
be careful.
Okay.
But he's, like, not hot.
You know what I mean?
He's like, like, your mom
would be like,
"Ooh, he's hot."
Not your mom,
I mean moms in general.
Moms that have been married
for like 10, 15 years
and they see, like,
him going out of a Starbucks...
Alice got to bring someone
without telling anyone.
So you do read the chat.
Why is everyone
so obsessed with the chat?
Now, you're here. I'm here,
we're here together, right?
Why are we worrying
about the chat?
When we can just
live in the moment.
Yeah, it's 'cause
you went to rehab
and you're not on drugs.
So, like, everything is like,
"Ooh, why don't
we just all be cool, man?"
You have a little problem
with Greg?
The lumberjack.
It's a new pod.
I'm not used
to the inhaling yet.
What is he, like, 40?
I don't know.
I think Alice found him
on Tinder, or some shit.
Apparently, he was
in Afghanistan.
I think he was in the Army,
or some shit, so...
Well, that's hot.
He's not...
He's not, like, that hot.
You don't have to think
he's attractive,
only Alice has to think
that he's attractive.
Like, I feel, like,
I'm more attractive than that.
You do?
Absolutely.
And what are the features
that you're bringing
to the table?
Well, I just look like I fuck.
You know what I mean?
Mmm.
I look like I... I fuck.
And that's the vibe
I like to put out there.
Yeah.
No, uh, yeah,
he's, he's really handsome.
Whatever.
I mean, we don't have to
talk about it all the time.
What the fuck
happened to your face?
Fucking Max.
Max did that?
Yes, fucking Max, really.
Okay? I was standing outside
and he just ran up to me
and punched me in the eye.
Just ran up to you?
He just did.
Look at it. He just came
up to you and did that, huh?
I think it...
actually think it looks
kind of dope, though.
Don't you think?
It's getting fucking darker.
I look like a,
like a warrior. Right?
Like, it's kind of...
It's kind of cool.
Like, it's kind of hot.
Like, if you saw me
coming out of a 7-Eleven,
you'd be like...
Um...
So have you had a chance to, uh,
talk to my parents at all?
What the fuck
are you doing here, Soph?
I missed you.
We both know that's a lie.
Nobody's ever missed me.
Ugh, no! Please, no!
Ugh, my God,
can you turn that off?
It's bumming me out.
Yeah. You're right.
You're right.
Hey, guys, can I...
Can I get on the Wi-Fi?
Oh, God, I can never
remember the password.
It's, like, an actually
good password.
I'll transfer it.
What's your email?
Uh... What?
What is your email?
Hey...
I'm sorry.
My service went out,
but I am on a Wi-Fi now.
So, that's good.
I 100% wanna do a
TikTok. All of you can do it.
Okay. Do you know this?
Which one is it?
I don't know what I'm doing.
Follow...
We'll watch it...
You'll catch it. Yeah.
Okay, ready, three, two...
Keep up, keep up.
- Go!
- Look at you.
Are we at the last part?
That was
good. That was good. Okay.
Greg went a little rogue
but we're checking the moves.
No, you didn't.
Again, again, again.
At the end you go like this.
Ready? Get ready.
You okay?
We should just, just post it.
It's very good.
I'm ready for
the flow. One more time!
Three, two, one, go!
Do you want a drink?
Do you want something?
Here you go. There we go!
She's having a good time.
Let's go!
Yeah! Oh, my God.
Okay, bitch.
I make it very salty.
It's incredibly salty.
Is this your first relationship?
Uh, no.
You just, kind of,
give that vibe.
- Not in a bad way.
- Yeah.
How long have
you guys been together?
Oh, uh, six weeks.
Nice.
Wow.
Six weeks with Sophie.
Alice.
In a good way, that's good.
Are you from Moscow?
No.
Oh.
Why?
Doctor Zhivago
is my favorite film.
Ugh, my God,
what is going on
with this storm?
I'm, like, make up your mind.
I want it to start,
like, pouring again
so that we can go fucking crazy.
Oh, you know that has
weed in it, right?
Not a lot,
I just wanted to let you know.
Just didn't want you
to go to town and then...
- Yeah.
- You know what I mean?
Ooh, we're getting
a lot of likes.
Ow! Ow!
What the fuck?
David! Ow! What the fuck?
Oh, my God!
Are you being an incel?
I'm coked up and I bit her.
Excuse me.
So did you, um...
Did you go to college
here in the States, or, um...
Yeah, here...
I, I mean, in Utah State.
You need to chill out.
I guess.
No, I'm serious, you need to...
You need to chill out.
I'm just really sweaty
and I need to hydrate myself.
Okay?
You should watch your girl.
Looks like she's
having fun with Jordan.
Silence!
What? Stop!
Who wants to play
Bodies Bodies Bodies?
- Ah, fuck!
- Yes!
So, if you draw
the piece of paper
that has the "X" on it,
you are the murderer.
And you have
to keep it a secret.
Guys, I get so stressed out
every time we play this.
Someone always ends up crying.
You always end up crying.
Okay, I can access
my emotions easily.
Very incredibly easily.
She's an actress,
she always cries first.
I'm just saying,
this game gets very ugly.
Oh, my God, no, it does not.
It gets ugly
when she ugly cries.
Literally, every single
time we play,
people start fighting.
Yeah, well, that's
what makes it fun, Emma.
Where's Max?
He's not responding to my texts.
Oh, Jesus...
So, how do you play?
So, I'm gonna
hit the lights in a second.
And if you are the murderer,
you have to sneak around
and kill someone
by, like, touching them
on the back.
And then, everyone else
has to avoid being killed.
And then, if you are killed,
you have to fall down
and pretend you're dead.
Like this.
Cool.
Hey, uh...
Alice, do you wanna...
- What?
- Do you wanna...
You know.
Oh! Excuse me, I have to go.
It's an emergency.
Excuse me.
The most important part
is if you do come across a body,
you have to yell,
"Bodies, bodies, bodies."
And then, once that happens,
we'll turn all
the lights back on
and then we'll try
to figure out who did it.
Could you hold this?
Did Greg touch that?
Oh, my God.
You're being such a dick
about Greg.
Just hold this.
David...
What?
I, ugh...
Okay...
Look, what the fuck's going on?
Come to the floor.
Get your ass over here, boy.
Okay.
All right.
Who will do the honors?
Oh...
Get into it. Let's go.
Ow!
Ahhh!
Bitch.
Are you mad at me?
- No.
- Okay.
- Ow!
- Jordan!
Whoa.
What? It's the game.
Wowza...
Oh, my God...
Oh, come on!
What was that?
Bee!
You have to hit more.
You got to put
some muscle into it.
You gotta... Yeah, go for it.
Yeah.
Come on!
Slap him around, he deserves it.
Fucking hit me!
- He wants it.
- No, he deserves it.
He really deserves it. Do it.
If anyone deserves
to be hit, it should be him.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Oh, for fuck sake like this.
Oh, my God!
David!
David.
See?
You're a fucking dick!
What?
You are such an asshole.
I'm teaching her
how to play the game.
Baby, stop, stop!
Wait, guys,
someone has to hit me.
Who's gonna hit me?
I'll do it.
Ow!
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Okay!
- Are we ready to go?
- Yes, let's fucking go.
- Yes.
- Let's play the game.
Holy shit!
I'm so fucked up.
Ahh.
You ready?
Yes.
Hey.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh!
I see white man...
Bodies, bodies, bodies!
You guys! Over here.
No!
All right,
who tried to take advantage
of my body in the dark?
Your wish, babe.
Oh, why, God?
Why? He was so hot!
Was it you?
No.
Okay. So, do we have
any nominations?
Emma Whoa.
Wow, coming in hot.
What?
Why?
Yup, I think it was Emma.
Why do you think it was me?
Yeah, David, why?
Okay, well, she just, like,
agrees with everything
that everybody is saying.
And that's her strategy
in this game
and it works every single time.
So, I'm just calling it now.
It's Emma.
Do we have
any other nominations?
Um... Yeah, David.
Oh, come on.
It's low hanging fruit.
I mean, he who casts
the first stone.
Guys, why isn't he moving?
Greg?
Baby, get up.
You don't have to keep
pretending for this long.
Baby?
Come on, Greg.
Greg...
Get up.
Wait.
Greg?
Greg!
Greg, get up!
Greg! He's not getting up.
Hey, relax,
this always works. I know.
Oh, hey!
Oh, my God.
You really scared me with that.
You're a little trickster, Greg.
I know, Jesus Christ.
Cute.
Okay, so... what about David?
Wait, maybe it's Jordan.
She's always really aggressive
when she's the killer.
There you go.
What? No, I am not.
You're lying.
Your voice always goes
really high when you lie.
No, it doesn't.
I... It... I've...
It's definitely David.
Why are you yelling?
That would be so fucking obvious
if I were the killer,
which I'm not.
I think you're digging yourself
into a little hole here, Dave.
Guys, Jesus Christ...
The best defense
is a good offense.
Hey, you shut up. You're not
supposed to talk. You're dead.
The dead are actually
not supposed to speak.
Oh, yeah, you... Sorry, baby,
you can't. It's a rule.
Oh, my B.
Yeah, no talking. Pack it up.
What the fuck
does that even mean, Greg?
What's up?
"The best defense
is a good offense."
What does that...
What does that mean?
Oh, you know, the best
defense is a good offense.
What...
What does it mean, though?
Uh, well...
It, um... It means
that the best defense
is a good offense.
Right, right, I heard you.
But, what does it mean
to you, Greg? Like...
I don't know, could you
elaborate on it for us?
Break it down.
Yeah, sure.
So, hey, look in sports,
there's...
Oh, my God.
You are such a fucking dick.
Hey, this is a teaching moment.
Oh, I see.
You're fucking with me.
No. No,
I'm not fucking with you, Greg.
I'm just having fun.
We're all just
having a good time.
Right, guys?
Right, Greg?
We're just having fun.
You know,
I think it's time for me
to put myself to bed.
- Oh, come on, Greg.
- Greg, no.
Good night, Greg.
You kids have fun.
Catch you later, player.
By the way,
can I just point
all of our attention
to the fact that Emma
hasn't said a fucking word.
Whoa, you're right.
Whoa, she hasn't!
I'm just pointing out
the obvious. That's all.
Look, she's doing
that swallowing thing.
She always does that
when she's fucking nervous!
Oh, my God!
Look, look!
Oh, my God, you're doing it.
You're swallowing it.
- I'm not.
- You are.
Okay, I love you,
but when you swallow,
it's just fucking...
Like, why?
Swallowing is normal.
- It's a normal thing to do.
- Yeah...
It's very un-attractive.
I don't know why you do it?
Oh, my God. Is that why
you guys never have sex?
What?
Alice.
What? It's not a bad thing.
Some people have sex a lot.
Some people have it less.
Alice, what are you
talking about? We do.
I have it a lot. Some...
- Are you fucking...
- Oh, my God.
Are you fucking talking
about us behind my back?
No.
Yes.
No, I'm not.
I'm not! I'm not.
- I just...
- That's just great.
No, I... We...
I... You never really... I...
I don't...
You're always gas lighting me.
"Gaslight," shut up.
It's a fucking dumb word.
Excuse me?
Gaslight is, like, one of
the most over used words ever,
to, like, the point
of annihilation.
Okay, it doesn't mean
anything other than the fact
that, like,
you read the internet.
Or, like, "Congrats,
you have a Twitter account."
Ugh, that is so fucking lame.
"Gaslight," get over it.
Like what's next? You're
gonna call me a narcissist?
Or a foot soldier of,
like, the white supremacy?
Like, come on, fucking,
be more original.
Lame.
What? I'm just saying,
that, this is what I'm saying,
she doesn't have a thought
in her fucking head
that hasn't been said
by anybody else.
Nothing that isn't preordained.
David, that's really mean.
Look, she's crying.
What?
Why is everybody
looking at me like that?
This is not her real cry.
I vote David.
Yeah, me too.
Are you fucking serious?
Guys, it's Emma.
She's an actress.
She's acting.
Third.
Wow, how fucking surprising.
Yeah, look at your
quivering upper lip.
Like, we all didn't see you
in Hedda Gabler. Fuck you.
Yeah, yeah, yup... Fourth.
Oh, my God.
Fuck this game!
Holy shit.
Relationships can
be really complicated.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Are you sure?
I'm fine. I'm 100% fine.
Are you sure, baby?
Yes. Let's play.
Ow!
Wow, good one.
All of a sudden
she loves the game.
That was crazy.
Give it to me.
Damn!
Ah! Oh, my God!
What was that?
- What the fuck?
- Is that the lights?
What was that?
- Oh, my God.
- Was that from the storm?
Oh, my God.
I bet you that it was David.
David! JORDAN: It's
not David. Come on.
I'm texting him.
David, are you fucking with us?
Turn the lights back on.
Hey, does anybody have service?
No!
Ugh, wait, mine's not working.
Okay, I think
the WiFi is also down.
Oh, my God, I'm
gonna fucking kill him.
Great!
David!
David! This is
real fucking cute!
Soph, can he disable
the generator from garage,
or the basement, or whatever?
I don't know.
David!
Okay, well, I'm gonna
go and flip the breaker.
Is it in the garage
or is it in the basement?
- David!
- Soph?
- Huh, what?
- Okay, whatever.
Okay, I'm gonna go
get some more flashlights.
I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
Where is a bathroom?
Um, uh, downstairs,
first door on your right.
Going there.
David?
David, are you fucking with us?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I meant the other stairs.
David! David!
Help! Somebody help!
No, no, no.
What the fuck happened?
Oh, my God! Why would...
- Check his pulse.
- What the fuck?
Oh, fuck!
Oh, my God!
Hold his head up!
Fuck!
- Fuck!
- Is he dying?
- Hold his head up!
- Come on, baby, hold on.
What the fuck
happened to his neck?
I love you, David.
Shit.
What is happening?
Shit!
What are you doing?
I'm calling 911!
Oh, my God! You have service?
Fuck, no! Do you?
- No!
- Shit!
Where are you going?
Landline!
We should move his body?
Why?
I don't know. Because he's...
No, you can't move him.
Did you watch SVU?
It's evidence.
- Of what?
- Cause!
Landline?
No, there's no connection.
Sophie, where are your keys?
Your keys, Sophie,
where are they?
They're in the pocket.
They're in her pocket...
Where? Fucking help!
Where are you going?
- I'm going to the car.
- To the car? Why?
To get some fucking help.
Wait, do you have a license?
Doesn't she not have a license?
I don't know.
I don't think so.
- Fuck!
- He's dead!
You have to go!
I don't know!
He stopped breathing!
Branch!
You have to push the gas.
I know how
to fucking drive, Alice!
- I can't see.
- Is the battery dead?
- Oh, no...
- What?
I, I think I left the light on,
on the mirror.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
What the fuck
are we supposed to do?
Wait, where are your cars?
We...
We only have one car.
Max picked us all up
and he fucking left!
Fuck, fuck, fuck!
Max will probably
be here any minute, right?
Where's Jordan?
She went to check
the generator, I...
What the fuck was he doing?
- What are you talking about?
- Fuck was he doing?
Why the fuck was he
outside in the storm?
Hey!
It's me, let me in!
I found this.
Outside in the mud.
Don't touch it
Um, does the security system
work if the power goes out?
Um...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it does.
David's dad explained it to us.
Nobody can get in
without the code.
Well, Max has the code.
So...
Max wouldn't...
I'm just saying, like,
where the fuck is he?
Couldn't he have come back
after last night?
Alice, stop.
What happened last night?
- Nothing.
- No.
We did shrooms
and Max told everybody
that he was in love with Emma.
Which David thought
was beautiful in the moment,
but maybe not today.
Alice, that literally doesn't
fucking matter at all.
Where is Greg? Where is he?
- What?
- Where is Greg?
I...
He said he was going to bed.
So my guess would be
that he's sleeping.
Okay, don't you think
it's a little bit strange
that he hasn't, like,
woken up yet?
Jordan,
what are you trying to say.
Maybe we should
just go check on him.
No, no, no.
Jordan...
What are you doing?
Jordan... Jordan.
What are you doing!
- I'm staying safe.
- Really?
Because it looks like
you're grabbing
a fucking meat cleaver
to go look for my boyfriend!
Wow. Boyfriend?
That's the first time
I've heard you call him that.
That's crazy.
Don't be such a bitch.
Alice, I'm literally
just protecting myself, okay?
Let me remind you,
our friend is dead.
So, if you could just, like,
not escalate the situation...
I'm not escalating.
You're holding the knife
and you're moving your hands
while you talk.
Alice, how long
have you known Greg?
Like...
long.
Alice.
Ugh...
I don't know exactly how long.
I... like...
two weeks.
Okay, uh...
What do you know
about Greg, Alice?
Oh, my God.
What do you know about him?
Oh, my God, guys!
Oh, my God!
Relax. Stop!
Stop! Stop! I know that
he's a good person, okay?
He's fundamentally
a good person.
He wouldn't do this. Like, no.
Do you know his middle name?
Do you know where he lives?
Do you know how much
fucking money he makes?
Do you know
his last name, Alice?
I know a lot.
Our first date was at...
was at a bar.
He drank, like,
a medium amount...
Okay, Alice... Stop.
He likes nature.
What is his middle name?
- He's a Libra moon.
- Where does he live?
You don't ask
what your middle name is!
- Okay? For a really long time.
- Oh... Fuck!
He's a Libra moon.
That says a lot!
Fuck!
Greg!
Shh!
What? You just said
we're looking for Greg!
Okay, well
don't fucking, Alice...
Greg! Can you come
into the kitchen?
We need you for a second.
Shut up.
Stop waving the knife at me!
Fuck.
You're making me...
Stop. Stop. Greg!
Stop. Just stop.
Just be quiet.
Stop. Stop.
Greg! Don't.
Relax.
Don't grab my mouth.
Relax. Relax. Relax.
You're silencing me.
Oh, my God.
Get the fuck off.
Okay, stop.
Don't grab me like that again.
And she came at me with a knife.
- I'm sorry...
- Back off.
Okay, buck!
Wait, where's Emma?
Oh, my God.
Emma?
Guys,
maybe Emma could have done it.
She was really pissed at David.
Alice, what the fuck?
Emma wouldn't do that.
She was devastated.
She's having, like,
a full-on panic attack.
Yeah, but she's an actress.
She's acting.
Remember Hedda Gabler?
Okay, not to be mean,
but she wasn't that good
in Hedda Gabler.
This is my room.
So open it.
You open it.
What happened to,
"Greg would never do this?"
He wouldn't.
Okay, so open it.
I will in one second.
I'm going to.
He's not here.
Soph, are there any guns
in the house?
Guns?
No. No way.
David's dad can be a dick,
but his politics check out.
Guys...
What the fuck is this?
Uh... But...
He wanted to be prepared
for the hurricane. He...
Why did he circle
the fucking house
on his fucking map?
We have to
find Emma before he does.
Okay.
Let's check my room next.
I don't think
he's hiding in my bra.
Guys...
Come here.
Oh, my God, Emma.
Emma.
Are you okay?
What's going on?
What are you guys doing?
You scared me What's happening?
It's so hot in here.
What is that?
Xanax. Do you want one?
Yeah, give me one.
- You want one?
- No.
Hey, you take this.
- Why?
- I'm gonna find Greg.
Greg, why? Where's Max?
Maybe Max did it.
Maybe he is here.
Max was really angry at David.
I'm serious,
he looked like he was gonna
do something really fucked up.
Alice! Shut up.
I'm just saying.
Max would never.
Let's go find Greg.
Okay.
What the...
- What the fuck?
- Oh, my God.
What the hell is on his face?
It's his light therapy mask.
He has seasonal depression.
Let's go.
Hey... Shh...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Greg.
- What's up?
- Where have you been?
Huh?
Where have you been?
Oh, I, uh...
I couldn't sleep,
so I came down here
to do my exercises.
Why didn't you answer me?
Were you calling for me?
Yeah.
I... I had my headphones in.
Are you guys
still playing Werewolf?
Greg!
Stop! Stop it!
All right.
What am I supposed to do, huh?
Why don't you tell us,
fucking Greg?
Is that my go bag?
Is that a knife?
Why did you bring a go bag?
The hurricane?
See, I told you.
Why did you circle
the fucking house
on your fucking map?
What's going on?
David is dead.
His body is outside.
David's body. Wait, what?
Why did you kill David?
You murdered my boyfriend.
No, no. David killed me.
Right?
This isn't a joke, Greg.
David is dead.
Somebody slit his throat.
- What?
- With a fucking sword,
you fucking sick fuck!
Oh...
You guys are fucking with me?
Oh, you guys
are fucking with me.
Fuck!
Cute.
No!
Okay.
Everyone needs
to take a deep breath.
Alice.
Give me my knife back!
What the fuck is going on?
I don't know!
- Put down the weapons.
- You put it down.
Now!
On the floor!
Okay, okay.
How about this?
- Put it down.
- Okay, okay, okay.
Okay, we'll put them down.
We'll put... We'll all
put them down.
Right? We'll put them down
if you put yours down.
We'll put them down.
Okay.
Yeah, please, please.
- That seems fair.
- Yeah.
Okay.
Putting it down.
We're good.
Yeah.
Okay, this is good.
All right.
Jordan!
Are you okay?
- Ow!
- Stop! Stop!
- Please stop!
- Alice?
Stop. Stop!
No! No!
Sophie! No.
No, no, no, Sophie!
Mother fucker.
Oh, my God.
This isn't right.
He didn't do it.
Alice, how do you know?
How do you that know he did?
Look, I mean, like...
If you look at all of us, like,
on paper, logically,
he is the most likely
to commit an act of violence.
On paper?
What the fuck
are you even talking about?
I mean, he's the only one
who served in the military,
right? So...
What?
He's a vet.
Right? Like Iraq? Or...
No, I thought
it was Afghanistan.
He was a veterinarian.
He was
a veterinarian's assistant.
Are you fucking
serious right now?
Then why did
you call him G.I. Joe?
Because... Have you seen him?
Well, regardless, either way,
like, out of all of us,
he is the biggest unknown.
We've known each other forever.
Jordan, what are
you trying to do?
I'm not...
I'm not trying to do anything.
He's dead, okay?
He's dead. We killed him.
She killed him.
Go change your shirt.
We need to leave.
We need to get out of here.
We don't have a car.
Okay, I'm going to walk.
Emma, stop.
What do you mean?
You can't just fucking...
Emma, you're literally
in the middle of nowhere.
Where are you going?
I mean, it could
have been any of us.
We all scattered
when the lights went out.
I mean, it could
have been Max, okay?
Alice, you don't know
what you are talking about.
He punched David in
the face because of you.
Just because Max
is in love with me
doesn't mean
he would kill David.
Oh, what the fuck
is wrong with you?
What?
This is not about you and Max.
Why are you being so mean?
Because I'm upset, Emma.
I'm upset because somebody
killed my best friend.
Sophie, did you use?
I can believe you're making
this about you.
I'm sad, too, okay?
I'm scared, too.
I loved him so much.
It didn't seem like it.
- What?
- It seemed like
you loved having a boyfriend.
And you loved
feeling comfortable.
But, no, you did not love him.
You didn't even
fucking like him.
You were just too scared
to do anything about it.
So you stayed for three years
longer than you should have
because you're a coward.
No, I'm not.
I'm not.
I'm not. Right? I...
You're... You're so toxic.
Emma, calm down.
You are.
No! No, I'm not gonna...
You are so toxic.
And, honestly, when you fell
off the face of the earth,
David was relieved.
He was relieved he didn't
have to deal with you anymore.
I wish they had chopped off
your head instead,
you spineless piece of shit.
Sophie.
Jesus fucking Christ.
Emma.
Emma, come on. Wait.
- Wait.
- Emma.
Emma.
That was real nice, Soph.
Guys...
Where the fuck is Bee?
Emma.
I'm so sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I'm so fucked up right now.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Okay? It was just, like,
things started coming...
Isn't that what you wanted?
Yeah, Emma,
that's what I wanted.
That's what I was
in the mood for.
Thank you very much.
What the fuck?
Jesus Christ!
You always think everyone
is in love with you.
It's so crazy.
I...
I'm sorry.
Do you want this?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Sure.
Bee?
Soph?
Emma?
Help!
Jordan!
- Help.
- Where are you?
Help! Please, help! Help!
Help! Help! Help!
Emma.
- Oh, my God.
- Emma.
Oh, my God.
What happened?
I don't know!
I don't know.
Don't touch her!
I'm just trying to...
Don't. No!
...figure out what happened.
How am I supposed
to know if I don't touch her?
Don't, just don't, just don't.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
I heard something.
Um, maybe she...
Oh, my God.
- She fell, maybe she tripped?
- No.
No, no. She...
She... She got pushed, okay?
She was pushed.
I told you it wasn't Greg!
Are you happy that she's dead?
No, but I told you
it wasn't Greg!
I did... I did tell you.
Don't you see what's happening?
What?
Who was the killer?
In the game?
It's following the same pattern.
The deaths.
Please... Please,
just stop talking, please!
David, Greg, Emma.
No.
Yes!
- Fucking yes, Jordan!
- No.
No, it's not
following the same pattern.
Greg died and then
we executed David.
But in real life,
David died and then we...
Okay, but Greg, David, Emma.
Greg, David, Emma.
I mean, why else would
somebody leave her there
unless they wanted us
to find her?
Why would they want us
Because they're playing
a sick fucking game.
Okay?
Who was the killer?
I wasn't the killer.
Alice, you're fucking coked out.
You're coked out, okay?
We're all coked out.
I'm not.
Are you wearing make up?
I... I was upstairs,
changing my...
You look weird.
Whose sweater is this?
I found it upstairs.
How long have you known her?
Stop, Alice.
Who are you?
What?
You show up here,
start smiling at my boyfriend.
What are you talking about?
Your voice is trembling.
No. No.
Yeah. It is.
I googled you.
And there was nobody
with your name
who graduated
from Utah State this year.
There's literally no record
of your attendance, at all.
What the fuck?
Listen, I can explain.
Oh, my God.
You discovered David's body.
No, I just...
You could have tampered
with the generator,
just like you tampered
with Sophie's car.
You said you
left the lights on, right?
Are you serious?
We watched you kill someone.
You literally murdered Greg!
Literally!
Literally! You sick fuck!
No, are you crazy? No.
Calm down.
Let's just talk about it.
Talk about it?
Yeah.
No... No.
Let's just talk about it, okay?
Mmm-mmm. I don't want to.
- Sophie... Sophie.
- No!
Sophie.
ALI, CE: Do not touch her!
Whoa!
You know what?
I don't...
I don't want you in here.
Okay, calm down.
No, seriously.
Alice!
I don't want you in here.
I... Relax.
Just shut up! Shut up!
I don't want you in here.
Get out of this room!
Let go of me, Alice.
Get the fuck out of this room!
I don't want to look
at your face anymore. Get out.
- Alice, calm down.
- I'm not...
- I'm not calming down.
- Let go of me, Alice.
No, you killed
my fucking boyfriend.
You know what? You know what?
It was self-defense.
I... I want her out.
Jordan, can you help me?
All right.
Jordan!
Jesus, Alice.
Get the fucking door!
Jesus fucking Christ!
I do not want her in here!
- Relax!
- No!
Sophie! Sophie, do something!
You killed him, get out!
- Sophie!
- Get out!
Sophie!
Stay here.
I'm so hungry.
How can you be hungry right now?
I wasn't planning on this.
Alice...
What the fuck?
How the fuck you get in here?
She has a gun.
Jordan has a gun
in her pocket, Sophie,
get away from her.
No, no, Sophie,
she's confusing...
Let go of me.
Are you kidding me?
I don't have a gun.
Then empty your pockets.
Slowly!
That's it?
That's it.
Oh, my God.
You are the killer.
In the... In the game... I...
How the fuck
did you get in here?
Where is the gun?
I don't have a fucking gun.
We locked all the doors.
How did you get in?
You killed him.
Why would I kill David?
Why would I kill Emma?
They are, literally,
my oldest friends.
You just fucking met them!
How dare you?
When I found David,
you were the last person
to get there.
It took you awhile.
That's true.
Where were you
when Emma died, hmm?
You pushed her!
Shut up!
Guy's, don't listen to her.
You don't know what the fuck
you're talking about!
And then, I saw you.
I saw you getting the gun.
That's a lie.
That's a fucking lie.
You're lying. You're a liar!
You're lying through
your fucking teeth.
You lied about everything.
You lied about
everything to Sophie.
You're a fucking liar.
Yeah, you...
You did lie to Sophie.
Okay.
I did go to Utah State
for one semester.
But my mom was...
She was having a hard time
and I came home
to take care of her.
And I did work at Game Hut,
but they shut down
our location, like,
a week after I met you. I...
I've been applying, but...
What were you doing
when I dropped
you off at the mall?
Hung out at
the food court. I...
didn't want to disappoint you.
I was embarrassed.
I should have told you.
I just...
My mom, she...
She has...
My mom has borderline.
Oh, my God.
I'm so sorry, that's...
That's really serious.
Mental health
is a really serious issue.
I mean, I've never actually
said this to anyone, but...
but I have body dysmorphia.
Oh, my God.
Shut the fuck up, Alice.
I wanted to tell you.
I just...
I just really wanted
you to like me.
You've got to
be fucking kidding me.
Oh, my God.
Jordan, what the fuck?
Are you telling me
that you believe that
pile of bullshit?
Is that supposed
to inspire confidence?
Her mom has "borderline."
Is that not a red fucking flag
to anybody else?
That's a serious issue.
Where the fuck did you get that?
David's Dad's rich!
Rich people
have fucking guns, Sophie!
My parents are rich.
They don't have guns.
Well, I mean, we're all rich,
but you and David
are like rich, rich.
That has never mattered to me...
Oh, shut the fuck up!
We didn't even
want to invite you.
We debated about inviting you,
but because it's David's house.
I didn't say that, but...
And, no, you did not
respond in the group chat.
And then, you show up
with this fucking psychopath.
Don't call her a psychopath,
that's so ableist.
Fuck you.
You deserve each other.
I hope she fucking suffocates
you in your sleep.
Yeah, you didn't
reply in the chat.
And David actually told me
that you, like, begged him
to talk to your parents
and, like,
unlock your trust again.
And that's why
you're actually here.
Oh, yeah?
Oh, yeah, did he tell you that
while you guys were railing
lines in front of me.
Your addict friend
who you're supposedly
so worried about?
- We are worried.
- No!
No, no, no.
Let me get this straight.
Okay, let me get this straight.
So, when the black girl
has a coke habit,
it's a problem.
But when everyone else
around her does it,
including her best friend,
who happens to be white
and male,
it's fine?
I understand and I'm an ally,
and I totally get how it...
looks that way.
And...
Um...
Jordan?
Oh, my God.
You are obsessed
with playing the victim.
Excuse me?
I had to ride
in the ambulance with you
three times,
thinking you were dead.
I needed help and I got it
and I'm sorry.
You got help?
You mean we had to narc
on you to your fucking dad
so he'd cut you off
and ship you off to rehab,
while you were quite
literally kicking and screaming.
Yeah.
And then you just
fell off the face of the earth.
'Cause that's what you do, Soph.
That's what you do when
things get tough, you run.
You ran away to go write
your fucking memoirs.
It's creative non-fiction
which is a valid response
to life in an attention economy.
Oh, fuck off and die.
You write little essays
about your mommy and her vodka.
And your pussy
and your feelings.
And your fucking feelings.
Oh, my God, we are all drowning
in your fucking feelings.
Feelings are facts.
No! No, they're not.
Facts are facts.
Why did you ghost us, Sophie?
Like why?
Because you fucking trigger me.
You enable me.
Does she know?
Does she know what?
That you begged me
to stop at your apartment
on my way up here.
And I did.
And we fucked in your car.
She's fucking lying.
She's lying through
her fucking teeth.
She's trying to get
in your head.
Don't listen to her, okay?
Check her texts.
You are unhinged, Jordan.
You are devoid of empathy.
You have no feelings.
Do you want to know
why I could never
ever be with you?
Because you schedule
everything in your
fucking Google calendar,
including sex.
Because you have no soul.
Fuck you.
You're emotionally abusive.
I had to go to therapy for PTSD.
You can fucking ask Alice.
Yeah, she did.
For a long time.
You hate Alice.
No, I don't.
Yeah, you despise her.
You complain constantly
about how vapid
and annoying she is.
You hate her.
It's pitiful how
you won't stop making fun
of her stupid little podcast.
Let her have the podcast.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
You hate listen to her podcast.
Wait...
What?
And you made us
swear on our lives
not to tell anyone.
Jordan, is that true?
I like your podcast, Alice.
What is your podcast about?
Hanging out with your
smartest and funniest friend.
Did you just groan?
No.
When I said "Hanging out
"with your smartest
and funniest friend."
Oh, my God.
Like that. Like that!
Fuck!
You just did it again.
No, I didn't!
First of all,
a podcast takes
a lot of work, okay?
You have to organize the guests.
You have to do a Google calendar
and you build a following.
It takes a long fucking time!
And I've been working
on it for a while!
Okay?
And then, let me say,
that nobody likes you, okay?
Nobody likes you!
Do you know when you're
drunk and you cry to me,
"Oh, I'm afraid nobody likes me
"because I'm mean
and a bitch and I suck."
Well, you do, okay?
You fucking suck.
And I only hang out
with you out of pity
and the suffocating weight
of our shared history.
And that is all.
And you're just so in love
with your rags
to riches narrative,
like you're the only
fucking person in the world
who didn't come from money.
You know what?
Your parents
are upper middle class.
No, they're not.
Jordan.
They are.
They teach at a university.
It's public.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, I mean,
no wonder Sophie OD'd.
Who could date
a fucking spreadsheet
with a superiority complex?
It's, like, you're such a...
Ow!
What the fuck?
What the fuck, Jordan?
Oh, my God.
Are you serious?
Did you just fucking shoot me?
- No.
- You fucking shot me.
With a gun!
No,
I didn't shoot you. I...
You fucking
murdered them, you freak!
You're the murderer.
I knew it!
I knew it, you're such a bitch!
You're such a fucking bitch!
- I didn't murder anybody.
- Yes, you did.
Jordan, put the gun down.
I've never been shot before.
It really fucking hurts!
Put the fucking
gun down, please.
You did this.
You made me do this.
Why did you make me do that?
What are you doing?
Put the gun down.
Why? Why did you shoot me?
I did not shoot you.
Yes, you did! With that gun!
Stop, stop, stop.
Alice, stop. Stop!
With that gun.
Stop waving it around.
I'm not waving.
Don't hit me.
You already shot me.
Stop! Don't touch me.
- No, no, no!
- Get the gun!
- No!
- Sophie, the gun!
Don't! Stop!
You're on my leg!
I want it. Give it to me!
- No!
- Let go!
No!
Ow!
- No!
- Give it to me.
Give me it! Give me it!
Get off of me! No!
Get the fuck off me!
Get off!
Ow! My fucking leg!
Where is it?
Ow!
I didn't do it.
Please, don't move.
Don't you fucking move.
It's okay...
It's okay, Jordan.
Please, don't do it.
Please, just...
Stop! I didn't do it.
Please, just stop, okay?
Just put it down.
Please, stop moving.
Please... please,
don't follow me, please.
Please...
Stop! Stop it! Stop it!
Stop, stop, stop!
Why are we doing this?
Don't come up here.
Don't, please, don't.
Please put it down.
Please stop.
Please stay there.
Oh, my God.
Please...
- Stop.
- I'm begging you...
Don't fucking come up here.
Please.
Sophie, I'm serious,
just stay there.
Stop.
Just stay there.
Just please stay there.
I'm begging you.
Please, fucking...
Fucking stay there! Fuck!
Bee!
Check her texts.
Sophie.
Did you kill Emma?
No.
Did you?
It's okay, if you did it.
It's okay.
I just want to know.
You can tell me.
Did you kill David?
What?
No.
You killed Greg.
To protect you.
I had to.
Will you answer this honestly?
Okay, I promise. What is it?
Did you...
With Jordan?
No.
No, I didn't...
I didn't. I would never.
I love you, okay?
Do you love me?
I just wanted to touch you.
You frighten me.
Bee!
We have to stay together!
Bee?
Where are you?
I love you.
We have to stay together.
Bee!
- Okay.
- Bee!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hey, hey.
I've been looking
for you everywhere.
I have to tell you something.
I went to Alice's room and I...
And then I found coke
and then...
I... I said all these things
to Emma and she...
I... I gave her pills
'cause...
And then she tripped and fell.
It's my fault.
Sophie, it's okay. It's okay.
I thought no one
would believe me.
Give me your phone.
What?
I want to see
your text with Jordan.
No.
I have to see your texts.
Please?
No.
Sophie.
Stop!
That's not my phone.
Oh... What?
What happened?
I have reception.