Are there any tickets left, please?
I'm awfully sorry, ladies and
gentlemen. I don't feel terribly well.
Please excuse me.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I'm sorry to have to inform you
that Mr Bergson has been taken ill,
and will be unable to continue the recital.
He has asked me to apologise...
Yes?
You heard it too, didn't you?
That music, didn't you recognise it?
Who are you?
Yes?
Yes.
Worse than yesterday?
No, I'll come straight over.
My mother's very ill.
I must call a taxi.
My car's outside. May I drive you?
Yes.
Do you remember your father?
No. He died the day I was born.
You play like him.
You're too young to have heard him.
He did make recordings.
- I never heard them.
- Why not?
Perhaps because I want to play like myself.
His music had an uncanny quality,
as if inspired by some unseen power.
Divine Mozart?
No, no.
You're wrong to mock.
This morning, I was observing
the sun's eclipse.
I'm an astronomer.
There was some extremely
violent turbulence on its surface.
It was as if the Earth,
or something from the Earth,
was drawing the sun's fire
towards us, like a magnet.
As I watched,
I kept hearing that music.
- Is she upstairs?
- Yes.
Would you wait here?
I'll make you a cup of tea.
Hello, Mother.
So much I want to say to you.
There's no time.
No time.
No more time.
She's come.
What are you saying, Mother?
She's here.
No.
No, let her stay.
Come nearer.
Nearer.
Nearer, nearer.
Find...
must...
must try...
Like as a father, pity of his own children,
even so is the Lord merciful
unto them that fear him.
For he knoweth whereof we are made.
He remembereth that we are but dust.
We therefore commit this body to be cremated,
in the sure and certain hope
of a resurrection to eternal life,
according to the mighty working
whereby he is able to subdue
all things to himself.
There, there. It's okay.
It's all right.
It's upstairs.
Now, would you like a whisky,
or would you like a Scotch?
Lovely.
It's all I've got, I'm afraid.
What did she say to you?
- Who?
- My mother.
Oh.
I could hardly hear her.
Something about the 'Master Magician'?
Musician?
The Master Musician.
He was somebody my father knew in Turkey,
who taught him special
breathing techniques for the flute.
He'd been having some trouble
with his playing.
After that trip, he never played again.
He became obsessed by fire.
And then, shortly afterwards,
he was found dead.
The lower half of his body
was really badly burnt,
and his fingers were locked
in a playing position,
with a flute between his lips.
...Security Council calling
for an embargo on all arms sales
was vetoed by the United States.
Great Britain abstained from voting.
We have just received news
of a volcanic eruption in Turkey,
in the remote region of Cappadocia.
So far we have no information
about the extent of damage
or loss of life.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
The volcano, Mount Ersias,
has been dormant for centuries,
and was believed to be extinct.
According to local legend,
Mount Ersias is known as the House...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hello?
Hello, it's me. Paul.
Did you see the news?
A volcano's erupted in Turkey,
near the place where my father died.
It's the sun. It's beginning
to affect the Earth.
I keep hearing that bloody music.
I had an accident on my way home.
I drove into a tree.
What?
You hurt?
No, I'm fine.
I thought I saw...
No.
Shall I come over?
Yes, I'd like that.
Look, I'm freezing cold.
I'm going to have a quick bath.
I'll leave the door on the latch.
Just let yourself in.
Okay? Bye.
Cat!
You hungry? Hmm?
Hmm?
Hello?
Anybody home?
- Oh...
- Hey.
Shh, shh, shh.
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
Cold.
Why don't you get in the bath?
Don't you want to know why your father died?
Yes.
And that music?
Then you must find him.
Who?
The Master Musician.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
You speak English?
Parlez-vous français?
Sprechen Sie Deutsch?
I'm looking for the Master Musician.
Musician?
Master Musician!
Master Musician... Master Musician...
These waters are the graveyard of the djinn.
They should not be disturbed.
You speak English?
My name is Bilal.
I summon the faithful to prayer.
I am told you are seeking the Master.
You heard?
Your flute will guide you,
as it once guided your father.
You know who I am?
You are your father's son.
He too came to seek the Master.
Where would I find him?
You shall meet him.
Look at these emission and absorption lines.
Aren't they unusual?
The peaks and troughs
look a little distorted.
Doesn't that indicate
the sun is becoming unstable?
The sun is a main sequence star. It's stable.
During its eclipse,
I detected an extraordinary
degree of turbulence on its surface.
I'm convinced there's a connection
with the recent volcanic activity in Turkey.
That's ridiculous!
There's no evidence.
Will you fund a visit to the volcano?
You're not serious?
I shall be taking some leave.
I almost ran over a woman on the way here.
- A woman?
- I think it was a woman.
Cloaked completely in black.
Except for her hand. I could see her hand.
It was really badly burned.
She was totally unaware of me.
And then, as she walked away,
smoke rose from her footprints.
You have seen a djinn.
A what?
The Koran has revealed
that the djinn was created
from the fire of scorching winds.
It can take many forms:
a snake, a scorpion, a beast of prey.
It can even transform itself into a man,
or a woman.
What is this place?
The Christians worshipped here
many centuries ago.
Your father wanted to be alone.
He chose to live here.
He believed it protected him
from evil spirits.
Don't be frightened. He won't harm you.
We call him the Silent One.
He's frightened of people.
He comes here to sleep.
You've had a long journey.
I shall leave you to rest.
And I shall come to you tomorrow.
She was there.
They were trying to kill her.
There is nothing there.
Why do I keep seeing this woman?
She was being stoned.
The woman was your father's wife.
My father's wife?
Your father married a woman here.
She was presented to him by the Master.
She gave birth to a deformed child.
Soon after, there were four infants
born dead in the village.
The mothers blamed her.
You mean that thing I saw last night was...
Your brother.
The Master.
- I must find him.
- No.
You are not ready.
Have you found him?
No.
But I've heard him.
Didn't you hear the music?
The music is created here.
Its source is fire.
You all right?
The sun's power is so strong,
it's damaging the surface of the Earth.
That volcano is the beginning.
Thank God you've come.
Paul!
It's okay!
It's okay.
He's harmless.
But he scared me, too.
Don't be afraid.
I won't hurt you.
Don't be frightened.
Don't be frightened. It's all right.
I won't hurt you.
Don't be frightened.
Ever since we arrived,
I've had the strangest feelings.
As though another part of me had surfaced.
It was quite uncanny.
And then this morning,
walking round this place,
I recognised everything.
Like recalling a dream.
Like I've been here before.
As if I were coming home.
But that village,
it really frightens me.
That's the mosque.
But no-one seems to use it.
Where is everybody?
I don't know.
This place is like a cemetery.
Who are you?
I must speak with Paul.
He isn't well.
He must learn to wield the power
that lies within him,
and turn the flute away from evil,
away from the fire.
Otherwise, it will cut him down like a sword.
The fever is a warning.
It is the fire of the blood.
Through his music,
he must learn to control
the hidden forces of the Earth.
In the solitude of its voice,
a secret is hidden.
As long as he does not understand its power,
it can be stolen from him.
When he has regained his strength,
I will show him the way.
It's a locket.
My father.
And...
Iblis inateçi.
Iblis ina... teçi!
Where is she?
Her life is in the hands of the Master.
Where can I find her?
He destroyed your father.
Now you must destroy him.
Fire will become the Master,
unless you force him to
submit to the will of Allah,
to bow before Man.
How?
You have the power.
Your music must conquer his.
Master Musician.
What can I do?
You must enter the circle.
You must remain in it,
and search for the never-ending note.
You will be tempted,
you will know fear.
Remember that the djinn can take many forms,
but the circle is your protection.
If you leave it before the will of the Earth
burns clearly within you, you will die.
The Master is dancing in his own blood.
We must act quickly,
or he will drown this Earth in fire.
# Allah, Allah, Allah
# Allah, Allah, Allah #
# Allahu akbar, Allahu akbar
# Allahu akbar
# Allahu akbar #
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)