Yeah,
You're a good boy,
come with me now when Mommy and Daddy go.
Be good, son, back in a couple of weeks.
Don't forget to tell me if
they like the preserves.
Oh, you're so sweet.
You be good now, Billy.
Don't give Auntie Cheryl any trouble.
You be careful.
Mommy and Daddy are
going over the mountains
all the way to the Pacific coast
to see Grandma and Grandpa.
Remember, we had to
change hotels in Cedar City.
Bye, Daddy.
Bye.
Good-bye.
Good-bye, Mommy.
Bye-bye, Honey.
Bye!
Bye-bye.
I love you.
The champs, the Packers,
and what a game.
The mighty Green Bay Packers,
who have dominated the
National Football League
for the past few years
with an unprecedented
three consecutive NFL championships,
were the winners of the first Super Bowl,
defeating the Kansas City Chiefs
by a score of 35 to 10.
For many, the Packers
win came as no surprise.
Billy looks so cute in that
baseball cap you bought him.
I miss him already.
The over-powered their rival
lightening their lead 14 to 10 at the half.
To a 25 point margin.
The brakes are gone!
My God!
What's going on!
The President and Mrs. Reagan will attend.
The President is also
expected to announce his
new energy policy later today.
Stayed tuned to KEOS
for full world and
national news at 7 o'clock.
In local news, gasoline
prices are climbing again.
Flagstaff dealers say the average price
of a gallon by April, $1.45.
KEOS weather, sunny and warmer today,
with high's in the mid to
upper 60s, here at Flagstaff.
60 up in the canyon.
62 in Sedona, and 82 in the Phoenix area.
Increasing clouds toward-
Billy.
Wake up, Sweetie.
Five more minutes.
Okay, Billy.
But you're beginning to make this a habit.
Gonna have to start getting you up earlier.
Five more minutes.
Right.
Yeah!
Billy, don't eat that now!
I just made you breakfast.
Well can't you freeze it?
I gotta pick up Julie on my way to school.
What am I going to do with you?
What's the matter?
Do you see this?
This is a glass.
We use this for drinking.
Why dirty a glass?
I was thinking,
can I invite Julie over
for my birthday dinner?
Julie again? Sounds serious.
I think she's got a crush on me.
She does?
Billy's got a girlfriend, Billy...
Billy!
Don't do that, that's disgusting.
I am going to be your date tomorrow night.
Sorry.
Whatever makes you happy.
I'll see you tonight.
You make me happy.
Yeah.
That's fine, that's fine, that's fine!
You guys look like a basketball team!
All right, c'mon, set
'em up now, set 'em up!
All right, let's go, let's go,
shoot the other way now!
Pass the ball, c'mon!
Hey, that's a foul! Foul!
You only say foul,
because you're trying to
dribble through him now!
Eddie, you gotta move the ball to back,
you can't dribble through the guy.
C'mon let's go, let's bring it back.
Let's go, shirts!
Shirts ball, get back!
Watch your back door!
All right, you traveled now,
let's go, let's go back
the other way, here we go!
Set 'em up, set 'em up, here we go, c'mon!
Get 'em up, that's right.
C'mon!
C'mon, Eddie, play some defense, son!
All right, that's good,
that's good, good job.
Now get out of here,
I'm tired of looking at 'ya.
It's a good practice, Russ.
Billy, can I talk to you for a second?
Sure.
Good practice, looking
good, good, all right.
Listen, Eddie, I gotta talk
to Billy for just a second.
Listen, I'll talk to you
tomorrow, all right?
Go work out.
I got some great news for you.
I'd like you to meet me in my office
right after you shower, all right?
Hey, check it out.
Look at him, will you?
The coach's number one wimp.
Gee Julia, I gotta meet
Coach after I shower.
Oh, that's okay.
Thanks.
C'mon, let's go inside.
Hey, Lynch.
Next time keep your queer
hands off of me, okay?
I don't like to be touched.
Knock it off, Eddie.
I didn't foul you.
Bull!
Hey, what are you getting
so hot about, now, huh?
We're on the same team.
Yeah, I know.
It's just that some of us
think we're better than others.
Some of us are better than others.
We'll find out about that.
Oh thanks, Cheryl, you're a life saver.
Hope he wasn't too much trouble.
No, he's good as gold.
Just a minute, Frank.
What about tomorrow
night? Do you need any help?
No Marge, I'm okay.
Okay.
Listen! Frank knows this guy at work.
35 years old, a real hunk.
Margie, I'm not interested in dates,
blind, or otherwise.
In a minute, Frank!
You know, Billy's gonna be 17-
Bye, Margie.
You're gonna need a man around the house!
Oh, I know, I know.
See you tomorrow, thanks
for the pickled tomatoes!
I am coming!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Gotcha!
Julie, I hate it when you do that.
What are you doing here, anyway?
Well, I thought that you'd think-
You thought that I was going-
You think, forget it.
All right.
What took you so long?
I had to meet with Coach Landers.
For an hour? It's 6 o'clock.
Oh, six.
Hey listen, Julie, can I talk to you later?
See I didn't call Aunt Cheryl,
and you know how she gets about dinner.
Call her now.
I can't, I gotta go home.
There's something I
gotta talk to her about.
Okay, I didn't mean to upset you.
I'm sorry.
How about I give you a
ride home on my moped?
Billy, I'm wearing a skirt.
You can ride side side-saddle with me.
You are late.
And I'm fixing your favorite.
The meat sauce will never forgive you.
I had to take Julie home.
I had a long talk with
Coach Landers this afternoon.
He's got great news!
Oh.
Yeah.
See he thinks I can get a full scholarship
to the University of Denver.
And there's a scout, he's
coming out to our next game.
Well, what do you think, huh?
What do I think?
Forget it.
You got a job next
year, I've set it all up.
Yeah, but this is a
full athletic scholarship!
Denver, that's where
Julie's going, isn't it?
Yeah.
Gee, that'd be nice.
College is for rich kids
and people with brains.
You wouldn't fit in there.
You never said that before.
You always said we couldn't afford it.
You didn't say you didn't want me.
Well, I don't want you to!
We can't afford it.
Besides, I thought you were gonna stay here
and contribute something.
All we have left is Mommy's house.
But I was figuring you'd sell this place.
It's too big for you, anyway.
All my life, I've lived in this house.
All my memories are in it.
And they're not for sale.
And as far as I'm concerned, you owe me.
For the past 14 years
I've sacrificed everything
to bring you up.
Aunt Cheryl!
You're the man of this house-
You're staying here, and that's it!
You're taking that job!
I'm gonna get that scholarship if I can!
I'm going away to school,
and no one's gonna stop me!
Not even you!
You upset me.
I'm gonna go upstairs and
lay down, cook your own meal!
I don't care.
Extra sugar, I can't
stand it, that's for you.
So afraid.
Chuck, I don't know why.
It's just a birthday.
One more and he'll be gone.
Something will happen.
He'll see I need him.
Billy?
Wake up.
Hi.
Good morning.
Happy Birthday
Thanks!
I thought after last night-
Sshh! Read the card.
"For my nephew on his birthday.
"Some extra special love."
"P.S., good luck with the scholarship."
Hey!
Took me some time to
understand it, that's all.
You're terrific.
You know what we both need?
Is a big cup of coffee, I'm exhausted.
Oh, before I forget,
stop by Brody's TV Repair
before school, will you?
We paid $38 to have the
set fixed and it still won't work.
Why can't you call him?
You know him.
Tell him I want him here this afternoon.
I have to go shopping this morning.
Buy someone a present.
I can't believe it!
A scout from the University of Denver,
from my school is coming here.
You didn't even tell me!
Well, that's why I was so long
with Coach Landers yesterday afternoon.
Oh!
There you go.
It's your birthday.
Oh, thanks.
So why didn't you tell me then?
Well, I wanted to run
it by Aunt Cheryl first.
Excuse, guys.
So what did Aunt Cheryl say?
How'd she take it?
Well, she's working it out.
It's too good to be true.
I feel like it's my birthday.
I haven't got the scholarship yet.
You will!
Oh, I forget.
Happy Birthday!
You're leaving now?
Yeah, I finished.
Don't go.
Lady, you got to be kidding me.
I'm gonna give you a.
Look Lady, I'm just not interested, okay?
I won't tell, I promise!
I can't believe this.
Please! I need a man!
Well, it's not gonna be me!
Please! I'll let you do
anything to me you want!
All right.
How 'bout you doing me?
Work on it.
You stupid bitch!
Cher, what?
What'd you do?
You saw him, he tried to rape me.
You saw him, you saw him!
He tried to rape me!
Billy, Billy!
You saw him, you saw him!
Frank, let me have the cake.
If I know you, you'll drop it.
Thanks.
I hope she likes it, it's a new recipe.
Oh, and Frank,
be sure to say something
about her pickled tomatoes.
They were terrible.
Frank, if you can't say something nice,
don't say anything.
I won't say anything.
Good!
Well, you think she
could put a porch light on,
you break your neck-
Give me your arm.
For crying out loud.
Where's the bell?
Just knock real loud.
Well where is everybody?
Cheryl, Billy! You-hoo!
Hello?
Hello, hello?
Oh my God!
Oh, Shit!
Okay to remove the body?
Yeah, go ahead.
You buy attempted rape?
No. Do you?
No.
It wasn't his day.
Poor guy didn't even get his pecker out.
Yeah. How are the twins?
They're fine, Joe.
You gonna have that operation?
What operation?
The snipping.
Hell, no.
Billy, how long had you been home
before they arrived?
We've already been through this.
Let's go through it again.
I already told you.
You gonna tell me again, son.
Well I came home just before they got here.
And then what?
Well, I was coming up the back stairs,
and I heard some voices in the kitchen.
So I looked through the window.
And then I seen this
guy hunch over my aunt.
So I went in to help her.
To help her.
That's very good, Billy.
That's exactly word-for-word
what you told me before.
Did she help you memorize all that?
No.
Did she?
C'mon tell me the truth, son! Did she?
You stupid bully, he's telling the truth!
Why you doing this to us!
Because there's a dead
man laying out there,
and I wanna know why he died.
I killed him! He tried to rape me!
If it's a hollering contest you want,
you're sure as shit gonna loose.
Be nice to me, lady.
He tried to rape.
I disagree.
There isn't a bruise on a you.
Your clothing hasn't been torn.
And these two walk in and find junior here
holding the knife.
It's interesting, folks.
Hold it, Cook.
Are you all right?
I don't know.
I feel kind of scared.
Honey, everything's gonna be all right.
No, don't!
Billy!
I just need some air.
Maybe you should go with him, Frank.
I don't think I better.
He's all right.
He's just disappointed.
He won't be able to go away now.
Hold it, Billy!
Where you going?
Outside on the porch.
Stick around.
Come back.
Did you, or your aunt, know Phil Brody?
Well yeah, he's been
here a couple of times.
We didn't know him.
You didn't know him?
But you knew him?
Turn around.
What?
Turn around!
Did you actually see Phil
Brody try to rape your aunt?
Yes!
I'm shy, I can't hear you.
Yes.
Between you and me, Billy,
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
did you kill him?
No!
Right.
Miss Roberts!
Miss Roberts, would you come in here?
I wish he wouldn't yell.
You know, you don't
have to go through this,
you have your rights.
He's got to understand that I killed him.
Thank you, Miss Roberts.
I thought you were going outside.
I changed my mind.
You do make a lovely couple.
I wanna ask you a couple of questions.
Please have a seat.
May I have a seat? Thank you.
Now you said you weren't
married, is that correct?
Yes.
Are you divorced?
No.
Widowed?
But you do have boyfriends?
No.
Do you like girls, Miss Roberts?
God, you're a pig.
Just sick.
Why don't you stop tormenting her?
Are you talking to me, lady?
Yes.
Don't.
Billy, where are your parents?
They're dead.
Let the boy answer.
Well, my aunt's been taking
care of me since I was three.
Just the two of you in this big old house?
It must get awfully lonely.
No, we're good company for each other.
I bet you are.
You claim attempted rape.
I took at little peek
at this fellow, Brody.
It seems to me that
was fairly athletic fellow.
How come he didn't just
pin you down on the sofa?
He tried, but I got away.
Now you said he touched your booby.
What else did he do?
I refuse to answer any
more of your questions.
Lady, I don't give a shit what you do.
Lieutenant, I'm leaving now.
Then go ahead and leave, Cook.
Fascinating.
I thought you had practice this afternoon.
Well, we had a short session.
Oh.
Kind of warm for a fire, isn't it?
I'm cleaning out the attic.
This junk has been around here for years.
I thought I'd make you
a little apartment loft
out of that space upstairs for next year.
Well, I might be going away to-
You're gonna like it
when I finish, you'll see.
Don't go up there
until I tell you to, okay?
Well, what's wrong with-
Promise!
Sure.
Hey, by the way, did
Detective Carlson call today?
No, maybe he's forgot about us.
No, he was at school.
And he still wants me to
take the polygraph test.
I do not approve of you taking that test,
and I do not wanna discuss it again.
Is that clear?
Sure.
Shit!
Good Lord, what happened to you?
Are you all right?
I'm okay, I just tripped,
I'm all right, I'm all right.
Why are you only fully coordinated
on the basketball court?
You shouldn't had been up there anyway.
I know.
Who is that?
Who is that? What's the matter?
It's, just some twerp
your mother used to go out with.
Chuck Strang, his name was.
Clean all this stuff up for me, will 'ya?
Okay.
All right, John, take it up to basket,
take it up to the basket.
Ledge, why don't you save
that fancy stuff for EU, huh?
C'mon, Tony!
That's great, Tony, that's great.
You look real pretty,
the shot hit the goal.
Coach Lander?
Yeah?
I'm Detective Carlson,
I need to talk to you.
Yeah, we're in the middle of a drill,
can it wait for about five minutes?
No, it can't.
Is that Billy Lynch out there?
Yeah, that's Billy.
It's remarkable how tough today's youth is.
I mean, take Billy, just
a couple of days ago,
he witnessed a
particularly gruesome killing.
And take people in general.
I mean, there are people today
who loose a loved one,
and seem totally unfazed by it all.
I know it's your ring, Coach.
What is it?
Does it surprise you
much, if I had to make good?
I found this ring on Phil Brody.
The man who got killed.
Inside it says, "To P.B."
I take that to be Phil Brody.
"From T.L."
And I take that to be Tom Landers.
Yeah, that's you.
Yeah.
How does Billy fit into this?
Well it doesn't figure into this, Carlson.
I've coached the kid four years,
and I've watched him
become a real good ball player,
and I care about him.
I don't doubt that.
I suggest you resign.
If you don't, chances are you're
gonna get yourself lynched.
Yeah.
You have a nice afternoon.
Hey, Carlson!
Hi!
I had to tear the wall down.
You're the only one I can talk to.
Billy's not going, I fixed it.
He's gonna stay here with us.
Everything's going so wrong.
I just wanted to show
Billy I needed his protection.
I didn't mean to kill that man.
But he hit me, he hurt me.
Just like you did.
Miss Roberts?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What the hell are you doing in here!
Easy, lady.
What do you think you're doing?
I, I, I knocked, nobody answered.
Do you have a search warrant?
I heard a noise, I just
thought something was wrong.
The only thing that's
wrong is you're in my house.
Now get out of here!
Now look- Get out!
I just- Get out!
I just wanted to talk to you.
I don't wanna talk to you!
Now get out!
All right, all right.
Get out!
Hey Lynch! Did you hear
about your buddy, the Coach?
Yeah, Eddie.
Kind of interesting.
Billy, ignore him.
You were always in Lander's office.
I always thought you guys were...
You know.
What?
Real close, Lynch.
I mean, real close.
Billy!
Oh, shit!
Hit him hard! Hit him hard!
Get him!
I'm gonna kick your ass, Eddie.
I'm gonna kick it!
Billy!
I'm gonna kill you, Eddie!
Let go of him!
I'm all right.
Yeah.
Nice shot.
That was a lucky shot.
You got technique, pal.
Damn good moves on the basket.
Coach Landers teach you those?
Yeah.
Doesn't it bother you that he's a fag?
C'mon.
Tell me, Billy, are you a fag?
No!
I'm gonna ask you again.
And keep it mind that it pisses me off
when people lie to me.
Are you a fag?
You're crazy.
Phil Brody, remember him?
The man who got wasted here?
Well he was a fag.
And it doesn't make a
whole hell of a lot of sense
for a fag to be raping
your aunt, now does it?
It does make sense if you are a fag, too.
Now I'm just postulating.
But I believe that you and Phil Brody
were having a lover's quarrel.
And the thing got a little out of hand.
And your aunt walked in and saw you
with a knife in your hand,
and decided to take the wrap.
Isn't that the way it happened, man?
You filthy pig!
You think you got it all
figured out, don't you?
Well, you're wrong!
Maybe.
You do that, Billy, so help me, God.
I'll break your arm.
On your outside jump, stay loose.
Helps.
And your wrist, keep it limp, like.
That shouldn't be too difficult for you.
You know what they
don't teach you in school?
What?
How confusing and difficult
life can be sometimes.
You really don't understand, do you?
Billy, everything's gonna be all right.
It's not all right.
Carlson doesn't believe us.
He thinks he can prove I did it!
No, he can't.
We won't let him.
You're not making any sense.
Did you know that Coach
Landers was a homosexual?
No.
Billy?
No!
Do you know that
homosexuals are very, very sick?
Do you know that, Billy?
Coach Landers is not sick!
Billy! Billy!
Hey, Billy.
Yeah?
Aren't you gonna say hello?
Don't you mean goodbye?
I heard you quit.
Why you leaving?
Look, this is something that
I'm gonna have to fight in my own way.
And I just didn't wanna
be here when I did it.
Carlson came over yesterday.
He told my aunt you were gay.
Don't you worry about it, okay?
I know.
You know what?
He also says he can
prove that I killed Brody.
Look, don't let it worry you, all right?
I'll go check it out.
And man, listen, if there's
anything that I can do,
all right, you call me?
Sure, Coach.
Any time.
Yeah.
Take care, partner.
You, too. Take it easy.
See 'ya, Bill.
Rapes are 18%.
What the hell are you
people doing out there?
Child molestation is up 3%.
I want all these fucking
deviants off the street. Pronto?
Y'all got that?
What are you doing here, Nancy?
Fuck you!
And fuck you!
God-damn hookers.
All right, I don't want anything.
That's right, it's just
you and me, ain't it?
Here, you want a cookie?
Landers, I was just talking about you.
Yeah.
Billy Green.
Does the name ring a bell?
No?
One of two young boys molested last night.
I figured you might know
something about that.
Well, it was just a thought.
I understand you resigned. Smart move.
Good for everyone.
What do you want?
I forgot to tell you something, Carlson.
What?
Phil Brody used to be married.
That means that Cheryl Robert's story
might possibly be true.
Why you telling me this?
I thought it might help you.
Help me?
Or help your phat boy, Billy.
Carlson, what's your problem?
People like you.
Get the fuck out of my office.
Deviant, Mackie, you know what that is?
Fucking deviant.
The world is full of 'em.
Oh hey, I'm sorry about the
last couple days, you know?
I mean, it's been pretty rough.
But you gotta let me work it out on my own.
Well, are you?
No.
But you're sure you don't wanna be helped.
Everything's so screwed up.
Do you wanna talk about it?
No, not here.
What are you doing tonight?
What about Aunt Cheryl?
Oh, she's going to Sedona
with Margie and Frank.
She won't be home till later.
It's about time.
Thunder, calm down.
I'm fine. Mother!
Would you call Thunder upstairs?
Sorry.
Okay, I like dogs like that.
Can I help you?
Are you Julie Linden?
Mm-hmm.
I'm Lieutenant Carlson.
I need to talk with you.
It's kind of private,
do you mind taking a walk with me?
Okay.
Thank you, thank you.
How long have you and
Billy been going steady?
About a year.
Is it serious?
It is to me.
He's very special.
Well he certainly has had
an unusual background.
Do you find his relationship
with Aunt Cheryl a bit peculiar?
I guess, I don't know.
How's Billy with you?
I mean, is he strong,
aggressive, kind of?
Lieutenant, you seem to
have something on your mind.
I'd like to know what it is.
I need to know if you two are making it.
That's none of your business!
A man got killed.
Supposedly by a woman
who's claiming attempted rape.
The man was a homosexual,
an acquaintance of Billy.
I have a responsibility to find out
whether or not Aunt
Cheryl is covering for Billy.
And whether or not he's a homosexual, too.
That's ridiculous!
So tell me, are you two making it?
I'm not going to answer that.
Julie?
I think you just did.
He's more of a man than you'll ever be.
Humph,
okay.
Hey, you want something to drink?
Sure.
I'm on my way.
Hurry back, okay?
Okay.
This house gives me the creeps.
Billy, I didn't wanna tell you this,
but I don't feel right
keeping it from you, either.
What is it? More bad news?
Not bad news, exactly.
That Detective Carlson came by my house,
and he asked me some questions.
Like what?
General stuff, mostly.
And he asked me, how many,
how often we make love.
What did you tell him?
That it was none of his business.
Good.
How come we haven't more often?
Billy, is there something wrong?
Something you wanna tell me?
No.
Yeah.
You have a terrific body, you know that?
You really do.
And you're really sexy.
Billy!
You get dressed and
get that slut out of here!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Sergeant Cook, homicide.
Oh Jesus, you scared me!
I'm sorry.
What are you doing here?
Well, actually, I came to ask
Miss Roberts some questions,
but I'd like to talk to
you, if you don't mind.
Did she catch 'ya?
You might say that.
Well that's good.
That's good for Billy's case.
You see there's kind of
a strong feeling that he's-
I know.
Are you finished?
Yeah.
So am I.
Okay.
Billy, I wanna talk to you!
Well, I don't! Okay!
Billy!
Do you mind!
I want you to promise me
that you will never do that again!
Hand me a towel.
Jesus, Aunt Cheryl, I'm 17 years old!
And it's not the end of the world!
I want you to listen to me!
No!
Do you promise?
Okay.
That's a good boy.
God!
Perverts and sluts!
They're doing everything they
can to take him away from us.
Did you know that he's
still thinking of leaving?
Sure you did.
You know everything, don't 'ya?
But he won't, 'cause
I'm gonna keep him here.
The same way I kept you here.
He'll never leave us.
Cook, walk with me.
Julie Linden's mother called
and complained about you
scaring the shit out of her daughter.
What were you doing out there?
Well, I was just checking.
See, I don't think that Billy Lynch
had anything to do with the murder.
I kind of see it different.
Oh, is that right?
And how is that?
Well for one thing,
Miss Roberts caught Julie
and the boy in the sack together.
That kind of weakens the fag theory.
The victim was a fag.
The coach is a fag.
And the kid is a fag.
He grew up without a father,
with only women around.
It's a classic case, Cook.
All right, all right.
There's something else.
This is from the "Flagstaff Courier",
September 12, 1967.
Bill and Ann Lynch, the boy's parents,
were killed yesterday outside Flagstaff
when their car crashed into a logging truck
on Interstate 89.
The cause is thought to
have been brake failure.
Now I talked to a few of the locals,
and they remembered that there were rumors
about the brakes being tampered with.
Cook,
I hope you're doing this
shit on your own time.
Because I forbid from
doing it on department time.
Incredible.
Schmuck.
Billy, can I talk to you?
Is it important? I'm in a hurry.
It's very important.
Billy, please?
Come sit down.
I thought you'd like a glass of milk,
some of your favorite chocolate
chip cookies for good luck.
I mean it, Billy.
I know how important tonight is for you.
I want you to know that if
you get that scholarship,
I'm behind you, 100%.
Good luck tonight, Billy.
I know you're in a hurry,
take these with you.
Mm, thanks.
Go get 'em. I'll be there.
See you later.
Bye!
Good luck!
Thanks!
The scout from Denver's
here, I know you'll get it.
I hope so.
I'm feeling kind of dizzy,
but it's a hell of a time to
come down with something.
Don't worry, you'll be all right!
This way, it's a point shot, all right?
You got hit.
You sure? All right.
Take it easy, all right.
Take your time.
Take it easy.
I'm okay, okay, okay.
Billy!
Billy, honey, honey.
Honey?
We're going home.
Hello, there! Welcome back!
You've been sleeping
on and off for 14 hours.
Where am I?
Remember I told you
the attic could make a
nice little apartment for you?
Well, you like?
I guess so.
I knew you'd be thrilled.
What happened at the game?
Honey, you slipped, or something.
You had a nasty fall.
You hit your head hard.
What time is it?
Noon.
Oh my God.
Where do you think you're going, young man?
School.
I promised I'd meet Julie by one o'clock.
Did anybody call?
No, no one called.
You stay right here.
You don't wanna go
back there anyway, Billy.
You learned enough.
Besides, it's full of perverts.
You stay here with
me, I'll teach you things.
Oh, look what I found
when I was cleaning up.
Look.
Your father gave this to your
mother when they got married.
I don't, you-
She had it on when she died.
No!
All right. I'll put it in here for you.
Hungry?
Sort of.
Why don't I come down?
You stay right there, you need your rest.
I'll bring you something up.
You can get washed if you want to.
Whoop!
You're so cute.
"Dear Cheryl,
"even though we've only
know each other for two weeks,"
"I know this is the start of
something very special-"
What do you think you're doing?
Nothing.
I'm just looking.
You're lying!
You're going through my private belongings.
That's very rude!
I don't want you to ever do that again!
Why didn't you tell me the truth?
About what?
Chuck Strang was your
boyfriend, not my mother's!
Honey!
Phil Brody didn't try to rape you, did he?
Billy!
He did!
You know he did.
You saw it!
Aunt Cheryl, there's something wrong.
You're lying to me.
Why would I ever wanna lie to you?
Lock her up.
Sit down.
Donde?
Ay, yah.
Sit down on the fucking floor.
Donde es su casa?
Aqui.
Bullshit!
Donde es su casa en Mexico?
Joe?
What?
I got some more information
on Cheryl Roberts.
Could you do me a favor
and keep it to yourself?
The more I find out about that woman,
the stranger she gets.
She dated a guy in high
school named Chuck Strang.
An older guy, not a local.
One day he just disappeared.
Left his clothes and everything.
Hasn't been heard of since.
You look tired, Cook.
You need some rest.
Go on home.
As a matter of fact,
I don't even mind if you go on vacation!
That's better.
Stop it, you! You're always teasing me.
I know, I cut it off.
You made me!
You're happy, aren't you?
Just you and me, and Billy.
No one's every gonna take him from us.
I feel so good.
Don't you?
You gotta help me.
She hates me, she won't talk to me.
Well yeah, she will.
If you go up to the house,
you can distract her for a few minutes,
then I can find out
what's in that jewelry box.
Okay.
Miss Roberts?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What are you doing in here!
I told you that Billy is
under doctor's orders to rest!
I know, I didn't come to see him.
I came to apologize.
I don't want any apologies from you!
I am inviting you to get out of here!
No! Not until I said what I came to say!
You can talk till you're blue in the face.
I saw you the other night.
I know what you do.
I hope you're not gonna
make me throw you out of here.
Miss Roberts, I just wish
you could understand.
Billy and I really love each other.
I still think of Billy as my little baby.
Everything moved so fast.
Yesterday's become
tomorrow's before you even blink.
I do understand.
I had a boyfriend once.
I do understand, Honey!
C'mere.
Oh, Honey.
I have another round
sitting in the refrigerator.
Honey, could you get it for me?
Sure.
Oh, you're so caring.
Thank you.
Hello, hello! It's me, Margie!
Hello?
Cheryl?
Hi, Margie.
Oh, hi!
What?
Your hair! What did you do?
You like?
Yeah.
I did it myself.
I think it makes me look younger.
Oh, definitely, yes.
Oh yeah, I love it.
It's different.
Thanks.
Hi, Margie. Hi, Cheryl.
Hi, Billy.
Billy! I thought you were upstairs!
Where have you've been?
Didn't you get my note?
No.
Well, I had to go to Julie's
house to give her books.
Her mother said she was coming over here.
Well, did she come?
Well, didn't she?
No, she came by, she had to leave.
She said she'd call you later.
Here you go.
Doctor says he's gotta have lots of milk.
Cheryl, what'd you do to your hair?
Don't you just love it?
Why, it's the latest thing.
I brought you some of my
homemade cheesecake.
And look, some new sports magazines.
Basketball.
Oh sit down, Billy, we'll all have some.
You know, some one was out of work
at Frank's office for three weeks!
Isn't this fun? It's like having a party.
And then my sick boy is
going straight upstairs to bed.
You really should take
care of yourself, Billy.
Maybe I should've brought
my chicken soup instead.
The doctor said the only way
to get rid of it is plenty of sleep.
Billy!
Oh, he's coming out of it.
Hi, Honey. Don't talk.
I still say you should call a doctor.
Margie, you have said that 10 times now,
he'll be fine, thank you.
Why don't you go home?
I don't need you any more.
I see.
Well, obviously you know what you're doing.
I just wanted to be of some help.
But if don't want me- I don't!
All right.
She seems to think
I need help taking care of you.
Oh, the reason that I
brought you into this room,
is that I didn't want her to
know about our little room.
You, Ma-
Save your strength,
Honey; Save your strength.
Oh.
The note.
I'm your mother.
Chuck.
Chuck's your father.
He was gonna leave me.
Just like you were gonna leave me.
He said he didn't love me.
Wasn't going to marry me.
So my sister and her husband adopted you.
But then I wanted you back.
So I had-
Be right back.
Hello?
No.
No, I haven't seen her all day.
Mrs. Linden, if Julie was
here, I would of seen her.
To the airport?
Why don't you take a cab?
I don't really care.
No, you cannot talk to him, he's very sick.
Yeah, I'll tell her, if I see her.
I thought you told Billy
that Julie had been here.
Do you always listen on
other people's phone conversations?
I wasn't listening, I was-
What are you doing here?
I closed your windows.
It looks like it's gonna rain.
You better go, Margie.
Do you mind if I use
your phone to call Frank?
I don't wanna get caught in the rain.
There's an umbrella in the broom closet!
You better use it.
Then go.
Would you hold, please?
Just one second.
Julie Linden's mother.
I don't wanna talk to her.
I already told her you were here.
Thanks.
Hello, Miss Linden?
Look, I'm sorry about...
What time was she supposed to pick you up?
I see.
I think Miss Roberts is
kind of peculiar myself.
Well maybe I should just
stop by and take a look.
Bye-bye.
What's wrong?
Is Westcott working the Injun Road area?
Yes.
I'm going out there.
Tell him to stop by the Robert's place,
and tell Carlson where I am.
Little boy Billy all dressed in blue
I love you
Yes I do
Little boy Billy with eyes so brown
Come to me, come lie down
I found the umbrella.
I'm leaving now.
Little boy, Billy.
You will drink it!
Drink it!
I spoke to Chuck about you.
It's all your fault. He agrees!
Drink the rest of this.
What a little messy baby.
I'll be back.
It's time to go to bed.
I'll be downstairs.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Cheryl! No!
Julie!
No!
Come here, slut.
Here, slut.
No!
My God!
Who are you talking to?
No one.
Girlfriend?
Forget it.
I'm your girlfriend now.
Honey.
I won't go.
Oh, I know you won't go.
I promise.
I know you won't go.
Chuck planned to go.
I put him down there where he belongs.
He's with me forever.
But a rotten sister.
She tried to take you away from me.
I took care of her, too.
Don't ever make me do that to you.
You promise?
I promise.
You little lying shit!
You're a lying bastard!
You're lying!
You lying bastard! You lying bastard!
Hello?
Hello? Coach Landers?
All right, this is Billy Lynch.
You all right?
I need your help.
My mother's dead.
Whoa, wait, your mother,
what are you talking about?
My mother's dead, I just killed her.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
All right, hold on, I'll be right there.
I killed my mother.
Mother!
Mother, Mother.
One is dead, Lieutenant.
You've seen Cook?
Yeah, he's dead.
Captain, I'm going in there.
Don't hold your breath, Billy.
Don't, just keep breathing.
You keep breathing.
There's nothing pumping
down there, there's nothing.
Ow!
Get your hand away from it.
You'll be all right.
Get away from there!
Back up.
Well, you really did it, Billy.
Hey, Lieutenant!
Oh, God!
Julie!
Which of you two assholes killed Cook?
No!
It was her. She killed him.
Look in the basement.
Get on the radio and get
her some medical attention.
Right away!
Shouldn't I check the basement?
She saw Miss Roberts kill Cook.
Carlson, the girl said-
I don't care what she says!
Get home!
No! No!
You son of a bitch!
Yeah!
Okay, Billy, here you go.
Not there!
Drop the gun, give me the gun.
Give me the gun!
C'mon, give me the gun!
Billy, give me the gun.
You're not gonna shoot nobody.
C'mon, give me the gun.
Give me the gun, Billy!
C'mon, give it to me!
Oh shit, drop it.
Billy!
Oh, Billy.
Julie.
Billy.