Hey, dog, I caught us some dinner!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Pancakes?
Aah!
Pancakes!
[dramatic music]
[instrumental music]
- Now you're gonna love it.
There's no professors,
there's no papers
there's just peace
and relaxation
the entire time.
And relentless pounding
for, like, 6 days.
[laughter]
-Gross. And beer!
Don't forget about the beer.
-And how can we forget
about beer with you in the car?
[music continues]
[gasps]
-Rise and shine!
-Aah, such an asshole.
I gave up two weeks
in Belize for this?
-Oh, come on.
You're gonna like this.
The cabin's gonna be great,
you're gonna love it.
-Mm-hmm.
[instrumental music]
-Creepy.
[music continues]
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
-Hey, there, little man.
[screaming]
Dammit!
-What the hell's
going on out here?
-Dennis!
Goddammit, what'd I tell you
about biting city folk?
-Hey, it's not his fault.
Take it easy on him.
-Take it easy?
Don't you tell me
how to raise my boy, boy.
Dennis isn't like
the other children.
Everybody knows
you don't talk to him.
-Maybe you should
make a sign, for the rest of us.
-Come on, get outta here.
There's a hose around back,
you wanna wash that hand up.
It's the best I can offer.
-Paul, you okay?
-Yeah. I'm fine.
-Hey, deliverance!
Is it smart leaving
your kid out here
knowing he's a danger to people?
-What are you
trying to say exactly?
-What I'm saying is that
such an incident
may result in a lawsuit.
You may be held liable.
-We don't know nothin'
about that around here.
Come on, Tommy.
-Peace and relaxation,
remember?
-God.
-What just happened?
[intense music]
[grunts]
-Aah, shit.
Freakin' hillbilly vampires.
-I'd be careful with that.
-What is it?
-This is fox piss.
You don't wanna drop that on you
you'll have every animal in the
county wanting to hump your leg.
-Hm.
-You should get
some of that for your mom.
-Mm.
-I'm gonna go get the beer.
-You kids here on vacation
or you just passin' through?
-Vacation.
-Ah. Well.
I hope you enjoy
our little slice of heaven
as much as we do.
-You okay?
-Yeah.
I'll be fine, just, just kids.
-Ah, I have a first aid kit
in the car, will grab it.
-Thanks.
-Ah, seeing as
you're such a fine group
I feel it's my..
...civic duty to warn you.
Be careful out there.
Especially..
...you go hiking in those woods?
-What's in the woods?
-Bad stuff.
-It's nothing we can't handle.
I'm sure.
-Lyme's Disease
is pretty bad in these parts.
All I can say is
check for ticks.
-Why, what happened?
-Few hikers got
real sick last week.
Uh, doctors took care of them,
I guess.
-What do you mean, uh,
what do you mean you guess?
- Hey, hey. Hey, hey. Hey!
-What?
-You wanna give me
one good reason
why you'd steal
a Snicker's bar? Huh?
-Would you believe me if I
told you it was for the nougat?
-The nouga-what now?
-Never mind.
Look, I'm sorry. Really.
Seriously, I, sometimes I just
take things, I don't know why.
-Get the hell outta here!
-Yeah, okay.
-Goes for the rest of you
as well, get outta here
before I call the sheriff.
-What? It was an accident.
- An accident?
[engine revving]
[intense music]
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
[horn blaring]
[instrumental music]
[music continues]
-Hey, listen to this.
"Welcome and enjoy your stay.
"Real remote mountain getaways.
"If you're looking for fun
you've come to the wrong place."
I think w-we'll have fun.
-Wow, this place is amazing.
Your mom really hooked this up,
except I can't find the TV?
- You coming?
-I'm not getting any bars.
Um, so no phone, and
I'm guessing no internet there.
-Whoa, wa-wa-whoa-oh-oh.
No internet?
Ha ha. No weed.
No GTA V, no Black Ops II
no Stimpy, no Minecraft,
no...weed?
-You mentioned weed twice.
-Yeah, I know. On purpose.
What, we're talking a whole week
here, there's no way.
Dude, my clan needs me.
-Just think of this as gamer
rehab, you'll get over it.
-But I don't wanna
go to gamer rehab.
[chuckles]
[instrumental music]
-You brought a gun?
-Okay, firstly,
it's not a gun.
It's a rifle.
More specifically,
an assault rifle.
Second, we're in the woods,
so I thought I'd practice
my survival skills.
-Don't you think
that's a little overkill?
-No.
Fully upgraded.
Barely legal.
I won't even go into
the tech specs
on this beast 'cause you
couldn't handle it.
-You're gonna
accidentally shoot one of us.
-Never happened.
I've years of training.
[Paul laughing]
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Video games don't count.
Will you just be
careful with that thing?
-Okay, will you relax?
I'm perfectly responsible.
[gunfire]
-Jesus, dude.
-My bad. My bad.
-Just keep
that thing away from me.
-Cool.
[grunting]
Whoa!
Epic.
I'm about to go ham
on some indigenous beastie.
[phone camera clicking]
-What happened to no signal?
-I can still post stuff.
It'll upload,
it'll just take longer.
-You could just
put that down and enjoy this.
[laughs]
-So, Karen..
...how long have we
known each other for?
-That's a weird question.
-Hm.
-I don't know,
was just thinkin'.
-Just thinkin'?
[chuckles]
Um..
...gosh, I don't know.
4th grade?
That's a long time.
-It's a long time.
¶ I find it strange
find it strange ¶
¶ That you're wandering
in this place ¶
-We gonna go swimming?
¶ I thought it changed
thought it changed ¶
¶ But the more
it stays the same ¶
I'll race you to the island!
¶ Some things are made
yeah they're made ¶
¶ To never separate ¶
¶ Have I ¶¶
¶ Car I need everything ¶
¶ Those clothes
I need everything ¶
¶ Like kicks I need everything ¶
¶ Them hoes I need everything ¶
¶ Your bitch I need everything ¶
¶ That gold I need everything ¶
¶ That work I need everything ¶
¶ That dough
I need everything ¶¶
[sighs]
-You know Toby Brown?
-Yeah.
Greasy Toby,
the guy with the OCD?
-Yeah. That and ADD.
He tried to kiss me.
-He did?
-Mm-hmm.
Two days ago.
It's weird, it's like..
...this family friend
I've had for 12 years.
Just...he put his hands on my
face and tongue down my throat
and it was, was gross.
It was just bad.
-What, was it...gross because
you'd known him for so long
or...because he's gross?
-Mm...it was definitely him.
[chuckles]
You know how, like,
sometimes you've known someone
a really long time
and you just wanna kiss 'em just
to see if they're a good kisser?
-Yeah.
-I don't think there's
anything wrong with that.
-Where are you going?
-Swimming.
[shrieks]
-Thought we were kissing!
-We were.
[instrumental music]
-Oh, shit.
Janny, I'm coming up
on your seven.
Fraggo!
Poof!
Aah! I think I just got
a team killed to save you guys.
It's all good, move it up!
[grunts]
Ninja3609..
...do you copy?
Agent36? Shit, they got him.
Shit, of course, now it's on.
[gunshots]
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Whoo!
God, that's most good.
-Aah!
-Oh, no! Oh, no.
Oh, no.
-You shot me!
-No fucking way.
Oh, my God, I'm sorry, man.
I am so sorry!
-Help me!
-Okay, okay. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Don't come near me, man, okay?
Stay back.
-Help me!
-Okay, okay, stay back.
-Ugh!
-Hey, stay back!
I said stay back!
[yells]
I'll get you some help,
just stay there!
Please!
Holy shit.
Fuck.
-Help me!
Help me!
[groaning]
-Oh, my God.
What the...fuck?
Aah!
-Bert. Hey.
Bert, come here! Come here.
- Holy shit.
-What are you doing?
What, were you trying
to burn the whole place down?
What's wrong with you?
-What are you?
Smokey the Clown?
-You mean Smokey the Bear?
-Seriously though,
how old are you?
We can't leave you alone
for five minutes without
you burning the place down?
And he brought a gun. Great, so,
what were you shooting at?
-Squirrels.
I was shootin' some squirrels.
-Okay.
-What is wrong with him?
- Video game
withdrawals maybe.
-What are you gonna roast
on that thing?
-Squirrel, if we even get one.
-I'm a vegetarian.
[laughing]
-So, Paul, tell your story.
-No, no, man, it's..
It's too traumatic.
I don't want to talk about that.
-We like traumatic stories.
I mean, not about me,
but in general.
-Plus trauma bonds people
so you can totally
talk to us about it.
-Trauma bonds people
who experience it
not the people
that you tell the story --
-Just tell the story!
-Fine. Fine.
[laughing]
-We used to go to this
bowling alley
Lenny Meads Brighton Bowl,
you remember it?
-It was in Brighton, right?
-Yeah, that's why
it's called Brighton Bowl.
-Okay, guys.
- Anyway, every weekend
I would go there either
with my dad or for a birthday
party or whatever.
One weekend I asked my dad
if we were going?
He said, no.
He said the alley was closed.
Apparently,
some disgruntled employee
was holding all the other
employees at gunpoint.
The police said that he tied
each hostage
to a chair and arranged them
in a circle.
That way everyone was forced
to look at one another.
Then after that they've been
gagged and beaten
this maniac breaks out
a ball-peen hammer
and one by one..
...smashes in the back
of their heads.
[laughs]
-Can you imagine
dying like that?
Just watching
all of your friends dying
knowing you're next?
-I can't.
-That's not all.
This guy doesn't stop,
he breaks out the fire axe.
The alarm sounds,
but he doesn't care.
He hacks off
all of their limbs
dismembers them completely.
When the police arrived
they just found
6 bloody torsos
tied to those colored
bowling chairs, remember?
Blood everywhere.
No sign of the killer though.
-And that was your childhood
playground?
-Yeah.
-True story.
-Oh, my God, you were lying?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
-No, it's true..
You can look it up.
-You fuckers.
-It's not a funny story.
It's Jeff's face
that's making me laugh.
[gasps]
Shit!
-Where the fuck
did you come from?
-You spyin' on us?
-No, not at all.
Just saw your campfire.
I was out on a midnight hike, I
thought I'd come and say hello.
I haven't seen
anybody up here in a week.
-Um, can you do
something about--
-Dr. Mambo.
His name is Dr. Mambo.
At least that's what I call.
He seems to like it.
-Psychiatrist or pediatrician?
-Little of both, I guess.
-What are you doing out here?
-Same thing you guys are.
Enjoying nature.
Some of the best free climbing
is right here in this valley.
-I hate heights.
-It's definitely
not for everybody.
So you don't mind if I sit here
and chill out with you guys
for a bit, do you?
-Actually we're having
a private conversation
so if you don't mind..
-No worries.
I get it.
-I guess I'll just take
this big bag of weed
and smoke it all by myself.
-Oh, hey..
-No, no, no..
-Are you sure?
-Hey, no..
-I'm so sorry.
What's your name?
-Connor.
But you can call me Grim.
-Grim like, uh, Grimace or..
-No...just Grim.
Like that..
Like the Grim Reaper.
I figure I'm gonna die up
in these mountains anyway
so...I don't know..
Just a nickname.
I didn't beg it.
I just came up here
from Berkeley.
Now that's a party town.
-Karen was just there.
-Oh, yeah?
-Yeah.
Oh, my gosh,
I met these guys in..
They won't let me drink
anything but beer
for, like, 5 days.
Just solid.
-I've done that.
I got drunk.
-Actually, it sounds
like a pretty cool idea.
Only drinking beer.
-I could do it.
I don't know if you could.
-If that is a challenge, sir,
then I accept.
-Alright, fine,
from here on out,
we'll only drink beer.
-Deal.
[thunder rumbling]
-Looks like rain
is headed our way.
It's gonna be a wet one.
-Yeah. Party's over.
-Why don't you, uh, come up
for a minute and hang out?
-That's cool, but, uh,
I gotta get back to my tent.
I left all my gear out
and if it gets wet
that $4000 destroyed.
- How far is your campsite?
-It's about 20 minutes
give or take
but, uh, I'm coming back.
-Can you bring the weed?
-Absolutely.
[thunder rumbling]
-Alright, Dr. Mambo.
Let's hit it.
[chuckling]
-That was pretty weird.
-He was okay.
[thunder rumbling]
-So how did you do it?
[chuckles]
-What do you mean how?
It.. It was..
Okay, had different settings
like, pulse, power, stream
all different kinds of speeds
and, uh..
that was on this length of hose
that I could reach
when I lay down in the tub.
[Karen laughs]
-Wait, did you come
every time?
-Absolutely. Yeah.
Imagine my disappointment
the first time I had sex.
[laughs]
-Tell me about it.
-What's that supposed to mean?
-Wait, I have a better story.
-Bullshit, you do.
-Nothing beats stories
about Karen
and her parents shower massage.
-Thank you.
[knocking on door]
-Oh, it must be the weed guy.
Okay. Alright.
[knocking continues]
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Oye, Grimace, I'm comin'.
-It's Grim.
-Yup, whatever.
-Help me.
-Oh, my God.
-I'm burnin'.
Help me.
I need a doctor.
-Uh, g -- get him a blanket.
-Oh, shit!
-You..
It's you.
-No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no way
I'm letting that
contagious freak in.
-No, no, Bert, he's sick
and he needs help, okay?
-What? No, look at him.
I mean he's got something.
He's got something bad.
-But we need to call him
a doctor or call someone.
-Okay, no, no, no,
we don't have any receptions.
-Oh, shit, that freak
is going to the car.
-What?
- Oh, wait, what?
What's he doing? What?
-Oh, fuck!
- Oh, my God.
-Hey, hey-hey, hey. Hey!
Hey! Get the fuck out.
Hey, get the fuck out
of the car.
Get the fuck out of the car!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Oh, what the fuck!
-Melting..
- Paul, come here and get him.
Paul!
-Hey, hey, hey.
[Karen screams]
-Hey!
-Hey, freeze!
Look at me!
Look at the guy with the gun.
Hey, get out of the car.
-No! Shoot the crazy guy,
not the car.
- Jeff, do something.
-No, no, stay back,
stay back!
-Get the fuck..
[screaming]
Go!
Oh, my God.
Help me.
[screaming]
[thunder rumbling]
- Look, what were we gonna do?
I mean this guy,
he gets in the car
he gets this shit all over the
inside of the car
he comes at us..
I don't want him to touch me.
I don't want him to touch
any of us.
It was self-defense.
And it's raining,
so it probably put him out.
-This is some
serious real shit.
They are worse.
I mean, it looked like something
was eating his skin..
...like biohazard style.
Like quarantine.
-I think we should tell
the police it wasn't our fault.
We should tell them...now.
We have -- we have to go
tell them right now. Please.
-That's where the reality
comes in. We can't.
I'm not about to ride
in that car
with that dude's blood
all over it.
Come on.
Tomorrow we can clean it up,
fix the tire
whatever else is wrong with it,
and report the accident.
The keyword here is accident.
-That guy's skin..
Holy shit.
[instrumental music]
-What's the plan?
-Divide and conquer.
-You better leave me
the rifle.
-He's right.
-What? Wait a second.
I'm not the one who went
ballistic last night.
-What's that supposed to mean?
-It means you raged
out of control, that's what.
-Well, that's fucked up.
-What was fucked up is you
beating the shit out of my car
with your fuckin' bat.
-What about Captain Jackoff
over here
with the assault rifle,
you forget about him?
-Alright, look,
we all fucked up the car.
-You guys are just gonna keep
arguing or maybe do somethin'
about it.
-Where you goin'?
-To get help.
[intense music]
-She's right.
[music continues]
[footstep approaching]
-I've brought you some water.
-Jeff and Bert have --
-I know.
-I know you know it.
Look, last night, we --
-Paul, somebody came
to our door and asked for help
and we lit him on fire...okay.
He could be anywhere out there,
and I just wanna go home.
-Karen, it wasn't our fault.
We didn't mean to do it.
Everything happened so fast.
It was an accident.
-Was it?
I don't know about you,
but every time I close my eyes
I see him burning,
I can see him screaming
and his skin crackling and
the smell of his burning hair.
-We saw him when he came
on the door last night.
He was very sick.
He was going to die anyway.
-You don't know that.
Oh, my God.
-Look..
Look, I can't change
what happened last night.
I wish I could, but I can't.
But if we just work together
we can fix this.
Okay?
-Okay.
-Alright then.
Better?
-Yeah.
Thank you.
-Okay.
-I feel like, we're gonna get
lost.
-We're not gonna get lost.
[music continues]
That place
just gotta have a phone.
-Uh, yeah..
It looks kinda creepy.
-Don't be a wuss.
Let's go check it out.
[howling]
[intense music]
[woman grunting]
-God damn, rot!
You see this?
You see this shit?
This is the third sick hog
this month.
You tell Marie I can't eat this!
There's some goddamn animal
runnin' around here
infecting everything.
Now what am I supposed
to do with a sick hog, huh?
Huh?
I'm not about to eat this meat.
Would you?
-N -- no.
No, I -- I -- I'm a vegetarian.
-That has nothin'
to do with it
because you know
all this stuff is no good.
It's all sick.
It all has to go back.
I want me a new hog.
-Yeah, um,
we just need a mechanic
and we're just wondering --
-A mechanic?
You're not gonna find one here
you got to go into town
for that.
-Uh, yeah, right.
That -- that's the, um, ahem,
the problem.
Our car is busted,
so we can't get into town.
We need someone
to take us to town
to get a mechanic.
-I already been in town
already today. Sorry.
-Uh, well, if you're going to
town again, can you let us know?
We're just stayin' at a cabin
a few miles down the road.
[intense music]
-I'm sorry.
Of course, of course.
Heck, why didn't you just come
right out with it?
Here I am pracklin' on
about my hog
and you just wanna find somebody
who's gonna find you a mechanic.
Come on up to the house.
I got a radio inside.
We'll call Ricky.
Uh, he's got a tow truck.
-That's actually great.
-Yeah, great.
-Thank you. Ricky.
[thunder rumbling]
Sorry to bother you,
but we really appreciate this.
Some crazy guy came out
of the woods
just tryin' to trash our car
or break into it or somethin'.
-Sounds terrible.
Uh, you two wanted
somethin' to drink?
-Oh, yeah.
-Yeah, please, thank you.
-Uh, you said this person
damaged your car?
-Yeah, it was this crazy
hermit guy, like, really
dangerous.
We just scared him off with bats
and everythin'.
-Crazy hermit guy?
I --it wasn't Henry, was it?
[music continues]
-Um, Henry..
-No.
Uh, my Cousin Henry.
Uh, he knows better than that.
Did you say
you hit him with bats?
-No.
-No, no, no.
What he means is, uh, no.
It wasn't Henry,
it was our friend, Walter.
-It was Walter.
- Our friend, Walter.
This crazy friend Walter.
He's.. He was drunk.
-Oh, that's not good.
-Uh, y -- you know what?
Let's forget the tow truck.
It's turning into such a nice
day. We'll just walk.
-Yeah. Yeah, yeah,
we'll fix ourselves.
-Yeah.
-A -- are you sure?
-Yeah, absolutely.
Thank you so much.
-Thank you, really.
-Well, uh, suit yourselves,
I -- I..
-I can't believe
we burned Cousin Henry.
-I know.
[instrumental music]
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
[all screaming]
[exhales sharply]
-Fuck. Did you find anybody?
-Nothing. Nobody's home.
-Place is locked up
pretty tight.
-Do you think the police
know about this yet?
-I doubt it.
If they did, they'd be
at the cabin already.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
-Whoa, whoa! Easy, easy.
-Town boy, that's how people
get themselves shot around here.
-Deputy Winston, Bunyan County
Sheriff's Department.
-What can I do for you?
-I'm just out here on patrol.
It's my jurisdiction.
I understand you guys
had a little commotion here
last night.
I was hopin' you could tell me
somethin' about that.
-Sure, sure. Uh, some...guy
tried to enter our cabin.
Uh, he was sick, really sick.
I don't know
what kind of disease he had
but he was a mess, and..
-Yeah. Ahem.
I kinda have to report this.
-My friends are out lookin'
for a neighbor right now
so we could call you.
We don't have a phone up here.
-No, most people got radios.
That's what I've got.
It looks like you guys were
having some kinda party
last night, huh?
-Yeah, you know,
w-we were drinking
and then this guy came along
and tried to..
He tried to break
into our cabin, and, you know
uh, we had no choice,
but to get rough with him
and we didn't know what to do --
-Stop talkin'.
-Yes.
[chuckles]
-Look, man, I already told
you, makin' a report.
That guy isn't gonna come back
and bother you.
I'll bet you scared him off
pretty good, huh?
Besides...I won't let him
ruin the fun.
[intense music]
-Thanks
'cause...my friend's inside
and she's pretty upset
about the whole thing.
She wants to go home.
We all do.
-Mm, lady friend, huh?
-I'll bet you like to party.
I bet you like to party
with the ladies.
-Paul?
-Hey. Is everything okay?
-Oh, hey there, sugar.
Oh, everything is, uh,
it's just fine.
Why don't you take your
pretty little self back inside
just relax, put your feet up
and, uh, pop up another 40.
It's all good.
-Okay.
Ahem. Okay, then.
-Shit.
Now that girl is hot.
If you're askin' me,
you gotta stay and party.
- Oh, you know,
that's why we came here
in the first place.
-Yeah, boy..
...ain't this some kind
of wonderful...shit?
I'd say that creep really did
a number on your jeep here.
-Do you think you can get
someone up here to fix it?
-Of course. I'm not an idiot.
I'll take care of you.
I could probably have
someone here by, uh
I don't know,
tomorrow afternoon?
I want you to know you're
in my top priority..
...'cause you're my party man..
...and this is party town.
We're all gonna party, right?
-Yeah.
-Yeah?
-You know how to find me?
-Dial 911?
-That's right.
Yeah, that's right.
Take care of that little peach
in there.
She sure looks sweet.
[engine starts]
[instrumental music]
-This is bullshit.
[gags]
Oh, shit.
So is she gonna report it
or not report it?
-I don't think she is.
But she didn't make it sound
like we did anything wrong.
She said she'll have a tow truck
up here by tomorrow.
-Sounds...weird.
-It was.
-How's Karen? Has she come out
of her room yet?
-No, I think she's sleeping.
Dude, I don't know
what's up with her
but she wants to get out
of here as soon as possible.
-Well, that kinda screws up
your plan, doesn't it?
-What plan?
-Uh, the plan you're being
trying to execute since..
...what, 8th grade?
-There's no plan.
Not anymore.
-Alright.
Well, she's a head case anyway.
All chicks are.
-Why makes you say that?
-Look at her.
I mean, you like her
'cause she's nice to you
and she likes you
'cause she can control you.
-Bert, don't move.
[dramatic music]
[growling]
-Man, it's that freak's dog.
Hey, pooch.
Hey, Mister Tango.
What the..
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa,
don't, don't piss it off.
-Should I hit it?
-If you hit it,
you better hit it hard.
[growling]
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
[intense music]
[gunshot]
-Where'd you learn
to shoot like that?
-I have 2 brothers.
Also you're not
the only gamer here.
-Whoa, cool!
-What the fuck?
Did you see how messed up
that dog was?
-Yeah.
So where's Grim?
- Thank you.
- I'll tell you where he is.
He's out there rotting.
There's some shit in that woods.
And cousin Henry's
spreading it around.
And I'm not waiting
for the deputy to get back
I say we leave right now.
-Shouldn't we maybe mention
on the way out that we burned
some alive?
-Yes.
-No.
-Jeff.
-Fine. Fuck it.
We'll tell them some sick guy
came by, so we set him on fire.
-They'll figure it out.
The deputy knows
something happened
we're the only outsiders here.
They'll trace it back to us.
-I feel really nauseous.
-Karen.
-How soon can you
get us out of here?
-Hey.
Sorry, I didn't mean
to wake you.
-It's okay.
-Are you hungry?
-No.
-Well, you should get back
to sleep.
-Don't go.
- Are you smaller doing
this now and not waiting?
-Yeah, I could fix
the tire pretty quickly
but I still have no idea
what's wrong with the engine.
-Well, hurry up.
I can't listen to
Marcy whine for..
Oh, shit!
- What.
-Just don't move, don't turn
around, just keep doing
what you're doing.
-I can hear it from here.
[barking]
-Fuck!
It didn't even flinch.
There's something seriously
wrong with this dog.
-Just quick scope the fucker.
-What?
-Just shoot it.
[gunshot]
-Just keep going.
-Really.
-Yeah, just do it!
[barking]
[instrumental music]
[music continues]
-Ow, ow, ow!
Stop, stop, stop. Ow!
[eerie music]
- Shit!
Marcy! Jeff, Bert!
[gasps]
-Oh, my..
[screams]
-Holy shit!
-Oh, my God!
-Oh, my God! She's got it.
-No, please don't leave, Bart.
-No, no, no, Karen. Just stay
back, don't come near me.
-Calm down, take it easy.
-No, no, no, get out,
get out, get out.
-Bert, please,
I'm bleeding. Bert!
-You stay in bed,
you're not going anywhere.
Dude, she's bleeding.
-No!
-I'm not letting you go!
It hurts.
-Karen, you got it, dude.
You're infected.
Oh, shit!
-Please.
Don't leave me. Paul.
-Goddamnit!
-Paul, don't leave!
-Paul, Paul, Paul.
She's sick, okay?
I'm doing this for you.
I'm doing this for all of you.
I'm not dying like that.
-What do you mean dying?
-Karen, Karen,
you stay in that bed!
- No!
Marcy!
Please.
-We're not gonna leave you,
the car is busted. Just..
[crying]
Stay in the bed
until we go get help, okay?
Please!
-What the fuck is going on?
[thunder rumbling]
- We need to find her help.
The sooner the better.
-No, we have to move
her first.
-Where?
-The boat shed.
- What? Come on!
-No, if she's infected with
whatever it is, we have to
quarantine her.
We have to get her away from us,
separate from us.
-Just let me go
and check up on her.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
-Look, they're probably right,
okay?
She'll be safe out there, we can
get her matches and a light.
She'll be fine.
-I get it, but I don't..
-Hey.
-Oh, shit.
-Don't bother.
[instrumental music]
[pants]
[grunts]
Oh, fuck you, guys!
-I'm sorry, Karen,
we just don't wanna get sick.
-I'm gonna die out here.
-You're not going to die.
-What about that dog?
-Hey, don't worry, I got this.
I'm gonna watch you.
-Somebody will be outside,
we're not gonna leave you.
- Are you hungry?
Can I bring you some food?
[sobbing]
-I just wanted to go home.
-Hey, it's only one night
I'm gonna go to try
to find help
in a cabin, you know, with a
phone or something, okay.
You're gonna be just fine.
-Please, don't..
-I'll take first watch.
-I'm gonna go find help.
-Where are you gonna go?
We checked this entire area
this morning, there's no one
around for mile.
-Well, I've got
to do something.
-What about the dog, Paul?
-Screw the dog.
I'll take my chances.
-Hey, wait.
We'll hold down the fort.
-This is so fucked up.
-Let's go.
[instrumental music]
[panting]
[dog growling]
[leaves rustling]
-Come on out,
you fucking mutt!
[growling]
Where are you?
Where you at?
Huh? Huh? Come on!
Come on, where are you?
[dog growls]
-You got to eat something,
please.
You let me know
if I can get you anything
or do anything, okay?
-You better shut the door.
I don't wanna infect everyone.
[song playing on radio]
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
-What the hell are you doing?
-Whoa! Whoa!
-Get off my land!
-I -- I -- I'm sorry.
You know what, you see,
my -- my friend, she's sick.
She's very, very sick and I --
-You're sick!
Spying on our love making.
-No, no, no,
I'm -- I'm sorry, I -- I --
-That's my husband.
-Okay, but my..
Please, my friend, she's dying.
We need a phone, like,
right now, we need help.
-Get off my property!
-Hey!
-Jesus!
Where have you been?
Did you find anybody?
-No.
-At least you tried.
Come on,
everybody is waiting for you.
[camera clicks]
[intense music]
-Nobody's hungry?
-Karen may have
used those bowls.
-Jesus, Jeff! I washed them.
-No, he's right.
I'm not eating anything
until we get to town.
-Now, anyone of you
could have it.
I-I know we checked,
but I'm not gonna risk it.
-I'm not sleeping next to you.
-Are you fucking kidding me?
-I don't know what the fuck
you've been doing.
I don't watch you
24 hours a day.
-So then, go sleep
in the car, please.
Do us all a favor.
-The car is a fucking
Petri dish.
I'm not gonna ride in it. My mom
will just give me a new one.
-Oh, my God.
-I cleaned it, it's fine.
-Why don't you sleep in it?
-Maybe I will.
-Alright. You guys are right.
We should all just
prepare our own meals
'cause I'm not cooking
for you guys again.
[chuckles]
Hey, you're all mine.
-What the fuck
is wrong with you?
-Hey!
Sit down! Chill out!
I can't take this shit anymore.
I can't do this by myself.
And I'd prefer if we didn't
fucking argue about everything!
Bert, you just lost the bet.
-What?
- Never mind.
Karen is dying out there.
And we're acting like
a bunch of fucking pricks.
If we don't start working
together, we're all doomed.
-He's right.
-Oh, of course, he's right.
-I'm just saying --
-Not another word!
I can't handle anymore
of this shit!
We can eat alone,
we can sleep alone.
But we have to stick together.
- Alright.
I'm with you.
-Good.
So anybody got
anything else to say?
What the hell is that?
[growls]
Jesus Christ, look at it.
-He's going for Karen.
[barking]
-Bert, you got the gun.
Shoot that thing.
-What if I miss?
I mean, wandering animals
are twice as dangerous.
-He's gone.
What..
-We gotta make sure
that thing can't get to her.
Where the hell did it go?
[dramatic music]
-Oh, shit.
Look at that.
[music continues]
-Hey, Karen.
[knocks]
Karen.
Hey. It's gone.
I'm gonna keep
an eye on you, okay?
[music continues]
[thunder rumbling]
[instrumental music]
[music continues]
-Oh, my God.
-Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
-Fuck!
Yes, baby, come on now. Yes.
Yes. Yes!
Woo-hoo!
Alright, let's go.
-Help us, you gotta sit up!
-Aah!
- We're getting you
out of here, okay?
-Oh, my God. Can you stand?
-No.
-Come on. We got you.
-Okay.
[Karen screams]
[coughs]
[dramatic music]
[gasps]
-Jeff. Jeff.
We're leaving, let's go. Now.
-Come on. Come on.
-Let's put her in the back.
-I'm not getting
in the car with her.
-Okay, put her
in the front with me.
-You're okay?
Well, what is it?
-Oh, my God. She's dying.
We need to get her
to a hospital.
-She's not gonna die.
-Okay. Come on, come on!
Let's go, let's go!
-What, are you fucking stupid?
She just infected the whole car.
-I'll take my chances.
-We're not leaving her.
-Hey, Bert, are you okay?
You don't look so hot.
-Yeah, I, I don't feel so hot.
The more we argue,
the more she rots, so let's go.
-Hey, how sick are you?
That hermit guy touched you,
huh?
Well, did he or didn't he?
-Oh! Fuck this shit.
I'm getting help.
-Bert!
[Karen crying]
[dramatic music]
-Where are you going?
Jeff? Jeff!
-Hey, don't come near me.
I told you not to move her
because I don't wanna get sick.
I don't want
any of us to get sick
but you fucking idiots
insist on moving her
and now you're covered
in her blood.
So the two of you can fucking
rot for all I care, alright?
I'm fucking out.
That's it. I'm gone.
-You are a fucking asshole!
[dramatic music]
[thunder rumbling]
We're all gonna get it.
We're all gonna get sick.
And Jeff's out in the woods
getting wasted.
-We're not gonna get it.
-Yes, we are.
-Bert will find help
and Karen will be fine --
-Paul..
-I promise.
It's like being on a plane
that you know is gonna crash.
And everyone around you
is just screaming
"We're going down.
We're going down."
And all you wanna do is just
grab the person next to you..
...and fuck the shit out of him.
Because you know you'll all
be dead soon anyway.
It won't matter.
[dramatic music]
[music continues]
[moans]
-What the hell
happened to you?
-My friend, she's sick.
-You hold it,
you hold it right there now.
-I need a doctor, please.
She's really sick.
-You stop, alright?
You don't look too good.
-Yeah, I know.
I just..
I need a doctor, please.
-Don't come any closer.
I'll call you a doctor.
-Thank you. Thank you.
- Stay right there.
[breathing heavily]
[coughs]
-Pancakes.
Pancakes.
-No, no, no, no!
Aah! Aah!
-Dennis!
-Ow!
What the fuck
is wrong with that kid?
Oh..
-Oh, God. Why?
Why did you come here, huh?
Now look
what you've gone and done?
-No, I'm sorry.
- My poor boy.
What'd he done to you?
- Hey, hey, hey.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
-Our last one boy!
I ain't losing another!
-Oh, fuck.
-Gettin' my boy sick
is the same as killin' him.
It's murder!
Boy, you come in here,
you getting sick and all
that was your problem.
But now Dennis is sick,
that's my problem!
[coughs]
God Almighty.
[gags]
No, we gotta stop the problem.
We're gonna
stop the problem right now.
Fenster, get me the gun.
[dramatic music]
-Ho -- hold on, hold on, okay,
I'm goin'. I'm goin'. I'm goin'!
I'm goin'!
Oh, fuck!
[tires screeching]
-Them kids got disease.
They just gave it to Dennis.
-Well, take it easy, Tommy.
[music continues]
When a cattle gets sick..
...you got to kill it
before it spreads
to the rest of the heard.
-It's like a dying dog.
We gotta put him down.
We gotta put 'em all down.
-Fenster, get in there
and call the sheriff.
Tell him we're having
big problems over that cabin.
Baily.
Baily, get the truck.
[intense music]
[breathing heavily]
-I brought you some water.
Karen?
[dramatic music]
[tires screeching]
-Yeah! Come on!
[indistinct shouting]
-What the fuck, you guys!
[engine revving]
[music continues]
-Jesus, Paul, you really did
a number on my back.
-I'm gonna find Jeff,
we're walking out of here.
-What about Bert?
-We're not gonna wait for him.
Let's go.
-What about Karen?
[panting]
[music continues]
-Jeff!
Jeff!
Hey, Jeff!
[music continues]
[engine sputters]
-Fuck!
[water running]
[sobs]
[crying]
[intense music]
-Jeff!
Jeff!
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
[screams]
[panting]
[groans]
[screams]
[intense music]
[grunting]
[screams]
[music continues]
[crying]
[panting]
-It's in the water.
It's in the water.
It's in the fucking water.
Don't drink the water.
It's in the water!
[intense music]
[gunshot]
-You missed.
-Shut your pie hole.
[music continues]
-Jesus.
Jesus.
[music continues]
-This way, boys.
I know exactly
where he's headed.
[crying]
[music continues]
-Jeff!
[crying]
-Jeff! Help me.
[dog growls]
Come on!
Come on! Fuckin' do it!
[barks]
Go!
[Marcy screams]
[intense music]
[panting]
[Karen screams]
[dog growls]
[dramatic music]
[Karen screaming]
[barks]
[gunshots]
[dog whining]
-Kill me.
Kill me, please.
-I can't.
-Please. Please. Please.
[Karen crying]
Shoot me. Please.
[gun clicks]
-Come on.
You're fucking kidding me.
-Please.
[Karen sobbing]
[grunts]
[instrumental music]
Try again.
Go ahead! Kill me!
Please.
[instrumental music]
[screams]
[music continues]
[Karen sobbing]
[Karen screams]
[screaming continues]
[screams continues]
[Karen crying]
[sobbing]
-Bert!
-They, they're coming.
They're coming.
They're gonna kill us.
-Who?
-The guys,
the g -- guys from the sto..
[gunshot]
-Bert.
-Wooh!
Did you see that?
-Goddamn bull's-eye.
- Uh-huh.
[grunts]
[all laughing]
-No, you got the safety on.
-Thank you.
[intense music]
[music continues]
[engine hissing]
No, no, no, no, no.
[tires screeching]
[groans]
[panting]
Can I get a fucking break here?
Oh, shit.
[intense music]
[guitar music]
Hey!
The tow truck?
What happened to the tow truck,
Winston?
You said you were
gonna help us!
-Alright, just relax.
Would you believe it,
the mechanic had car trouble
I had to send a tow truck to
get his fucking tow truck.
Man, you're not looking so good.
-No? I don't look so good?
-Need some help?
-Yeah, alright,
that would be good.
Can you gimme a ride?
-Alright.
Take it fucking easy, alright?
Ride? Sure.
I'll get you a ride.
- Winston, Winston,
do you copy?
-I copy, sheriff,
go ahead.
- Some kids are up
in the cabin
apparently on some type
of killing spree.
Probably 3 casualties.
They're armed and extremely
dangerous.
I repeat, do not go
anywhere near them.
They have some kind of
skin disease
that will eat you alive.
So if you see them, don't
hesitate to shoot
them on site.
Do you copy?
-Say that last part again.
- I said if you see the kid,
shoot them on site.
-Copy that.
-You give me that ride,
Winston.
-Are you fucking nuts?
Shoot him.
-Shut up and back off.
-I need that ride, Winston.
-Stay back.
-Oh, Jesus.
You did this?
-Stay back.
-Fuck you!
You did this.
-Stay back.
[groaning]
-Great party, Winston.
-One more step,
I will kill you.
-You don't have to do that.
-You heard the sheriff.
-No one else has to die.
-No one else has to fucking
die right now.
You wanna fucking kill me?
Then fucking kill everyone.
No one else has to die.
We're gonna make a deal.
This is what's gonna fucking
happen, you bitch.
You're gonna go look for me
at the cabin..
...and I'm gonna go look
for a doctor.
Please!
-Oh, goddammit, party man.
Alright.
I'm not gonna kill you.
Take that path.
It's a shortcut.
It takes you straight
to the main road.
-Thank you, Winston.
Thank you.
Don't touch anything
at the cabin.
It's all infected.
[instrumental music]
[music continues]
There's no road.
There's no fucking road.
You fucking lied to me, Winston.
There's no fucking
road out here!
Fuck you, Winston.
There's no fucking road!
[crying]
[screaming]
Fuck you, Winston.
There's no fucking road!
[instrumental music]
-Oh, fuck!
Fuck!
Oh, fuck, no!
Fucking, Marcy..
[crying]
Fuckin' Bert!
Bert!
[sobbing]
I fucking told you!
Told you, Bert.
I told you first thing.
[laughing]
I fucking made it.
I fucking,
[laughing]
I fucking made it.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What the..
[gunshot]
[instrumental music]
[dramatic music]
[music continues]
[thunder rumbling]
[chuckles]
[intense music]
[music continues]