Day by day, my life's
turning to survival.
Money flies. What a
strange time we live in.
Everything's torn apart.
Since love is our only hope,
and unity's a powerful force.
Let's go together,
on a dream cruise.
Bring your week next to mine,
that'll make us a fair two-weeks.
We'll face anything with tenderness.
A velvet game,
that could last for ever.
Bring your week next to mine,
that'll make us a fair two-weeks.
We'll be together as
the mind and the body.
For all our life, we'll do fifty-fifty.
Merry Christmas everybody !
I'm really happy to meet you again.
A new year is about to begin,
I wish you a year full of joy
full of happiness, but above all...
full of songs...
...love songs, of course.
Yes, come in.
Come in, have a seat.
I'm just taking this off.
Marc, it was such a pleasure again.
Thanks Mrs Langolf. May I help you?
Your songs are a source
of youth for me...
a source of memories...
You know...
next year...
I may not be here, when you come back.
Don't be silly, you'll be here.
May I ask you something?
Of course, anything you want...
You looked at me during the show.
I don't know what happened
to me... I'm sorry.
I can't believe it,
you dirty old bitch...
You cunt, look what you've
done... you've ruined it all.
Where are you going now?
South...for a Christmas show.
Some producers should be there.
I hope you'll come
back when you're a star.
Of course I'll come back. Excuse me.
Everybody loves you here
Marc, you know that ?
Well, I gotta go...
Oh, of course...
Thanks a lot.
Marc...Marc.
May I kiss you before you go ?
We will miss you.
Oh Marc...we will miss you.
Please let me go now.
I gotta go.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Did you see a dog...a short haired dog?
That big...with short hair.
Excuse me?
I'm looking for my dog.
I saw something on the road...
couldn't tell if it was a dog.
You saw her ?
No, I saw something cross the road,
but I can't tell if it was her.
Where did she go?
I don't know... this way I think.
There, this way...
Hey come back ! Come back
young man ! Come back !
Hey young man...come back!
My name's Boris.
Ok Boris, can you help me ?
My van's stuck and I
saw a sign for an inn.
The inn ? The inn isn't far away.
But I gotta find Bella.
Just tell me where it
is, that's all I need.
Can you please tell
me where the inn is ?
Follow me. But be quiet,
so I can hear Bella.
Hey wait, I can't live my van here !
I asked you to be quiet.
Are you sure I can leave
my van there all night ?
Are we getting close now ?
Sir, I asked you to be quiet, and it
means being silent with your mouth.
Mister Bartel !
I got someone for you.
He's coming down.
I got someone for you Mr
Bartel. He needs a room.
Good evening.
Evening.
I'm sorry to wake you up,
my van broke down and...
Allright, come in.
The rooms have been empty for quite a
while, but don't worry, they're clean.
Here you are.
Good night.
You slept well artist?
Very well, thank you.
I towed your van,
I know a bit of
mechanics, if I can help...
Thanks, but...
Among colleagues, that's natural...
Hey, I've read the
inscription. Move away please.
Singer? I'm an artist
too...well I was. A humorist
You're an artist for life, but
it's not what it used to be...
I hope you didn't tow my
van with the handbrake on.
So we're like...colleagues.
I'm going to fix you a breakfast,
I'll check your engine afterwards.
Can't we call a mechanic?
I don't want to disturb you.
Bella.
There must be a mechanic around here.
- We could call...
- Shut up
Since he lost his dog, he's
not the same guy anymore.
You got a phone inside?
May I?
You must have a phone inside.
Excuse me?
Do you have a phone inside ?
Of course I have a
phone... what do you think ?
Oh...all right...yes...
so...when will he be back ?
This afternoon ? Maybe ?
Are you sure or not ?
All right, all right, thanks, good bye.
- It was his wife.
- So?
He's working outside. He's busy
for the afternoon, maybe longer.
Don't worry... I'm gonna
have a look at your engine.
- Are you such in a hurry ?
- I've got quite a long road.
Where are you going?
South, for a Christmas show.
Christmas! It's in 2 days.
An artist like you should rest
for a while from times to times..
You must be right.
Come on, I'm gonna fix you a good breakfast,
then I'll have a look at your machine.
Thanks Sir.
Bartel. Call me Bartel. No
Sir here, only an artist.
All right Bartel.
Have a seat.
Can I help you?
No, no...I'm sure you don't know
a thing about mechanics, do you ?
You're right, I must admit that.
That's what I thought. I'm taking
care of this, go get some rest.
I was going to walk around
I should advise you against
going to the village.
Why ?
Because they're not like you and me...
They're not artists.
So please, don't go there.
OK, but tell me why.
Because they are...they
can.... they...they are...
Ok, Bartel, calm down, I
won't go to the village.
- You promise?
- Yeah I promise.
See you later.
So, have a good walk my friend !
Be careful, paths are slippery
at this time of the year...
- You're driving me crazy.
-
- Marc, we love you.
- Marc, come back soon !
-
- Oh Marc, if you knew...
- I languish for you
-
That's a good one,
he's fine, he's tender.
Go ahead.
Come on kid...
and what am I supposed to do ?
I never said it was your fault.
All right, All right.
So ! How was your walk ?
It's very nice around here.
You went to the village ?
No, I just walked in the surroundings.
Anything new ?
I worked hard on your van...
The engine's all right,
I think it's the battery.
I just talked to the mechanic's
wife, he could fix it...
...but tomorrow.
- Tomorrow ?
That's what I told them !
I'm gonna try to start it again.
Marc, wait...wait.
You can't start it, I've
spent the afternoon trying.
Trust me.
Don't insist.
I understand, you're disapointed...
I can understand that.
I'm gonna fix you a good dinner,
you'll taste Bartel's cooking,
and I promise you'll leave tomorrow.
Here you are. Lard and
potatoes au gratin, with cream.
It's my specialty.
It was... when the inn was still open.
A lot of peole used to come here...
...especially artists.
Now that Gloria's gone...
it's not the same anymore.
Gloria. My wife.
You're married ?
I called her my wife, but she left me.
She was a singer, just like you.
Very talented.
You should have heard her.
I'm sorry to bring back bad memories.
How could you know...
So what's the problem?
With the villagers I mean.
You should have heard
her. It's was marvelous.
She was everything for me.
I lost everything when she left me.
That's why I'm so happy
to meet another artist.
I'm gonna show you something.
You see. It's written
on it. First prize.
I won it thanks to my sense of humor.
When she left, Bartel's
sense of humor left too.
Bartel's fantasy...gone.
While when she was here,
when Gloria was here,
I was happy all the time,
I was crooning all day long...
I was kidding,
I was always the first
one to crack a joke...
Listen. A dwarves association...
...decides to create a football club.
So...
They play games every Sunday.
and... they meet in a bar, on the
first floor, in a private room.
One sunday, there's this
guy, standing at the bar,
he's quite messed up already,
and then he sees 2 dwarves,
dressed in blue, coming down the stairs.
then 3, then 4, 5, 6, 10, 11 !
He thinks he's having hallucinations,
then, he pours himself...
he orders another whisky,
then he sees dwarves
again, dressed in red,
coming down the stairs, 2, 3, 5, 11 !
He orders another whisky,
and calls the bartender,
and he says...
I don't want to worry you,
but I think your
Foosball's running away !
Your Foosball's running away !
That's a good one, isn't it ?
And I'm not telling it right !
Back in the days,
People were rolling
on the floor laughing.
You know why ?
Enthusiasm Marc.
Enthusiasm I tell you.
Enthusiasm is the key to success.
When Gloria left,
I decided to fill my head with work,
I decided to write an essay, "Notions...
...of enthusiasm in the principles
of humor. " It was the title.
I never finished it.
I never finished it, 'cause
when a woman leaves you...
You become a mess.
It was very good.
But I got a long road
tomorrow. I need to sleep.
Already ?
You're gonna leave without...
...singing me a song ?
I beg your pardon ?
You got to sing me a
song... show me your talent.
I don't know, it's late and I'm tired.
Come on, don't make me beg
you. We're both artists.
I did told you a story.
Ok, but I don't know what
to sing, I got no music...
Improvise.
A love song. Love
songs are always great.
I told you: enthusiasm is the key.
Like a rose of May,
Youth and beauty were given to you,
Me, in the dark, staring at my life,
I see too many looks shining with envy,
You're too beautiful and too
sensual, for a guy like me.
I've the simple dream, of a peaceful
happiness, you couldn't give me.
Here you are.
You mean that's all ?
I didn't tell you half a story.
You have to finish that song.
You're too beautiful and flirting
wouldn't be enough for me.
I'd like to offer you my bed,
but for all my life.
Even the dove, happy in its nest,
sometimes flies away,
for ever to infinity.
I'm afraid, but am I right or wrong,
that some day you fly away,
making for new horizons.
You're too beautiful and too
sensual, for a guy like me.
I've the simple dream, of a peaceful
happiness, you couldn't give me.
You're too beautiful and flirting
wouldn't be enough for me.
I'd like to offer you my bed,
but for all my life.
This time it's over.
I'm going to bed. Don't
forget to wake me up tomorrow.
- Marc.
- Yes ?
Thanks for this wonderful moment.
Bartel ?
Anybody here ?
Bella !
Boris.
I'm looking for Bartel.
- You hear me ?
- Leave me alone.
Please answer me. You saw him ?
- I'll never find her again.
- Who ?
Bella, my dog.
I'm sorry about your dog
but did you see Bartel ?
She's alone in the woods.
In the cold.
Bella...Bella...
Boris do you hear me ?
I'm looking for Bartel.
Lost.
- Boris.
- She must be so afraid...
Can I help you ?
I was looking for you. The
door was open, I thought...
I was ordering a new
battery for your van.
The mechanic should be here
soon. Just wait a little more.
You didn't wake me up and
I got a problem with my van.
You were sleeping so well I
didn't want to woke you up...
You found it? You left
it yesterday night...
I was about to give it back to you.
What are you doing ?
You're crazy !
Stop !
Calm down Bartel, I
don't wanna hurt you.
That's what you're looking for ?
That's what you're looking for !
Why do you leave now you're back,
you wanna step on my heart again ?
What are you doing ?
Bartel...I won't tell
anybody Let me go...
You see. It's easier when
you don't move your head.
I'm doing this to protect you.
I don't like making you ugly.
I'm suffering as much as you do.
I'm happy too.
It's gonna be the greatest
Christmas that ever took place here.
Where is my axe ?
You know, the one with an oak handle...
You should know that.
You never put things at the same place.
Here it is ! We're gonna
find the best Christmas tree,
and you'll decorate it.
You always loved to hang balls up,
stars, garlands, that's
you thing, isn't it ?
You try to leave me again,
I cut you in two like a log !
Let's go.
You got a ticket to ride ?
You hear ? Bartel's laugh !
My enthusiasm is back, thanks to you !
Let's go.
Hey ho, let's go !
You see that, like a young man.
Bitch !
What a fucking bitch !
What a fucking damn bitch !
Gloria...Gloria...
Gloria !
Gloria for Christ sake !
Anybody here ?
Boris.
Daddy promise to Bella he'll find her.
Bella won't stay alone in the woods.
- Untie me.
Untie me.
Boris...come back... come
back, untie me Boris...
Here you are Mr Bartel.
Cheer up Boris,
You'll find your dog.
But you got to insist. Obstinacy pays.
Obstinacy's the key.
So, you're coming with us ?
No thanks. I'm gonna do like
you said. I'm gonna insist.
You're damn right to
insist ! I gotta go.
You see what you make me do.
What's in your head ?
I don't like it either, but
you don't want to understand.
You, don't forget I know.
I forgive you, but I
know what's going on.
A beer.
Two beers.
A beer I said.
I'm here to warn you.
I'm gonna be happy. Starting now.
All I want is to live in peace.
You understand ?
- I'll kill anyone looking at my wife.
- Your wife ?
Why do you think she's your wife ?
Probably his sense of humor.
Don't come around my house
anymore. You hear me ?
Stick your threats up your ass.
She's my wife.
My wife.
You've been warned.
What do you want ?
Good.
Good to eat Bartel's
soup again, isn't it?
Eat slowly.
We're gonna live just
like before, aren't we ?
Aren't we ?
Watch out, it's pouring everywhere.
I thinked about it you know.
We're gonna reopen the inn.
You'll sing of course,
I'll do the support act.
I don't want to worry you,
but I think your
Foosball's running away.
I found Bella.
That's great Boris.
I did like you said
Mr Bartel. I insisted,
and I found Bella.
I insisted and I found Bella.
So let's drink.
Let's drink to Christmas
miracles gathering the lovers.
I insisted... and I found Bella.
- How does she look ?
- She looks good. That's great.
I think you're great too.
- Are you all right Mr Bartel ?
- I'm all right.
Bella came back home,
Gloria came back home.
We're all together for Christmas.
I love you, you're my family.
You hear that ? We're family !
Don't move.
Help me...
Rescue me.
I got it dad, let's go.
What's going on ?
Shut up bitch.
Come on, sing.
Sing I said.
Come on, sing. Better than this.
Come on.
- Yeah come on.
- Come on, come on, come on...
Shut the fuck up !
Why did you come back Gloria ?
I loved you.
I'm not Gloria. I'm Marc Stevens.
A singer.
Liar ! Damn liar !
You left like a whore,
you'll pay like a whore.
- You wanna fuck her ?
- Yeah ! - So fuck her !
Don't touch my wife or I kill you all !
- Kid !
- Daddy !
- Daddy...
- Kid...kid...kid...
Run away, quick, run, run !
- Let's go.
- Come on, find the bitch, find the bitch...
What ?
We've reached the swamps.
You find her. Then you
can do anything to her.
Come on.
Come.
Gloria...
Why did you come back Gloria ?
Did you love me a bit ?
You loved me right ?
Tell me, tell me you loved me.
Say it...say it !
Louder...louder !
I loved you.