wWw.ZOCINE.COM
WATCH MOVIES AND SERIES.
Hey.
Sweetie?
Honey, are you all right?
He hurt me.
Look Tom may not be your
knight in shining armor
but you could do worse.
That's a ringing endorsement.
He is more like a court
jester, and self appointed.
Look I've got to go,
but call me tonight, okay?
I should get a break
around midnight.
I bet you look
great in that uniform.
I do, you know I've always
liked a man in uniform,
and now I'm one of them.
You won't say a word to him?
Of course not.
Never.
Fuck.
I could really use a word
of advice right about now.
Helen.
Great, thanks.
Hey, what are you doing?
Let's go.
What?
The Parker gig.
That's tonight?
It's now, come
on, I'll drive you.
Dad I'm really not
feeling up to it.
Can't he find someone else?
Five minutes before
you're supposed to arrive?
The guy just moved in,
doesn't know anyone in town.
Who is he supposed to find?
It was your idea to
look for more work.
Where were you?
Just in the woods.
I told you, you
shouldn't wander around
out there by yourself.
I saw that man again.
Who, that old bird watcher?
Lucas, you're going to
have to learn to respect
your elders.
You're going to look
like that when you're 80.
Do you really have
to go out tonight?
Hey where did I pack my ties?
I think I left them
in the basement.
Would you run down there
and grab that for me?
Lucas, did you find them?
Casey is doing
pretty well at the station.
I have to admit, I wasn't
sure what to expect.
Great.
You can talk to me, you know?
Tell me what's going on.
Is it the house?
Dad, I'm not 10.
I mean that story
still creeps me out.
Eating the eyes of kids to
keep himself from going blind.
It's disgusting.
Thank you so much for coming,
I don't know what
I would have done
if your dad hadn't offered.
Lucas doesn't know the
history behind this place
so I would appreciate it if
we could keep that quiet.
He has a pretty
active imagination.
She won't say a word.
I'm going to head
back to the station,
but I just wanted to
make sure everything
was okay, Mr. Parker.
Awesome, thanks,
sheriff, I owe you one.
Don't mention it.
Owes you one?
Christ.
I should get Lucas,
get you two acquainted.
It's just the two of you?
Yeah.
Lucas' mom Linda passed
away when he was born.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to...
No, don't worry.
She would have hated this house.
There he is.
Hello there.
Come down, don't be shy.
I'm Helen, nice to meet you.
Yes, the squatter,
yes I remember.
The sheriff?
No.
Yeah, of course.
I'll transfer you right
now, Mrs. Haggemeyer.
Widow's Peak sheriff
office, this is Casey.
Excuse me?
I've seen things, heard things.
Who is this?
Tell the sheriff Ginger called.
Tell him he's awake.
Keep going!
I've got it, V.
You should probably
turn this off.
No, no, it's fine.
When you have terrible
nightmares tonight
we'll talk about whether
or not it's fine.
What's that you've got there?
It's my mom's.
Was my mom's.
It's supposed to
be for protection.
It's silver and silver
keeps the monsters away.
It's stuck.
What, Lucas?
You hear that?
It's a bird in my bird house.
Your what?
It's so dark.
It's a sparrow.
Sparrow flies through a house,
someone is going to die.
Ginger, you're sure
that's what she said?
Yes, absolutely.
Did she say anything else?
Just that song
and "he's awake."
Thank you.
You weren't kidding about
liking this horror stuff.
Wait.
Could you leave that light on?
Of course.
What is it, Lucas?
I think I saw someone
around the house.
In the woods.
An old man.
An old man?
He's always there.
Today I found a hole in
the wall in the basement.
There was wind in there.
What if it leads outside?
What if he can come inside?
What if he knows about it?
Shh, shh.
No one is coming inside.
I saw him today.
I think he was
going to the farm.
No, Lucas, the
farm is off limits.
It's very dangerous, you should
not go there alone, okay?
When I was a kid, I
used to think children
couldn't die, but they can.
A lot of them died, over there.
I Googled it.
You should know that that
happened a long, long time ago.
You have nothing to worry about.
It's time to go to bed, okay?
Okay.
Yes, sir?
I need you to
look up some files for me.
What are you doing here?
I tried to call but there's
no reception out there
and I'm really
terrified of the dark.
You're eating melted ice cream.
That's super gross.
Nope, it's best like this.
How did you know I was here?
Casey might have
told me something.
I do think it's super
weird that I've got to
talk to Casey to figure out
where you are these days.
Yeah, I've been working a lot.
So this is the old Bowery place?
Got to admit, I expected
something a little more Gothic.
Did you find any dead
bodies in the walls?
No.
It's just a house,
a normal house.
Yeah, people that bought
it might be a little, right?
Nope, perfectly normal.
Well...
Well?
I don't know, maybe I
don't understand boys.
Did you ever trap animals
when you were a kid?
Trap animals?
Not to hurt them, I don't think,
I think he just
wanted to keep them.
I don't know.
Maybe he is a little weird.
Maybe.
But you know that's really
none of your business.
You should go.
Come on, it will
be like we're teenagers.
I'll be the bad
boyfriend sneaking in.
We're not teenagers anymore.
Helen, who's he?
He's here to help me babysit.
What up, little man?
I'm Tom.
You're not supposed
to have company.
I know.
Tom was just about to leave.
What is it?
Is anything wrong?
First it was like breathing.
Then, a voice, whispering.
See I told you that
movie was a bad idea.
It's not the film, I heard it.
Someone is in there.
Okay.
Let's see then.
Wait!
It's nothing, Lucas.
Old houses make strange
sounds sometimes.
wWw.ZOCINE.COM
WATCH MOVIES AND SERIES.
See, empty.
Now you're going to go to bed.
You think I'm making it up.
You just want me to stay up
here, so you can be with him.
I already told you I was
going to tell him to leave.
No you're not.
Listen you don't need
to worry about things
that don't concern you.
There is nothing in your closet.
The only reason you're
scared is because
I let you watch
that scary movie.
What if it's that old man?
There is no old man, okay?
It's just all in your head.
Yeah because I'm a weird kid.
Lucas...
You can leave now.
I'm going to bed.
So was it Robert Bowery?
You're still here.
He's not scared
of the Boogie Man.
He's got a crush on you, and
he wants to get rid of me.
Smart kid.
I think I messed that one up.
What are you talking about?
He's a kid, he's going
to forget in two seconds.
What does that even mean?
If you mess up, you can't
babysit here anymore?
Big deal.
I think it's actually
a good thing,
because you really should be
spending more time with me.
I miss you.
It's good to hear
that you miss me too.
I know that's got to
be a complex emotion
to sort of put into words.
Tom, I'm pregnant.
What?
Is it mine?
When were you going
to tell me this?
I just told you.
Are you going to keep it?
Did you hear that?
Hear what?
Lucas?
Tom, check the study.
He's not there.
I think I know where he went.
Lucas?
Lucas, where are you?
Kid could be
anywhere, this is pointless.
No he would have followed
the path, he's a smart kid.
I think we should call someone.
Why, so they can
clean up our mess?
Your mess.
See, this is why
I've been avoiding you.
You can't deal when
things get serious.
Helen.
No please, let me finish.
No, Helen, what is that?
That's feathers.
That's his blanket.
Hey wait a minute,
what do you got there?
Just some files
Connolly asked me to get.
From the basement?
Let me see.
The Bowery case?
What the hell for?
What are you looking at?
I should probably get
these to the sheriff.
The Child Eater of Widow's Peak.
Bowery was a weird one.
No one suspected a thing,
little did we know.
My mom says it's
because of those woods.
Said he spent too much
time there, went too deep.
Bunch of horse shit, he snapped.
Developed an eye disease.
Macular degeneration.
It's genetic.
He slowly went blind.
But at some point it
seems he started believing
eating other folks'
eyes would cure his own.
Said the younger, the better.
He put a mask over their heads
to make them as blind as he was.
This death mask.
What is this, ghost
stories around the camp fire?
Should I go out and buy
some goddamn marshmallows?
Old bastard was
just a sick sadist.
Did you hear that?
What?
The sound of every
bone in your body
telling you not
to go any further.
He is just hiding somewhere.
Lucas?
Okay you got what you wanted,
we're out here, now let's go.
Stop!
Jesus Christ,
that's a fucking bear trap.
Are there bears in these woods?
What if Lucas
stepped into one of these?
I mean we know, we would hear
him screaming his lungs out.
Tom.
No I mean it, Helen,
seriously, we would know.
Are you in here?
Tom, look at this.
Someone has been here.
Of course someone has been here,
this place is legendary.
Did you ever come here?
No but I was never into
this kind of stuff any way.
Used to play hide and seek.
Apparently he was so unassuming,
you could just be
in a room with him
for minutes before you
would even notice him.
It wasn't until
you heard him breathing
that you realized
he was right there.
I remember the stories.
They used to keep me awake.
Lucas?
Hey.
Teeth.
Hey, you!
Hey we're looking for
someone, it's a little kid.
Help, Helen!
Help!
No, fuck, no!
Tom?
Fuck!
Hello?
Is anyone here?
I just need to use your phone.
I need to call the police.
So close them shut.
Run away, or you'll never
see the light of day.
Help!
Somebody please help me!
Call Lucas.
Please let me go.
Call him, and
we will end this now.
He may not be able to see,
but he can hear everything.
He can smell blood.
He knows these woods like
the back of his hand.
The boy out there with him
or here with us?
Who are you?
I was the one that got away.
They thought he was dead.
But evil never dies.
In these woods, it lingers.
Dwells.
When I was a child, long
before Robert Bowery went mad,
there was an old, old story.
They say the stork comes
at night and brings people
their newborn babies.
But this was another
kind of stork.
One with black feathers.
Every once in a
while, he would call.
A call only children of bad
unworthy parents could hear.
They would crawl out of
their beds in the middle
of the night and follow
the call, all the way
up the hill to where
the stork was waiting.
Once they got there, he
would peck out their eyes
with his beak, and all the
blind babies would crawl
around the woods and couldn't
find their ways back home.
Then the stork ate the babies.
Their blood soaked up the soil.
The trees and the grass
grew from that bloody soil.
That place is built on
that blood of innocents.
Widow's Peak
sheriff's office, this is Casey.
Casey, Casey I'm being attacked.
Helen, is that you?
Lucas got lost in the woods
and there was someone.
He killed Tom.
What do you mean killed Tom?
Helen, talk to me.
I think someone is in the house.
Come now, please.
What is it?
It's Helen.
No.
Hey, it's okay, relax.
You're in the hospital.
Tell me what happened.
Lincoln S2S51, copy.
Copy, sheriff, over.
She said there was someone
in the house with her also.
Gave me a description.
Tall, long pale face, long
limbs, wearing glasses.
Sir that sounds a lot like...
I know exactly what it
sounds like, lieutenant.
Just keep your eyes open.
Somebody is hiding
out in those woods.
Copy that.
We traced them out to the zoo,
we're going to take a look.
Let's be careful, there is
a little kid out there also.
So just don't get trigger happy.
I'll be there as soon as
I locate the kid's dad.
Must have been a good date?
Focus on the
task at hand, lieutenant.
Over and out.
Your little friend over there,
the sheriff's daughter
might be a little
coo-coo in the head, if
you know what I mean.
Right, let's do this.
wWw.ZOCINE.COM
WATCH MOVIES AND SERIES.
Hello?
Helen?
Shh, quiet, boy.
Don't you know who
may be listening?
Hi.
Here, for you.
You must be hungry.
And cold?
Why don't you come back
with me to my house?
We'll call the police.
Who are you?
Shh.
Come on, Lucas.
Come with me.
No, Lucas.
You were lucky.
The knife in your side
didn't hit any major organs.
A matter of millimeters,
but nothing serious.
And the...
The baby is going to be fine.
You are both doing just fine.
Where is he?
Where is sheriff Connolly?
Sheriff?
Mr. Parker.
Where is my son?
What happened?
Everything is
going to be fine, trust me.
Trust me on this one.
Everything is going to be fine.
Nurse.
Where were you?
You were supposed
to take care of him.
to protect him.
Could you give her something
to calm her down, please?
I will take responsibility
for this situation.
I have every officer in my outfit
working on this right now.
Your son will be found.
This is the place.
What place?
The nest, where he took them,
to play hide and seek.
Except he knew the
building by heart,
so he always found them.
Come on,
Wesley, give it a break.
We're, we're going in?
You two take the back,
I'll check the front.
What kind of animal
did they keep in there?
Something big.
Hey, Casey, there is
someone under the bridge.
A monster.
You're too stressed out, man.
This job is a lot of
running around in the dark
for reasons you
don't understand.
Better get used to it.
I'm fine.
There's something down here.
Come take a look.
What does that look like to you?
I don't know, mud?
Doesn't smell like mud.
Come out.
It's the police, I
have my gun drawn.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Was that Wes?
Wes?
I'll check it out.
Wesley?
Fuck.
Sheriff?
Anyone?
Goddammit.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hey.
Lucas.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
No, no.
Run, boy.
This ends now.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Lincoln 72S51, 10-20.
Wesley, come in, over.
Sheriff, sheriff.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
My God.
Daddy?
Hello, I need an ambulance,
please send help.
Dad, Dad, can you hear me?
Are you okay?
Are you all right?
I already called
the 100 dispatch,
they're on their way.
They'll be right back, okay?
Just in a few minutes and
I'm going to send for help.
No, don't go back out there.
He's my responsibility.
Helen.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
You be a good mother.
You have, fresh eyes.
Lucas?
Lucas.
Helen?
Lucas?
Lucas.
Shh, quiet, or he'll come back.
Come on, let's go.
Helen.
Casey.
All the stories are
true, they never stop.
wWw.ZOCINE.COM
WATCH MOVIES AND SERIES.
Hey.
No, Lucas stop, Lucas run.
Lucas, get out of the way.
Move, Lucas.
Okay.
You go that way.
Hey, Bowery, I'm right here,
come and get me.
Come and get me.
Come on, I'm here,
come and get me.
Helen!
Lucas.
Wait, no.
No!
You're dead.
You want it?
Choke on it.
Is he dead?
He's dead.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
They're best when they're fresh.
wWw.ZOCINE.COM
WATCH MOVIES AND SERIES.