Good morning, Elisa.
- Morning.
Reverend, thank you
for the focus.
- Morning.
- It was a great sermon.
It was about three years ago.
I was the only kid
in church that day.
The others were with Isaac
out in the cornfield.
I didn't get to go
'cause Dad didn't like Isaac.
He was pretty smart,
my dad.
After church, we went to Hansen's-
just like always.
Sarah was home sick
with Mom.
She'd come down
with the fever real sudden.
Morning, Dave.
- Morning, Pop. How are you?
- How are the wife and Sarah?
Dad was worried, so he went
to call Mom first thing.
Sarah's been better.
I'm going to call your mom, okay?
Okay.
Mr. Hansen:
I bet dad wants a cup of coffee.
- Okay, Joby, you want your usual?
- Yeah, strawberry shake.
That's when I saw
Malachai and the others.
I guess their meeting
with Isaac was over.
- Hi.
- They were acting real creepy.
Francis.
- Here you go, Joby.
- Oh, thanks.
How is she?
I'm worried, Dave.
Her fever's gone
from 101 to 104.
Sure.
How are you?
- May I have some cream?
- Okay.
Good coffee.
What's going on?
This young man's
got a weapon.
Oh my God!
No!
Stop it!
Dave, are you
listening to me?
Don't do it!
Don't do it! No!
Don't! No!
What are you kids-
It happened everywhere in Gatlin that day.
That's when Sarah
started drawing these pictures.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Happy birthday!
What are you doing?
- You're crazy.
- Come on, come on!
Make a wish.
So what did you wish for?
To live happily
ever after.
- Mm.
- Is that a proposal?
No... it's not.
Okay.
Well...
I guess I'll
give you this anyway.
- Come on.
- What is it?
Oh, that's nice.
Turn it over.
I like this.
In honor of this
special occasion,
we have a birthday
serenade.
- # A one, a two #
- # A one, two, three, four! #
# No more books
and studies #
# Now I can stay out late
with my buddies #
# I can do the things
that I wanna do #
# 'Cause all my exams
are through #?
# I can root for the Yankees
from the bleachers #
# And don't have
to worry about teachers #
# And I'm so glad
that school is out #
# I could sing
and shout #
# School is out,
everybody gonna have some fun #
- # School is out #
- # Everybody gonna jump and run #
- # Come on people, don't you be late #
- # School is out #
- # I just got time to take- #
# My girl out
on a date... #
Yay!
You're wacko!
Holy cow!
We'd better get going.
We've got a lot of driving to do today.
Couldn't we just say,
"the hell with it"?
- Stay here for a couple of hours?
- Mm, I wish.
Starting Monday,
I've got 50 patients a day to look at.
I've got a couple
of things you can look at.
Is that right?
Well...
Hello? Hello? Maid service.
Um, we'll be out
in a minute.
Oh, we got to
get going.
I wanna grab a quick shower
before we go, okay?
You're making something
out of nothing.
Right. To me it's something;
to you it's nothing.
I'm just worried about
this internship, okay?
I've been working
for this for four years.
I know.
I do understand.
Why do you have to be such a jerk about it?
"Welcome to Nebraska."
We weren't the only ones
who thought Isaac was weird.
One day Joseph told us
he was running away.
He said he couldn't
take it anymore.
He was pretty scared.
I wasn't.
- I'm scared!
- Me too!
There's nothing
to be afraid of.
I said I'd come back for you.
I promise.
- Can't we go with you, please?
- No!
I'd never make it
with you two.
- But we don't like it here.
- I said you'll be all right!
As long as nobody finds
them pictures you've been drawin'.
She can't help it.
That won't matter
to Isaac and Malachai.
They'll take it as a sign.
Anyways, you know crayons
and drawings are forbidden...
just like having
that record player.
But we like it.
Isaac doesn't let us do anything!
Well, you just better
mind him till I get back
or else you know
what happens.
You're not going
through the corn, are ya?
- I can't go no other way.
- But what about-
I said it'll be all right!
Unless you tell
anybody I'm gone.
- We won't.
- Cross your heart? Hope to die?
Stick a needle
in your eye.
Okay, you know what
that means now?
If you tell, you're gonna
burn in the lake of fire for all eternity!
Make sure nobody's lookin'.
Okay! Go!
Nobody's looking!
I spy with my little eye
something that begins
with the letter C.
- Corn.
- Right.
So now we know...
the backroads are even less interesting
than the highway.
Maybe they've
discovered music.
- Halleluiah!
There are many mansions
in His house.
But there's no room
for the fornicator!
- Oh no room!
- No room...
- for the homosexual!
- No room!
- No room for the drug abusers!
- Oh no, no room!
Amen! Peanut butter
and white bread!
There's no room
for the college graduate!
No room for people
who watch public television!
- No room for commitment!
- Amen!
Come on.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Here it is.
I wonder how it
got in here.
Not me.
Okay now,
it looks like...
this one goes goes
to Grand Island,
and this one cuts
up to the highway.
Where's this Gatlin
we've been seeing signs for?
It's not on here.
What do you mean?
It's gotta be on here somewhere.
Burt, look out!
Hang on.
Let me check.
- Where, right there?
- Yeah.
It's just a bump.
Just try and relax.
That was an animal, right?
I got to go
back there, okay?
Just stay here
and try and rest.
Come on, buddy.
Oh lord.
Is... he...
Oh, yeah.
- Oh my God!
- Easy, easy, easy. Come on.
Easy.
Take it easy.
Don't look at him.
Okay, now,
listen to me.
There's something
very wrong here.
So I want you to go back to the car
and wait for me there,
Understand? Keep all the doors
locked until I get back.
- Why? Where are you going?
- I'll tell you when I get back.
- Just do what I say.
- Okay.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Burt?
Burt?!
I'm so sorry.
- Vicky, come on.
- Burt!
- Easy, calm down.
- I kneeled-
I kneeled down next to him.
He said...
It's okay.
Take it easy.
Just take it easy.
Relax.
You're okay.
You understand?
- Yeah.
- You're okay.
It's okay.
Everything's okay.
You're okay.
Me and Sarah were playing
in our old house.
We played there lots.
Malachai said
it was forbidden.
But I think that was 'cause
nobody ever asked him to play.
When I grow up,
I'm gonna have all
the money in the world.
Me too.
- You can't.
- Why not?
- Because I'm gonna have it.
- I'll get it first.
- Will not.
- Will too!
- Will not!
Oh yeah, how?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
It's easy.
Seven.
One, two, three,
four, five,
six...
seven.
All right, see?
$200.
Uh-uh, Joby.
How much?
13 thousand
hundred dollars.
hundred dollars?
Uh, okay,
$2,000.
Mm-hmm.
I thought so.
100, 200-
I got a great idea.
Let's pretend
this guy is Isaac.
And we're gonna
put him in jail.
What if he gets
a get-out-of-jail-free card?
Simple as that.
What cards?
Do you think it might have been
some kind of accident,
like farm equipment
or something?
Not a wound
like that.
His throat was cut
deliberately.
He was already dead
when he stumbled out into the road.
Whoever killed him-
do you think he saw us?
I mean, I felt like
we were being watched.
It's possible.
Blood starts to coagulate
in four minutes.
When I went to get the suitcase,
it was still fresh.
- Then he could have been out there.
- I couldn't leave it there.
I mean, what if it
holds some sort of clue?
- Let's open it.
- No.
Let's just get to a phone
or a house or someplace.
Malachai took us
right to Isaac.
I figured he finally
talked the little squirt
into punishing us
for being unbelievers.
Up till then, we'd been forgiven
'cause we weren't in the corn
the day He Who Walks Behind the Rows
made himself known.
That bothered Malachai.
He had a lot of problems.
I found these two
in one of the old homes.
They had a game and music.
And this.
They come already.
You have the gift of sight.
This is a blessing, my child.
I've seen this car
upon the road.
Go to the old man.
Make sure
he tells them nothing.
What about these two?
Take them back
where they were.
But they had a game
and music.
- They're forbidden!
- Question me not, Malachai.
I act according
to His will.
Ugh, you'd think
we were on the damn moon.
We haven't even
seen a truck.
We'll be
in Gatlin soon.
You think
he lived there?
We may never
know that.
I really think
we should open it.
Okay.
Let's see if I
can get some news.
Atone!
Only by the blood
of the Lamb are we saved!
I'm getting tired
of that crap!
- Ugh!
- What is it?
- Jesus Christ.
- Not in my book.
Looks like some kind
of primitive folk art.
I think it's repulsive.
Sarge, how about that number six?
Oh damn it.
Better make it an eight.
Come on, come on.
We ain't got all day.
Oh, good boy, Sarge,
We'll have that transmission
fixed in no time!
Then we'll get on
the radiator.
Damn, this road
is becoming a regular highway.
Ain't this about the third car
in a month, huh?
We know what to do,
don't we, boy?
You'd better put
that suitcase away.
Be right back.
- Hi, we've had ourselves-
- I ain't got no gas.
- No, I don't need gas.
- I ain't got no diesel if you all need it.
No, you don't understand.
I need to use your-
You don't buy no gas,
you can't use no restroom.
Your telephone.
I need to use your phone.
Telephone?!
I ain't got no telephone.
Sarge.
Sarge, you be still now.
Mister,
what you want to do
is to go to Hemingford.
- About 19 miles down that right fork there.
- What about Gatlin?
Gatlin? There ain't
nothin' in Gatlin.
What do you mean
there ain't nothing in Gatlin?
Folks in Gatlin's
got religion.
They don't cotton to outsiders and
probably won't have a phone either.
Sarge! Mister, I'd like to stay here
and shoot the breeze with you
about politics and stuff,
but I got a transmission to fix.
You get on that right fork there
and you'll be in Hemingford in no time.
Right.
Sarge.
I said at ease!
Yeah, thanks a lot.
Sarge!
Either that man's senile or he's been
out in the sun too long.
Sarge!
Come back here!
Sarge, get back here!
I don't have time for this.
You hear me?
Come back here.
Come on.
That's an order!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Who is it?
Is that you?
What do you want?
What are you
doing in there?
There really isn't that much stuff in here.
Just kid's stuff-
clothes, matches,
compass, pocket knife.
- I don't get it, camping stuff?
- Yeah.
Oh great.
This must be our day.
Didn't the last sign
we saw say Gatlin was three miles
- and point that way?
- That's what I thought.
Did I miss a turn?
No, we've been
going straight.
Somebody's been messing
with these signs then.
- Hemingford's gotta be straight ahead.
- Yeah.
Must have been
the wind.
Those latches
ain't worth a damn.
Blow over in a bad fart.
I never told them nothing.
I swear it.
I kept our bargain just like always.
Jesus Christ.
Gatlin! What do they have a monopoly
on road signs?
What about Hemingford?
For people who don't like visitors,
they sure do advertise enough.
Over there.
Of course,
it's the wind.
Why did you have
to go after them, Sarge?
Why you bastards.
You can't do this to me.
I know you're in here.
Come on.
Come on!
I can smell you,
you stinkin' little skunks.
Come on!
You murdering
little devils.
Come on!
What was that?
That probably was just my golf bag.
- Are you sure?
- What do you mean am I sure?
God, this isn't
even a road.
- We're never gonna get out of here.
- We will too, now stop it!
Sorry.
- Just tell me where we are.
- I don't know.
We're right back
where we started from.
We never should have
listened to that old fool.
Hemingford's 19 miles.
Gatlin's only three.
I don't care how much religion
they've got,
we're going there
right now.
Don't ever show up
in my emergency room, buddy.
Behold.
A dream did come to me in
the night.
And the Lord did show
all this to me.
Praise God!
Praise the Lord!
A time of tribulation
has come.
A test is at hand.
- The final test.
- What has the Lord commanded?
In the dream,
the Lord did come to me
And He was a shape.
It was He Who Walks
Behind the Rows.
And I did fall
on my knees in terror,
and hide my eyes,
lest the fierceness of
His face strike me dead!
And He told me all
that has since happened.
He said,
"Joseph has taken his things
and fled this happy place,
because the worship
of Me is no more upon him.
So take you his life
and spill his blood."
- He did?
- Yeah.
"But let not the flesh
pollute the corn.
- Cast him instead upon the road."
- And so it was done!
Joseph the betrayer
was cast out.
And He Who Walks
Behind the Rows did say,
"I will send
outlanders amongst you,
a man and a woman.
And these outlanders
will be unbelievers
and profaners
of the holy."
I wish Isaac
never came here.
But he's always been here,
just like He Who Walks
Behind the Rows.
"And the man shall
sorely test you.
For he has great power,
Even greater than
that of the blue man!"
The blue man.
Yes, the blue man.
And just as the blue man
was offered up unto Him,
so shall be the unbelievers.
Make sacrifice unto Him.
Bring Him the blood
of the outlanders.
Praise God! Praise the Lord!
Praise God!
Praise the Lord!
Praise God! Praise the Lord!
Praise God!
Praise the Lord!
Praise God! Praise the Lord!
Let's get out of here.
It looks like
a swinging place.
I guess nobody told them
we were coming.
I hope not.
God, I don't see anybody.
Town hall.
Grocery store.
Hansen's Cafe.
Let's see if they've got a phone, huh?
Unless a ghost is using it.
What is it
with this corn?
You got me.
Phew.
It's dead.
Just like everything else
around here.
Yuck!
- A rat.
- Yeah.
Just your ordinary
coffee shop rat.
Now can we get
out of here, please?
Hey.
Hey hey, wait a minute.
Come back here!
Come on, Vicky.
Hurry up, I don't want to lose them.
So what are you
gonna do if you catch them?
Ask them where
we could find help, what else?
- They cut off that way.
- Okay.
Damn it. Where'd they go?
Look, we're already
in the car.
Why don't we go on to Hemingford?
It'll take us 20 minutes.
We just found people.
Yeah, three kids who tried
to steal our car.
There's something
very strange about this town.
Maybe you're right.
We'd be better off
in a bigger town anyway.
- The size of Seattle.
- Yeah.
- Over there.
- What?
I just saw a door
open and close.
I didn't see anything.
Let's check it out.
Why? I thought
we were going!
Settle down.
Jeez.
- Don't patronize me, Burt.
- I'm not patronizing you.
I just want to see
if somebody's there.
Hello?
Anybody home?
We've had an accident and we need
to use your phone.
Okay?
Now can we go?
Burt, this is
somebody's house!
I know, I just want
to use their phone.
Hello?
Gross.
I'm going to check
out back.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
I found the phone.
It matches the decor perfectly.
This is three years old.
I don't understand
what's going on here.
Well, can we go?
Burt.
Hello?
Is anybody here?
Don't be afraid.
We didn't mean to scare you.
Hi.
- What's your name?
- Sarah.
Oh, Sarah.
That's a beautiful name.
This is Burt
and I'm Vicky.
Are you here alone, Sarah?
Do you live here?
You just come here
to play?
Are your mommy
and daddy around?
They're in the cornfield.
What are they
doing there?
All the grown-ups
are there.
Are they working there
or are they having a meeting?
No, Isaac put
them there.
Who's Isaac?
Come on, sweetheart.
Tell us who Isaac is.
Our leader.
Leader of what?
Of everybody.
Of course.
Listen, could you
take us to Isaac?
- Huh-uh.
- Why not?
He's scary.
Look, Sarah,
it's very important
that we speak to some
grown-ups as soon as possible.
We're wasting
our time here, Vicky.
Well, give her a chance.
I'm gonna go look
at the town hall.
Why?
Because we have
a murder to report.
And we're standing here
talking in circles wasting our time.
Maybe she can help.
Well, fine, then you
stay here with her.
Listen, things just
aren't happening fast enough.
So I'm gonna
leave you the car.
I won't be gone very long.
If anybody comes,
just honk, okay?
Are we safe?
Yeah, it's a little weird
here, but it's safe.
I'll be back.
So looks like
it's just you and me.
What were you doing here by yourself?
Just playing records?
Come on, you can tell me.
- Drawing
- Drawing.
What's so secret
about drawing?
I'm not supposed to.
You're not supposed
to draw?
Who says?
Isaac?
Malachai.
Malachai?
Well, I'll tell you what.
Why don't you draw me
a picture
And we won't tell Isaac
or Malachai or anybody?
- How's that sound?
- Okay.
- So how's it coming, huh?
- Fine.
- What did you draw?
- You.
You did?
Could I see?
What is this?
Burt?
Burt, is that you?
Is somebody here?
Who are you?
What do you want?
We want
to give you peace.
Seize her.
Come on, get her.
Come out of there.
Sarah!
No!
Burt! No!
Are we safe?
It's weird here, but it's safe.
Vicky.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Help me!
Where are you
taking me?
Burt!
Burt! No!
Vicky!
Sarah, what
happened here, huh?
What happened?
Where's Vicky?
You've gotta think.
Now think.
What happened
to her, please?
Does He speak
to you, Isaac?
He speaks to me always.
But today He is
displeased.
He is displeased
with you, Malachai.
What have I done?
Question Him not in vain.
Do you not know you did sacrificed
Joseph without an offering?
And did you not
spill the blood of the old man
when his oil and gasoline were
still useful to us?
We have our own
fuel now from the corn.
Show not your pride, Malachai.
We have not enough.
Maybe He is displeased
we have not offered Him Sarah and Job.
Sarah has the gift of sight.
She warned us of the coming
of the interlopers.
Question not my judgment,
Malachai.
I am the giver
of His word.
Go you and bring me
the husband.
I must offer them tonight
when Amos leaves.
Sarah, come on.
Tell me what happened to her, please.
Sarah, look at me.
Now think.
- Malachai.
- What?
- Who's Malachai? What do you mean?
No.
Vicky?
Oh my God!
Kill kill kill kill...
Now the blood
of Amos will be shared!
Stop it!
Stop that!
- What?
- Hold the outlander!
What the hell's
going on here?
Are you crazy?
What do you think you're doing?
My passage,
it's my birthday.
You got a pretty sick way
of celebrating it, pal.
- Listen, I-
- Silence, interloper!
Your presence does
profane this holy place.
He will reckon with you!
That's terrific.
I don't know who he is,
but maybe he'd like to discuss the medical
side of what's going on here with me.
- It's as it should be.
- Amos!
It's as it is written.
Speak no more to him!
He is an unbeliever.
Hurry, get Isaac.
No, wait.
Bring Malachai.
So what do you mean,
"as it is written"? Written where?
What, in this?
You rewriting the whole thing orjust
the parts that suit your needs?
Back off, fellas.
Sit down!
What do we have here?
19, 19 year-
what is this?
These people
all died so young.
Not die. We go to Him
- on the first night of our 19th year.
- YEAH!
Who the hell's him?
He Who Walks
Behind the Rows.
Malachai comes!
- Seize him!
- Get him!
Back off!
Stay back.
No!
Come on, hurry up.
Get him. Do not
let him escape!
Get him!
Kill him!
- Let's go. Get him!
- Where is he? Come on!
He went
around the corner!
There he is.
Go get him, you guys. Go that way.
He's getting away!
I need your help.
Come on.
Come on!
Help me, help me!
Outlander!
Hey!
- He's here.
- There he is.
Come on.
Get him.
- Got you this time.
- This isn't a game, understand?
Back off.
Get out of here.
Outlander!
Go get him!
Down the alley.
Damn it!
Check the door.
Check the doors.
You guys,
go back up the alley.
You, over there.
You two, follow me.
Shit.
Damn it.
Psst.
Hey, mister.
I know a place
to hide.
But we gotta hurry.
- Who are you?
- Job.
Come on.
Stop asking questions.
Will you come on?
Careful.
Hey, don't be
a scaredy cat.
- Come on. It's only me and Sarah.
- Sarah?
Yeah, my sister.
Isn't this neat?
My dad built it
for when the communists
launch their first strike.
I don't think it's the communists
we have to worry about.
Don't worry.
Nobody knows about this place.
It's secret.
- Are those guys friends of yours?
- No way.
They listen to Isaac
and Malachai.
Who are Isaac
and Malachai?
Isaac started
the whole thing.
If he hadn't had come,
this would never have happened.
When he was young, he was a preacher,
so everybody believed him.
They thought he had
great spirit.
I thought he was weird,
huh, Sarah?
We must sacrifice
them both tonight.
Amos will satisfy Him.
We need the woman.
She'll bring the man to us.
No, he must be
taken without her.
We cannot remove her
from this place. It is holy.
We will bring the Lord
two by using one.
Do not blaspheme,
Malachai!
You know not the laws.
He speaks them only to me.
I think not, Isaac.
You're the one who's lost favor with Him.
He's the god of blood and sacrifice,
not ceremony.
Ah, sacrilege!
Down on your knees, heretic!
Shut your mouth, Isaac.
You've grown prideful
and apart from us.
Oh my gosh. Oh no.
He Who Walks Behind the Rows
will decide your fate.
Don't just sit there.
Seize him!
Punish him!
Cut him down! I command you!
I am the word and the giver
of His laws.
Disobedience to me
is disobedience to Him.
Do it now or your punishment shall be
a thousand times a thousand deaths.
Each more horrible
than the last.
They are tired
of your talk, Isaac.
I have shown them
what I can do.
Cut the woman down.
Put Isaac in her place.
You will see how
the Lord favors you.
No, you dare not.
You blaspheme.
He will punish you.
The god of hell will devour you.
All of you! No!
When my dad
wouldn't get up,
I ran from Hansen's
to get Officer Hotchkiss.
But I was too late.
Why, what happened to him?
He got away...
that time.
Then he went down to the barn
after he talked to the minister.
The minister?
What happened to the minister?
Malachai.
Outlander!
Get over there.
He's gonna come. Get over there.
- You come with me down this street.
- Outlander!
Outlander!
We have your woman.
She still lives.
Outlander, maybe you don't
hear so well.
Burt!
Outlander,
her blood will spill
unless you give
yourself up.
We won't wait
much longer.
Night is coming.
Night is His time.
Outlander!
Come on!
Come on, outlander!
Outlander!
Are you looking
for that lady?
Yeah, you know
where she is?
- They took her out to the clearing.
- What clearing? Where?
In the cornfield.
- Are you sure?
- Of course, I'm sure.
- I followed them like I followed you.
- Show me.
- Okay.
- Come on, let's go.
Okay.
Quiet.
Come on.
Follow me to the barn.
Careful.
I'm ready to celebrate
my birthday.
Malachai, He will not forgive you!
None of you
will be forgiven!
All of you
shall feel His wrath!
We have a surprise for you, Amos.
You morons. Don't you understand
what he's trying to do?
Isaac's going
to keep you company.
He Who Walks Behind the Rows
will decide your fate.
I am the word and the giver
of His laws!
This is the end!
Come on.
Come in through here.
You can see
everything from here.
Okay, you two.
You stay here
and wait for me, all right?
But if anything
happens to me,
you get to Hemingford
as fast as you can.
You get on that road
and don't get off, understand?
Go past
the irrigation pump.
It's him.
He's come for me.
He's come
to welcome me.
Go to him, Amos!
I'm here, Lord!
I'm ready.
Take me now, Lord.
Your will, Lord.
Thy message.
I did as You commanded.
I was good.
I swear it.
I did everything
You wanted.
No!
It's the outlander!
Come on, go.
Run to the barn.
Get him!
Help Malachai!
- Get him.
- He came back.
Vicky, get out of here.
Was this how it was
with your parents, huh?
Was it?
Just because some
self-proclaimed holy man
said this is what
God commands?
So?
What kind of a god tells his children
to kill their parents, huh?
Answer me that, buddy.
Did you ever hear
of that before Isaac?
Did you?
I can't believe
you're this blind.
Maybe you've been listening to these
holy rollers so long,
it's all starting to sound the same.
Well, it's not!
- What's he talking about?
- Any religion...
without love
and compassion...
is false!
It's a lie!
Did he kill Malachai?
Is this what
you want, huh?
Is this what He
commands?
I don't think so.
Get him.
Stop him.
Malachai!
Oh my God! Isaac!
He wants you too...
Malachai!
He wants you too.
Use these!
Should we board this up?
- Vicky?
- Burt?
Over here.
You're hurt.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Get down.
Joby, get some help
and get those doors closed, quick.
- Peter, Robert, come on.
- What do we do?
I don't know.
If I knew what it was,
I could tell you.
It's He Who Walks
Behind the Rows.
What if we tried to run for it
and make it to the road?
I think we're
safer here for now.
Joby, has anybody
ever tried to hurt the monster?
Any of the adults?
The parents before they were killed?
The blue man.
Who's the blue man?
What did he do?
Officer Hotchkiss.
I told you.
He came down here after
he talked to the minister.
He was reading a page
torn out of the Bible
- and he was working with the still.
- Wait a minute.
Why was he reading out of the Bible?
What was it?
Do you know?
You have it?
Hurry up.
Where is it?
It's all Malachai's fault!
"And the devil
that deceived them
was cast into the lake of fire
and brimstone
where the beast and the false prophet
are and shall be tormented
day and night
forever and ever."
What's that
supposed to mean?
Job, what was
the blue man doing at the still?
He hooked the hose up
to it and was trying to roll it out.
- What stopped him?
- Malachai.
"Lake of fire." Fire!
He was going to burn the field.
Oh, yes.
The gasohol. The still.
- How?
- Never mind, never mind.
You kids, get me as many hoses
as you can find, quick!
Job and Sarah,
find me a bottle, a glass one.
A pop bottle.
Quick, move.
Vicky, come here.
- Over here.
- I can't find anything.
It doesn't fit.
There's gotta be a connector
around here somewhere.
Try these.
Get somebody
to hold this on tight.
- Okay!
- Hang on to it.
You got one, good.
Vicky, see if you can find me
a thick rag.
Joby, come here.
Hey, that's not a rag.
Sheesh.
Okay.
Now get them to hold
onto that tight.
- Open it up when I get out there, all right?
- All right.
Burt, be careful.
- I love you, Vicky.
- I wish we'd never done this.
Okay.
What are you doing here?
Get back to the barn. Hurry up.
Go on, move. Now.
Excuse me.
Joby, get that valve.
Quick.
Joby, do you know how
to run this thing?
- Crank it.
- What?
Crank it.
Push the button
at the top.
Yeah.
All right.
- Get the bottle.
- Okay.
Come here.
Block the wind.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Joby! Joby!
Come back here.
You'll get killed.
Joby!
Run. Come on.
Run, Joby.
Here's the bottle!
Throw it.
Throw right this time.
Burt!
- Joby!
- Burt!
Joby!
- Vicky! Vicky!
- Sarah!
Joby!
Look! Look!
Come on, come on.
Let's go.
- Is He dead?
- I think so.
- Then why are we still running?
- Just keep going.
Where did you get this guy?
Well, Hemingford's 19 miles, right?
You mean walk?
Sure.
Burt, are you sure
you're strong enough?
I'm okay.
What about you?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'll make it.
I got a great doctor.
You better believe it.
Jealous?
What are we gonna do
with these two little munchkins, huh?
Oh, I don't know.
You guys want to come live with us
for a couple days?
- Hmm?
- How about a week?
- Okay.
- How about a month?
No.
All right.
I'll grab the map.
- Ever been to Seattle?
- What's Seattle?
Interloper!
No!
You must die.
Oh, boy.
Oh, she's out cold.
What are we
gonna do now?
Send her a get-well
card from Seattle.
Let's get the hell
out of here.