Oh, fuck.
Holy shit.
Fuck no.
Hello?
Hey, man.
Hey, you okay?
You look troubled.
Oh, yeah, sorry.
It's just, um, you should come see this.
Uh...
What's going on, buddy?
Remember I told you
I was getting those calls,
and I had that DVD sent to me?
I know.
It's happening again?
Yeah.
- Oh, my god. -I thought
that was over, but...
I just had a package
outside, and...
- Just now?
- Yeah.
That was in there.
This person sent you
a stuffed baby wolf?
I mean, I guess.
It doesn't make any sense.
There was also
this DVD that was in it.
Dave, this is your...
That's your home.
Dave.
Yeah, I know, I know.
This is serious.
Whoever shot this,
they shot it last night.
And that's me last night.
We have to call the police.
- You need to call the police.
This is serious. -No, no.
No, I already called
the police the last time,
and nothing happened, okay?
They said they...
Well, that's unconscionable.
- That's unconscionable. -No,
they even sent a patrol car.
- That's unconscionable.
- Nothing has actually happened.
Where's your gun?
Are you serious?
- Well, you need...
- I don't own a gun.
- You're gonna need something.
- That's not necessary.
- It's not necessary. -Dave, I don't think
you're taking this seriously enough.
I'm sorry, I kinda just
ambushed you, uh...
No, it's okay man.
- It's good. It's good.
- No. No, uh...
Do you want a beer?
- I would love one.
- Yeah?
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
I think I need some alcohol.
- Okay.
- Okay, great.
It's crazy, Dave.
It's fine. It's fine.
It's okay. It's okay.
Hi, sweet boy.
Hello.
So, what is going on with you?
Are you serious?
What's going on with me?
Yeah.
God damn, you're awesome.
I mean, here you are, dealing with
this potential stalker situation,
and you're concerned
with me and my feelings?
Mmm-hmm.
Fuckin' love you, man.
Aw.
- Cheers.
Mm.
This is great, isn't it?
- Yeah.
- Two guys just hanging out,
throwing back
a couple of cold ones.
Really wish I didn't have to say
what I have to say to you tonight.
Oh. What's that?
I'm worried about us.
Mm.
- Oh, uh, you are?
- Aren't you?
Uh, us, we're good.
We're friends. We...
We hang out
sometimes. We're...
Come on, Dave.
You and I both know there's a
lot more at stake than that.
- Okay... -Meeting at
the same coffee shop,
in the same Tuesday morning,
reading the same exact
edition of infinite jest?
Hmm.
And if that wasn't kismet,
if we weren't meant to
be best friends or soulmates,
and started out so hot and
heavy like that, and then...
We turned into this...
Well, it's disappointing.
And I can't help
but think if we...
If we aren't
headed for greatness,
then maybe we just
end it right here...
Tonight.
Okay, I don't
think that's necessary.
Dave, if I ask you a question,
would you answer me honestly?
Yeah, of course.
Do you ever think about how...
We met right
around the same time
you received your
first DVD in the mail?
You just thought
about it, didn't you?
I didn't.
Dave, you just thought about it.
I didn't, I swear.
Dave, listen to me.
It's okay, okay?
Everything that's about to
happen to you here tonight
is okay, and it's
not your fault.
You understand me?
- No, I don't understand...
- Okay, now, listen.
There's a camera
inside this wolf, okay?
Now I've been filming you in some way,
shape, or form since the day we met.
This is baby peach fuzz.
Say hi.
I was gonna record
our entire relationship
and commemorate it with
a beautiful 80-minute film,
and you deserve that.
You deserve it because
you're a beautiful person,
and I want to give that
to you so bad, but...
I can't.
'Cause ever since I turned 40,
I don't know what's happening
to me, Dave. I just...
I've lost my inspiration,
I have no joy,
and my work...
I don't even know
if I can do this anymore.
- God damn it.
What's happening to me?
Hi, I'm Sara.
Welcome to encounters.
The show where I look behind the
strange world of online personal ads
to try to uncover
the humanity underneath.
- Hey, Wade.
- Hey.
I'm Sara.
Hey, Sara, how you doin'?
I hope you don't mind
I brought my camera.
If you don't mind, Marilyn Monroe
already lives in the wall.
Oh, yeah.
There she is.
So you were trying to make
your pottery earlier.
- Yeah.
- You were telling me about it.
Who are these people
who write these ads?
What is their story?
This place has
a cold energy to it.
Mmm-hmm.
Most of the spirit pots
that I build
are to deflect that cold energy.
This is my little jaws 2.
He's a little shark.
- Yeah, it does look good.
- It does.
Little jaws.
Maybe we're all a little bit weirder
than we give ourselves credit for.
- May I come in?
- Yeah, come in.
What did you... What were you looking
for when you posted your ad?
You know...
You know, life is lonely.
- Yeah. -It's nice to
have someone to talk to.
So subscribe
and join me on this journey.
- Hey.
- Hi, welcome.
You never know who you
might meet on the next...
- Is it okay?
- Yeah.
Encounters.
No.
Nine views.
Awesome.
Hey, this is Sara.
Welcome to encounters,
the web series that
nobody gives a shit about,
and I am starting to realize
why nobody is watching.
It's because it sucks.
I think I might be
deeply untalented.
Aw, man.
I thought I had a talent for bringing
out something weird and special
and taboo and secret in people,
that there was a loneliness
that I could detect,
that I really empathized with.
And I... I see glimpses of it
sometimes, and it's so exciting.
And I'm close.
I can feel it,
but I never follow through
in the right way,
and I'm tired of trying,
and I'm tired of failing.
It is humiliating.
I never expected to
make money doing this,
but I thought at least I would be
able to reach some other weirdos
and make something
special for them.
So I'm Sara.
Welcome to encounters.
This is our finale, the closing
episode of the entire season.
Join me as we encounter...
My failure.
I hope you enjoy it.
Hey. Sorry about last night.
I got a little bit dramatic,
but I'm feeling
a lot better now.
I've had my coffee,
and... I found this.
"Looking for videographer.
$1000 for the day.
Honesty and
emotional bravery a must.
Fans of interview with
the vampire a plus.
Let's go deep. Together."
Interesting.
Oh.
Ah...
Fuck it.
What?
Here we are...
In the woods.
I've been driving
three hours now.
This is a lot more off road
than I had anticipated.
745.
Okay.
Hey.
Welcome to encounters.
I'm Sara. This is
episode 10 of 10.
And normally,
this is where I tell you
that I'm gonna go see John, a
mid-level manager at Walgreens,
and that we're gonna work through
his mommy issues through...
I don't know, synchronized
swimming or some shit,
but I don't have that today.
I know very little
about this guy.
He's been ghosting me
since he sent me his address,
and I have no idea
what I'm stepping into.
Normally, this is not a situation
I would allow myself to get into,
but maybe that's why this show
has been sucking so much.
So let's see what happens.
Hello?
Hello, I'm Sara.
Oh.
Sorry.
Hi.
Green smoothie?
Okay.
Very healthy.
Kale, four frozen strawberries,
one banana, one heaping tablespoon
of non-fat plain Greek yogurt,
two pinches spirulina and
one pinch of cinnamon.
Thank you.
- Cheers.
It's good.
It's also poisoned.
Obviously I'm kidding.
I'm Aaron.
Sara.
Wow. That's your real name.
Yeah.
Yeah, I can tell.
Thanks for that.
You're welcome.
Can we start with a hug?
Okay.
Mm.
I like that you came in
already filming.
Yeah, I want you
to get your money's worth.
Yeah. You know, people
don't really believe in that.
You got to keep the camera on
if you wanna keep the magic.
I mean... you know.
You and I kinda have a thing.
I like that.
That's a nice camera, by the way.
Are you a filmmaker by trade?
I shoot wedding videos
to make money.
I'm actually applying to grad school
right now. I'm trying to save up.
Mm. You don't do
anything else?
No.
Cool.
What about you?
What's your story?
My story, um...
I am what is commonly
known as a serial killer.
Um, I don't love
that nomenclature.
I sort of consider
myself a murderer,
but, uh, my numbers are such that I'm
now classified as a serial killer.
- Serial killer?
- Yes, I am a killer.
I have killed 39 people.
This is something
that I love to do.
It's the greatest job
in the world.
That's what I'm built to do.
Um, but I'm also
turning 40 this year,
which is like, grays in the
beards, a lot of stuff happening,
and it's making me
a little mid-lifey,
and it's kind of set me
into a little bit of a spiral.
And I think I fucked
myself in the head.
I don't trust
my instincts anymore,
and I feel like I may have
lost what made me great.
There was a time in my life when
I would meet a man at a bar
and I would take him outside
and lay him on the floor,
and I would put a knife
in his chest and cut him open.
And... open his insides,
and the universe would reveal
itself to me, and it was beautiful.
And I felt part of every time and every
place that had ever existed. It...
It was my religion.
But now, it...
It's like a job.
And it makes me
really fucking sad.
And I don't wanna get emotional,
but, um, I'm having a hard time.
But then,
I read an article about
the great Francis Ford Coppola.
He said something that
blew my fucking mind.
He said, "I've not made an original
film since the conversation in 1974.
I am not sure I'm capable of it,
but I really wanna
keep trying."
And then it hit me
like a sack of bricks.
Here's a man who's in the middle
of his artistic decline...
Is he running from it?
No, he's embracing it.
So, I'm like...
What am I doing, trying to make
the films that I used to make?
What if I embrace
where I'm at right now?
What if I make a documentary?
And this is where you come in.
A documentary about the world's
most prolific serial killer
that no one knows about.
A documentary that
you and I make here,
tonight.
I mean, like,
I realize I'm throwing
a lot at you.
You haven't even had the chance
to finish your green smoothie,
so if you wanna bail,
I completely understand.
Take your money,
no hard feelings.
I understand.
But if you don't...
And I really hope you don't...
I can offer you two things.
Firstly, I won't kill you
over the next 24 hours.
That would be
counter-productive.
And secondly,
I will give you the deepest
personal access into my soul
that you could possibly imagine.
I will rip myself open
and let you see
every last inch of me.
And together, I believe
we will make magic.
But you gotta be into it.
I'm into it.
Are you just saying you're into
it because you want a job?
No, I've heard you out,
and I think this sounds great.
Wanna do it?
I don't hear any
passion in your voice.
Aaron, I wanna make
this film with you.
Hmm.
What am I looking at here?
You'll see.
Who's this guy?
He's my friend.
Is that you?
Sara...
All good things
to those who wait.
Oh.
Shit.
So...
What do you think?
I think it's interesting.
Mmm-hmm.
Did it scare you?
Did you want it to scare me?
Hmm.
I'll be right back.
Fuck.
What the fuck?
So.
I was thinking upstairs that...
When men are in the locker room,
they snap towels
at each other's genitals
without any inhibitions.
Uh, when women try on
clothes in changing rooms,
there is no barrier
to their intimacy.
But with a man and a woman,
there is always a wall
between them.
And that wall is...
"I wonder what
you look like naked."
And if I'm being honest,
that's something I've felt.
And if we're gonna embark
on this journey together,
we need to tear that wall down.
Do you agree?
I agree.
How do you feel?
I'm good.
You?
I just think it's important
that there is a wall
and a gender divide.
This is a spiritual journey,
so we need to eradicate it.
I agree.
Okay.
Then we're good.
Is it my turn?
I'm sorry?
Um, can it be my turn now?
Here.
Uh...
You can sit down.
Yeah, okay. Yeah.
You got your frame?
Yeah. Yeah.
Are we good?
Yeah.
Okay.
I'll be right back.
Holy shit. Holy shit.
Holy shit.
Okay.
Sara, every red flag
you have has been raised.
Um, he is highly unpredictable
and potentially dangerous,
and you were not there for ten minutes
before his dick was in your face.
Sara, you were not there for ten minutes
He is everything you
ever wanted in a subject.
You have to chase this.
Sara, come on,
we're losing light.
I'm coming.
I have to do this.
I'm like 99.9% positive
he is not a killer.
But just in case, because I'm
not a total fucking idiot...
Knife.
I'm coming.
One minute.
Hey, I'm Sara.
Welcome to encounters.
Here we fucking go.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Are you ready to go?
Wow. You're
a tough nut to crack.
Mm...
What's with your beard here?
What... what do you mean?
Right there.
Oh, this. That's just
my beard pattern.
Some men have little patches.
This is one of my patches.
Um, all right,
we should get going.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
We are losing light.
Okay.
Aaron, come on.
Really?
All right.
I'll get you at some point.
We'll see about that.
Where are you from?
So where did you grow up?
What do you think about my mask?
As a passenger,
I'm not super excited about it.
Can you see in that thing?
Oh, now you're scared?
Do you believe in god?
It could complicate
what you do for a living.
You still haven't answered
my question about my mask.
I think it's cute.
Really?
Sure.
You're a cute little wolf.
What would you say if I told you
I'm a naughty wolf?
I'd say that's very scary
coming from someone like you.
Okay.
Well, what if I told you that
at the end of this road,
I was gonna cut off your head
and snugglefuck it?
Did you have
any friends growing up?
Uh-huh.
Did you have a best friend?
Sure.
You think your best friend...
You're asking a lot
of questions. Um...
I'm sorry.
I have a perfect, idyllic spot
picked out for this interview.
Can we just...
Let's just save it. Okay?
Okay.
Thanks, Sara.
You're gonna love it.
Oh, this is really nice.
No. No, no!
Where's the water?
Where's the fucking water?
That's the water.
No, no, no. The raging river of water that
was here when I scouted it. It was...
You know, I had
the whole shot planned.
I was gonna be here,
submerged in the water
up to my neck
for the whole Jesus metaphor
and that's the... I mean, and the...
the bridge!
That was the final scene.
I was gonna jump off the bridge,
splash into the water,
you cut to
something really cool,
I mean, that's the ending
of the scene. We...
We don't even have a scene.
This is not...
This is...
This is... no. No, no!
Aaron?
Hold on. I'm gonna.
I gotta think about this.
- Aaron.
- What!
Coppola.
Poppola?
Why are you
saying Coppola? What...
Aaron.
Francis Ford Coppola.
What would he do?
Huh.
That's really fuckin' smart.
December 1978.
It was the last days of disco.
The cold war was
heating up by the minute.
But in a nondescript home,
in a nondescript town...
Sorry, what are you
doing with your arms?
This is, uh, well, if the visual
effects of the water's up here,
this would be me
just sort of floating...
- Ah. - ...With it. You
know what I'm saying?
- Yeah, I don't think... -this
one feels a little more real.
What do you think?
Should we...
I don't think you need it.
- We don't need it?
- No.
Sorry, I got a little...
I got some sunblock in my eye.
Mm.
Airplane.
Wait. Let's wait
for the sound...
It's a really slow airplane.
How's the pony?
- Beautiful.
- Yeah?
- You sure?
- Yep.
Would you mind coming up real quick
and just giving me a little fix?
Um, yeah. Okay.
Sorry, I don't want to get your shoes wet,
but I just wanna make sure it's right.
- Okay.
- Yeah, come on up.
Just tighten it.
Oh, I didn't want you to redo...
Oh, that's okay.
No problem.
We'll do it. We'll just
do the whole thing.
December 1978.
It was the last days of disco.
The cold war was
just heating up,
but in a small tow...
Little bird right there.
Hold on.
- December 19...
it's like a bad joke.
Hey.
One more.
Try it one more time.
One more time.
I want you to do it.
I want you to do it!
Hey! No!
No!
No! This is my movie...
It was December 1978.
It was the last days of disco.
The cold war was just...
I'm getting a lot of shadow
on your face.
You wanna retake this?
Aaron?
I'm gonna take a break.
Okay.
If you'll excuse me.
Aaron?
Okay, so it turns out Aaron
is a bit of a drama queen.
I'm not sure if
he's used to collaboration.
Aaron?
This day might be a wash.
- I'm just not...
Aaron?
Aaron, is that you?
Don't leave.
I won't.
Hey.
Aaron's not talking anymore.
He's kind of shut down
since his tantrum at the river.
And I don't know
if you can hear it,
but he's been blasting the same
shit '90s jam band song on loop
for the past hour.
He's so vulnerable right now,
and I know the decent thing to
do is just give him some space,
but at the same time, it would
be so easy to go down there
and provoke him...
And get the material I need.
Go.
Why should I go?
'Cause I want you to go.
How come?
Because I don't want you to
make this documentary anymore.
Take your money and go, please.
What's going on?
- What's the problem?
- Sara, leave.
Aaron, I'm not leaving.
I'm sorry.
You told me once we got started,
there was no turning back.
I'm not turning back.
Turn that song back on.
Why?
Because I said so.
Tell me why.
Because it's my favorite
song in the world,
and I need it because I love it.
What do you love about it?
Um, maybe because it does more
with one instrumental slow jam
than any poet with any quill has ever
done in the history of time, ever.
I've never heard of it before.
Well, you wouldn't have.
Barely anyone has.
It's from an unknown band
from a long time ago.
Tell me about it.
Sara, I know what you're trying
to do, and it's not gonna work.
Why won't you tell me
about it, Aaron?
Because...
You think you want to
know my story,
but I promise you, you do
not wanna know my story.
But I do.
Oh, you do?
Really?
Yes.
Fine.
I was 15 years old,
but I could pass for 18
'cause I was big for my age.
I could go to bars
and see live music.
An obscure band came to town.
There weren't more than
seven of us in the audience,
but I was mesmerized,
in particular by a song called
"Sara loves her juicy fruit."
It transported me.
That night, I went
out of town with the band
and I partied with them
where they were staying.
I felt like I belonged
for the first time.
But of course,
they had to move on
to another city the next day.
I walked back towards town,
and a man pulled over
to offer me a ride.
He had a nice, kind face.
And as he opened the door,
he said something to me.
I'll never forget it.
He said...
"Oh, my god.
Oh, my god.
This is gonna be a good day."
He didn't take me back to town,
he took me to
a remote part of the woods
where he beat me
within an inch of my life.
He gave me a shovel, he forced
me to dig my own grave,
he tied my hands behind
my back and informed me
that he would be burying me alive
within the next couple of minutes.
And I remember
thinking to myself,
"I should be feeling
really badly about this man,"
but he was magnetic.
I loved him.
He was smart, he was commanding,
he was wonderful in all ways.
He only had one flaw.
He was not very good
at tying knots.
And as I loosened my hands
from behind my back,
and I wrapped them
around his neck,
overpowering him with my size,
I drained...
His life
with my hands.
And I thought to myself,
"well, this is my destiny.
Sara loves her juicy fruit.
And Aaron loves to kill."
I stripped him of his clothes,
I threw his body in the hole
he made me dig for myself,
and on instinct,
I took off my own clothes,
and I lay there communing
next to him, all night, naked.
And something very
interesting happened.
You see...
I lied to you earlier.
About what?
About my beard holes.
It's not my hair pattern.
It's actually a rare disease
called trichotillomania.
You know, people pull hairs out
of their beard or their scalp
or even their eyebrows.
You see, my first victim
had this disease,
and when I lay with him naked,
my spirit consumed that
from his spirit...
And it became a ritual of mine.
All of my victims,
I lay with them naked,
and I take a part
of them with me.
And here I am now,
a strange but
wonderful amalgamation
of all the 39 men and women
that I have killed,
and it has been the most
glorious part of my life.
It has been my raison d'etre.
And now...
It's gone.
And that is why I'm sad.
And that is why I have
nothing to live for anymore.
And that is why I want
you to go, because tonight
is going to be a very...
Bad...
Bad night.
Aaron.
Sara.
Stay right there.
Close your eyes.
I don't want to.
Do it.
- Shh...
Shh...
Do you feel better?
A little bit.
Good.
I'm gonna go take a shower now.
Hey, Sara,
it's me. Um...
Thank you...
For...
Um...
Doing what you just did. I think
you are really, really...
Special.
And you are inspiring
feelings in me that...
I thought I would
never feel again,
and...
I don't know what to do.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh, my god.
Oh, god, you got me.
Yeah?
How do you feel?
I feel like...
Forty-seven...
Forty-eight,
forty-nine,
fifty.
Ready or not, here I come!
Sara?
Where'd you go?
I'm coming for you.
I got...
Uh-oh.
I think I found you.
Sara?
Are you being bad?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Sara, where's you go?
Damn it!
You got me!
You don't scare me.
Are you rolling, Sara?
Yeah.
Aaron, if ask you a question,
will you answer honestly?
Of course. Always.
When you're holding that ax,
is there a part of you that
wants to ram it into my face?
You know, considering your past?
Well, of course.
But then...
You know, we wouldn't be able to
have all the fun we are having.
That's interesting. I...
I think I always thought
I was gonna die
before I could share
my work with anyone,
but now I have you.
Which is kinda cool.
Do you feel remorse
for the people you kill?
Um...
Maybe a little bit,
but I also...
I feel like I'm pretty
fair to my victims.
I try to give them a warning as
to what they're walking into.
That's why I put stuff
in the ad, like...
"Are you a fan of
interview with the vampire?"
Like, I want them to know
that I'm dangerous.
You know...
Actually, this is...
One of my latest
was this big ol' sweetie
and... I called him "buddy."
And I stuck an ax in a stump
outside of the house I rented.
He passed by, he saw it,
he came in anyway and he stayed
with me all night, you know.
I mean, it's almost like...
It's almost like...
Like they wanna die.
Did you kill him with that ax?
Uh-huh.
Does that mean you're gonna
murder me with the blender?
That's actually
a brilliant idea.
I've never thought of that
as a weapon before.
But alas, Sara...
I promised I wouldn't kill you.
And I never lie.
Not in the cards for us.
Well...
But you said you wouldn't kill me
within the next 24 hours. So...
Now why would you bring that up?
That only gets you into trouble.
Hey.
What you doin'?
The dishes.
What are you doing
with my camera?
Have you ever spent
any time in the woods?
Sure.
You ever...
Just watched a deer, just...
Just being a deer?
Put that away. That's my job.
Okay.
Psst.
Mommy needs her juice.
Where is mommy's juice?
Mommy is thirsty.
Oh, yes!
This better be Coppola wine.
Oh, thank you, sweetheart.
Mmm.
- That's nice. Thank you.
- Mmm-hmm.
What are you thinking about?
Uh, I'm thinking about this really
cool book that I once read,
called the journalist
and the murderer.
- Have you heard of it?
- No.
Oh, it's really great.
You gotta give it a read.
What's it about?
It's sort of about the moral quandary
that journalists face, you know,
uh, how they
sometimes have to lie
and ingratiate themselves
with their subjects, you know,
this little flattery and little
flirtation to get the material they need.
And...
I thought about it
while I was...
Watching a little show
called encounters.
Didn't know I knew
about that, did you?
I know a lot of things, Sara.
Like what?
Oh, no, you don't
make wedding videos.
Um, and I know you have
a knife in your boot.
- What are you talking about?
- It's okay.
Don't worry
about it, okay? Look.
Let's see.
I don't think you've been "lying"
here, traditionally, you know.
I think you've been, uh, you've been playing
around with the facts a little bit,
but look, everybody
does that, okay?
Look, it's one of
my favorite things to do.
It's what I do for a living.
But...
While I do play
around with facts,
I never lie.
My eyes, my heart, my soul,
I always tell the truth
and that's the same kind of truth I've
been feeling from you here today.
So I want you to know
everything's okay.
I'm not mad. Okay?
Okay.
That said,
I'm gonna ask you a question and I
want you to answer me honestly.
Do you believe that
I'm a serial killer?
- No. -Good. Thank you
for your honesty.
Why not?
Well...
First off, the stories you've
been telling are ridiculous.
Okay.
And, like, what's up
with this whole documentary?
If you were a killer,
why would you invite me into
your home and have me film you
confess all the details
of your murders?
Like, what would stop me from
going to the police with this?
It's a fair point.
It is a moot point, however.
You won't go to
the police tomorrow,
because tomorrow,
I'll be dead...
Because tonight,
you are going to kill me.
- Aaron...
- Now before you protest,
I've thought about this.
I'm very excited about it, okay?
Why would I make my 40th film
another random kill film?
I made 39 of those, okay?
Also, why would we make some
stodgy, pedantic documentary?
Plenty of those.
You know what we need?
A murder film...
Where the pupil
fells the king.
That's the movie I wanna make.
What makes you think
I'm gonna do this?
Because I know you well enough to
know that you will do anything
to make a great piece of art.
And this will be the most
unbelievably exciting
episode of encounters
that you can possibly imagine.
I know I just laid a lot on you,
but I have a lot
of experience with this
and I'm the easy way to it.
- I'm super excited.
- Aaron, what is...
First things first.
Put that camera down, girl.
What are you doing?
I said put
that camera down, girl.
What's with the mask, Aaron?
Now you remember, this is peach
fuzz, the friendly wolf.
Here, give me the camera.
Okay.
Come with me.
How are you with an ax?
I've never used an ax before.
Okay, it's like a bat.
Are you a lefty
or are you a righty?
- Righty. -Okay, you know what, it
doesn't matter. Just get into it.
Okay, I'm wearing a mask
so you don't have to look into
my eyes while you kill me.
It's a little difficult.
Did I mention, it's like a
cartoon, like a funny noise.
Also, I sharpened the ax.
It should go straight
through my neck.
There are very few bones.
Let's do it!
Okay, so, just to be clear,
you want me to take this ax
and chop your head off with it.
Yes, 100%.
Camera heard it first.
Consider it assisted suicide.
It's totally cool.
All right.
Any last words?
Nope.
I've talked enough
for ten lifetimes.
Wait. Wait.
Okay. Go for it.
Whenever you're ready.
Just reach back
and take a swing.
What's wrong?
- You all right, Sara?
- Yeah.
- Got your frame?
- Yep.
Okie dokie.
Okay.
So, this is a much better idea.
I should have thought of this
in the first place.
This is essentially going to turn
this into a passive endeavor.
What I' going to do,
I'm gonna jump off the ledge,
and unless you come and save me,
I'm gonna die,
which make you complicit
in the murder.
Pretty cool, right?
I mean, obviously, not as cool as
putting an ax through my neck,
but for a first-timer,
it'll do.
Ready, Sara?
Actually, to be
honest, I don't...
Oh, my god. Oh, my god.
Oh, my god.
Pull yourself up.
Can you breathe?
Aaron? Aaron!
- Aaron!
Sara.
Sara?
You in here?
Hello...
Where'd you go?
Hey, there you are.
Okay, so...
Before sunrise,
put the camera above us.
I play you "Sara loves
her juicy fruit"...
What are you doing?
Are you leaving?
Jesus.
- Sara, did I freak you out by
hanging myself? -Fuck off.
What?
I said "fuck off."
I'm so...
Please don't go. Please.
Do you have any idea
how fucked up that was?
I'm sorry. I was...
I can't believe you
put me in that position.
Can you just stop for a
second so I can explain?
What is wrong with you?
Okay, wait, just give me one...
What's wrong with you?
One second, please. Just promise
me you won't leave. One second.
Please.
What the fuck is this?
It's a harness.
That's what I was wearing underneath
my shirt when I hanged myself.
I connected a black wire
to the harness,
so I was hanging by my chest,
and I wouldn't...
Actually hang myself.
Look...
I'm sorry it freaked you out.
I thought...
I don't know what
I was thinking. I'm just...
Look, I'm not really good
at this, okay,
but I'm just gonna
lay it out there.
I really, really like you.
And I'm just trying
to connect with you.
I'm not really
doing a very good job.
And I know you don't really
wanna connect with me, so...
What I figured I would do is
give you what
I can give you, which is...
The best episode of encounters.
I can give you. I can...
Be a fucked up guy
and show you...
Everything that
hopefully gives you
what you want as an artist.
Look...
Am I a murderer?
No.
Of course I'm not a murderer.
Am I a...
Sociopathic pathological liar,
who is completely disconnected
from the world and people?
Yes.
Am I majorly connecting with you
and having a fucking
great time today,
because I get to just lie and be
weird like I really like to do?
Yes.
I just...
I really like you.
And I think you're incredible.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I think it will make
a really good scene.
I know, right?
I'm sorry I freaked you out.
You freaked me out.
I'm so sorry.
What are we doing?
We're gonna play a game.
What kind of game
are we playing?
It's called
"two lies and a truth."
You play this game
in your castle?
- Yeah.
- Okay, good.
So in "two lies and a truth"...
- Mmm-hmm. - ...You're gonna
tell three stories,
and one of them will be true.
And none of that bullshit,
like, from your heart...
I got you. I got you.
I want facts that are
technically correct.
Okay. All right.
Two lies, one truth.
And I get to guess
which one is the truth.
Okay.
I was born
three months premature.
I have never slept with a woman.
I can hold my breath for
two and a half minutes.
Okay.
I think that it's...
The... the breath one.
It's number two.
You want me to be honest,
it's number two.
You're fucking with me.
I... I wish I was.
Did it look like
I was fucking with you
when you came on to me
in the hot tub?
Did it look like
I knew what I was doing?
It was just a weird...
Series of events.
I didn't have
a normal childhood,
you know, I...
I started to notice
my chemistry was off,
like in those pre-teen years
when I had my first sort of...
Like psychotic break
when I was like 14.
So I was in an institution
until I was about 19,
and they didn't really know
how to properly medicate then,
so by the time I got out,
I had a split with my family,
and um...
And I got a job at security,
which was mostly older people,
so I didn't really consort
with people my age,
and then I just missed...
I just missed the boat.
I just missed it.
Um...
Have you ever had a girlfriend?
Nope.
I...
Have you ever seen that movie,
never been kissed?
Yeah.
I should have written
and directed that movie.
It's embarrassing.
No, it's not embarrassing.
It's really embarrassing.
It's really weird,
but it's not embarrassing.
I don't know.
Do you wanna
have your first kiss?
Shut up.
It doesn't have to
be a big deal.
Really?
Yeah.
You would kiss me?
Okay.
Who makes the move?
That was cool.
You know, I'm super
excited about this idea.
I have the climax
to the episode.
So where are you taking me?
Like I'm gonna tell you.
Watch your head.
All good things to
those who wait, my dear.
Come this way.
Okay.
All right, now,
before we get started,
I do have a surprise for you,
but you have to close your eyes.
Why would I close my eyes?
There's no fucking way.
I'm in the middle of nowhere
at night with you.
That's a very good point.
Point taken,
but it will be worth it.
Trust me.
Okay.
All right.
Open it.
What is this?
It's a symbol of
my affection for you
and of our amazing day
we spent together.
Sorry, there's a picture of
me and another guy in there.
I didn't have a chance to make
one specifically for you.
You were a bit of a surprise.
May I?
Okay.
Cool.
All tight. It's time
for part two.
Ready?
Okay.
I don't get it.
Oh, shit.
When did you dig that?
I dug it before you got here.
I wasn't sure if it was
supposed to be for me
or for you.
But I think I finally
figured it out.
Okay.
Tada!
Nope, nope, nope.
It's yours.
I snuck it out of your boot
after I fell on you.
Thought for sure
you would have noticed that.
Are you ready
for the grand finale
of the episode?
Okay.
It's all right.
We both stab each other
and we both crawl in the grave
and we die together
like Romeo and Juliet,
and somebody would
find the tapes.
And when they see it,
we'll be like,
history together.
Look, you're afraid.
Don't be afraid.
I'm not gonna stab you.
Here. I love you too much.
Take it. Take the knife.
You do it.
Come on.
Do it.
Sara...
Wait!
Sara!
You're in the middle of nowhere.
Come on, Sara.
I have the keys.
There's nowhere to go.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Sara?
Your best episode...
So...
I don't think
I'm gonna die tonight.
I kind of feel bad
about it. It's...
It was my whole idea
in the first place.
But, Sara...
You did it.
You made a great, great episode.
You should be really
proud of yourself.
I'm bummed you're not
gonna be here to see it.
It's kind of ironic 'cause
I never thought I was...
I really don't wanna kill again.
That was real,
but then it was you,
my muse.
You inspired me.
My Coppola.