What are you doing?
Is your Spotify working?
Yeah. Why?
I dunno, mine's being retarded.
Alex Freeman probably hacked you.
He did mine and changed every
single playlist to Jason Derulo.
I still haven't forgiven Alex
for changing all my contacts
to Harry Potter characters.
~ What a twat!
~ He put himself as Voldemort.
Oh, please! More like
Neville Longbottom.
My mum was Bellatrix Lestrange.
At least he got that right.
Here, what do we think
of this bronzer?
You look like a Wotsit.
See, this is why I need you.
My mum is now on
Snapchat, by the way.
Urgh! Why?!
I'd like to say she's just
trying to reconnect,
but I actually think she likes it.
What are you doing?
Checking flights to Barca.
Casey! We're going to Outlook!
Why are you fighting this?
Sonar! Barcelona has culture.
Er, Pula has a beach!
Barcelona has a beach,
and plus, if we don't get any more
money, we're not going anywhere.
Casey?
What?
Nathan.
Please don't use the N-word.
You should look.
At what?
His tweet.
I unfollowed him. What does it say?
It's not very nice.
Can you just read it?
"I guess it's no surprise that Casey
Jacobs is on antidepressants.
"I spent one night with
her and it depressed me."
How could he write that?
Are you OK?
How does he know? I
haven't told anyone.
Tamara?
You're the only one I've told.
He was in your room,
did he see your pills?
Casey, I didn't tell anyone.
Yeah, I know.
Oh, my God, no!
We are doing this!
~ What?
~ You know who!
Oh, no, Megan, just leave it.
What? No way! He owes us.
~ Hey, Alex.
~ Hey. What do you guys want?
Thanks for hacking my friend's
Spotify account.
You think I have nothing better to
do than hack your Spotify accounts?
We KNOW you have nothing
better to do.
Put the porn away. We need your help.
I'm not looking at porn!
Have you seen what that dickwad
Nathan Legg has just tweeted?
Oh, peak!
Don't say "peak", Alex
I didn't even know you and
Nathan broke up. Sorry, Casey.
Yeah, don't be, he's a fucktard.
So, what do you want me to do?
~ Hack that motherfucker.
~ Megan...
~ What? Come on, let's do him!
~ Just wait.
Er, I'm not hacking Nathan Legg.
~ Why not?
~ Guess what? He's not going
to kick the shit out of you.
~ How would he know it was you?
~ Yeah, how WOULD he know, genius?
As soon as anyone in school
gets hacked, they blame me!
You should have thought of that
before you hacked
everyone, Voldemort!
All right, fuck you, Megan!
I've hacked, like, two people.
All right, get back to
your porno, then, Useless!
Oh, shit. Jack's here.
Wait, you're going out?
Text me, OK?
OK, but won't Jack mind?
I love you, bitch.
I love you, ho.
Case?
Yeah?
What's wrong?
Nothing!
What do you want for dinner?
(For fuck's sake...)
I'm not hungry!
When will you be hungry?!
I DON'T KNOW, OK? CAN YOU
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE?!
Jesus!
We both call each other
bitch, you idiot!
(Nathan's profile?)
Erectile dysfunction makes me bitter.
So bitter,
I vent my limp-dicked anger on women.
Please pray for me
and my pathetic penis.
Nathan.
Kiss.
Shit!
Who the fuck...?
No, we don't!
'Hi, it's Megan. Leave me a message
and I MIGHT get back to you.'
Hey, bitch. Sorry, I
know you're with Jack.
Er, can you give me a call?
I think someone's online as Alex.
Yeah, just call me back.
Fuck off!
Of course.
Whatever!
A fan of what, you freak?
How the fuck...?
I can't stop shopping.
I don't know what it is,
I see it and I literally
am in love with it.
Sometimes I feel like there
are just the odd item
that you can't live without.
I'm a big blazer, kind
of kimono fan...
And you can open and close
them by turning the top.
'This is the perfect neon
I've been looking for.
'I never know what to pick!
'This is the perfect neon
I've been looking for.
'I never know what to pick!'
This is muchos, muchos affordable.
Muchos, muchos affordable
Barg, barg...
Hypocrite.
Without anyone judging us.
No fucking way!
'Hi, it's Megan. Leave me a message
and I MIGHT get back to you.'
Hey, bitch. I'm sorry
I missed your call.
You need to check your Instagram,
some fucker's into Alex's stuff
and mine and now yours. Just call me.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
(Fuck, fuck, fuck...)
Casey?
Case?
Yeah?
I'm taking Simon to football.
You all right?
I'm fine!
Are we alone now, Casey?
I know. It's awful...
I sound like a constipated
Stephen Hawking.
What the fuck?
And yes, I can totally hear you too.
Now, sit down, Casey.
What did you do with that photo?
Nothing yet.
Why did you take them, Casey?
Nathan practically begged me to!
And it was just that one.
Now, now, Casey.
Pants on fire, I counted
five, at least.
Nathan, if this is you...
I'll tell everyone what you told
me your mum did on holiday
in Weston-super-Mare!
I could've put that in
the tweet, but I didn't!
What did Nathan's mother do on
holiday in Weston-super-Mare?
Please, Casey. Do you really
think Nathan Legg could do this?
~ What are you doing?
~ Flexing my muscles.
No wait, show me again, show me
again, do it again, do it again.
No, no, its more like...
~ Stop checking me out.
~ She needs to just hurry up and come out.
Seriously, it's getting embarrassing.
It's like a dog on heat.
~ She'll wait till she's at
Uni, then she'll go full dyke.
~ God!
Yeah, then we'll be like, "Tamara,
no shit you're gay?" Who knew?
All those times you came over,
just as we happened to be getting
changed, and stared at us half
naked, for like, ever...
We had no idea!
~ Next time she stares at me
I'm going to say something.
~ Well, like what?
Like, Tamara, you're a total
fucking lesbian, deal with it.
What are you doing?
This is Tamara, right?
~ Wait.
~ You said she needs to come out.
Wait, what are you doing?
No, no, no! Please, don't. Stop!
No wait, show me again, show me
again, do it again, do it again.
No, no, no, it's more like...
~ What have you done?
~ Stop checking me out.
That was nothing.
Seriously, It's getting embarrassing.
Now imagine if I did that
with your special selfies?
You know what happens to girls
when those photos get out there?
If you try to shut down...
If you try to switch
off the router...
If you leave the room,
the pictures go online.
What do you want?
Patience, Casey.
First of all, I want you to sit.
Look! Twitter-storm alert.
Oh, God!
Don't be too sad, Casey.
You upset ME first!
You lied to me, Casey.
About the door.
It wasn't closed, was it?
You promised.
And you weren't going to eat a
chicken dinner either, were you?
No more lies, Casey.
Only truth.
Say, you promise.
Fine.
I promise.
Tell me what you're thinking, Casey.
Hi, its Megan, leave me a message
and I might get back to you.
Tell me what you're thinking, Casey.
I'm thinking about what
my friends will do
when they find out that
my webcam has been hacked
and that it wasn't me that posted
that video about Tamara.
I'm thinking about how
they'll track you down,
find you and fuck you up!
Knock, knock.
~ Knock, knock.
~ Who's there?
You'll never, ever know.
I know you're over 30.
It's the way you speak.
With the BFFs and the lols?
You sound like a parent.
Get that right, did I?
How old are you?
Just tell me one thing
about yourself.
What colour is your hair?
Or are you bald?
That's it, isn't it? I am sorry.
I've heard it can be a really
traumatic time for a middle
aged man losing all his hair.
What makes you think I'm a man?
It's not fair!
You know everything about me
and I know nothing about you.
Pick it up.
Go ahead. Get the phone.
Hey, Casey, does this sound familiar?
Hi, its Megan, leave me a message
and I might get back to you.
I'm thinking about what
my friends will do
when they find out my
webcam has been hacked.
I'm thinking about how
they'll track you down,
find you and fuck you up!
Casey, if I can take
over your computer,
do you really think I'd let you have
a smartphone to play with?
Why are you doing this?!
I told you, I help victims
of cyber bullying.
Really?
Oh, yes.
How the hell is this helping me?
Ouch, that hurts! Soooo funny.
What's so fucking funny?
You're not the victim, Casey.
You're the Cyber Bully!
How am I a cyberbully?
Wow, let me see.
So many examples.
'I can't stop shopping.'
'Sometimes I feel like there are
items that you can't live without.'
What? You think THAT
is cyber bullying?
'I don't know what it is, I see it
and I literally am in love with it.'
You're ridiculing people
on the internet.
What would you call it?
These are the sort of girls that
bully ugly and fat kids at school!
And that makes it OK
to bully them online?
It's not bullying!
It's...
It's sarcastic!
What about Mr Soft?
What Nathan? What about him?
Erectile dysfunction?
Can you imagine how much shit
he's going to get for that?
It wasn't him, was it?
You that sent that tweet.
You didn't even stop to question it.
What do you want from me?
Three things...
First, I want you to admit
what you really are.
What.. a bully?
Then I want you to realise
who you have hurt.
Nathan?
And some idiot shoppers?
What, her?
You took her down.
Jennifer Li? No, I didn't.
Oh, God, she is just beyond awful.
~ ♪ Keep burning, keep... ♪
~ How did you know her?
I told you, she was in the
year above me at school.
You really found her funny, huh?
Chronic Youth, that's
you, right, Casey?
"When singers are too
deluded for X Factor."
Steerpike underscore 84...
"Har har - too shit for X Factor."
Alise underscore Dr1...
"Wat a talentless whore."
Mike2Rite...
"Go drink a bleach cocktail."
Urpaltommy...
"I fucked her and she
gave me chlamydia."
Mike2Rite...
"Just the kind of plastic bitch
who should be destroyed."
I didn't write all this!
But you started it, Casey.
You threw in the grenade and ran.
I just shared what
was already out there.
That's not all you did.
Is it... Moe?
Oh, Come on! Moe Lester?
~ How did she not see..?
~ Read it.
Aloud.
"Jen. My name is Moe Lester.
"I am CEO of Columbia Records.
"Would you be interested
in signing with us?
"Columbia!"
"Hi, Moe. Yes, thanks
for your message.
"I would be super stoked
to sing along with you guys,
"it would be awesome."
Hi Moe.
Yes, I would be super stoked
to sing with you guys.
"Super Stoked," who says that?
'We are putting together
a new girl band.'
Like you never pretended
to be someone you're not.
I do it to help victims
of cyber bullying.
Everyone does it!
Nathan and Stuart Gorton pretended
to be a Russian lap dancer,
flirting with Kyle Harris for weeks!
Kyle was going to meet her in a hotel.
He thought they were in love.
The whole school knew about it!
And you think that's OK?
See, this is how I know you're old,
you don't get it!
Of course I don't think it's
OK, it's fucking nasty.
But it's normal, it happens
and we deal with it.
Like Jennifer did?
Why, what did she do?
You don't know?
No, she moved away
Hi, guys.
This is just a video to say,
I'm sorry the new website
isn't up and running yet.
I know most of you have been following
me for the right reasons,
and I thank you for
your love and support.
Unfortunately, there are some haters
who follow me wherever I go,
who have forced me to change domain
names and make a new website.
I would just like to say that
if you are one of the people
sending pictures of
dead animals to me
there's something wrong with
you and you need help.
For those of you who are looking
forward to my next recording,
I can reveal that I'm working
on some new songs of my own,
and they will be about Autumn because
that's my favourite season.
Oh, apart from Spring.
It's important the haters realise
that expressing creativity
is a fundamental human right...
Why is she doing this to herself?
.. and you shoot me down,
but I won't fall. No hate.
Peace out.
Rule number one, don't
feed the trolls!
And let me guess, they
trolled this video too?
Hello?
Oh, shit!
(Jennifer...)
Jennifer?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry I hurt you.
I should have just kept
my stupid mouth shut.
I had no right to judge you.
The truth is...
.. I've always been kind
of jealous of you.
At school you looked so...
.. comfortable...
with yourself.
And then online you
put yourself out there
for everyone to see.
And that's so cool.
I could never do something like that.
I use fake names.
Which makes me a bit of a coward,
I guess...
Touching, Casey.
Almost truthful, even.
But I'm not Jennifer.
What is that?
Girls at Jennifer's new school
dressed up as her for Halloween.
The pictures were sent
to her family members.
These arseholes that did this...
That's fucked up!
But why are you picking on me?
Because you were the first
to troll Jennifer's video.
It started with you.
It would have happened anyway.
Someone else would have done it.
You can't know that.
Yes, I can!
Because if there's
one thing we all know
it's that everything
gets slated online.
Jennifer Li knew that when
she posted her videos.
Didn't you, Jennifer?
I'm not Jennifer.
Yes, you are.
You're Jennifer Li.
Blaming me for all this just
because I was the first person
who posted that video is
just the kind of corny,
sentimental bullshit Jennifer
Li would come up with.
It fits perfectly with that,
"look at me" victim identity.
You know why you get
bullied, Jennifer?
It's because you ask for it.
Wow!
Well done, Casey.
Now you're talking
like your true self.
A bully.
Well, then, I guess we're all
bullies, aren't we, Jennifer?
I am not Jennifer Li.
What is that?
She didn't.
Jennifer thought that
if she posted this
the troll's would leave her alone.
She was wrong.
Steerpike underscore 84...
"Lame effort."
99Badman99...
"Attention whoring bitch."
I can read it for myself.
Blaze underscore 7
underscore Blaze...
"Try the other side of the
arm, you'll bleed more."
You don't need to read it out loud.
Would you like to see her last video?
No.
Oh, I've seen these.
They tell their sad story...
Why do they take so long over it?
My parents are divorced,
I didn't subject the world
to my singing voice.
I didn't know that.
I didn't know any of this.
I get it.
It's fucking terrible.
~ I don't need to watch any more.
~ Yes, you do, Casey.
This fucking music...
Look at the screen, Casey.
The abuse went on and on.
It only stopped two weeks ago.
What happened two weeks ago?
Shut the fuck up.
Go on.
I would've heard about it.
Jennifer did not make
the front pages.
Cybersuicides aren't
what they used to be.
You...
You're lying.
I'm surprised you didn't
troll her memorial page.
'Sup, Casey?
Regrets?
B-Bu...
But she-she was unstable -
with her mum and who knows what
else was going on at home?
You were Jennifer Li's first troll.
You have to face up to that.
You can't seriously blame m...
I wonder what your friends will say
when they realise you started this.
Nobody knows Chronic
Youth is you, right?
Not even Megan.
Will she still be your BFF?
I think I know who you are.
I can't...
I can't even imagine what it must
be like to lose someone you love...
.. especially like this.
I've never lost anyone.
My mum...
She doesn't live with us.
Of course, you know that.
You know everything.
She's not well.
I know what it's like...
.. to have a mum...
who's different...
.. and isn't there for you.
I know what it's like to
go to school every day
and pretend there's not
a problem when there is.
And... anxiety? Well...
I...
I am so sorry.
SO sorry for what happened
to your daughter.
And it makes me feel sick
to think that I was one of
those people who hurt her.
Wrong. I am not Jennifer's father
Well, stepmum, or stepsister?
I know that I'd want
to get back at someone
if they ever tried to
hurt my little brother.
I am not Jennifer's sister, brother,
lover, or anyone who knew her.
WELL, WHO ARE YOU, THEN?!
Why are you doing this, you
pathetic fucking loser?!
< I'm back, Case.
< Case?
Careful, Casey.
No daddy, Casey.
You in there?
I'm getting changed.
You going to bed?
What? No.
So what you getting changed for?
Fuck you.
What?!
Nothing! I just...
Can I help you?!
I'm making you something
to eat, come downstairs.
I'll eat later.
Well...
.. just come down anyway.
Barcelona are playing.
What's wrong, Casey?
Can I come in?
No!
I'm fine. Please!
Did you have an argument
with Megan or something?
~ Why would you even say that?
~ I don't know!
How can I know what's going
on if you don't speak to me?
Dad! Just go!
Casey...
No! Dad, please!
What don't you understand
about privacy?!
Can't I just have a minute
to get changed?!
What is wrong with you?!
What is it you want from me?
You want me to admit I'm a bully?
I'm a bully.
You're recording this?
Of course you are.
Make sure you get this.
I...
take responsibility...
for Jennifer Li's suicide.
It was me.
You mean it?
I mean it.
Truth, Casey.
Promise.
Weird.
What's weird?
After all the build-up...
it feels kind of underwhelming.
I think it's because it's insincere.
I believe you'll wait
until I've gone away,
then tell everyone that's some crazy
hacker forced you to confess.
Well, what do you want me to say?
Nothing.
We need action, not words.
What action?
It's time to take your medicine.
I've already had my medication
for today, thank you.
There's going to be a second helping.
'Ask yourself a question, Casey.
'What will life be like
after I've posted this?'
But you said you wouldn't!
'Will it be worth living?'
I've done everything that you asked!
'I asked for three things.
'You've accepted you're a bully.
'You admitted you killed Jennifer Li.
'Now you have to make amends.
'The pills or the pictures.
'Either way, your life is over.'
Fuck you.
'One pill, Casey.'
What?
'All you need to do to stop me from
tweeting this picture is swallow
'one of your little white pills.'
One?
'One pill, one picture.'
'I know what you're thinking, Casey.
'Did you shoot six topless
selfies, or only five?
'To tell you the truth,
in all this excitement,
'I've kind of lost track myself.
'In any case, five or six
pills won't kill you.
'We both know that.
'For this to work,
'we're going to need
some more photographs.'
Leave Megan out of this.
'Take one pill, or it gets tweeted...
'from your account.'
'Time's up.'
No!
'Next.
'Your BFF again.'
'One more pill won't hurt you, Casey.
'But it might spare Megan some hate.
'Time's up.'
'Wow. Bad friend.'
'How about this one?
'It's different when it's you, huh?'
'So, you're happy to pop pills to
save yourself from a slut-shaming.
'But you don't mind ruining
your BFF's life.
'Next.
'One pill.
'Wow. Loyalty!'
Ha-ha. You're funny(!)
'Har. Har. You too.'
Go on. Laugh some more.
I'll give you this one for free,
if you laugh at me again.
'O-M-F-A-O.'
No. Laugh at me properly,
you know, har har.
'Har. Har. Har.'
Slainte.
I wasn't the first, was I?
I wasn't the first person
to comment on Jennifer Li.
'Of course you were, Casey.'
Show me.
Show me, and I'll take five pills.
'Chronic Youth.
'You were the first.'
Yes.
But you were the second.
Steerpike underscore 84.
I can tell it's you
from the way you type.
H-A-R. No-one spells it like that.
'Five pills, Casey.'
You must write like that because it
sounds better in the Hawking voice.
You must have got used
to typing like that.
'You're embarrassing yourself.'
Does that mean I can track
you down now, Steerpike?
'Take the pills, or it all goes up.'
84?
What's that, the year you were born?
~ 'Take the pills.'
~ I'll do you a deal.
You leave me alone,
right now,
and I'll forget about Steerpike 84.
'OMFG! This is the funniest
video I have ever made!'
Really?
How many of these have you made?
How many kids have you bullied
to death? What about Jennifer?
You trolled her more than anyone.
You take responsibility,
you sick twisted fuck!
You want me to overdose?
Here's my suicide note.
They'll find it next to me.
And then they'll come and find you.
'Maybe.
'But you'll be dead.
'I still win.
'Now swallow the fucking pills, or
your pics will be online for ever.'
Megan's on the phone.
Case?
I'm not talking to her.
Look, it's none of my business, Case,
but it sounded like
she'd been crying.
I don't care. Tell
her to stop calling.
'Great job, Casey. Outstanding.
'There's only one way
to end the pain now.'
Case?
'He is really starting to annoy me.'
I told her you didn't want to talk,
and she said to give you a message.
She told me to tell you,
"Whatever is going on,
she knows this isn't you."
All right?
Here endeth the message.
'He interrupts again, Casey, I'm
going to have to take action.
'Casey?'
'No, Casey!
'You stupid, ugly bitch.
'Now you have to start over.
'Where are you going, Casey?
'Casey?'
'Stay where I can see you.'
Need to get rid of this
before it sets in.
There's nothing worse than
a puke smell, don't you think?
'Three seconds, and it all goes up.'
One time, Megan puked all
over her mum's living room.
We were scrubbing that carpet
for hours, and it still stank.
Raspberry vodka puke.
'Three...'
I told her mum it was me, so
she wouldn't get grounded.
'Two...'
She'd do the same for me.
'I'm poting your shit, Casey.'
Poting?
'Posting, bitch.'
You having finger trouble?
Slow down.
Relax.
Go for it.
Post what you like.
'Your life is over.'
Is it?
What are you going to do?
Are you going to come here?
And hack my family?
Hack my best friend?
Which reminds me...
.. I need to call her back.
'Stay with me.
'I'll tell you who I really am.'
Promise?
'Promise.'
I thought you said I'd never know.
I thought you had some super
geek firewall IP rerouter,
and I'd never find out
who you really are.
But you know what?
It doesn't matter.
What are you when I
stop talking to you?
Nothing.
'Case...'
Dad!