Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
Okay, latte.
There you go.
Oh, your nails are so cute.
I love it.
- You want another?
- Yeah, that'd be great.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
You need to calm down.
Do not tell me how to feel.
Did the fucking doctors...
No.
They don't need to.
Jesus Christ.
What, are you going to break
every fucking dish in the house?
Do you want me to pick them up
and pack them up
for you when you go?
You know what?
You need help.
- I have had help.
- I am done with this shit.
- Help doesn't help.
- Okay?
This medicine
doesn't make me me.
I'm not me anymore
when I take the medicine.
I'm perfectly fine.
You are not a doctor.
It will be okay, Wilbur.
Oh, you're going
to take my baby?
You want to go play?
Ill show you guys this way.
- Alright?
- We should go the other way.
I'm going to pull up
my laser sniper.
Okay.
Aah!
We're being shot at!
Luke?
Luke, don't ever run away
like that ever again, okay?
- Come on.
- Wait.
Can Daniel come with us?
Daniel?
Who's Daniel?
Mom, he's my friend.
Okay.
Sure.
Daniel, would you come
to our house for dinner?
Yes, thanks.
You're the last hope to guard
the king's fortress.
- Aah!
But right now, I'm going
to skydive out of a helicopter,
and you will be
flying down videoing it.
Yep.
You have to fold that part in,
and then you have
to fold it in half.
Ah.
A-ha.
What's that?
It's an origami tea set.
Wow.
Did you make that?
I wanted you to have
a nice tea party
because you've been sad.
Oh.
Thank you.
Three, two, one.
Say, "cheeseburger."
Click.
We're going to be just fine,
just you and me.
I have a really cool idea.
You have to press it down
while you turn it.
What are these?
They'll give your mom
super powers.
Luke?
Hey, baby.
What did you do?
What did you do to me?
It wasn't me.
It was Daniel.
Daniel?
Baby, no more Daniel, honey.
No more Daniel.
Okay?
Here, baby.
Take this key, and you can
lock up your,
um, imaginary friend
in Grandma's dollhouse.
I don't want to.
You... You have to.
You did something bad.
Now, get in.
Get in.
Get in!
Get in! Get in!
Get in! Get in! Get in!
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
I'll come by on the weekend.
When are you coming?
Yeah, like, uh,
today or tomorrow.
- I don't know.
- I mean, you can...
you can do that
if you want to do that,
but just don't do that
because you think I need you
to do that
because I'm fine.
- I just...
- Mom...
No.
You don't have to do that.
Well, of course
I want to see you.
Don't just come home because
you don't like the school.
Maybe you just need to make
some friends or something.
Yo. Yo.
Check her out.
I'm not trying to be mean.
Do you think... I think...
Jesus, goddess
of the digital age.
I want to see you because I do.
I want to see you.
Of course,
I want to see you, but...
Can't decide if I want
to bang her or worship her.
And so a successful
photograph is not only
about technical equipment...
the lens, the focus,
the lighting.
I expect you really have
something
The most important thing is
the relationship between you,
the photographer,
and your subject.
Mom?
Hi.
Beautiful boy.
Mm.
I brought sandwiches.
It's ham and cheese.
Yeah.
It's your favorite.
Thank you.
What are you working on, Mom?
Uh, it is, uh, sometimes,
it's the words.
Sometimes... I feel like
they speak to me.
There's messages in them,
in the books
and message in the...
Mom, what happened
to the mirror?
Uh...
I didn't like what I saw.
It's common
for people to see things
that aren't real.
Stress, alone, can do that.
I wouldn't worry.
Well, if I faint like
a Victorian duchess every time
I get stressed out by college,
it's going to be
a long 4 years, right?
That's why you're here.
Uh, my, uh, my mom, she
doesn't really trust doctors.
Uh, she would not
want me to be here.
She's not well.
Um, I think it's been worse
since I left home.
I worry about her a lot.
Fuck, I worry that
I could become like her.
I mean, this is supposed to be
the age where
you can start to...
It can be.
What else do you worry about?
Um, sex and death, I guess.
The only topics
that should interest an adult.
Yeah?
Says who?
Lou Reed, but he also said,
"Life is like teaching Sanskrit
to a pony."
It's good.
Have you ever seen things
like this before?
Fuck.
Um, never, really.
No hallucinations?
No.
Well...
I had an imaginary friend
when I was a kid.
Um, his name was Daniel,
and he was my best friend.
He was my only friend, really.
It's really pathetic.
We all have needs.
Well, I must have had
some pretty sick needs, man.
Did something happen
with this friend?
- No, no.
- Something painful?
No.
No, no, just, you know,
kid stuff.
Well, then, it's kind
of a strange notion,
but maybe you shouldn't be
afraid of your imagination.
Maybe you should try to connect
with that part
of yourself again.
Ah, yo, what the fuck?
Uh, uh, I didn't see you.
Are you okay?
I'm practically bleeding
to death?
Really?
What?
Yes, I'm fine.
- Ugh.
- Phew.
Ugh.
Yeah. I'm okay too.
Great.
Have a lovely day.
Okay, yeah.
Alright.
Not really,
but you know how it is.
You never miss the water
until the well runs dry.
Oh, big bad lummox like
you, hiring an aeroplane to ride.
You got to love yourself.
What?
I don't want to brag,
but I still got the general
and in the same place.
Look, Hilde, I only acted
like any husband
that didn't want to see
his home broken up.
- What home?
Hey, Wilbur.
How's it going, buddy?
Can't sleep?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Mom?
Somebody is going to be
looking for Lawrence.
Mom?
Hu-u-u-h?
Mom, what's going on?
- I'm fine.
- Mom, it's not fine.
What's happening?
- Let me in.
- Luke, no.
Stay away from the door, okay?
I'm coming in.
Jesus.
What did you do?
I can't...
I can't look at this face.
I can't look...
I... It keeps trying to...
Don't touch me!
Don't touch me.
Don't even look at me like that.
Like you're any different.
It'll be okay, Luke.
- I can't let you live like this.
- You what?
I can't let you stay here.
- You can't let me stay here?
- Okay, Mom.
- You can't let me?
- I can't let you.
That's okay because
I'm leaving anyway.
No, no. No, no. No, no, no.
Mom, stop it.
- Let go.
- Stop it.
- Mom, stop!
Hold the blade to your throat.
Let go. Let go.
Put the blade
to your own throat.
Let go, Luke.
Let go.
No. No, don't.
- Let go or kill me.
- No!
Let go, or you're
going to kill me.
- No! What are you doing? Stop.
- Let go.
- Stop.
- Let go!
Oh, my beautiful boy.
Okay. We can... We can
get you help, Mom.
It's okay
She's going to get through this.
So are you.
I didn't know that
you'd be there after so long.
You needed my help.
Hey.
Oh.
Hi.
My blade swings sharp, sire.
My blade is a broom, Daniel.
Symbolic logic strategies.
Why would you study this shit?
Because it's going to help
when I apply to law school.
Law school?
Wasn't your father a lawyer?
Last time I saw you,
you were this kid bursting
with imagination.
What happened?
You know what fucking happened,
Daniel.
Sorry it took me so long.
Oh, I did not even notice.
Who is this?
Are you always
such a space cadet?
Don't let a gorgeous girl
leave your apartment.
Okay.
Um, let me get you a reward.
Um...
Satisfaction of a job well-done.
I... Just give me a second.
I have some, um, uh, here.
Here.
It's cool, really.
Insist.
I insist.
You came all the way from...
I'll just buy some new paint
and think of you.
You're a painter?
You're an artist too, Luke.
But I do photography sometimes.
Yeah.
Uh, um, my...
my mom had an accident.
Pfft, with a chain saw?
That was mean.
- She going to be all right?
- I don't know.
I mean, she's in the hospital.
No, that's good.
Be vulnerable.
She'll be okay.
I... I've just been cleaning up
and trying to take my mind
off of it, you know?
Mm.
I'm going to this
opening tonight.
I have a space in Green Point,
bunch of different artists
and photographers.
Thanks.
So you're a photographer
now, huh?
Um, okay.
Uh, oh, yeah.
I'm coming, right?
I don't think
this is a good idea.
I usually get really overwhelmed
at these things.
That's because I haven't
been around, Luke.
Stop.
You're really acting crazy.
You think I want to smash
this bottle
across your smug-ass face.
We are not going to do this.
I knew it. I knew it. Come on.
Well, maybe you should've
came prepared then.
Think you can diffuse this one?
What? No.
Bitch!
- Trust me.
- Do you hear yourself?
You're, like, acting,
like, crazy.
- You got this.
- Like...
You going to call me crazy
right now
with a bottle in my hand?
You're going to call me crazy?
- What?
- Oh, my god.
Mm.
Sorry.
I just realized this place
is full
of fucking bullshit-ass posers.
Whatever, Cassie.
So you're having a rough night?
Yeah.
Sorry.
Fuck.
This place literally sucks.
You coming?
Yeah.
All the real artists
are either dead or broke,
and you can't even make art
and live in the city anymore.
I feel like I'm looking
for a phantom approval
from trust-funders and assholes.
You ever feel like you have
no idea who you really are?
Look.
I mean, sometimes,
I can't even remember
why I started doing this shit
in the first place.
I feel like, I don't know,
like I was born too late.
You did this one too?
It's an experiment,
one that clearly didn't work.
- It's the best thing here.
- What do you mean? Yeah.
It's... it's...
it's, uh, it's really good.
I like it a lot, actually.
Well, if you think
it's interesting,
who do you think that guy is?
- Her father.
- Uh, I don't know.
My dad.
Well, uh, that's good.
It's... it's melancholic,
you know, in a really good way.
Well, that's sweet of you
to say.
Hey.
I have an idea.
Since that one is so awesome,
I should probably trash
the rest of this then, huh?
No.
Don't destroy... Oh, fuck.
Get your camera out.
You know what?
I think it's starting
to look like an improvement.
You want to try?
I've never made anything.
I'm not an artist.
She's, like, the coolest person
I've ever met.
Luke, you're living
in a mental prison.
You need to break out and live.
I like you.
William Blake said his poetry
was a dictation
from an archangel,
but really, he was
just gifted, just like you.
Is that why you're here, to give
me bleak little pep talks?
Is that it?
I'm here because you're here.
I'm part of you.
Okay.
So I'm fucking insane.
- That's fun.
- No.
Not insane, awake!
Hey, Richard.
Richard!
He could use a good scare.
I'd say.
What the fuck?
Oh, Jesus.
Fuck, that is not cool, dude!
What is your fucking problem?
That is not fucking cool, dude!
Whoa, oh!
What the fuck, dude?
This is...
I bet you could get
a phone number
from any girl
at this party.
Okay, man.
She's smart, romantic.
Think silver screen,
"Pandora's Box."
Hi.
This might sound weird,
but you have a real
Louise Brooks vibe.
What?
Louise Brooks,
she's a silent film star.
She's in "Pandora's Box."
Yeah, the German classic
about a woman
whose raw sexuality
brings ruin to herself
and everyone who loves her?
- Yeah, that one.
- That one.
- That's the one.
- Yeah.
So you're studying film?
I watch films.
I study psychology.
Okay, so then tell me
what I'm thinking.
That I look like Louise Brooks.
You've got it.
You nailed it.
You must be at the top
of your class.
Do you mind if I just...
Oh.
This is better.
Here.
That's my number.
Text me that picture.
Okay.
- I'm Luke.
- Sophie.
Chug, chug, chug, chug, chug,
chug, chug,
chug,
chug, chug, chug, chug.
That's not good.
I don't like doing it
that much at a time.
No. Fuck it. Let's go for it.
Here we go.
Two shots for you,
and then two shots for me.
Oh.
You know I can't touch those.
Four shots for you.
For Sophie!
College!
Hey, Sophie.
I fucked up.
Oh, I fucked up.
No.
No, no, no, no, no.
Hey.
You did great.
Luke?
Drop it or kill me, Mommy.
Hey.
How does the water feel?
I don't know.
You're making
some pretty good stuff.
Yeah.
I'm, uh, just trying to connect
with people,
you know, empathy, I guess.
Uh...
Whatever you say.
What are we doing?
Trespassing.
These motherfuckers really need
to change their locks.
I worked here for, like,
3 weeks a year ago.
Ooh!
"Where the Wild Things Are,"
I've always wanted
to be a wild thing.
You like that book?
"The night Max wore
his wolf suit
and made mischief
of one kind or another"...
"The night Max wore
his wolf suit
and made mischief
of one kind or another"...
..."his mother called him
a wild thing."
I've always wanted to do this
because they're so adamant
about you not hopping seats.
Whoa!
Now spin.
I'm hopping them all.
"The Ways of Seeing,"
this one totally blew me away
when I first decided
to become an artist.
Ah, "Ways of Seeing," me, too.
That's actually one
of my favorite books.
- I believe it's...
- "To be naked is to be oneself."
"To be naked is to be oneself."
"To be nude is
to be seen naked by others
and yet not recognized
for oneself."
Okay, super brain.
Ah!
Oh, yeah, the Bible?
That's easy.
- Come on.
- My favorite.
I know it like
the back of my hand.
- Exodus 20.
"And God spoke all these words."
"I am the Lord your God
who brought you out of Egypt
out of the land of slavery."
"There once was a man
from Nantucket
whose cock was so long,
he could suck it."
"And you shall not
bow down to them
or worship them,
for I am your God."
"He said with a grin,
as he wiped off his chin..."
"And you shall have
no other God before me"!
Amen.
- Great.
- Yeah.
That's not
a very well-known verse.
Hmm.
Let's go get some fresh air.
You are so funny.
- Why?
- I don't know.
It seems like you always have
some type of private joke
or something going on
in your head, all by yourself.
Oh, hey.
I, um...
I have something
I've been working on.
I'd love to show you.
I'm taking a lot of photos.
I like that one.
Damn.
These are hot.
You know you're my inspiration
for this entire project, right?
Really?
I figure you deserve
to be immortalized.
We... We deserve
Oh, yeah? You think that
I deserve to be immortalized?
Shirt off, please.
What's that thing, uh,
behind me?
What's that supposed to be?
It's, like, your shadow,
your hidden self.
It's, like, I saw something
full of danger, mystery.
Okay. Um, and you can see it,
like, visually, or...
Maybe I'm the crazy one.
Well, crazy isn't always
a bad thing.
This okay?
Yeah.
Okay.
Help me!
Right on time.
What?
Did you order a pizza?
No.
I brought a friend.
- Hi.
- Hello.
Welcome, ladies.
You know, if we threw
your roommate off a bridge,
we could have these girls
to ourselves.
Mikayla, meet the fabulously
talented Luke Nightingale.
Mm, he's a total perv.
Can we do something fun?
I swear to god,
if I drink one more...
- We've been texting.
- ...flat beer, I... I will die.
Hmm. Oh.
These are your friends now.
- Right, guys?
- These are what friends do.
Fucking groovy, very erotic.
- Hmm.
- Hurry, bitch.
- Yeah.
- Apocalypse sex, right, guys?
We've got to get it in
while we can.
We're all going to be wiped out
by a nuclear war,
a super flu
or a fucking tsunami.
I'm so fucking tired
of this little Muppet.
We're ever going to fuck
as much as the boomers,
we got to pack it in now.
Honestly, I'd rather die
of the super flu than fuck you.
Well, Mikayla doesn't.
You know, he kind of reminds me
of these guys.
I thought it was funny.
You guys, I got a great idea.
Steam tunnels, miles and miles
underneath campus.
Yeah!
Hey. Check this out.
This place got five stars
on Yelp.
Yeah, well, do you think we're
going to be able to get a table?
The, uh,
Jacuzzi is down this way.
Ugh.
Do you ever feel like
you're hiding your true self?
What?
- What do you mean?
- I don't know.
Like, you have to make
a whole new identity
just to conceal
who you really are.
Yeah, I guess.
I... I mean, I...
I feel like I have this...
Just kiss her, Luke.
...this voice in my head
that tells me what to do,
but I don't always do it,
you know?
- I... I don't always...
- I feel like there is something
intense inside you,
like an animal.
Oh, I like her.
What do you mean?
Why would you say that...
animal?
What are you doing?
Is this is about Cassie?
You're not married, man.
Just kiss her.
Hey.
You there?
Yeah.
Sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- You okay?
Um, Yeah.
I'm just... I'm...
I'm a lightweight.
Just...
Can you just give me a second?
Hey.
If you're not going to do this,
let me take over.
It's not cheating if it's me.
Oh, wow. Okay.
We're doing this.
Smile for the camera.
Smile yourself.
Come here.
You're in my body.
Stop it.
Stop it!
No. Stop it!
I want my body back!
Ow!
Please, I want it back.
Give me my body back.
You look good in that picture.
I want my body back.
Please, I want my body back.
I want my body back!
Aah!
Hey.
We, uh... We done here?
- Ugh, this fucking guy.
- It's hot as fuck.
Whoa. Hey.
Fuck you, man.
You dumb fuck.
Luke!
Stop it, Luke!
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Right.
Okay.
They're going to kick me out of
fucking school because of you.
Then I've set you free,
just like I promised.
Okay, I'm going to...
I'm going to count to three.
I'm going to close my eyes.
I'm going to count to three,
and when I finish,
you're going to be gone.
Alright?
Okay.
One...
...two...
...three.
I imagined you.
I can make you go away.
Well, then you might as well
cut your own head off.
Okay.
Get in.
Get in!
You can't put me
back in the box.
- Get in!
- You're too crazy!
Can't keep a lid
on your delusions.
Fucking asshole.
This place hasn't changed much.
They even put me
in the same room.
Do you think you can
come home soon?
I don't know.
This time it isn't up to me.
When did this all start for you?
Uh, when did I start
to lose my fucking mind?
You know what I mean.
20.
I tried to burn down
the college radio station
because I thought
the deejays were taunting me.
They sent me home for a semester
as though that was
a better place for me.
What'd that feel like?
Uh, like being jacked
into an electrical socket.
It was awful and wonderful
at the same time, and...
and then suddenly
it was only awful.
That's because you weren't
doing it right.
You don't have to hide anything,
you know?
No.
You can... You can talk to me.
Did you know this would
happen to me, too?
- No. No.
- Why wouldn't you tell me?
No.
I didn't... I didn't know.
I... I... I... I... I didn't...
I always hoped that whatever
was happening back then,
whatever happened that you were
doing because you were angry,
it was... it was a reaction
to your father leaving.
- What is happening?
- I'm fine.
- What is happening right now?
- Luke.
- Honey, what is it?
- Time to say goodbye to Mommy.
- I can see something's wrong.
- I don't know what's wrong.
- Luke!
- No. I want to help you.
I need to help you.
He needs help.
- My son, he needs help.
- No. I'm fine. I'm fine.
Okay. He needs help.
He needs help.
What? What?
No, Luke!
No!
You need help!
I wish we killed you
when we had the chance!
I can feel it!
There's something wrong!
You're not safe!
Something's wrong!
Let me go!
Luke! Luke!
I can't keep this.
I can't keep going like this.
I don't...
If this keeps going this way,
I don't know what I might do.
Hey, Sophie.
I'm scared.
I'm scared of what I could do.
- Don't come any closer.
- Sophie, I...
You're not even supposed to be
on this fucking campus!
All this fuss about what?
I only came here to apologize.
You want to see what
I really want to do her?
I don't want to hear it.
You're out of
your fucking mind.
Fuck!
No, wait.
No. Look. Sophie.
- Look. It wasn't me.
- I told you not to touch me!
I'm warning everyone about you,
you fucking monster!
Aah!
Help me, doc.
I'm... I'm just so confused!
Shut the fuck up!
This doesn't sound like you.
No, because
it's fucking not me!
Right? It's... it's...
Or maybe it is me.
You're not a child, Luke.
You have to take responsibility
for what you've done.
Daniel is simply
an aspect of your mind.
It's not fucking me.
I... when I fall asleep,
I think he's...
he's... he's taking
over my body, you know?
He's making me do things
that I...
I... I don't want to do.
I need this to stop.
Talk to me.
Luke, you hurt someone.
What have you done?
I tried to kill my mother...
when I was a kid.
Because of Daniel?
God, I'm just like her.
No.
No, Luke, you're not.
You're something
so much more interesting.
Can you help me?
I just want him to be gone.
What the fuck?
Medication may help you...
You do this?
...which is a fact
of brain chemistry,
not a judgement
of character.
Leave me alone!
What?
I just want him to be gone.
Don't do it, Luke.
It's going to
cripple your brain.
You can say goodbye to all
that photography and the women.
Don't do it.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Aah!
Aah! Argh!
Gragh!
What the fuck?
Oh, you should've seen
the look on your face.
Get in! Get in!
Get in!
It was quite a spectacle,
wasn't it?
All that blood.
Who is it?
Are you Percy Thigpen,
John's father?
How did you get this address?
I need your help, please.
It's the middle
of the God damn night.
Please, please.
How the hell am I supposed
to help you?
Look, I'm sorry to bother you.
I... I was there when your son,
you know...
You saw it?
Yeah.
Uh, after the police had come,
but I saw it.
Hard to go on
after a thing like that.
Yeah, I... I just...
I think that John
and I might be similar.
- Similar? How?
- Okay.
How did you find out that there
was something wrong with him?
Like, when did you...
when did you learn?
We tried to help him,
uh, medicate him.
He'd, uh, he'd get better for
a while, but it wouldn't last.
Drawing seemed to calm him.
It's the one thing
that made him happy.
Drawing?
Did... do you have
any of his drawings?
Can I... Can I look
at his drawings?
There's one on the fridge.
Did John ever have a friend,
like, uh, a friend
that only he could see?
Well, you mean, uh,
an imaginary friend?
When he was a kid, I guess.
Okay. Well, how about
when he was older?
Did he ever hear voices
or anything?
Why don't you sit down?
Let me get you a glass of water.
Look, I need you
to tell me everything, okay?
I need to stop this
from happening to me.
Please, just sit down, okay?
I can show you
more of his drawings.
- You want me to do that?
- Yeah, I do.
Here they are.
Can you tell me your name?
Luke.
Luke, what are you afraid
you might do?
You know, he's got
the cops on the phone.
Show me your hands.
Your other hand, show me.
It's okay.
We can get you
whatever help you need.
All right?
Whatever you need.
Wait, wait a minute.
Hold on.
- Calm down, son!
- This is... this is Daniel.
♪ La, la, la
La, la, la ♪
This is Daniel, and he was
with John until he was dead.
- We can help you.
- And now he's with me, okay?
- Okay?
- We can help you.
- Wait.
- ♪ La, la, la, la, la, la ♪
Hey.
I missed you.
Are you okay?
I have... I have to sit down.
- That's who you saw.
- What?
That's who you saw
when you painted me, right?
What are you talking about?
That's just a drawing.
No.
This is a drawing of...
12 years ago, the kid
who drew this, this kid,
John Thigpen, he killed
a bunch of people, Cassie.
The same fucking thing
that happened to him
is happening to me.
- Wait.
- And I... I'm scared that
I could do the same thing.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
No.
You... Okay.
You think you're going to kill
someone because of a drawing?
Uh, okay.
When you painted me,
you saw a shadow, right?
What did he look like?
There's no he.
The shadow was a metaphor for
what I saw hiding inside of you.
No.
His name is... is Daniel.
- Love me!
- What? Please stop.
Whatever you're doing,
this freak-out, please stop.
Just talk to me.
Oh, the things that I'm going to
do to her when you let go.
- Luke.
- You saw him, Cassie!
You saw him.
Look.
You fucking saw him!
Look there, there, there.
It's right here.
That's him.
Luke, stop, stop, stop,
stop, stop, no.
You saw him.
He's right fucking here.
I saw your darkness,
and that's okay.
It's something
we all have inside...
Not again.
Not like this, Cassie.
- Get out.
- He's right there.
- Get out!
- You painted him when you saw him.
Go, go!
No. No.
- He's going to kill you.
- Get out!
He's going to fucking
kill you, Cassie.
I don't know what
he's going to do.
I can't go to sleep like this.
He'll take over.
I need your help, please.
Please.
Why don't I come
down to your mother's apartment?
You're going to regret this,
Luke.
Those pills don't work.
To be honest, I try not
to depend entirely on
Western medicine.
There are other approaches.
The mind reflects
its environment.
This was your world
when it all started.
I want to know
what Daniel has to say.
What, so you think he's real?
He's a real part of your mind,
but he doesn't have to be.
I'm going to induce a state
of hypnosis in both of us.
The Tibetan singing bowl is said
to bring clarity to the mind.
The dagger is strong enough
to pierce illusions,
to destroy our demons
or as we call them
these days, our trauma.
Do you think
this is going to work?
We need to engage with
the delusion on its own terms.
Is Daniel here now?
Of course.
He's always here.
What's he saying?
He says, "Fuck off."
He says...
He's saying
some really nasty stuff.
Lie down.
Close your eyes
and go inside the sound.
Fear and loneliness are some
of the most powerful emotions
humans can experience.
These feelings can grow
inside us
until they rule
our every thought.
The mind will do anything
to avoid confronting
just how alone it is
in the universe.
Luke, can you hear me?
In the distance.
Follow the sound of my voice.
Daniel, can you hear me?
Daniel, talk to me.
Daniel?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Daniel, talk to me.
About what?
It's just like you said.
He's weak.
He's lonely.
And he's nothing without me.
What are you?
Oh, just a traveler...
searching for a home.
This is going to be
really painful for you.
Oh, my God.
Fuck!
Oh, my god!
Stay back. Stay away.
You know, the more you tell
somebody not to do something...
the more they just go ahead
and do it.
It's okay.
I feel a lot better now.
I am the abyss.
Get in. Get in.
Get in.
Behold.
Your castle, sire.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
No!
Wait!
Wait! Wait!
I need to be sure
you're completely calmed down
before I even think
about letting you in.
I know.
I wasn't in control before,
but I'm...
I'm doing a lot better now.
- Great.
- You know how it is.
When you get so angry,
you just can't control it.
You know, I really do like this.
People usually don't see me,
not like that.
- Luke.
- Ugh.
I know you feel alone
and like you can't get rid
of your shadows, but...
I don't think we should get
rid of the shadows.
I think that we should let
that shadows rule us.
Hey.
We should go away together,
don't you think?
Yes.
Uh, what did you have in mind?
Uh, I don't know.
We could rob a bank,
fly around the world,
start a revolution somewhere.
Remember when you painted me?
You wanted to touch
that darkness, didn't you?
You don't get it.
I saw the true Luke.
I wanted that shadow
to go the fuck away.
Fine.
I've been...
I've been kind to you.
I've shown you sensitivity.
Fuck this whole charade.
I am so sick of this face.
Oh, my God.
Luke.
Cassie.
I've worn a lot of
different faces.
Cassie?
No!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
You John Thigpen?
You're John Thigpen, aren't you?
Uh-huh.
How do I get out of here?
Get back here!
Where's Luke?
I know you're in there.
What's out there?
The abyss.
And what did they do to us?
Luke!
I know you're in there.
You're a fucking parasite!
For centuries,
I've helped people.
I've solved their problems.
I've given them visions, and no
one has deserved any of it.
You're the parasite, Luke.
If I go,
you go.
You're not strong enough.
Luke.
Luke!
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org