No, no, not tomorrow.
The day after tomorrow. Right.
You, me, Gary, Brad.
We'll be teeing off at...
Well, I like Gary.
Dr. Dandewar,
I'm kind of in
a bit of a hurry.
We'll be teeing off at 7:30,
and if you're not there
because of Gary,
well, come on,
you know. I gotta go.
Am I missing something?
Why did Dr. Cho
order a head X-ray
when the man
was bitten on the hand?
The patient
was in a bar fight.
He was communicative
when he was admitted
at 6:00.
That's 6:00 a.m.
This morning. That's when
I started my shift.
Where's the patient now?
I'd like to see him.
They moved him.
I'm sure one of the night
nurses can tell you...
Page me when you find him.
Sure.
I'll do that.
Hey, Cora, can you
do me a favor
and locate a patient for me?
Hey, Ana. Sure.
Edward Solomon?
Yeah.
Aren't you off?
An hour ago.
Here he is.
They had him backward.
Solomon Edward.
He's upstairs in I.C.U.
From a bite?
I don't know what from.
Toxicology is gonna
work him up
in the morning.
Okay, I'm gonna
get outta here.
Can you do me a favor?
Can you page Dr. Dandewar
and let him know?
Sure.
Thanks.
You talk to Luis
about Sunday?
I will. Night, Cora.
Night.
Hey.
(WOMAN CHATTERING ON RADIO)
Hey, Ana?
Let's go.
It's starting early.
Great.
Let's go!
(AMBULANCE SIREN WAILING)
WOMAN ON RADIO:
Unconfirmed reports...
MAN ON RADIO: Confirmed
it is not an isolated...
(MUSIC PLAYING)
ANA: Hey, Vivian.
Ana, look.
I can go backwards.
Let me see.
Hey, that's amazing!
Maybe tomorrow after work
I'll do a few backward
laps around the block
with you, okay?
Okay.
All right. Careful now,
I gotta pull in.
Say hey to your mom
for me, okay?
Okay.
Hey.
Hey, you.
You're late.
You missed it.
They just cut
the mailman loose.
ANA: No, Richie?
The chubby one?
Oh, my God.
He had such a sweet voice.
I can't believe that.
(MAN ON TV TALKING)
Hey, you.
How'd it go today?
Not bad. You?
Good. I'm trading
shifts with Cora,
so if I take Sunday,
I can have a three-day weekend
at the end of the month.
Is that okay?
Sunday?
Yeah.
I think Cora's got
this new guy
she doesn't want me
to know about.
Really. Wow. Lucky her.
I thought maybe
you'd gone out
with the girls
or something.
What? And miss date night?
MAN ON TV:
Twenty-seven horsepower,
turbo-charged, all...
MAN 2 ON TV:
Please stay tuned
to this special news bulletin.
We will return
to our regularly
scheduled programming
immediately following
this report.
LUIS: Vivian's here.
Vivian, honey.
Sweetie, are you okay?
LUIS: Oh, God! Oh, fuck!
Call an ambulance!
(LUIS SCREAMING)
ANA: Vivian! Vivian!
(HISSING)
Luis! Luis! Luis!
Let go! Let go! Let go!
I can't get it!
Hold it! Hold it! Hold it!
Let go! Let go!
Let go, Luis!
I'm gonna call for help!
WOMAN ON PHONE:
All circuits are busy.
God, no. No, no, no!
(BANGING)
WOMAN ON PHONE:
All circuits are busy.
Don't do this to me!
Please, don't do this to me!
WOMAN ON PHONE:
All circuits are busy.
Luis? Luis,
what are you doing?
(LUIS SNARLING)
(GRUNTING)
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Luis?
(SCREECHING)
Help!
Get back, Ana.
Get back!
Jesus, just tell me
what's going on.
I told you to get back.
(AMBULANCE SIRENS WAILING)
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
(EXPLOSION)
(LUIS SCREECHING)
(LUIS SNARLING)
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
MAN ON RADIO:
...emergency broadcast
here in the Milwaukee area...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
...information for local
evacuation centers.
If you live
in Waukesha County...
Help! Can you help?
Please, help!
...22 Robin Lane.
If you live in Southern
Milwaukee County...
(POLICE SIRENS WAILING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
133 Henderson Road.
If there is no activity
where you live,
stay inside
and lock all doors.
(MAN SCREAMING)
If you live
in Jefferson County...
This is the Emergency
Broadcast System
for the greater
Milwaukee area.
If you live
in Racine County...
Pease stay inside
and lock all doors
and windows.
Miller Park
is no longer considered
a safe haven.
Please avoid the stadium
and proceed
to other locations.
Meanwhile, civil unrest
is still being reported
in the area of the Riverwalk.
Please avoid traveling...
There are unconfirmed reports
that several
military personnel
have fallen ill
and that some military bases
are no longer classified
as safe havens.
The following locations are...
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
(SCREAMING)
MAN: I'll take your questions.
MALE REPORTER: Is it a virus?
MAN: We don't know.
FEMALE REPORTER:
How does it spread?
Is it airborne?
MAN: Airborne
is a possibility.
We don't know.
MALE REPORTER: Is this
an international health hazard
or a military concern?
MAN: Both.
FEMALE REPORTER:
Are these people
alive or dead?
MEDIC: Hold him down!
We don't know.
FEMALE REPORTER:
Is that true?
(THE MAN COMES AROUND PLAYING)
Now, listen,
we lost a teleprompter.
(SIRENS WAILING)
(SCREAMING)
WOMAN: Yeah, but I've just
spoken with the President.
He's been in constant contact
with both the C.D.C.,
as well as F.E.M.A.
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
SOLDIER: Stay back,
right there!
A U. S...
God, they're here!
(SNARLING)
MAN: And I looked and behold,
a pale horse.
And its name,
that sat on him, was Death.
And Hell followed with him.
(GUN CLICKING)
Say something.
Please.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
All right! Okay!
Put the guns down!
What are you doing?
Come on. He's a cop!
Come on.
Put the gun down!
I thought you
were one of them.
You do not wanna
go that way.
What's that way?
Officer, sir, you do not
wanna go that way.
What's that way?
It's pretty bad.
What about Fort Pastor?
Maybe if you had wings.
The road's thick with those
motherfuckers that way.
How do you know?
We just tried.
Come on.
Back when there
was eight of us.
We're going to the mall.
Shit.
Damn.
(LUDA SCREAMING)
Hurry up!
Back up!
(ZOMBIE SNARLING)
Open the door!
(BANGING ON DOOR)
Lights.
Here.
No?
No.
Come on.
Sit right there.
We need to make sure
this place is safe.
I'm gonna see if the doors
over this way are locked.
I'll check down there.
Maybe, Officer,
you could go down
that direction. Check for...
All right. Okay.
Maybe it's better
you stay here with the gun.
Andre and I
will check around.
All right, baby,
I'll be right back.
No, no, just stay
right here, okay?
Stay right here.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Shatterproof, asshole.
Shit!
(BANGING)
(ZOMBIE SNARLING)
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
(ZOMBIE SNARLING)
Hey, what happened?
Come on, move!
You all right?
Move!
LUDA: Which way?
Here. Elevators.
Let's go! Let's go!
Can I see that arm?
We need to suture that.
Yeah.
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
You okay?
KENNETH: Yeah.
Find someplace else.
Look, we just need a place...
(GUN CLICKING)
Maybe you didn't hear me.
There is no place else.
Well, that's tough shit,
'cause this is our place,
and you can't stay here.
Yeah, and you already
trashed Metropolis.
Look, dumbass.
My wife is pregnant.
We can't run anymore.
His arm.
Those things are down there.
Well, these are all
your problems, not mine.
If I put my foot up your ass,
would that be your problem?
Hey, asshole, I'm the one
pointing the gun at you.
He is a cop, C.J.
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
So what?
ANA: We're not going
to cause any trouble.
Just let us stay here
for a little while.
Please.
Okay.
Come out of there slowly,
and give your weapons
to Bart and Terry.
Don't do it.
You must be out
of your fucking mind.
You can take your ass
on over to Quality Inn
if it's still there, Shaq.
Huh?
Wanna do that?
Let's go.
Hey, don't give
him that gun.
Fuck.
Smart move.
MAN ON TV: They're everywhere.
Nobody seems to know
what's going on.
There's a lot of blood.
We have bodies.
There's a slew of fires.
We're back to
a live picture now.
All right.
Can I get one second here?
Ma'am, are you American?
All right.
Let's go, guys.
Come on.
Get your own little TV.
Come on. Let's go.
Excuse me, please.
Is there a restroom?
No. You're staying here.
So then why don't you
tell us which spot in here
you'd like us
to take a piss.
All right. It's around
the corner, that way.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Where do you think
you're going?
She's not going
anywhere alone. Come on.
Oh, well,
"She's not going any..."
This is a fucking
nursery school.
Terry, go with them.
MAN ON TV: Hi. I'm Bill Vibert
with 23V Cable News.
I'm at one
of the collection depots
waiting on an interview
with Sheriff Cahill.
I understand you're
having a difficult time
killing these things.
Just shoot them
in the head.
They seem to go
down permanently
when you shoot them
in the head.
Then you gotta burn them.
We gotta burn...
Danny! Danny!
Put another round
in that woman over there!
Look, she's a twitcher.
"Twitcher"?
Now that is one
cool motherfucker.
The bleeding's not
gonna stop on its own.
I need to stitch his arm.
What are you,
a fucking doctor?
No, I'm a fucking nurse.
I know some of these people
that we're putting down...
First Aid kit's
in the security office.
What are you gonna do?
It's gotta be done.
Huh? What did I
tell you, boys?
Get those bodies
off the truck!
Haven't got all day here!
America always sorts
its shit out.
You know, you're lucky.
They could have bitten it off.
Yes, I believe
you're referring to a report
that came in this morning.
But that report
was completely...
REPORTER:
What can you tell the people
out there watching TV
that don't know what to do?
What I would suggest
is that you come
to Fort Pastor.
And if you can't
make it here,
we have multiple
search-and-rescue teams
out there
and they will find you.
My brother's there.
He's waiting for me.
What's the hold up,
darling?
Hmm?
So what's the plan?
The plan is you drink
a nice tall glass
of shut the fuck up.
MICHAEL: Okay.
That's one idea.
What about locking
this place down?
'Cause sooner or later,
they're going to get in here.
Mmm.
That's good.
Like I hadn't thought of that.
MICHAEL: Hey, no doubt.
And you probably
already thought about
putting a sign up on the roof.
Because, you know,
there's still planes
in the air.
Might be good.
Let them know we're alive.
We can get some paint
from Case Hardware.
We need some office doors
to board up the weak spots.
That's a solid plan.
C.J., is it?
Yeah.
All right, C.J.
(CLEARS THROAT)
All right, everybody,
listen up.
I'm gonna give everybody
a job to do,
and I expect you
to do all of it.
I don't wanna see
any half-assing.
You know what?
Why don't you start off
by cleaning up that mess
you made in Metropolis?
Hey, C.J., look.
Terry, take a look
at Ben Cozine.
Hey, Ben. Ben!
Look at him.
BART: Look, he's a twitcher.
TV says you gotta shoot
them in the head.
TV said a lot of things
that aren't true.
Well, fuck the fucker.
I told him not
to go downstairs.
Let's go.
Let's get to work.
Holy shit.
(ZOMBIE GROWLING)
(GUN FIRING)
TERRY: Let's do it.
BART: All right.
Let's pick him up then.
All right.
Ready? One, two...
BART: On two.
All right.
One, two...
(ZOMBIES GROWLING)
What are they?
I don't know.
Why are they coming here?
KENNETH: Memory, maybe.
Instinct.
Maybe they're coming for us.
(GUN FIRING)
(ZOMBIES GROWLING)
(GUN FIRES)
ANA: Hey, look over there.
There's someone on the roof.
C. J: Yeah, his name's Andy.
He's alone.
He may as well be
on the Moon.
ANA: Poor guy.
What's he pointing at?
MICHAEL: Helicopter.
ANDRE: Hey, it's coming.
Hey!
Please!
What's he doing?
Where's he...
No, no. I mean,
they saw us.
So, I mean, they're gonna
be coming back, baby.
Don't worry.
I mean, they're gonna
send somebody or something.
ANA: It's safe here.
We'll just wait for them
to come back.
I don't want anybody
sneaking around
and stealing shit.
Comprende?
Sweet dreams.
Those assholes
are gonna get us killed.
We have to do something.
I'm not doing anything
to create problems
for Luda and me.
The helicopter's
coming back soon.
I hope so.
And what's that
supposed to mean?
It means it might come
and it might not.
We don't know.
What do you mean
it not come back?
You said it was
coming back!
We have to get to hospital.
Hey, baby, listen, listen.
Don't worry. This guy,
he doesn't know shit.
All right?
It's coming back.
Hey, my man. You know,
I hear you talking a lot.
You know, you're always
saying something.
Who the fuck are you
that we should listen, huh?
What are you, like,
in Special Ops?
You in the Marines?
What the fuck do you do?
I sell televisions
at Best Buy.
ANDRE: Wow.
Hey, Officer,
how you like following
a guy that sells TVs?
About as much
as I like following a guy
who steals them.
I'm not following anyone.
I'm going to Fort Pastor
to get my brother.
They seem to need
to feed on warm flesh.
Some basic skills remain.
They don't seem to have much,
if any, reasoning power.
And how does this spread?
These guys
are so full of shit.
They've been saying
the same damn thing
all day.
MAN ON TV: Everybody
they kill gets up.
Tell me something
I don't know, asshole!
I've just been informed
that we are going
off the air...
BART: Wanna hear
something that sucks?
...and switching over
to the Emergency
Broadcasting System.
You guys know that chick
at Dairy Queen?
I don't know when
we'll be back on the air.
The fat one?
Yeah.
She was coming
over tonight.
I would have tapped
that shit for sure.
Bart, dude,
everybody's dead, okay?
Your mom's dead.
Your brother's dead.
That fat chick at Dairy Queen?
Dead!
It's been a pleasure
to report the news to you
in these past 26 years.
God bless you.
Yeah.
God bless America.
That sucks too.
Hell is overflowing.
And Satan is sending
his dead to us.
Why? Because
you have sex out of wedlock.
You kill unborn children.
You have man-on-man relations.
Same-sex marriage.
How do you think
your god will judge you?
Well, friends,
now we know.
When there is
no more room in hell,
the dead will walk the earth
What the hell...
Hey, dumbass.
It's the timers.
It's? :00.
Terry.
Go shut them off.
It's Bart's turn.
You're the trainee, man.
Shit rolls downhill.
I wish somebody was working
at Hallowed Grounds.
How hard is it
to make a cup of coffee?
I wanted a soy
mocha latte with foam.
Faggot.
What are you doing?
What's the news?
Bad.
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
Hey. Hey!
Hey!
What?
The bathroom in here
is fake. It doesn't work.
I'll tell C.J.
I'm telling you.
You're the type of cat
that goes to church
and all that kind
of shit, right?
Yeah, I do all that
kind of shit.
So what you think? Hmm?
What is this?
Is this the end of times?
'Cause if it is,
I'm telling you,
I'm fucked.
No, I'm serious.
I've done some
bad things in my life, man.
Oh, I get it.
You saw hell yesterday.
Now you're scared
of going to hell
for all the bad things
you've done.
I'll tell you what.
Go in the stall,
say five Hail Marys,
wipe your ass,
and you and God
can call it even.
You think I feel
like I deserve to be here?
Yeah.
Yeah, well, I don't.
And I'm cool with that.
But you see, that's not it.
'Cause I feel like
I'm here for another reason.
I feel like I'm here
to bring that baby
on this earth.
And give it everything
that I never had.
I just want the opportunity
to change things.
Shit!
C. J!
How did you get out?
And who gave you permission
to loot the goddamn stores?
What are we gonna do
about that truck?
We're not going
to do anything
about that truck.
There's people in there.
Yeah? How do you know
they're not all fucked up
like everybody else out there?
Well, for one thing,
they're driving a truck.
(GUN FIRING)
Oh, and shooting guns.
If we start letting
people in here,
then we're gonna let
the wrong ones in.
And then I'm dead.
You know what?
I don't wanna die!
Who are the wrong ones?
Nobody here is sick.
And I intend on
keeping it that way.
I just think we should...
I did not ask
for your opinion, lady!
Now, if you wanna
argue with me,
you can argue with this.
MICHAEL: Hey, hey,
take it easy.
Shut your fucking mouth.
Get the gun
outta my face.
You can't just
turn them away, C.J.
You'll kill them.
Tough shit. Self-defense.
I'm not killing anybody.
You know what?
I'll kill you.
No, no, stop it, C.J.
Don't do this!
Shut up!
I'll kill each and every one
of you to stay alive.
You hear me?
I said get the fucking gun
outta my face!
You got quite
a mouth on you.
Somebody should show her
how to use it.
Is there a holding
cell in there?
Yeah, back
of the security room.
That's real good, man.
You're gonna get us
all killed, dumbass.
Fucking traitor!
BART: Get off me.
I hope you got
a good plan.
Come on.
(ZOMBIES GROWLING)
Hey! Up here!
Can't see
a damn thing.
Me neither.
Why's he backing up the truck?
Through here!
Hey!
Shit.
Fuck. We gotta go out there.
Man, you better
throw that bullshit
right out your head.
I'm not going back out there.
That's not part of the plan.
Change of plan.
I'm gonna open the door.
No.
Okay.
One, two, three.
No. Don't do it, man.
Come on, man.
Thanks.
Yeah.
(ZOMBIES GROWLING)
ANDRE: Shoot them
in the head!
I don't see anybody.
Get back inside!
They're fine!
Here you go.
There's six more people
inside the truck.
Andre, look!
(ZOMBIES GROWLING)
MONICA: Thank God.
I couldn't stay in
that fucking truck anymore.
ANA: All right,
anybody who's injured,
let's get you into
Metropolis right away.
I'll come take a look at you.
Let me take a look at her.
Can you help me with...
Sir, what's your name? Sorry.
Glen, yeah, sure.
Just give me a second
to collect myself, okay?
Thanks.
If you wanna just go
wait for me in there,
I'll take a look at your leg.
Here. I'll hold this.
Just go and wait there.
My arm!
It's okay, ma'am.
We're gonna make you nice
and comfortable, all right?
The rest of you,
we've got plenty
of food and water.
Help should be along soon.
(LAUGHING)
Help? Did you hear that
from the same jackass
who told us to go
to St. Verbena?
The church downtown?
Yeah.
That's the first place I went.
Some dipshit on the radio
said it was safe there.
He was wrong.
Is that where
you picked them up?
Well, I get this call
on the C.B.
From that guy Glen
saying all these folks
are in the chapel.
He's a priest?
No, he plays the organ.
I was in the neighborhood,
so I picked them up.
Well done.
Thanks.
Hey, I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
When you two fellows
are done blowing each other,
maybe Davy Crockett
can tell us the deal here.
Well, we haven't
heard much
since the TVs
went out last night.
KENNETH: Excuse me.
Whose rig is that?
It's mine.
You mind if I borrow it?
I'm not using it,
Officer.
Keys.
They're in the cab.
Truck's not gonna make it
to Fort Pastor.
No, forget the truck.
That place is fucked, man.
Bloodbath city.
How do you know?
We just came from there.
Is everyone there dead?
Or dead-ish.
Yeah, in the sense
that they all, sort of,
fell down, and then...
I gotta look for myself.
You're not gonna make it.
...got up and...
I'll get as far as I can.
Right now it's about
one foot out that door.
...started eating each other.
I'll take my chances.
Don't be an idiot.
Please, there's people
here right now
who could use your help.
Fuck y'all.
It's nice to see
that you've all bonded
through this disaster.
(ZOMBIES GROWLING)
Hey. You need anything?
No, we're fine.
Don't worry about us.
He's got a bite
on his hand.
She's cold.
That's good, right?
ANA: I don't know,
it's weird.
I've never seen
an infection this bad
that didn't come
with a fever.
That guy's arm
looks pretty bad
over there.
You should probably
check it out.
All right.
Stay with her for a minute.
Here. Want me to take
a look at that?
I'm fine. Really.
They don't hurt
much at all.
Tucker could use you
more than I could.
His ankle's cut
pretty bad.
Here. I'm just gonna
clean it up a bit.
TERRY: You okay?
(GASPING)
Ma'am, can I
get you something?
Like a glass of water?
(GASPING)
Ana! Ana, come here!
Anyone know her name?
Died without a name?
Damn.
Guys, do you wanna move
into the other room?
Holy shit!
Oh, shit.
I think it's the bites.
Frank said she was
walking on her own
when she got in the truck
five hours ago.
The bites killed her.
The bites brought her back.
How do you know?
I watched it happen.
I felt her pulse.
She was gone.
Then... Yesterday
I saw the same thing
happen to somebody else.
I think that's why
it spread so fast.
All right.
So who else
in the group is bitten?
Frank, for sure.
How about the one
with the foot?
Tucker?
He says no, he fell.
So, it's Frank.
Tall guy, right?
Right. So we have to
quarantine him right away.
Where exactly do we do that?
I don't know.
There must be someplace
to keep him in here.
Then what?
I don't know, but...
It's too dangerous
to keep him on here.
I'm sorry. What are we
talking about here?
Are we talking
about killing him?
Would you rather
we waited for him to die,
and then he tries
to kill us?
Yes. No.
You can't kill him.
Ana...
He's got a daughter!
I'm sorry.
I don't think
there's any other choice.
He's right.
Michael, you can't do this.
What if I'm wrong?
You've seen it
happen before.
Frank,
Michael's coming
to shoot you.
What are you talking about?
You're infected.
You're gonna become
one of them.
Is this true?
Are you gonna kill me?
You've been bitten.
It's only a matter of time.
No, no, no!
Leave my dad alone!
Go away!
You can't do this!
You have to understand
that she's lost everyone.
Her mother,
her two brothers.
I'm all she's got.
Well, Michael,
what are you waiting for?
Go ahead, kill him.
(NICOLE SOBBING)
Hey, kill Tucker, too.
Wait a minute.
I was never bit.
We can't be sure.
Do it, Michael.
Are you sure
it's the bite?
No.
She's sure.
I'm sorry.
Hey.
Hi.
You okay?
Let me see your arm.
It hurts.
It's already
starting to heal.
Andre, I can't have baby here.
Why not? People have
been having babies
for millions of years.
All on their own.
No hospitals.
Wait.
Oh, yeah.
It's moving.
I felt it.
ANDRE: So now
we gotta come up
with a name for this baby.
I want Russian name.
Don't start that again.
African name.
Please?
Come here.
Give me a hug.
FRANK: Sweetie,
I'm so proud of you.
I couldn't ask
for anything more
in a daughter.
I love you, baby.
I love you too.
Time to go, honey.
No.
Terry, come on, man.
Open the door.
Shut up.
C. J: Come on, man.
Don't tell me to shut up.
Just come open the door.
BART: I got you this job.
Come on.
You want...
...every...
...single second.
Ana.
I'm glad you didn't do it.
(ZOMBIE SCREECHING)
(GUN FIRING)
(VOCAL JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING)
(ZOMBIES SHOUTING)
(GUN FIRING)
(HORSE GASPING)
(BICYCLE BELL RINGING)
(ZOMBIES SHOUTING)
C. J: Okay, okay.
Here's a good one.
"Top Ten Ingredients
To A Successful Relationship."
(MUMBLING)
All right, I'm gonna skip
to the top three.
Number three,
"He listens to me."
Number two,
"He tells me he loves me."
And number one...
Oh, it's "trust."
Number one's trust.
(ZOMBIES SHOUTING)
(GUN FIRING)
Holy shit. He got him.
So, who do we have next?
Yeah. Burt Reynolds.
Tell him to get
Burt Reynolds.
(CHUCKLES)
STEVE: Oh, my goodness.
Man, he's good.
It barely even
looked like him.
Oh, oh. Rosie O'Donnell.
Tell him to get Rosie.
Oh, yeah. Rosie.
No, too easy.
Give him something hard.
You guys had
really rough childhoods,
didn't you?
A little bit rocky?
Hey, sweetheart.
Let me tell you something.
You have my permission.
I ever turn
into one of those things?
Do me a favor,
blow my fucking head off.
Oh, yeah.
You can count on that.
I guess the first time
I knew I was gay...
I was 13.
This guy...
Todd.
He was building a deck
in our backyard.
Okay? Just, please, stop.
I remember he had the most
astonishing blue eyes.
Oh, my God!
I'm in hell.
(GROANING)
Hey, Andre.
How's Luda doing?
She's fine.
Hey, where's that
lemon stuff?
It's all gone.
Steve likes to put it
in his booze.
Try the vanilla stuff.
All right.
I'd like to drop by
and check on her,
just to see
how she's doing.
No, thanks. She's fine.
You sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
It's okay, hon.
We understand.
(MEOWS)
Thanks.
(ZOMBIES SNARLING)
Before that I worked
in a stationery store.
And I drove a snowplow.
Fixed copiers.
God, it's such a shame
that this whole
end of the world thing's
holding you back.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Okay, worst job.
I know which job
I was the worst at.
Being a husband.
That's not a job.
It sure is.
(ALL LAUGHING)
You guys just haven't met
the right girl.
Yeah, I tried it three times.
I got pink slips every time.
What were you best at?
Being a dad.
I think
I was best at that.
(ALL GASPING)
KENNETH: Everybody calm down.
NORMA: Are they inside?
MICHAEL: No.
This place have generators?
(SCREAMING)
(SHUSHING)
ANDRE: It's all right, baby.
(SCREAMING)
(SHUSHING)
Baby, please.
You gotta be quiet. Okay?
It's gonna be all right.
Our baby's on the way.
It's coming.
That's it. It's in
employee parking,
level three.
They keep them in a pen
near the parking shuttles.
Have fun.
Hey. Wait a minute.
You're coming too.
No, I'm not.
I said I'd tell you
where the generators are.
I never said I'd show you.
Did you think
I was gonna leave
you two up here?
You come with me,
or you go back in that cell.
All right.
I ain't going anywhere
without a gun.
You're not getting a gun.
Trust.
Primary ingredient
in any relationship.
Have at them, cowboy.
Asshole.
Bart, get the chains.
(GUN CLICKING)
Shit.
Are we ready to roll?
You coming with us?
No, you're coming with me.
I've done this before.
Know how to use that?
This one's
the dangerous end, right?
Now it is.
This is level one.
We gotta walk down to three.
(RUMBLING)
What the fuck was that?
I just saw something.
You didn't see shit, Bart.
Shut the fuck up.
(RUMBLING)
Oh, shit.
Here it comes.
(PANTING)
Jesus Christ!
It's a fucking dog.
Come here, boy.
(DOG WHIMPERING)
At least you know
nothing's down here.
It would've eaten him.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
See? I told you
I saw something.
(DOG BARKING)
MICHAEL: What's wrong, boy?
There's nothing wrong.
That dog's just fucked up.
(GROWLING)
(ZOMBIES SNARLING)
Run!
BART: Wait, C.J.
Wait up! Wait!
It's locked!
It's fucking locked!
No! No!
KENNETH: Come on! Let's go!
(BART SCREAMING)
C.J.!
(SCREECHING)
(GROANING)
I'm out.
C.J.! Matches!
(SCREECHING)
Breathe.
You're doing good.
(GASPING)
You're doing good, baby.
I'm sorry.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Thanks.
Okay. That's the last.
I'm gonna go
check on Luda.
I haven't seen her
in a while.
I'll go.
You sure?
Yeah.
Take them some candles.
Okay. Let me know
if they need anything.
Okay. I'll have a little
smoke on the way.
See you.
Bye.
It's coming.
I see it.
(GROANING)
Guys?
Oh, my God.
It's a girl.
You wanna kill Luda?
You wanna kill my family?
(LUDA GROWLING)
Norma? Come on, Norma.
What happened?
Son of a bitch shot me.
Get away from her.
ANA: Wait.
Just wait.
She died of the gunshot.
She wasn't bitten.
She's gonna wake up
though, right?
ANA: No.
No. If she was one of them,
she'd be up by now.
Terry.
Yeah?
Hold this.
(SCREAMING)
Oh, God.
(GUN FIRING)
Somebody should
say something.
Yeah.
MICHAEL: Glen?
No.
You worked in the church.
I played the organ.
C. J: Come on, man.
You must've heard
the priest say something
about life and death.
It was a job.
I don't believe in God.
I don't see how anyone could.
Somebody should
say something.
Nothing to say.
Been to a lot of funerals.
Folded the flag and given it
to a lot of wives,
and fathers, and kids.
I told them
how sorry I was.
But that's not what
I was really feeling.
In the back of my mind,
I was always saying,
"Better them than me."
But I don't believe that now.
Because now I realize
there are some things
worse than death,
and one of them
is sitting here
waiting to die.
I don't wanna die here.
I saw a couple of buses
in the garage.
We could fix them up.
We could reinforce them.
Then get as far
from here as possible.
And then what?
Oh, I have an idea.
While we're at it
why don't we
swing by the marina,
and hop in my boat,
take it for a pleasure cruise,
you jackasses.
Wait a minute.
That's a good idea.
There's islands
out in those lakes.
There's not a lot
of people on them.
I was kidding.
How far is the marina?
Oh, my God.
You're serious?
I think it's
a damn good idea.
How about
the rest of you?
Kenneth?
Yeah, it's a good idea.
We have to pick up Andy.
He's part of the group.
Excuse me, not to shit
on anyone's riff here,
but let me just
see if I grasp
this concept, okay?
You're suggesting
that we take some
fucking parking shuttles
and reinforce them
with some aluminum siding,
and then just head on
over to the gun store
where we watch
our good friend Andy
play some cowboy-movie,
jump-on-the-covered-wagon
bullshit?
Then we're going
to drive across
the ruined city
through a welcome committee
of a few hundred thousand
dead cannibals.
All so we can sail off
into the sunset
on this fucking
asshole's boat?
Head for some island
that for all we know
doesn't even exist?
Yeah.
Pretty much, yeah.
Okay.
I'm in.
We have 12 of these
shotgun shells,
26 of those pussy nine mils
and 16 of those.357 Magnums.
ANA: Yeah? Well, it's still
not very much, so...
Hopefully we'll get
to the dock
and there won't be
too many of them.
Well, it's nice to see you
busting your ass today.
Oh, that's sarcasm.
That is awesome.
Yeah, you know,
I would love to help, but
a captain never works
alongside his men.
(IMITATES WHIP CRACKING)
You guys, have a good one.
What a total dick.
Guys, where'd Chips go?
Chips?
NICOLE: Where'd
you go, Chips?
I can't find him.
Chips, come here.
Come on, Chips.
(IMMITATING)
NICOLE: Chips, come on, boy.
Where'd you go, honey?
(WHISTLING)
(DOG BARKING)
NICOLE: There you are.
Come on. There's my boy.
Don't you ever
leave me again, okay?
Ever, ever.
Hey. Kenneth wants
everyone upstairs
for a meeting.
Come in here first.
I want you to see this.
When those things
are on the side of the bus,
this'll get them off.
Cool, huh?
Wow.
That might be
the most romantic thing
anyone's ever shown me.
I'm trying here.
Yeah, I know.
It's not just about
him starving, Steve.
If we go to pick him up
and he doesn't have
his strength,
then we're going to be
carrying him. It's...
TUCKER: She's right.
He's a hell of a shot too.
We're going to need him.
Tucker, I'm not saying
we don't need him.
There's no point
in arguing about this.
We need a solution.
We need to get
some food over there.
STEVE: Okay. I have an idea.
We draw straws
and the loser runs
across the lot
with a ham sandwich.
ANA: Could you be
a bigger prick?
STEVE: I think so.
But, you know,
that's irrelevant.
My question to you is,
what's your plan?
(ALL ARGUING)
Come on.
MICHAEL: We're not going
to leave him on his own
to die, all right?
I got it.
MICHAEL: We gotta get
over there anyway.
Shut up.
Because we need
more ammunition,
all right?
I have an idea.
Stop, it's hurting him.
No! He's not safe.
Nicole, they're not
interested in him.
I promise.
Look at me.
They want us.
Chips is gonna be fine.
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
See? Look.
He's walking right by them.
They're not even
paying attention to him.
KENNETH: The walkie's
in the bag, right?
TERRY: Yeah.
Let me see.
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
There he is. Good boy.
Good boy, Chips.
Okay. He's there. He's in.
Give me those.
KENNETH: Oh, man.
What?
KENNETH: No.
No. Oh, man.
They got him. They got him!
(GUN FIRING)
(ZOMBIES GROWLING)
Try him on the radio.
Andy. Andy, do you copy?
Andy, can you hear me?
Andy?
ANDY: Can you hear me? Hello?
Is this working?
I'm dinged up pretty bad,
but I think I'm gonna be okay.
Where are you hurt, Andy?
Goddamn, those bastards
bite hard.
I just have to stop
the bleeding.
It's really going.
(DOG BARKING)
Easy, boy, easy.
Is this Ken?
Is that you, man?
Yeah, it's me, brother.
Hey, man.
Good to hear your voice.
I guess we're going
to meet up close
pretty soon, huh?
Oh, shit. Hang on.
Oh, Jesus, he got me good.
Now, you just hang in there.
You got the food, right?
Yeah.
Do we tell him?
Hey, this dog got a name?
See, Nicole, Chips...
Nicole?
(TIRES SCREECHING)
What the hell's that?
Oh, my God! It's Nicole!
Shit.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
That idiot's going after
the fucking dog.
She made it. She's in.
NICOLE: You guys?
I found Chips.
I got him. He's okay.
Nicole, how's Andy looking?
I don't know. There's a lot
of blood in here.
It's everywhere.
There's blood everywhere.
Wait a minute. I see him.
He's on the roof.
He's writing something.
What's it say?
Guys?
Tell her to get out.
What's wrong?
Nicole, baby,
how's the truck?
(DOG BARKING)
I'm not going back out there.
Chips, be quiet!
Tell her to get
the hell out now!
Honey, listen to me.
You need to find
a place to hide.
Can you do that?
What do you mean?
What's going on?
MICHAEL: Nicole.
Oh, here's Andy.
Oh, my God!
No! Tell her to get out!
Nicole, listen to me.
(CRYING)
I'm in a closet.
But he's outside.
He's trying to get...
MICHAEL: Nicole?
Nicole?
Help me! Please,
you have to help me!
I'm gonna die!
(STATIC ON RADIO)
We need to do something, now.
Tucker, listen. When we
come back through here,
we may have company.
You need to stay here
and make sure
that fire door stays open.
Whoa, whoa.
Wait, wait, wait. I'm sorry.
Why does he stay here,
while I go on the suicide
mission to rescue Terry's
already dead girlfriend?
Fuck you, man.
We don't know that.
You know what, asshole?
Either way
we gotta get over there
and get the guns
and get out of this
parking lot, all right?
Michael, it's okay.
Let him stay.
Yeah.
Steve, don't fuck this up.
Yeah. Totally.
C. J: All right.
That's it.
MICHAEL: Are you sure?
I ain't a plumber,
but I'd say we're pretty much
at the end of the line here.
(ZOMBIES GROWLING)
(METALLIC CLANGING)
C. J: Go! Go!
(ZOMBIE SNARLING)
Through here!
C. J: Hurry up!
Hurry up! Hurry!
(ZOMBIES GROWLING)
.357,.357...
What do you need?
.3? .3?
TERRY: Here.
Damn it.
Come on. Hurry up.
All right.
C. J: Oh, shit.
Nicole?
(METALLIC CLANGING)
(GROWLING)
KENNETH: Andy.
I'm sorry, brother.
MICHAEL:
Nicole, are you in there?
NICOLE: I'm here! I'm here!
(DOG WHIMPERING)
KENNETH: Get as much ammo
as you can.
You got a plan?
Uh-uh. You?
How about a barbecue?
How do we know if he hits it?
Oh, shit.
TERRY: C.J.! Over here!
Hurry up!
Over here!
Go! Get down!
TUCKER: Look out!
(ZOMBIES GROWLING)
C. J: Come on, Tucker!
Come on!
Oh, shit!
(SCREAMING)
TUCKER: My leg!
C. J: I got you, Tucker.
Go! Go!
Shit.
Go!
(SHOUTING)
MICHAEL: Let's go!
(ZOMBIES SCREECHING)
Shoot me! Shoot me!
NICOLE: Terry, come on!
(DOG BARKING)
Hurry! Hurry!
Goddamn Steve Markus!
NICOLE: Steve, come on!
Steve!
NICOLE: Open the door!
Open the door!
TERRY: Steve!
Fucking kill him!
TERRY: Come on!
Open the door, Steve!
Let's go!
(ZOMBIES SCREECHING)
KENNETH: Move!
(ZOMBIES SNARLING)
Go!
C. J: Move it, guys! Move it!
MONICA: Where are you
guys going?
Let's go right now.
We're going.
MICHAEL: Go! Go!
ANA: They're right behind us!
(ZOMBIES GROWLING)
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
KENNETH: Come on, move!
They're right behind us!
(ELEVATOR MUSIC PLAYING)
I like this song.
(DOG BARKING)
Everybody in!
Hey, there you are.
What the hell
happened to you guys?
Give me the keys.
ANA: Prick.
What?
I'll deal with you later,
motherfucker!
Wait a minute! Nicole!
Man, get in!
I'll take the gun. Okay.
GLEN: Okay, let's get
out of here.
Hold on!
(ZOMBIES GROWLING)
Oh, Christ!
C.J., now! Go!
They're trying
to turn us over!
Hit them with the saw!
STEVE: Come on, damn it.
C. J: Give me the shotgun!
Holy shit.
(GROWLING)
There's still one hanging on.
Which fucking side?
Right side.
GLEN: I got him.
You gotta drive faster, man.
Hard left! Hard left! Here!
Whoa! Stop! Stop, guys!
What?
We lost them. Back it up.
Back it up! Back up!
Kenneth, are you there?
Kenneth?
ANA: Kenneth, are you there?
Kenneth, are you okay?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What the fuck?
(SNARLING)
(SCREAMING)
What are you doing?
Fucking nursery school.
C.J.!
Ana, no. Everyone's dead.
Steve took off.
What?
C. J: Let's go! Come on!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Steve!
(SCREAMING)
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I got him.
Damn.
Watch out!
Come on! Come on!
(GROWLING)
TERRY: Open the door!
Hurry up!
Come on!
Guys, get in!
KENNETH: Let's go.
Where's Ana? Ana!
Ana!
Get in! Get in!
What the hell
were you doing?
Hold on!
NICOLE: Come on, boy.
Go.
Kenneth! Here.
Go to the end of the dock.
KENNETH: C.J., come on.
Do it, man. I'll catch up!
There it is.
MICHAEL: Terry,
get the bowline.
Shit.
C.J.!
It's jammed! Fuck!
Come on!
Bitch! Shit!
Come on.
(ROARING)
It fucking figures.
(ZOMBIES GROWLING)
Okay, let's go. Let's go.
I can't go.
What?
Downtown when
they jumped on us.
Oh, no, Michael. No.
I have to stay here.
Wait. You can't.
Not you. Please.
I'm sorry, Ana.
I can help you.
MICHAEL: No, you can't.
You can help them.
MICHAEL: Stay on the boat.
I can help you.
It's okay.
It's gonna be all right.
No.
It won't.
Hey.
It will.
You sure you wanna do this?
Yeah.
I think I'll just
stay here awhile.
Enjoy the sunrise.
(ENGINE STARTING)
(GUN FIRING)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
I run a tight ship.
Where did you get that thing?
TERRY: I found Steve's camera.
Put that down. Help us.
TERRY: Kenneth,
fucking shoot it! Shoot it!
(GUN FIRING)
TERRY: Christ!
(ENGINE SHUTTING DOWN)
TERRY: Shit.
Get that damn camera
out of my face.
Doesn't look
like there's anyone there.
Terry, put the camera down
while I dock the boat.
(DOG WHIMPERING)
TERRY: Nicole, what is it?
NICOLE: Chips, no!
(BARKING)
(PANTING)
(ZOMBIES GROWLING)
TERRY: Oh, shit!
(ZOMBIES SCREECHING)
KENNETH: Stay behind me!
(GUN FIRES)
(GROWLING)
(GUN FIRING)