Upcoming jump scare (Major)
[ Screaming ]
[ Helicopter Blades Whirring ]
-NOTHIN',
NOTHIN' AT ALL.
- SEND IT AGAIN.
I'VE BEEN SENDIN' IT UP
AND DOWN THE COAST FROM SARASOTA
TO THE EVERGLADES.
IT'S STILL GETTING BACK
THE SAME DAY IT AIRED.
THERE'S NOTHING.
THERE'S NOBODY, OR AT LEAST
NOBODY WITH A RADIO.
ALL RIGHT THEN.
LET'S SET DOWN.
WE'LL USE THE BULLHORN.
[ Man ]
SET DOWN? WAIT A MINUTE.
THAT'S NOT IN OUR CONTRACT.
IT'S THE BIGGEST CITY
WITHIN 150 MILES. WE'RE
GONNA GIVE IT EVERY CHANCE.
JESUS, MARY AND JOSEPH.
SET DOWN, JOHN.
I'LL SET US DOWN,
BUT I WON'T LEAVE MY SEAT, AND
I'LL KEEP THE ENGINE RUNNING.
NOW, THE FIRST SIGN
OF TROUBLE, I'M GOING UP.
IF YOU AIN'T ON BOARD WHEN
THAT HAPPENS, YOU'RE LIKELY
TO HAVE A LOUSY AFTERNOON.
CALLING ANYBODY
ON THIS FREQUENCY.
THIS IS
HELICOPTER 4-0-ALPHA.
IF YOU CAN HEAR ME,
PLEASE LISTEN CAREFULLY.
HELLO?
IS ANYONE THERE?
[ Flies Buzzing ]
[ Wind Whistling ]
HELLO?
IS THERE ANYONE THERE?
[ Footsteps Approaching ]
[ Gasping ]
HELLO?
[ Moaning ]
IS THERE ANYONE THERE?
- [ Gasping ]
-HELLO?
[ Moaning ]
HELLO?
IS ANYONE THERE?
[ Grunting ]
[ Low Moaning ]
[ Moaning Intensifies ]
WE CAN LIFT YOU OUT
TO SAFETY. PLEASE ANSWER
MY CALL IF YOU CAN HEAR ME.
FORGET IT, BILLY BOY.
IT'S A DEAD PLACE.
THEY GOT THE OTHERS,
YOU KNOW.
LISTEN.
[ Muffled Moaning ]
YOU CAN HEAR IT
OVER THE ENGINE.
JESUS, MARY AND JOSEPH.
[ Moaning Nears ]
[ Helicopter Blades Whirring ]
[ Low Moaning ]
HEY, YOU FIND ANYTHING?
YEAH. A BUNCH
OF REAL ESTATE FOR SALE
AT CLOSEOUT PRICES, MAN.
GAS UP THE MACHINE.
SHE'S DOWN TO FUMES.
NO. WAIT TILL IT'S DARK.
THERE ARE TOO MANY OF THEM
OUT THERE.
YEAH-HEY,
IT'S NO GOOD
TO LEAVE THE GAS TANK EMPTY.
- SUPPOSE WE NEED TO GET
OUT OF HERE IN A HURRY.
- THEN WE'RE SHIT OUT OF LUCK.
THEY'RE GETTING TOO RILED UP.
DO IT TONIGHT WHEN
THEY CAN'T SEE YOU.
THEY KNOW WE'RE IN HERE EVEN IF
THEY CAN'T SEE US. WHAT GOOD IS
IT TO LEAVE THE GAS TANK EMP--
THE ACTIVITY EXCITES THEM.
THERE ARE TOO MANY OF THEM.
AND MORE AND MORE EVERY DAY.
IF WE GET A LOT MORE, COME OUT
AND SHOOT SOME. OTHERWISE,
STAY INSIDE THE BUILDING.
STAY OUT OF SIGHT.
BE THANKFUL YOU LIVE
IN THE SUBURBS, JOHNSON.
YOU OUGHTA SEE
HOW CONGESTED THE CITY'S
GETTIN' TO BE.
MIGUEL, COME ON.
LET'S GET BELOW.
MIGUEL, WHAT CAN I DO?
YOU-- YOU--
WHAT?
LET ME HELP.
NO. I-- I DON'T NEED HELP.
I DON'T NEED HELP.
COME ON. GIVE ME THIS.
I'M ALL RIGHT.
I'M JUST TIRED.
YOU'RE NOT. YOU'RE COLLAPSING
FROM STRESS. NOW, LET ME HELP--
COLLAPSING FROM STRESS?
WE'RE ALL COLLAPSING.
THIS WHOLE FUCKING UNIT
IS COLLAPSING--
EVERYBODY EXCEPT YOU.
I KNOW YOU'RE STRONG,
ALL RIGHT? SO WHAT?
STRONGER THAN ME.
STRONGER THAN EVERYONE.
SO WHAT?
SO FUCKING WHAT?
[ Moaning Continues ]
- THAT'S A NEW GRAVE.
- MAJOR COOPER.
HE DIED THIS MORNING.
AND THEN THERE WERE 12.
A BURIAL THIS MORNING.
THAT'S WHY THERE ARE SO MANY
OF THEM.
WHAT'S GONNA BRING THEM
TOMORROW, SARAH? AND THE NEXT
DAY AND THE NEXT DAY AFTER?
THERE ARE HUNDREDS OF 'EM
OVER THERE, THOUSANDS.
A MILLION OF THEM!
YOU STICK YOUR HEAD IN THE SUN,
THEY'RE GONNA COME UP BEHIND YOU
AND BITE OFF YOUR ASS!
THIS IS BULLSHIT. CRAZY.
IF YOU'VE GOT AN ALTERNATIVE,
WE'D BE HAPPY TO LISTEN TO IT.
I GOT AN ALTERNATIVE.
YEAH, YEAH. I GOT
AN ALTERNATIVE.
LET'S GET IN THAT WHIRLYBIRD,
FIND US AN ISLAND SOMEPLACE,
GET JUICED UP...
AND SPEND WHAT TIME WE GOT LEFT
SOAKIN' UP SOME SUNSHINE.
HOW'S THAT?
YOU COULD DO THAT,
COULDN'T YOU?
WITH ALL THAT'S GOING ON,
YOU COULD DO THAT
WITHOUT A SECOND THOUGHT?
RIGHT. I COULD DO THAT
EVEN IF ALL THIS WASN'T
GOIN' ON.
[ Hydraulic Whirring ]
[ Electronic Beeping ]
ANOTHER WASTE OF TIME,
RIGHT?
GOT THAT RIGHT, MAN.
[ Whirring ]
WHAT'D YOU FIND?
NOTHIN'.
NOTHIN'? HOW FAR
UP THE COAST DID YOU GO?
- A HUNDRED MILES EACH WAY.
- [ Groans ]
JUMP IN HERE, SOLDIER.
WE GOTTA BRING IN TWO MORE
DUMB FUCKS. LET'S GO.
-[ Sarah ] TWO MORE? WHAT'S
LOGAN DOING TO THEM IN THERE?
-[ Man ] GET IN HERE.
HE'S BEEN AWAKE
FOR 24 HOURS. CAN'T YOU
GET ANYONE ELSE?
WHAT "ANYONE ELSE"?
THERE ISN'T ANYONE ELSE.
WE'RE IT.
THE TWO OF YOU
CAN'T GO IN THERE ALONE.
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS.
CHRIST. I'LL GO!
- WHAT'S THE MATTER
WITH YOUR FRIEND THERE?
- THERE'S NOTHING THE MATTER.
ALL RIGHT. LET'S GO.
[ Man Talking,
Indistinct ]
[ Man #2 ]
YOU GOT IT, STEEL.
[ Men Continue Chattering,
Indistinct ]
[ Man Laughing Maniacally ]
[ Screeching ]
[ Maniacal Laughter Continues ]
LET'S KICK IT OUT.
COME ON. STEP FORWARD.
[ Mechanical Whirring ]
[ Spitting ]
[ Wind Whistling ]
THIS SHOWS THE 15th
AS THE LAST TIME YOU
TOOK ANY OUT.
THAT CAN'T BE RIGHT.
OH, YEAH. WE FORGET TO
WRITE 'EM UP SOMETIMES.
YOU'VE GOT TO WRITE THEM UP.
IT'S ESSENTIAL.
CAN'T YOU GET THAT
THROUGH YOUR THICK SKULL?
HOW THE HELL ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO KEEP TRACK OF HOW MANY
WE GOT LEFT?
[ Screaming ]
[ Whistling ]
LET'S GO, YOU DUMB FUCKS!
GET OVER HERE!
HEY! HERE WE ARE!
[ Low Moaning ]
COME ON!
[ Steel ]
COME ON, YOU DUMB FUCKS.
COME ON. COME ON.
- [ Steel Knocking ]
- COME ON, YOU FISH BRAINS. WHAT
THE HELL'S THE MATTER WITH YA?
THEY'RE SCARED.
HUH?
THEY KNOW WHAT'LL HAPPEN
WHEN FRANKENSTEIN
GETS 'EM.
[ Sarah ]
IF YOU'RE RIGHT, RICKLES,
THEN THEY'RE LEARNING.
THEY'RE ACTUALLY
LEARNING.
[ Steel ] COME ON!
COME AND SEE
WHAT I GOT FOR YOU!
COME ON, YOU DICK FACES!
HERE'S A NICE ONE HANGIN'.
COME ON. COME AND GET IT.
-COME AND TRY TO BITE IT OFF!
- THAT'S IT. WHIP IT OUT.
THAT'LL BRING 'EM ON.
FUCKIN' "A."
BIGGEST PIECE OF MEAT
IN THE CAVE.
I DON'T WANNA
EXCITE THE LADY THOUGH.
NOT WITH HER BOYFRIEND AROUND.
YOU'RE INCAPABLE
OF EXCITING ME, STEEL, EXCEPT
AS AN ANTHROPOLOGICAL CURIOSITY.
- WHAT THE HELL'S
THAT MEAN, RICKLES?
- IT MEANS YOU'RE A CAVEMAN.
YOU'RE A FUCKIN' THROWBACK.
YOU'VE BEEN SPENDIN'
TOO MUCH TIME UNDERGROUND, HUH?
IT'S OKAY, STEEL.
THROWBACKS ALL GOT BIG DICKS.
OH!
[ Laughs Hysterically ]
ALL RIGHT, YOU DUMB FUCKS!
GET OVER HERE, YOU SCUMBAGS!
YOUR OLD PAL STEEL
WANTS TO SEE YA.
[ Growls ]
- SHIT.
- I'M COMING UP.
YOU'RE NOT STRONG ENOUGH
FOR UP HERE. SEND UP THE POLE.
I'LL WATCH OUT FOR LOVER BOY.
DON'T WORRY.
I'M NOT STRONG ENOUGH? I'VE
DONE IT DOZENS OF TIMES.
I DON'T WANT YOU UP HERE, LADY.
SEND UP THE POLE.
THEY'RE GETTIN' CLOSER.
HE'S CLAMPING.
LOOK AT 'IM.
LET GO OF THE POLE.
LISTEN TO ME.
LET GO OF THE GODDAMN POLE.
- HERE THEY COME! LET'S GO!
-[ Moaning Continues ]
DUMB FUCKS.
PUS-BREEDING BAGS OF SHIT.
YOU DUMB-FUCKING BAGS OF SHIT,
I'LL KICK YOUR FUCKIN' ASSES.
COME ON!
- [ All Growling, Moaning ]
- [ Laughing Mockingly ]
COME HERE, SCUMBAG.
[ Continues Laughing ]
[ Growling ]
[ Steel ]
HOOK HER UP, WILL YA? HOOK HER.
[ Growling ]
HEY, NICE HAT,
ASSHOLE.
[ Screeching ]
COME ON!
GET THE OTHER ONE OUT
OF THERE!
[ Zombie Grunting,
Screeching ]
[ Continues Grunting ]
-[ Steel Shouting,
Indistinct ]
- [ Screaming ]
STEEL, STEEL, STEEL,
COVER! COVER!
-[ Steel ]
I GOT IT.
- GEEZ.
THAT'S IT. THAT'S IT.
THAT'S IT. I GOT IT.
I GOT IT. COME ON.
COME ON. COME HERE.
COME HERE.
[ Zombie Continues Growling ]
YOU ALMOST KILLED RICKLES.
YEAH. YOU ALMOST KILLED RICKLES.
- [ Screaming ]
-LET 'IM GO, STEEL.
- HE SHOULDN'T HAVE BEEN
UP THERE IN THE FIRST PLACE.
- [ Yelling, Indistinct ]
STEEL, STOP IT!
[ Continues Roaring ]
YOU DIRTY SON OF A BITCH!
LET HIM GO!
LET HIM GO,
GODDAMN IT,
OR I'LL CUT YOU IN HALF.
[ Growling ]
[ All Yelling, Indistinct ]
SHUT UP, YOU DUMB FUCKS.
I HOPE THEY CHOP YOU UP
FOR DOG MEAT.
COME ON, RICKLES.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
I HOPE YOU FUCKIN' ROT!
FUCK YOU!
[ Groaning,
Whimpering ]
I AM NOT GONNA LET YOU
DOPE ME UP.
YOU NEED A SEDATIVE.
YOU'RE BEHAVING
DANGEROUSLY.
- I'M JUST TRYING
TO HELP YOU, MIGUEL.
- WELL, I DON'T NEED YOUR HELP.
YOU MADE ME LOOK
LIKE AN ASSHOLE
OUT THERE.
YOU MADE ME FEEL
LIKE A PIECE OF SHIT.
YOU STAY AWAY FROM ME
WITH THAT, SARAH.
- YOU STAY AWAY FROM ME.
- [ Gasping ]
OHH.
[ Crying ]
[ Shrieks ]
[ Gasping ]
YOU BITCH.
[ Groans, Sobs ]
WE'VE GOT TO HAVE
STERILE CONDITIONS.
HALF THE WORK WE DO...
GOES DOWN THE TOILET
DUE TO CONTAMINATION.
YOU'LL WORK WITH
WHAT YOU GOT, FISHER.
BUT IT'S MADNESS!
- CAN'T YOU UNDERSTAND--
- I UNDERSTAND THIS:
YOU AND YOUR PLAYMATES,
YOU'RE RUNNING OUT OF FRIENDS
FAST AROUND HERE.
[ Sighs ]
LOOK, MAJOR COOPER
PROMISED THAT--
MAJOR COOPER IS DEAD.
I'M IN COMMAND NOW,
AND I'M TELLING YOU...
THAT YOU WORK
WITH WHAT YOU GOT.
AND YOU'D BETTER
START SHOWING ME SOME RESULTS...
OR YOU WON'T HAVE THAT
VERY MUCH LONGER.
HOW CAN WE SHOW YOU RESULTS
WHEN WE DON'T HAVE
THE PROPER WORKING CONDITIONS?
WE'RE IN
A DESPERATE SITUATION HERE.
WE NEED EACH OTHER.
CAN'T WE JUST GET ALONG?
[ Man ] YOU NEED US,
THE WAY I SEE IT, LADY.
I'M NOT SURE WE NEED YOU AT ALL.
[ Steel ]
FUCKIN' "A."
I'M NOT EVEN SURE
WHAT THE HELL IT IS
YOU'RE DOIN' IN THERE,
JUST WHAT THE HELL MY MEN
ARE RISKIN' THEIR ASSES FOR.
IF THERE WAS MORE COOPERATION,
YOUR MEN WOULDN'T HAVE TO
RISK THEIR ASSES AS OFTEN.
[ Rifle Cocks ]
- MIGUEL SALAZAR'S
IN BAD SHAPE.
- [ Chuckles ] NO SHIT.
I WANT HIM PULLED OFF
ACTIVE DUTY FOR A WHILE UNTIL
WE CAN EVALUATE HIS CONDITION.
- CAN'T SPARE 'IM.
-HE'S OVER THE EDGE.
HE'S TURNING INTO JELL-O.
-JELL-O?
- THAT'S THE WAY THE SPICKS
SAY "YELLOW": JELL-O!
MIGUEL IS SERIOUSLY
DISTURBED. HE'S CLOSE
TO THE BREAKING POINT,
AND THAT'S DANGEROUS
FOR ALL OF US.
HE CAN'T HANDLE
ANY MORE STRESS RIGHT NOW.
WELL, MAYBE I SHOULD CUT OFF
HIS EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES.
MAYBE YOU'RE
KEEPIN' HIM TOO BUSY AT NIGHT.
WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT A MAN'S LIFE HERE,
YOU SON OF A BITCH,
AND THE LIVES OF OTHERS
HE MIGHT PUT IN JEOPARDY.
MAYBE I SHOULD
PUT HIM IN QUARANTINE.
HOW 'BOUT IT, STEEL?
YOU CALL IT, CAPTAIN.
I'LL BUILD HIM A CAGE.
[ Captain ]
YEAH. MIGHT NOT
BE A BAD IDEA--
GIVE SOME OF THE REST
OF US A SHOT AT SOME LOVIN'.
[ Steel ]
HEY, IT'S GONNA
BE A LONG WINTER.
COME ON, TED.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
[ Captain ]
I'M CALLIN' A MEETING
FOR 7:00 TONIGHT.
I WANT EVERYBODY PRESENT.
EVERYBODY,LADY,
INCLUDING DR. FRANKENSTEIN
AND INCLUDING YOUR BOYFRIEND.
- I GAVE HIM A SEDATIVE.
HE WON'T BE AWAKE.
- LOOK HERE, WOMAN.
I'M SHORT ON MAN POWER.
I WON'T HAVE YOU GOIN' AROUND...
DOPIN' UP ANY OF MY MEN
WITHOUT ORDERS FROM ME.
- IS THAT CLEAR?
- YES, SIR!
FUCK YOU, SIR!
[ Door Slams ]
OUT OF THE FRYING PAN,
INTO THE FIRE.
I THOUGHT COOPER WAS AN ASSHOLE,
BUT HE WAS A SWEETHEART
NEXT TO RHODES.
WE COULD BE IN REAL TROUBLE.
YOU'D BETTER WATCH YOURSELF-- I
MEAN, PHYSICALLY WATCH YOURSELF.
I CAN HANDLE IT.
DON'T WORRY. IT'S NOT
GOING TO COME TO THAT.
WE'VE JUST GOTTA POUND
SOME LOGIC INTO THEIR HEADS.
IMPOSSIBLE.
[ Sighs ]
WHERE'S DR. LOGAN?
FRANKENSTEIN?
HE'S IN HIS LABORATORY.
WHERE ELSE?
[ Man ] THERE'S A LOSS
OF INITIATIVE, CAUTION, MANY OF
THE HUMAN COGNITIVE FUNCTIONS.
APPARENTLY THE RESULT
OF DECAY IN THE FRONTAL,
PARIETAL,
TEMPORAL
AND OCCIPITAL LOBES.
ON REVIVAL,
THE RATE OF DECOMPOSITION
SLOWS SUBSTANTIALLY.
[ Switch Clicks ]
INDICATIONS ARE
THAT THESE BEINGS...
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
COULD FUNCTION
OVER A PERIOD OF YEARS--
IN CASES OF EARLY REVIVAL,
10 TO 12 YEARS BEFORE DECAY
WOULD THREATEN MOBILITY.
- [ Screams ]
-[ Growls ]
[ Moaning ]
THE BRAIN IS THE ENGINE, SARAH,
THE MOTOR THAT DRIVES THEM.
THEY DON'T NEED ANY BLOOD FLOW,
DON'T NEED ANY
OF THEIR INTERNAL ORGANS.
NOW, I'VE SEVERED ALL
THE VITAL ORGANS IN THIS ONE.
THERE'S NOTHING LEFT
OF THE CORPSE BUT BRAIN AND
LIMBS, AND STILL IT FUNCTIONS.
OH, LOOK, SARAH. LOOK.
[ Grunting ]
SEE, IT WANTS ME.
IT WANTS FOOD,
BUT IT HAS NO STOMACH.
IT CAN TAKE NO NOURISHMENT
FROM WHAT IT INGESTS.
IT'S WORKING ON INSTINCT,
A DEEP, DARK,
PRIMORDIAL INSTINCT.
DECOMPOSITION OCCURS
FIRST IN THE FRONTAL LOBES,
THE NEOCORTEX,
AND NEXT
IN THE LIMBIC SYSTEM,
THE MIDDLE BRAIN.
BUT THE CORE-- THE CORE
IS THE LAST THING TO BE
ATTACKED BY THE DECAY.
IT'S THE "R" COMPLEX, SARAH--
THAT CENTRAL BIT OF
PREHISTORIC JELLY...
THAT WE INHERITED
FROM THE REPTILES.
HERE. I'VE GONE INTO THE CENTER
HERE AND ATTACKED THE
"R" COMPLEX DISCRETELY.
I'VE REMOVED IT
FROM THE EQUATION--
THIS CORPSE.
I BELIEVE THIS CREATURE WOULD BE
BENIGN EVEN IF IT HAD ITS
EYESIGHT AND ITS OTHER SENSES.
ITS PRIMITIVE INSTINCTS
HAVE BEEN ERASED.
[ Machine Whirring ]
IT STILL HAS MOTOR FUNCTION,
PROBABLY STILL HAS POWERS
OF DELIBERATION.
IT CAN BE DOMESTICATED,
SARAH, DON'T YOU SEE?
IT CAN BE CONDITIONED
TO BEHAVE THE WAY
WE WANT IT TO BEHAVE.
AND ALL THAT'S REQUIRED
IS 15 HOURS OF FANCY SURGERY...
THAT ONLY A HANDFUL OF PEOPLE
ARE TRAINED TO DO.
WE WERE GOING TO STOP WORK ON
THE NEUROPHYSICAL, CONCENTRATE
ON SOMETHING MORE PRACTICAL.
THESE FINDS ARE CENTRAL TO
THE CONDITION. I WILL
NOT STOP WORK...
THAT MIGHT LEAD TO AN ANSWER,
LET ALONE IN AN AREA THAT IS
CENTRAL TO THE CONDITION.
[ Exhales Forcefully ]
BUT YOU'RE JUST PROVING THEORIES
THAT WERE ADVANCED MONTHS AGO.
AND YOU'RE NOT EVEN
PROVING THEM CORRECTLY. YOU'RE
MAKING A LOT OF ASSUMPTIONS.
YOU'RE WASTING TIME TRYING
TO DEFINE WHAT'S HAPPENING...
INSTEAD OF LOOKING
FOR WHAT'S MAKING IT HAPPEN.
AND JUST SLICING UP
TOO MANY SPECIMENS.
IT'S EXTREMELY DANGEROUS...
TO GO UP ON TOP
AND ROUND THEM UP IN THE WILD.
WELL, WE CAN'T CONTROL THEM.
WHAT HAPPENED TO THIS ONE?
[ Doctor ] IT WAS TOO UNRULY.
I COULDN'T HANDLE IT.
I HAD TO DESTROY IT.
- WE CAN STILL
GET INFORMATION FROM IT.
- DR. LOGAN,
WE ARE LOSING
THE COOPERATION OF THE MEN.
I'M NOT EVEN SURE THEY'LL
GO UP TOP WHEN WE RUN OUT
OF THE SPECIMENS WE HAVE.
I'M NOT SURE THEY WON'T
JUST TRY TO SHUT US DOWN
COMPLETELY.
WELL, I'LL SHOW THEM RESULTS.
I'LL SHOW THEM RESULTS.
I'LL SHOW THEM THAT THESE
CREATURES CAN BE DOMESTICATED
EVEN WITHOUT THE SURGERY.
KNOWING WHAT THEY ARE, WE CAN
BEGIN TO APPROACH THEM PROPERLY,
CONDITION THEM,
CONTROL THEM.
WE'VE GOT TO DO THIS, SARAH.
IT'S OUR ONLY HOPE.
YES, THIS IS MAJOR COOPER.
I NEEDED HIM, SARAH.
HE'S HELPING US MORE NOW THAN
HE EVER DID WHEN HE WAS ALIVE.
- BUT I SAW THE GRAVE.
- THEY BURIED ONE
OF THE SPECIMENS.
JESUS. GOD, LOGAN.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT
THEY'LL DO TO YOU
IF THEY FIND OUT ABOUT THIS?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- DO YOU KNOW WHAT THEY'LL DO
TO ALL OF US?
- THEY'LL NEVER FIND OUT.
HE CAN'T BE RECOGNIZED.
[ Moaning ]
[ Gasping ]
NOT A PEEP. LONG-RANGE OR SHORT,
HIGH-BAND OR LOW, I CAN'T
RAISE ANYBODY.
[ Man ] HOW CAN THAT BE,
McDERMOTT? THERE MUST BE
OTHER GROUPS LIKE US.
SOMEBODY ELSE MUST BE TRYIN'
TO RADIO.
YEAH. WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
MAYBE WE ARE THE ONLY ONES LEFT.
I'M SURE THERE'S OTHERS.
THIS IS NOT THE BEST PLACE
TO BE SENDING FROM, AND A LOT
OF THE EQUIPMENT I'M USING...
HAS BEEN ROTTING DOWN HERE
SINCE THE SECOND WORLD WAR.
WELL, IT'S UP TO YOU
TO GET IT WORKIN' RIGHT.
LAY OFF THE FUCKIN' BOOZE
FOR A WHILE, WHY DON'T YA?
AND GET SOMEBODY
ON THAT FUCKIN' HORN, PRONTO.
WELL, IF WE STAY DOWN HERE
LONG ENOUGH, I'LL HAVE TO LAY
OFF THE FUCKIN' BOOZE, STEEL,
'CAUSE THERE WON'T FUCKIN'
BE ANY OF IT FUCKIN' LEFT.
IN THE MEANWHILE, I WILL
CONTINUE TO INDULGE MYSELF, AND
I WILL CONTINUE DOING MY BEST...
IN THE GOOD FIGHT
AGAINST DRY ROT AND RUST.
YEAH? WELL, YOUR BEST
AIN'T GOOD ENOUGH, ASSHOLE.
YOU THINK I'M NOT AWARE
OF OUR SITUATION? YOU THINK I
WANT TO STAY ISOLATED DOWN HERE?
YOU KNOW, I'D MAKE A DESPERATE
EFFORT TO RAISE SOMEBODY...
JUST IN THE HOPE OF GETTIN' AWAY
FROM YOUR NASTY MOUTH, STEEL.
THE FACT IS--
THE FACT IS...
EITHER WE ARE
THE ONLY ONES LEFT...
OR THERE'S NOBODY WITHIN RANGE
OF MY PUNY LITTLE
SECOND WORLD WAR SIGNALS.
WE USED TO TALK TO WASHINGTON
ALL THE TIME. THEY COULD
HEAR US THEN.
WE WERE ON RELAYS THEN.
WE WEREN'T OVER THE AIR.
YOU KNOW, THE POWER'S OFF
ON THE MAINLAND NOW, IN CASE
YOU HAVEN'T HEARD.
ALL THE SHOPPING MALLS
ARE CLOSED.
WE DON'T APPRECIATE YOUR JOKES.
KEEP IT UP, AND I'LL SHOVE
THAT BOTTLE OF YOURS RIGHT
UP YOUR WISE ASS.
I'VE GOT BETTER THINGS
TO DO THAN LISTEN TO THIS
KINDERGARTEN. ARE WE FINISHED?
NO, WE AIN'T
FINISHED HERE, LADY. SIT DOWN.
WHAT ELSE DO YOU WANT?
WE'VE GIVEN YOU THE REPORTS
FOR THIS WEEK.
WE'VE GIVEN YOU EVERYTHING
YOU'VE ASKED FOR.
YOU'VE GIVEN US GREEK SALAD.
FORMULAS, EQUATIONS,
A LOT OF FANCY TERMS
THAT DON'T MEAN A THING.
I WANNA KNOW IF YOU'RE DOIN'
SOMETHING THAT'S GONNA HELP US
OUT OF THIS DEEP SHIT WE'RE IN,
OR IF YOU'RE ALL IN THERE
JUST JERKIN' EACH OTHER OFF.
SHE DOESN'T HAVE TO JERK OFF
LIKE THE REST OF US, CAPTAIN.
SHE GOT AN HONEST-TO-GOD DICK...
TO GET OFF ON, HUH?
[ Laughs Mockingly ]
IT MAY BE YELLOW,
BUT IT'S STILL A DICK!
[ Yells, Laughs ]
[ Others Laugh ]
I SAID WE AIN'T
FINISHED HERE, LADY.
SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN, OR SO HELP ME,
GOD, I'LL HAVE YOU SHOT.
- YOU'LL WHAT?
- I SAID,
"I'LL HAVE YOU SHOT."
HAVE YOU LOST YOUR MIND?
NO, MA'AM.
HAVE YOU? I JUST TOLD YOU I WAS
WILLING TO KILL YOU IF YOU
DIDN'T GET BACK IN YOUR CHAIR.
YOU DIDN'T GET BACK
IN YOUR CHAIR.
GODDAMN IT!
YOU CAN'T SHOVE US AROUND
LIKE THIS.
SINCE WHEN DID THIS
BECOME A MILITARY OPERATION?
SINCE I TOOK OVER.
STEEL, SHOOT THAT WOMAN.
BANG! YOU'RE DEAD.
SHOOT THAT WOMAN
OR YOU'RE DEAD.
YOU THINK
I'M FUCKIN' AROUND, STEEL?
YOU'RE WRONG.
NOW, YOU GOT TILL A COUNT
OF FIVE, AND THAT'S TWO
YOU WASTED.
- [ Spits ]
- THAT'S THREE.
- FOUR.
- SIT DOWN, SARAH.
WHAT IS THIS?
SHUT UP AND SIT DOWN.
THAT'S FIVE, STEEL.
[ Gun Cocks ]
ALL RIGHT.
- [ Gun Cocks ]
- NO!
ANYBODY ELSE HAVE ANY QUESTIONS
ABOUT THE WAY THINGS ARE GONNA
RUN AROUND HERE FROM NOW ON?
THIS AIN'T
A GODDAMN FIELD TRIP, PEOPLE.
THIS IS A FUCKIN' WAR!
I'M NOT DOWN IN THIS CAVE
FOR MY HEALTH. I'M DOWN HERE
ON ORDERS.
YOUR ORDERS ARE TO FACILITATE
THE JOB OF THIS SCIENTIFIC TEAM.
THIS IS A CIVILIAN TEAM,
AND WE DON'T HAVE TO BE
SUBJECTED TO YOUR TYRANNY.
WHO'S BEING SUBJECTED
TO WHAT, FISHER?
YOU'VE LOST ONE MAN.
[ Men ]
YEAH. RIGHT.
WE'VE LOST FIVE.
[ Men Murmuring Agreement ]
WHERE DOES IT SAY WE GOTTA
KEEP THOSE DUMB FUCKS NEXT DOOR
TO WHERE WE SLEEP?
WHERE DOES IT SAY WE SHOULD
DO ANY ONE THING BUT SHOOT
THE MOTHERS IN THE HEAD?
[ Logan ]
WE DON'T HAVE ENOUGH AMMUNITION
TO SHOOT THEM ALL IN THE HEAD.
THE TIME TO HAVE DONE THAT
WOULD'VE BEEN AT THE BEGINNING.
NO. WE LET THEM OVERRUN US.
THEY HAVE OVERRUN US, YOU KNOW.
WE'RE IN THE MINORITY NOW.
SOMETHING LIKE 400,000
TO ONE, BY MY CALCULATIONS.
I HAVEN'T EATEN.
IS THERE FOOD?
YOU WERE SUPPOSED
TO BE HERE AT 7:00 SHARP,
MISTER.
I KNOW. SARAH TOLD ME.
I'M SORRY. I COULDN'T
BREAK AWAY. IS THERE FOOD?
LISTEN, EGGHEAD, LET ME
BRING YOU UP TO DATE ON WHAT'S--
EXCUSE ME.
LET ME--
EXCUSE ME!
- IS THERE FOOD?
- I'M RUNNIN' THIS MONKEY FARM
NOW, FRANKENSTEIN,
AND I WANNA KNOW WHAT THE FUCK
YOU'RE DOIN' WITH MY TIME!
'CAUSE IF WE'RE JUST
JERKIN' OFF HERE,
I'M GONNA HAVE MY MEN
BLOW THE PISS...
OUT OF THOSE PRECIOUS SPECIMENS
OF YOURS,
[ Men Murmuring Agreement ]
AND WE'RE GONNA GET THE HELL OUT
OF HERE AND LEAVE YOU AND YOUR
HIGHFALUTIN ASSHOLE FRIENDS...
TO ROT
IN THIS STINKIN' SEWER!
IS THAT FOOD ENOUGH FOR YA?
WHERE WILL YOU GO, CAPTAIN?
YOU CAN DESTROY MY SPECIMENS,
BUT WHAT ABOUT THE MILLIONS MORE
THAT ARE WAITING TO GREET YOU
OUTSIDE?
DO YOU REALLY THINK
YOU CAN "BLOW THE PISS"
OUT OF THEM?
ALL OF THEM? THEY HAVE YOU
IN A HOPELESS SITUATION,
STRATEGICALLY.
YOU'RE LOST. WELL,
YOU'RE LOST UNLESS--
UNLESS WHAT?
UNLESS WHAT,
FRANKENSTEIN?
- UNLESS YOU CAN
MAKE THEM BEHAVE.
-[ Men Scoffing ]
THIS IS A FUCKIN' LOONY BIN!
I AIN'T BEIN' PAID ENOUGH TO
WORK IN A FUCKIN' LOONY BIN!
- I AIN'T BEIN' PAID AT ALL!
- PAID? WHAT THE HELL ARE THEY
PAYIN' HIM FOR?
[ Captain ]
ALL RIGHT. SHUT UP!
JUST SHUT UP!
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU
TALKIN' ABOUT, FRANKENSTEIN?
I'LL BE ABLE TO
SHOW YOU SOON ENOUGH.
SARAH KNOWS.
SHE'S SEEN THE PROGRESS
I'VE BEEN MAKING.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, SARAH?
YES. THERE'S BEEN SOME PROGRESS.
WHAT KIND OF PROGRESS?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKIN' ABOUT,
"MAKE THEM BEHAVE"?
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
IT MEANS KEEPING THEM
FROM WANTING TO EAT US,
FOR ONE THING.
IT MEANS
KEEPING THEM IN CHECK,
CONTROLLING THEM.
- CONTROLLING THEM.
- WHEN ARE YOU GONNA SHOW US
SOMETHING WE CAN UNDERSTAND?
VERY CLOSE. VERY CLOSE.
I THINK IN A MATTER OF WEEKS--
I DON'T THINK THERE'S ANY WAY
YOU CAN TELL HOW LONG ANYTHING
IS GOING TO TAKE.
IT COULD BE MONTHS;
IT COULD BE YEARS BEFORE WE KNOW
EXACTLY WHAT WE'RE DEALING WITH.
[ Men Murmuring ]
SARAH'S RESEARCH--
[ Louder ] SARAH'S RESEARCH
IS MORE ESOTERIC THAN MINE.
[ Murmuring Stops ]
SHE'S LOOKING FOR A WAY
TO REVERSE THE PROCESS,
A WAY TO ERADICATE THE PROBLEM.
THAT COULD TAKE A LONG TIME,
A VERY LONG TIME.
SHE MAY NEVER FIND
WHAT SHE'S LOOKING FOR.
WE HAVE A LIMITED SUPPLY
OF CHEMICAL AGENTS.
OUR EQUIPMENT
IS HOPELESSLY INADEQUATE.
McDERMOTT DOESN'T
HAVE DECENT RADIO GEAR.
NOW YOU'RE TELLIN' ME
THAT YOU DON'T
HAVE THE SHIT YOU NEED?
WE'RE RUNNIN' LOW ON AMMUNITION.
WE'RE RUNNIN' LOW ON MEN,
FOR CHRISSAKES!
IT WAS VERY RUSHED.
THIS OPERATION WAS PUT TOGETHER
IN A MATTER OF DAYS.
YEAH, WELL, IT CAN ALL
BE TAKEN APART IN A MATTER
OF MINUTES, LADY,
AND I'M HERE TO TELL YOU
THAT I'M READY TO
DO THAT LITTLE THING.
I'M READY TO
TAKE THE NEXT TRAIN OUTTA HERE!
[ Logan ]
I ASK YOU AGAIN, CAPTAIN:
WHERE WILL YOU GO?
YOU HAVE NO CHOICES.
YOU'LL HAVE TO GIVE US THE WEEKS
THAT WE'VE ASKED FOR.
YOU HAVE TO GIVE US
HOWEVER LONG IT TAKES.
LOOK.
THERE HAVE TO BE SURVIVORS
IN WASHINGTON.
[ Man ] MY ASS.
THEY HAVE MORE SOPHISTICATED
SHELTERS THAN THIS ONE.
[ Man ] BULLSHIT.
THERE HAVE TO BE PEOPLE
IN THOSE SHELTERS WHO KNOW
ABOUT US, WHO KNOW WHERE WE ARE.
WITH NO RADIO CONTACT,
THEY'LL COME LOOKING FOR US.
-[ Men Murmuring ]
- I SAID SHUT UP!
YOU GOT
A LITTLE MORE TIME.
A LITTLE MORE.
I AIN'T SAYIN' HOW MUCH.
BUT YOU'D BETTER START
SHOWIN' ME SOME RESULTS, AND
YOU'D BETTER NOT PISS ME OFF.
YOU UNDERSTAND?
NOTHIN' HAPPENS AROUND HERE
WITHOUT MY KNOWIN' ABOUT IT!
AND ANYBODY FUCKS
WITH MY COMMAND,
THEY GET COURT-MARTIALED,
THEY GET EXECUTED.
YOU'D BETTER KNOW
I MEAN IT, TOO, PEOPLE.
[ Men Murmuring ]
HE WOULDN'T HAVE DONE IT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HE WOULD'VE.
NO, HE WOULDN'T
HAVE DONE IT.
- HE WOULD'VE HAD STEEL DO IT.
- HE CAN'T BE THAT INHUMAN.
NO. HE'S HUMAN.
THAT'S WHAT SCARES ME,
YOU KNOW.
HE WON'T SHOOT BILLY 'CAUSE
HE DOESN'T HAVE ANYBODY ELSE
WHO KNOWS ELECTRONICS.
HE WON'T SHOOT ME,
'CAUSE I'M HIS RIDE.
HE PROBABLY WON'T
SHOOT OLD FRANKENSTEIN, 'CAUSE
THE OLD DOC CAN TALK HIM SILLY.
BUT THE REST OF YOU...
BETTER START WORRYING,
YOU KNOW.
MAYBE IF WE TRIED
WORKING TOGETHER, WE COULD
EASE SOME OF THE TENSIONS.
- WE'RE ALL PULLING
IN DIFFERENT DIRECTIONS.
- THAT'S THE TROUBLE, SARAH.
PEOPLE GOT DIFFERENT IDEAS
CONCERNING WHAT THEY WANT
OUT OF LIFE.
[ Gasps ]
YOU ARE AFRAID,
AREN'T YOU?
JUST AS AFRAID AS I AM.
WHY DON'T YOU TAKE A SEDATIVE,
SARAH, SO YOU CAN SLEEP?
YOU'RE FULL OF SHIT,
SARAH, YOU KNOW THAT?
YOU'RE REALLY FULL OF SHIT.
I'M THROUGH WITH YOU.
FINE THEN. GET OUT.
JUST GET OUT!
[ Clattering ]
[ Growling ]
[ Growling Continues ]
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
[ Clattering ]
- HEY, GUYS!
COME ON, MAN!
-[ Sarah ] FOR GOODNESS SAKE!
[ Men Grunting, Muttering ]
I'M ALL RIGHT.
THANKS, BILL.
HERE.
I'VE JUST FILLED IT UP.
GOT A REFILL AS WELL.
NO, THANKS.
I'M ALL RIGHT. REALLY.
IT'S JUST BRANDY.
GOOD FOR THE HEART.
IT'S SHIT FOR YOUR HEART,
AND IT EATS UP YOUR LIVER.
[ Coughs ]
WE DON'T GET A LOT
OF VISITORS OUT HERE,
AND WE LIKE IT THAT WAY.
HERE IT IS: THE RITZ.
MADAM.
JOHN'S PROBABLY
OUT THE BACK.
HEY! WELL,
WHAT DO YOU KNOW.
WELCOME
TO CIVILIZATION, SARAH.
THE LAST HOLDOUT.
IT'S PRETTY NICE.
NICER THAN WE GOT INSIDE.
- NOT A BAD IDEA.
- IT'S A LITTLE SAFER
WHERE YOU ARE.
BUT WE LIKE
TO LIVE DANGEROUSLY,
BILLY BOY AND ME, YOU KNOW.
THAT'S A LAUGH. I HAVEN'T
SEEN YOU DO ANYTHING DANGEROUS
SINCE WE GOT HERE.
WE STICKIN' AROUND.
THAT'S GETTIN' A BIT DANGEROUS,
AS I HOPE YOU NOTICED
THIS EVENING.
YOU'RE A MYSTERY TO ME.
YOU REALLY ARE.
NOT LIKE
THOSE OTHER GOONS IN THERE.
YOU HAVE A SENSE OF--
[ Scoffs ]
OF WHAT?
[ Chuckles ]
NEVER MIND.
NO, NO, NO.
COME ON. LET'S
TALK ABOUT IT.
I CAME DOWN HERE
TO GET DRUNK.
I DON'T HAVE THE ENERGY.
HEY, HEY. IT TAKES MORE ENERGY
TO KEEP QUIET THAN IT DOES
TO SPEAK THE MIND.
GO AHEAD.
LET GO OF WHAT
YOU GOT, NOW.
YOU WERE SENT DOWN HERE
TO DO A JOB.
MY JOB IS TO FLY THE WHIRLYBIRD.
I'VE BEEN DOIN' THAT JOB
JUST FINE.
YOU HAVE THE PROTECTION
OF THIS FACILITY. YOU EAT
OUR FOOD. YOU DRINK OUR WATER.
AND YOU DON'T
LIFT A FINGER TO HELP.
NEITHER ONE OF YOU.
[ John Laughing ]
WE DON'T BELIEVE
IN WHAT YOU'RE DOIN' HERE,
SARAH.
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT ALL
THEY KEEP DOWN HERE
IN THIS CAVE?
MAN, THEY GOT THE BOOKS
AND THE RECORDS OF
THE TOP 500 COMPANIES.
THEY GOT THE DEFENSE DEPARTMENT
BUDGET DOWN HERE.
AND THEY GOT THE NEGATIVE
FOR ALL YOUR FAVORITE MOVIES.
THEY GOT MICROFILM
WITH TAX RETURN
AND NEWSPAPER STORIES.
THEY GOT IMMIGRATION RECORDS,
CENSUS REPORTS,
AND THEY GOT OFFICIAL ACCOUNTS
OF ALL THE WARS
AND PLANE CRASHES...
AND VOLCANO ERUPTIONS
AND EARTHQUAKES AND FIRES
AND FLOODS--
AND ALL THE OTHER DISASTERS
THAT INTERRUPTED THE FLOW
OF THINGS...
IN THE GOOD OLD U.S. OF A.
NOW, WHAT DOES IT MATTER,
SARAH DARLING?
ALL THIS FILING
AND RECORD KEEPING?
WE EVER GONNA GIVE A SHIT?
WE EVEN GONNA GET A CHANCE
TO SEE IT ALL?
THIS IS A GREAT BIG
14-MILE TOMBSTONE!
[ Voice Echoing ]
TOMBSTONE!
[ Distant Moaning ]
WITH AN EPITAPH ON IT
THAT NOBODY GONNA BOTHER
TO READ.
NOW, HERE YOU COME--
HERE YOU COME WITH
A WHOLE NEW SET OF CHARTS...
AND GRAPHS AND RECORDS.
WHAT YOU GONNA DO?
BURY THEM DOWN HERE
WITH ALL THE OTHER RELICS...
OF WHAT ONCE WAS?
LET ME TELL YOU WHAT ELSE.
YEAH, I'M GONNA TELL YOU
WHAT ELSE.
YOU AIN'T NEVER GONNA
FIGURE IT OUT, JUST LIKE THEY
NEVER FIGURED OUT...
WHY THE STARS
ARE WHERE THEY'RE AT.
IT AIN'T MANKIND'S JOB
TO FIGURE THAT STUFF OUT.
SO WHAT YOU'RE DOIN'
IS A WASTE OF TIME, SARAH.
AND TIME IS ALL
WE GOT LEFT, YOU KNOW.
WHAT I'M DOING...
IS ALL THERE'S LEFT TO DO.
SHAME ON YOU.
THERE'S PLENTY TO DO.
PLENTY TO DO. SO LONG AS
THERE'S YOU AND ME AND MAYBE
SOME OTHER PEOPLE,
WE COULD START OVER,
START FRESH,
GET SOME BABIES.
AND TEACH 'EM, SARAH,
TEACH 'EM NEVER TO COME
OVER HERE...
- AND DIG THESE RECORDS OUT.
-[ Distant Moaning ]
HEY.
YOU WANT TO PUT SOME KIND
OF EXPLANATION...
DOWN HERE
BEFORE YOU LEAVE?
HERE'S ONE AS GOOD
AS ANY YOU'RE LIKELY
TO FIND.
WE'RE BEING PUNISHED
BY THE CREATOR.
HE VISITED A CURSE
ON US...
SO WE MAN COULD LOOK AT...
WHAT HELL WAS LIKE.
MAYBE DIDN'T WANT TO SEE US
BLOW OURSELVES UP...
AND PUT A BIG HOLE
IN HIS SKY.
MAYBE HE JUST WANTED
TO SHOW US HE WAS STILL
THE BOSS MAN.
MAYBE HE FIGURE...
WE WAS GETTING TOO BIG
FOR OUR BRITCHES...
TRYING TO
FIGURE HIS SHIT OUT.
[ Growling ]
[ Fisher ]
YOU SON OF A BITCH!
[ Continues Growling ]
[ Fisher ]
DAMN IT!
IT'S NO GOOD.
IT'S NO FUCKIN' GOOD.
WHAT IS THAT STUFF?
IT'S SOMETHING
CALLED BEEF TREATS, WHICH
THE ARMY PROVIDES US WITH...
SO GENEROUSLY.
- HE WON'T TOUCH IT.
- SHIT. I WOULDN'T EITHER.
SORRY. WE'RE FRESH OUT
OF FILET MIGNON.
-[ Groaning Continues ]
- WHAT IS THIS?
PART OF LOGAN'S PLAN...
TO TRY
AND SOCIALIZE THESE THINGS?
HE TOLD ME HIMSELF
THEY DON'T EAT FOR NOURISHMENT.
WHAT ARE WE HOPING FOR HERE?
HOPING TO SATISFY THE URGE.
YOU SEE, SARAH, THEY'RE--
THEY ARE US.
THEY ARE THE EXTENSIONS
OF US.
THEY ARE THE SAME ANIMAL,
SIMPLY FUNCTIONING
LESS PERFECTLY.
THEY CAN BE FOOLED, YOU SEE?
THEY CAN BE TRICKED INTO BEING
GOOD LITTLE GIRLS AND BOYS,
THE SAME WAY WE WERE TRICKED
INTO IT ON THE PROMISE
OF SOME REWARD TO COME.
[ Moaning ]
THEY HAVE TO BE REWARDED.
REWARD IS THE KEY.
I'M CONVINCED OF THAT NOW.
COME. I'VE GOT SOMETHING
TO SHOW YOU.
THAT WASN'T VERY NICE,
YOU KNOW. THAT WASN'T
VERY NICE AT ALL.
LET'S GO.
AND YOU CAN JUST SIT THERE
IN THE DARK AND THINK
ABOUT WHAT YOU'VE DONE.
THINK ABOUT IT.
THINK.
[ Moaning Over P.A.,
Feedback ]
I CALL HIM BUB.
THAT'S WHAT THE CLUB FELLAS
USED TO CALL MY FATHER. CAN YOU
IMAGINE A SURGEON CALLED BUB?
NOBODY SEEMED TO MIND,
THOUGH. HE WAS RICH.
[ Moaning ]
MY FATHER WAS RICH.
HE USED TO SAY
I'D NEVER BE RICH
DOING PURE RESEARCH.
I'D NEVER BE RICH.
UH, BUB'S BEEN RESPONDING
SO WELL LATELY,
I'VE LET HIM LIVE.
WELL, IS HE ALIVE OR DEAD?
WELL, THAT'S THE QUESTION
THESE DAYS, ISN'T IT?
WELL, LET'S SAY
THAT I LET HIM
CONTINUE TO EXIST.
HELLO, BUB!
[ Both Snickering ]
[ Over P.A. ]
HERE ARE SOME TOYS FOR YOU.
SOME NICE THINGS
FOR YOU TO PLAY WITH.
YOU REMEMBER THEM
FROM BEFORE?
FROM BEFORE.
WELL, HE'S SEEN
THE OTHER THINGS BEFORE,
BUT THE BOOK IS NEW.
LOOK, LOOK, LOOK.
I THOUGHT HE'D DO THAT.
[ Scribbling ]
[ Moaning ]
- OPEN IT UP.
- [ Gasps ]
HE REMEMBERS.
HE REMEMBERS EVERYTHING
THAT HE USED TO.
BUB, I'M VERY PLEASED.
VERY PLEASED.
WHAT'S HE TRYING
TO PROVE?
I SAW ONE OF THOSE THINGS
SITTIN' IN A CAR IN D.C....
TRYIN' TO DRIVE
DOWN INDEPENDENCE AVENUE.
IT DIDN'T MAKE ME
WANNA BE ITS FRIEND.
NO. IT'S AMAZING.
IT'S NOT WHAT THIS ONE DOES,
BUT WHAT HE DOESN'T DO.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
HE DOESN'T GET EXCITED...
AND DOESN'T GET AGITATED
WHEN LOGAN WALKS
IN THE ROOM.
HE DOESN'T
SEE LOGAN AS--
LUNCH.
DINNER.
BREAKFAST.
HAVING FUN?
WHAT'S HE DOIN'
IN THERE?
[ Logan ]
NO NEED FOR THAT, CAPTAIN.
HE'S QUITE DOCILE.
COME IN.
YOU CAN ALL COME IN.
BUB WON'T MIND.
[ Moans ]
EXTRAORDINARY,
ISN'T IT?
THAT'S RIGHT, BUB.
SAY HELLO.
COME ON, CAPTAIN.
GIVE ME A BREAK,
WILL YA?
SAY HELLO
TO YOUR AUNT ALICIA.
SAY, "HELLO, AUNT ALICIA."
"HELLO, AUNT ALICIA."
[ Moaning, Muffled ]
HEL-LO, AUNT ALICIA.
"HELLO."
[ Logan ] APPARENTLY,
HE WAS IN THE MILITARY. RETURN
THE SALUTE AND SEE WHAT HE DOES.
YOU WANT ME TO
SALUTE THAT PILE
OF WALKING PUS?
SALUTE MY ASS.
YOUR IGNORANCE IS EXCEEDED
ONLY BY YOUR CHARM,
CAPTAIN.
HOW ARE WE GOING TO
SET AN EXAMPLE FOR THEM
IF WE BEHAVE BARBARICALLY?
TAKE THE BULLETS OUT,
PLEASE, AND LET ME
HAVE YOUR PISTOL, SARAH.
[ Steel Laughing Hysterically ]
[ Moaning ]
[ Gun Cocks ]
IT'S EMPTY, CAPTAIN.
WE SAW THE BULLETS
COME OUT.
LET'S SEE WHAT HE DOES.
LET'S SEE WHAT BUB DOES
IN THIS SITUATION.
[ Gun Clicks ]
[ Moans ]
JESUS... CHRIST.
WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSED TO DO?
TEACH 'EM TRICKS?
WHAT THE FUCK
IS WRONG WITH YOU PEOPLE?
THEY'RE DEAD!
THEY'RE FUCKING DEAD,
AND YOU WANNA
TEACH 'EM TRICKS?
THEY HAVE TO BE REWARDED,
CAPTAIN. WHY ELSE WILL THEY DO
WHAT WE WANT THEM TO DO?
I DON'T WANT 'EM
TO DO ANYTHING BUT DROP OVER!
YES, WELL, APPARENTLY
THEY'RE NOT INCLINED
TO DO THAT FOR YOU, CAPTAIN.
IS THIS YOUR PROGRESS?
IS THIS THE SHIT
THAT'S SUPPOSED
TO KNOCK OUR SOCKS OFF?
IT'S THE BEGINNING, YES.
IT'S THE BARE BEGINNING
OF SOCIAL BEHAVIOR.
OF CIVILIZED BEHAVIOR.
CIVIL BEHAVIOR IS WHAT
DISTINGUISHES US FROM
THE LOWER FORMS.
IT'S WHAT ENABLES US
TO COMMUNICATE,
TO GO ABOUT THINGS IN AN ORDERLY
FASHION, WITHOUT ATTACKING
EACH OTHER LIKE BEASTS.
CIVILITY MUST BE REWARDED,
CAPTAIN.
IF IT ISN'T REWARDED,
THERE'S NO USE FOR IT.
THERE'S JUST NO USE
FOR IT AT ALL.
- [ Grunting ]
-[ Zombie Growling ]
[ Growling Continues ]
- 'POSSUM READY?
- [ Growling ]
COME ON. GRAB IT.
COME ON.
YOU GOT IT?
HEY. YOU GOT IT?
[ Growling Continues ]
NO!
NO! NO!
MILLER! MILLER!
- [ Screaming ]
- [ Gunshots ]
I CAN'T DO IT.
I CAN'T DO IT!
- [ Screaming ]
I CAN'T DO IT.
- [ Moaning]
[ Yelling ]
[ Growling ]
[ Screaming ]
-[ Gunshot ]
- [ Continues Screaming ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Departing Footsteps ]
DON'T LET THIS HAPPEN.
DON'T LET THIS HAPPEN TO ME.
I DON'T WANNA BE ONE OF THEM.
TAKE ME. PLEASE. TAKE ME.
[ Gasping ]
[ Gunshot ]
[ Body Thudding ]
[ Bats Screeching ]
[ Miguel Yelps ]
[ Miguel Yelling, Screaming ]
[ Miguel Grunts ]
I NEED FIRE.
[ Screaming ]
[ Men Talking,
Indistinct ]
JESUS, MARY AND JOSEPH!
[ Weapon Cocking ]
[ Panting ]
GET OUT OF THE WAY, LADY.
NO. I AMPUTATED
THE INFECTED AREA.
I THINK I CAUGHT IT IN TIME.
YEAH?
BUT WHAT IF YOU DIDN'T?
IF I DIDN'T,
I'LL SHOOT HIM MYSELF.
IT'S THE SPICK.
THE YELLOW SON OF A BITCH.
IT'S HIS FAULT THIS HAPPENED.
IT'S HIS YELLOW FUCKIN' FAULT.
GET OUT OF THE WAY, BITCH,
OR I'LL GO RIGHT THROUGH YOU
WITH THIS.
WE'RE GETTING TO MAKE THIS
A HABIT, MAN-- POINTING GUNS
AT EACH OTHER, YOU KNOW.
WE JUST LOST TWO MEN
'CAUSE OF THIS MOTHERFUCKER.
WELL... THAT KINDA EVENS
THE ODDS BETWEEN US THEN.
[ Steel ]
THE SPICK'S BEEN BIT, CAPTAIN.
WE GOTTA BLAST HIM.
HE'S BEEN BIT!
I GOT THE INFECTION
IN TIME.
THAT'S BULLSHIT, LADY.
I SEEN A THOUSAND OF 'EM.
HE'S GONNA DIE.
IF HE DIES,
I'LL DESTROY HIM MYSELF.
UNLESS HE GETS YOU FIRST.
YOU MAY STILL WANT TO SLEEP
WITH HIM.
I DON'T WANT HIM
INSIDE THE COMPLEX.
WE'LL KEEP HIM OUT HERE,
WITH US.
WE GOTTA BLAST HIM,
CAPTAIN.
THAT'D BE DOIN' 'IM A FAVOR,
STEEL.
YOU THINK HE WANTS
TO WALK AROUND AFTER HE'S DEAD?
YOU THINK HE WANTS TO BE
ONE OF THOSE THINGS?
THINK ABOUT IT, LADY.
AND THINK ABOUT THIS,
ALL OF YA--
FROM NOW ON,
YOU AIN'T GETTIN' SHIT
FROM ME AND MY MEN.
TOMORROW MORNING,
WE'RE GOING INSIDE THAT CORRAL,
AND WE AIN'T COMIN' OUT...
TILL EVERY ONE OF THOSE
ROTTEN PILES OF GARBAGE
HAS BEEN WASTED.
COME ON, STEEL.
[ Shouting ]
GET OUT OF THERE, STEEL!
WE GOT BETTER THINGS TO DO!
YOU'RE ON MY SHIT LIST,
FLYBOY.
[ Holsters Gun ]
THANK YOU.
LET'S TAKE HIM INSIDE,
CLEAN HIM UP.
THINK YOU CAN MOVE HIM?
I-I THINK SO.
[ Torch Clatters ]
[ Sobbing ]
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
IT'S OKAY.
SHH, SHH, SHH.
SHH, SHH.
- IT'S A MAN'S SWEATER.
TRY IT ON.
- THANKS.
I HAVE TO GO TO THE LAB.
HE'S GOING TO NEED
SOME MORPHINE...
ALONG WITH
SOME OTHER SUPPLIES.
I'D BETTER GO ALONG.
I'M SURE THOSE BOYS HAVEN'T
CALMED THEMSELVES DOWN YET.
I'M SORRY I SAID
THOSE THINGS ABOUT YOU.
I'M SORRY TOO. REALLY.
WELL, WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
WE ARE HEROES AFTER ALL.
WHAT A RELIEF.
SARAH.
HE MIGHT NOT MAKE IT,
YOU KNOW.
I KNOW IT.
AT LEAST WE GAVE HIM
A CHANCE.
I'LL KEEP AN EYE ON HIM.
HEY.
YOU GUYS BE CAREFUL.
YOU'RE NOT BACK IN HALF AN HOUR,
I'M COMING OUT TO LOOK FOR YOU.
THEY'LL LEAVE US ALONE.
HALF AN HOUR.
WE'LL BE BACK.
[ Liquid Bubbling ]
JESUS GOD ALMIGHTY.
THE RESIDENT SURGEON
HAS BEEN BURNING THE
MIDNIGHT OILS.
WHAT THE HELL HAS HE BEEN DOIN'
DOWN HERE, SLAUGHTERING CATTLE?
IN HIS MIND, THAT'S PROBABLY
NOT FAR FROM THE TRUTH.
[ Clicks, Rewinds ]
[ Stops ]
[ Man On Tape ]
GRANDFATHER'S TALKING.
HIS MIND'S TALKING.
THERE. I'VE PUT IT AWAY.
I'VE PUT IT AWAY, MOTHER.
I'VE PUT IT AWAY.
- BASTARD. BE CIVILIZED!
BE CIVIL.
-[ Man Groaning, Growling ]
CHRIST! TAKE THAT OFF.
TAKE THAT OFF! TAKE THAT OFF!
[ Groaning,
Growling Continues ]
FIVE MINUTES, MOTHER.
JUST FIVE MINUTES.
OH, MY GOD.
[ Tape Continues,
Indistinct ]
-[ Crashes ]
- NO, SARAH! DON'T!
IT'LL JUST BRING OUT
RHODES AND THE MEN.
LEAVE IT BE,
LEAVE IT BE.
LET'S GO.
LET'S GET OUTTA HERE.
I'M BEGINNING TO THINK
WE SHOULD TAKE THAT HELICOPTER
BEFORE SOMEBODY ELSE DOES.
[ Door Opens, Shuts ]
[ Faint Groaning ]
HELLO, BUB.
MOTHER IS VERY PROUD
OF YOU.
VERY, VERY PROUD INDEED.
YOU DID QUITE NICELY TODAY.
[ Groaning ]
???? [ Choir: "Ode To Joy" ]
[ Soft Groaning ]
- [ Clicks Off ]
- [ Angry Groaning ]
???? [ Resumes ]
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
LOGAN'S STAR PUPIL.
- NOW, TOMORROW, WE CAN PLAY
WITH THESE THINGS AGAIN.
-[ Clicks Off ]
NOW IT'S TIME
FOR YOUR REWARD.
I BROUGHT YOU
SOMETHING GOOD.
[ Groans ]
WHAT IS THAT?
IS THAT--
IT CAN'T BE.
OH, GOD. I CAN'T LOOK.
CAN'T-- [ Gasps ]
- [ Soft Groan ]
- GOOD NIGHT, BUB.
WHAT ARE YOU GIVIN' HIM
IN THERE, FRANKENSTEIN?
WHAT?
- HUUH!
- WHAT IS IT, HUH?
WHAT DO YOU GIVE HIM?
SCUM!
NO, YOU-- YOU MUST LISTEN TO ME,
CAPTAIN. YOU MUST LISTEN.
LISTEN TO THIS.
HOLD IT, FISHER.
TORREZ, GET HIS GUN.
TAKE ALL THE GUNS.
ALL OF 'EM.
ALL THEIR FUCKING GUNS!
TAKE ALL THEIR GUNS.
ALL THEIR GUNS!
THOSE ARE MY MEN IN THERE.
MY MEN.
[ Shouting ]
THOSE ARE MY MEN IN THERE!
[ Rhodes Talking,
Indistinct ]
HOLD IT RIGHT THERE.
FRANKENSTEIN'S DEAD.
THIS SCUM GETS IT NEXT
UNLESS YOU THROW
YOUR WEAPONS OUT RIGHT NOW.
HE MEANS IT, JOHNNY.
HE KILLED LOGAN
IN COLD BLOOD.
I KILLED LOGAN
BECAUSE HE WAS A BUTCHER.
I'LL KILL THE REST OF THEM ONE
AT A TIME, UNLESS YOU GET YOUR
BLACK ASS OUT HERE, FLYBOY.
- LET HIM GO, RHODES.
- TORREZ, GET HIS MACHETE.
WE'RE GETTIN' OUTTA HERE
RIGHT NOW.
YOU GIVE ME ANY SHIT ABOUT IT,
I BLOW HIS HEAD OFF.
WHIRLYBIRD CAN'T
HOLD US ALL.
"US ALL" AIN'T GOING.
ME, MY MEN, YOU. THAT'S IT.
YOU'LL NEVER GET ME TO DO THAT,
RHODES.
NO!
HEY!
RICKLES, OPEN THE GATES.
STEEL, SHOVE 'EM IN THERE.
[ Indistinct Talking,
Laughing ]
HAVE A NICE VISIT
WITH McDERMOTT, HUH?
[ Zombies Growling ]
RHODES...
DON'T DO THIS, PLEASE.
GONNA GIVE US A RIDE,
FLYBOY?
I'LL DO WHATEVER YOU SAY, MAN.
LET HER GO NOW.
RHODES. LET 'EM OFF.
I'LL TAKE YOU...
WHEREVER YOU WANT TO GO.
LIKE YOU SAID,
CHOPPER CAN'T HOLD US ALL.
[ John ]
RHODES, DON'T DO IT.
YOU DO IT, AND I WON'T FLY.
I SWEAR, YOU GOT TO KILL ME
BEFORE I FLY.
LET 'EM OUT.
THAT'S THE DEAL.
I MAKE THE DEALS AROUND HERE,
NOT YOU.
NOW YOU GET YOUR SHIT TOGETHER,
WHATEVER YOU NEED.
ISN'T THERE
AN OLD SILO BACK THERE?
NO. WE CAN'T GO BACK THERE
WITHOUT GUNS.
-[ Sarah ] WE CAN'T STAY HERE.
THEY'LL TEAR US APART.
- OH, JESUS, MARY AND JOSEPH.
DON'T SHOOT 'IM!
WE NEED HIS ASS.
STEEL, KICK HIM AROUND
A LITTLE BIT.
MIGHT KNOCK SOME SENSE
INTO THAT JUNGLE-BUNNY HEAD.
-[ Rickles ] CAPTAIN!
-[ Rhodes ] THAT'S IT.
RUN, YOU FUCKIN' LUNATICS.
[ Zombies Groaning ]
OH!
UUH!
[ Grunting ]
THEY'RE GONE, FLYBOY.
LET'S GO.
NOT A CHANCE.
[ Whirring, Beeping ]
- JESUS CHRIST.
THAT'S THE ELEVATOR.
- CHECK IT OUT.
[ Lips Smacking ]
[ Groans ]
[ Zombie Groaning ]
AW, JESUS.
ROCK SLIDE.
WE CAN'T GET THROUGH.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
THIS WAY.
WE CAN TRY AND GET AROUND.
[ Groaning ]
AAH!
[ Shrieking ]
- [ Screams ]
-[ Gurgling ]
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
[ Gasps ]
OH, IT'S YOU.
THIS WAY.
[ Bat Screeches ]
LET'S GO, TORREZ. GET UP.
[ Gunshots ]
UUH!
AW, SHIT!
SOMEBODY TOOK THIS APART.
THE ONLY OTHER CONTROL'S
UP ON THE PLATFORM
WITH A HAND BOX.
STUCK.
- RICKLES, WE CAN'T
GET OUT OF HERE.
- FIX IT. CAN'T YOU FIX IT?
IT'S THAT FUCKIN' SPICK
THAT DID THIS!
FIX IT!
COME ON, MAN!
FIX WHAT?
FIX THE BOX, MAN!
COME ON! FIX IT!
THEY TORE THE GUTS OUT!
I CAN'T FIX IT!
WE GOT THE BOOK HERE!
WE CAN FIX IT!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
THE BASTARD.
[ Bat Screeches ]
SARAH!
[ Echoing ]
WILLIE!
JOHN!
[ Echoing ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Gunshot ]
[ Distant Gunshots ]
[ Zombie Groaning ]
UUH!
[ Barks ]
LET'S KEEP MOVING.
[ Growling ]
AHA!
[ Grunts ]
UUH!
[ Groaning ]
[ Zombies Groaning ]
[ Muffled Scream ]
HOLD DOWN. AW, FUCK!
WHAT'S GOIN' ON?
THAT SPICK.
HE RIPPED THESE CONTROLS OUT,
THE LITTLE YELLOW BASTARD.
THE LITTLE SHIT.
THE LITTLE FUCKIN' SHIT.
YOU TRIED TO MAKE
A RUN FOR IT.
[ Whirring, Beeping ]
[ Steel ]
HOLY SHIT.
HOLY FUCKIN' SHIT.
[ Shouting ]
RHODES!
RHODES, YOU BASTARD!
[ Moans Softly ]
[ Wailing ]
[ Sniffling ]
[ Screaming ]
OH, SHIT!
AAH! SHIT!
FUCK!
HA, HA!
[ Whooping ]
HOLY SHIT!
[ Cackling ]
[ Screaming ]
SHIT!
RHODES! GODDAMN, RHODES!
OPEN THE DOOR,
YOU SON OF A BITCH!
RHODES!
SHIT!
[ Gunshot ]
[ Nasally Voice ]
COME ON, BUB.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
COME ON, YOU PUS-BRAINED
BAG OF SHIT.
YOU WANNA LEARN
HOW TO SHOOT, BUB?
I'LL TEACH YOU HOW TO SHOOT.
COME ON, YOU BAG OF--
[ Growling ]
[ Screaming ]
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- [ Zombies Groaning ]
- OH!
[ Sarah ]
LET'S GO. FOLLOW THE RED LIGHTS.
- IT'S TEMPORARILY
OUT OF SERVICE.
- THE LADDER! GO AHEAD. UP, UP.
UP!
[ Screeching ]
[ Growling ]
[ Gunshot ]
COME ALONG, JOHNNY.
WE'RE COUNTIN' ON YA
TO FLY US TO THE PROMISED LAND.
COME ON, COME ON.
COME ON!
OH, SHIT!
AAH!
UUH!
YOU FUCK.
AAH!
[ Groans ]
YOU PUS FUCK! YOU FUCK!
YOU PUS FUCK!YOU PUS FUCK!
[ Screaming ]
YOU F-- AAH!
COME ON!
COME ON! COME O-O-ON!
COME O-O-ON!
[ Zombies Gasping
Delightedly ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Gasping ]
SALAZAR!
[ Ghostly Moaning ]
[ John ] LET'S HOPE
THEY FILLED UP THE GAS TANK
FROM THE OTHER NIGHT.
OH, MY GOD.
COME ON, COME ON!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
[ John ]
GET IN, GET IN!
AAH!
[ Screams ]
[ Gulls Cawing ]
?? EYES ??
?? EYES, EYES ??
?? IS IT YOU ??
?? IS IT ME ??
?? HOLDING ON FOR SO LONG ??
?? TRYING DESPERATELY ??
?? IS IT RIGHT ??
?? OH-OH-OH, IS IT FAIR ??
?? WANTING MORE, SO MUCH MORE ??
?? AND IT'S NEVER THERE ??
?? I AM WITH YOU WHEN ??
?? I FEEL LIKE I'M ??
?? ALONE ??
?? IT'S EASY TO PRETEND ??
?? THIS WORLD COULD NEVER END ??
?
?? COME TAKE MY HEART, MY SOUL ?
?? MY LOVE ??
?? MY LIFE ??
?? TONIGHT ??
?? LOVE ME ??
?? TONIGHT, BABE ??
?
?? TAKE ME TO THE WORLD INSIDE ?
?? YOUR EYES ??
?? TONIGHT ????