(coins chinking)
- [Man] One
(beating drums)
Two
Three
Four
(car driving)
Five
(woman tremulous voice)
(dog barking)
six
Seven
(man's low pitched voice)
Eight
Nine
(dog barking)
Ten
Hello.
Twelve
Thirteen
(beating drums)
(coins chinking)
(fast beating drums)
- [Woman] And what
was your last job?
- Well I've kinda just done
odds and ends to get by,
you know, waitress and cleaning.
I just really would like
a job doing something
where I could feel like I
was doing something good.
- This is our training room.
We don't get to use it that
often but it's great to have
when we get to use it.
We help support individuals
with disabilities
in the community to
live in their homes
and have lives just
like you and I .
And here's our kitchen where
the DSP stores their food
and prepares their lunches.
The hours are kind of crazy.
You come in and
work two days on.
Then you come back
and work two nights on
and you have to stay
awake all night.
- I don't sleep much
anyway so that'll be fine.
- This is the area they come
in if they want to do puzzles
or whatnot.
And this is Patricia.
- Hi.
- Patricia can you say
hi to my friend, Katie?
- How are you?
- Hi Barbra
Can you say hi to
my friend, Katie?
- Hi there. How are you?
- Good.
- Good
- You guys said hi
to my friend Katie?
- Hello.
- Hi. How are you doing?
- You getting sleepy Ricky?
- No I ain't sleepy
- We're getting
ready to eat okay.
This is Jeffrey.
- You getting hungry?
- Danny
- Yeah.
- And this is Stephanie.
- Hi Stephanie.
- Hi Stephanie this
is my friend, Katie.
She's gonna be
working in your home.
- Hi.
- Is that okay?
- Yeah
- This is Declay
- Hi
- Brittany.
T
- Hello.
- This is Katie she's gonna
come to work for us guys.
- Look at that pretty coloring.
What are you coloring?
Are you coloring?
What's that?
That's pretty
- And this is Brandy.
She's gonna be who
you're following
for the next few days.
- Hey
- Hey, can you take her on?
I'm gonna go up I've got
some things I need to do.
- Sure.
- Thank you.
- So this is our room
we use for the clients,
for the jobs they train in here
so that they're all out for
the day right now, though.
- Okay.
- Our computer room
you do your notes
and stuff like that in here.
A lot of employees
just gossip mainly.
- (laughs)
- we use this area over
here for our planner outings
in the morning.
That's what are they.
- okay
- Puzzles. They love
working on puzzles.
- Pretty
- We usually hang them
up but we got a couple
that rip them off the walls.
- (laughing)
- They get tired they can
rest in there or whatever.
- Okay.
- Here it's the moore's is
what their medications they get
what the doctor prescribes
all health information.
We use this room for
physical therapy.
If they're sick and
want to take a nap,
they'll just come in
here and lay down.
You make sure you keep your
medications locked at all times.
And you lock the
door when you go out.
- Okay.
- You'll get used to it
it ain't no big deal.
- That's a lot.
Are those your
trophies over there?
- Yeah
- [Katie] What'd
you win them for.
- (mumbles)
- [Katie] You must be good.
- Oh yeah.
- [Katie] How many
trophies do you have?
- Two
Two two three
- [Katie] So you like fishing?
- Yeah
- [Katie] Where do you
usually go fishing at?
What kind of fish do
you like to catch?
- How do I help you?
- [Katie] What's on it?
- (mumbles)
- [Katie] Are you
making me a picture?
- Yeah. Your picture
- [Katie] Oh, it's pretty.
Do you want help coloring?
- No I can do it.
- You can do it yourself okay.
- I might mess it up.
- Can you put your name on it?
You wanna do that
in red or green?
Green?
Yeah.
You have a lot of
friends in here?
Yeah.
- (mumbles)
- Oh, I love it.
It's for me?
- Yeah
- Oh.
- Done
(laughing) I'm done
(coins chinking)
(low pitched sounds)
(door knocking)
- Hey . How was your first day?
- It, it felt really good.
- [Woman] Brandy said
that you did really well
with the clients back there?
- It was, it was a lot of fun.
- [Woman] So where
are you staying at?
I know you're new in the area.
- I actually got a
place in the country.
It needs a little work,
but I'm hoping to
stay there for awhile.
(loud drumming)
(coins chinking)
- [Man] Your family
didn't understand you.
They didn't deserve you.
(coins chinking)
You have a new family now
The devils
they listen to the
sounds of the innocent.
One
Two
Three
(loud drumming)
(coins chinking)
- [Man] This is Katie.
She's going to be
a guest for awhile
Come on
- [Katie] You're
ready for this dance.
Okay.
Alright. Let's go get in
Alright, come on and
get in over here.
Okay.
Do you sit up here in the front.
Do you want to get in on
this side or the other side?
- Yeah. The other side.
- Do you want me to bring
Stephanie over there?
Right I'm going to scoot
over you if you don't mind.
- I don't mind.
- Can I sit by you Steph?
Thank you. Oh, thank you.
- (mumbles)
- Alright. Are you buckled up?
You need a tissue.
- [Stephany] Yeah
- [Katie] Well you
got two in your hand.
(laughing)
Who's ready to go dance.
- [Woman] I am
- [Katie] You are.
You excited Petra?
- [Petra] I guess so.
- [Katie] We're almost there.
Hold on. Don't take
your seatbelt off yet.
- Alright,(mumbles) come on.
Let's go dance.
- [Katie] Hold on Stephie.
- Stephie can't go?
- [Katie] Hold on.
- You guys sit down
and wait your turn.
(country music playing)
(coins chinking)
(low pitched voices)
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
My head just hurt
me all of a sudden.
- [Woman] Lets go
ahead and have a seat.
Go ahead Jeffery.
- All right
- All right Petra
- What kind do we have?
Look I just want cheese.
Can I sit by you?
Okay.
- Okay. I'd like to take
this time to welcome Katie
to our team.
Can you say hi, Katie?
- Hi. Hi.
- So if she needs anything
you guys help her out.
Cause we need her to
hang around for awhile.
(clients clapping)
- [Katie] Thank you
- She's never done this
for anyone else before.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah. I'm just getting
a headache again.
Can I use the client bathroom?
- Yeah, that's fine.
(coins chinking)
(shaky breathing)
- It's gonna be fine.
It's just going anyway.
It's gonna be fine.
- You sure you're okay?
- Yeah. I'm good.
(coins chinking)
The blood shows
the devils the way
(coins chinking)
(suspenseful loud drumming)
(heavy metal grinding)
(baby breathing )
- [Man] For a life is
given and the devil is born
( car knock)
- You're at theú group home
tomorrow night don't forget.
I hope your head feels better.
- I'll be okay.
Thanks.
- [Woman] All right. Call me
if you need anything okay.
- [Man] You are so special.
If you only knew.
(garage door opening)
- [Brandy] Hello. Are we home?
(mumbles)
- Hey
- Oh, careful.
All right
- Okay
- Does this go down
- Yep
- All right
All right watch your fingers.
- Now this door usually be
on lock this to let you in.
- Okay.
Sounds good. Here let
me get the door for you.
It's nice.
- Yeah, it's cozy.
I like it.
So this is Stephanie spot and
she comes in she plops down.
Don't try to take her
spot cause she's going
to let you know.
- This is where you
always sit Stephanie?
- Stephie talk to Ms. Katie.
Stephie?
- That's okay
- I want chicken and bread
- [ Katie] Chicken and bread
she's talking about dinner.
You're already ready to eat.
- ( mumbles)
- (laughing)
- You wanna say hi to Ms Katie?
- Yeah.
- Hi. How are you?
- This is the bathroom.
Steph's gonna use
it so (mumbles)
- All right.
- Little small.
- Yeah
- This is Ms. Patricia's room
- It's pretty.
- This is Stephie's room
She's going to be up and
down all through the night.
You have to be awake
very important.
- Okay.
I don't sleep much
anyway, so it's good.
- Her PJ's are in
the third drawer.
Socks is in the second drawer.
Day clothes is in her closet.
All of her toiletries it's
gonna be in the bathroom.
- It sounds pretty easy.
- I'm getting ready to head out.
- Alright.
- Vehicle keys is right
here if you need them.
Nothing too crazy
happens you can call me .
Anything really crazy
emergency contacts
on the board.
- We'll be good.
I'm sure
- Bye ladies.
See you in the morning Stephie.
- [Stephie] Yeah
- All right. Have a
good night. Thank you.
- You too.
- What's in it?
Can you show me what you got?
- A dog.
- I like that dog.
That's cute.
- And I got cellphone.
- You do?
Who do you call?
- My brother.
- Yeah. What's his name?
- Charles Weber
- Okay. Brenda, do you
have a birthday coming up?
- (mumbles)
- [Katie] When?
- The mall
- Well, happy birthday.
- Thank you.
- [Katie] What are
we going to do?
- Eat cake.
- [Katie] What's your
favorite kind of cake?
- Chocolate cake.
- [Katie] Me too.
- [Brenda] You do.
- [Katie] Do you like
with chocolate icing?
- [Brenda] (mumbles)
(air whooshing)
- Hey.
What are you doing?
- Yeah.
Are you getting tired?
- Yeah. You're
going to go to bed.
Do you need some help?
- No.
- No. Okay your
walker's right here.
- Okay
- Alright. You go ahead
and go to bed then.
- Okay.
- All right. Here you go.
I'll get your Walker.
There you go.
Night.
Night night.
Hey, Brenda.
You ready to go to bed?
I'm chilling here
- Yeah. Okay.
Let's get you up.
All right.
Here we go.
Let me get ya.
All right here
give me your hand.
Hey, Steph I'll be
back to put you bed
in just a minute okay?
- Yeah
- All right.
(coins chinking)
( low pitched voices)
- Hey Steph.
Who are you talking to?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
You tired?
- Yeah.
- Yeah
Why don't we go ahead and
get up and go to bed okay.
You can bring your
pictures come on.
All right.
Here we go.
Okay
- Yeah.
- There you go
All right
Goodnight
Get some rest okay.
Alright.
Goodnight.
(coins chinking)
- [Man] The blood shows
the devils the way.
- (mumbles)
- Well you guys is
up and ready to go.
- Yeah. Everything went great.
- That's awesome.
- You guys must've knew
you was in good hands, huh?
- [Stephanie] yeah
- All right. Who's is this one?
- (mumbles)
- Okay. This is yours.
There you go,
- Patricia
- Yeah.
- Alright. And
there's yours, Brenda.
And what time do
I need to be back?
- Maybe back here around three.
- Okay.
Oh, good.
Good.
- Okay guys. Center time.
(loud gong)
- Hello?
Hello.
(loud gong)
(fly buzzing)
(door clinking)
Hey,
- I didn't hear you come in.
- Sorry. I knocked, but
I didn't hear anybody.
- You need something?
- A cow heart if you've got one.
(loud drumming)
(coins chinking)
(cow mooing)
- [Man] come on, come on.
Get over here. Come on
There you go. Come on
(loud drumming)
So we use them all to
know when they're coming.
(mumbles) feel the beat.
(mumbles)
(fast drumming)
- [Brandy] Be careful
- Well, Hey, welcome back.
- Hello
- You want to go in here?
You want to go in and sit down?
- I wanna sit down.
- You want to sit
down there okay.
Hey, how are you?
Do you have a good day?
Let's go to your chair.
Sound good?
- No.
- Okay.
Hey Steph,
- You all rested up?
- Oh yeah. Like I said, I
don't really sleep much so
I'm good.
How was Stephanie today?
She stayed by herself
most of the day.
Why?
- That was probably
nothing. I was just
it was probably nothing.
(playful music playing)
All right. Let's
get you in here.
Is that good stuff?
- yeah
- Okay.
Here you go.
That look good?
Here's your spoon.
(playful music playing)
(coins chinking)
(low pitched voices)
(woman screaming)
Steph are you okay?
It's okay
- Stephanie is sick.
- I'll get this out of your way.
(playful music playing)
(loud low-pitched sound)
(loud drumming)
(coins chinking)
(man laughing)
(woman laughing)
- [Girl] Where are you mommy?
(loud deafening sounds)
- [Man] Take a big breath
in and out one more time.
(Breaths heavily)
Okay, good.
Okay. Did you say she
got sick last night?
- Yeah, but I didn't notice
a fever or anything though.
- Okay.
I think she might
have just a little bit
of a respiratory infection and
we'll just watch it
for now and maybe get
some lab work and see
what that shows us okay.
- [Katie] Thank you
- You're doing
good. You're good.
Okay.
(coins chinking)
- Hey.
You can't have you
getting sick you hear me?
I'm not gonna let
them get you too.
- Yes
(loud drumming)
- The devils.
They listened to the
sounds of the innocent.
- What do you write in stories?
- No, I just write things
down so I don't forget them so
- I drank every night to
do the total opposite.
Are you okay though?
- I just (chuckles) I
just worry a lot you know
- About Stephanie?
She hardly ever gets sick.
She just exaggerates
everything a lot.
- I hope so.
(coins chinking)
(loud drumming)
- [Man] You are so special
If you only knew.
(loud slapping)
- (Charles singing)
- [Katie] Hey Charles.
- Goodbye Ms Kimmy.
- Have you seen Stephanie?
You know where she's at?
- I don't know.
- [Brandy] Stephanie
you wait on me okay.
(mumbles)
(coins chinking)
(coughing)
- [Katie] Hey,
- Hey. Sorry it took us forever
to get here this morning.
- Is she okay?
- Yeah. She was like
stuck in the bed.
I don't know it's like
she was glued down.
(coughing)
(coins chinking)
(loud gong)
- [Man] The blood shows
the devils the way.
The devil they'll call
out for you if you listen.
Listen.
(loud gong)
One
Two
Three
Four
Five
Six
Seven
- A sacrifice will
keep the devils away.
- Left hand side of this
are our dogs and our cats.
There are adoptions
we like to make sure
that they have a yard.
Do you have a yard?
So we're needing
something small.
(dogs barking)
There are cats.
(cats chirrup)
- Who's this one?
- [Agent] That's
Mr. Will Pickle.
There you go
- All right.
Thanks.
- [Agent] Yes ma'am be careful.
(cat meows)
- Hey you just won't
be quiet will you?
I'll come back for
you a little bit okay.
Hey Steph did you do okay today?
- [Brandy] Yeah. She's still
up on and off all day long.
- She doing any better now or?
- No we had our doctor's
appointment rescheduled for
tomorrow.
Maybe they can do something
and she's just getting worse.
- All right. Well,
I'll take care of her.
- Okay.
- All right. Have a good one.
- You too.
(Suspenseful loud drumming)
(coins chinking)
- Guys stay in here.
I'll be back.
- [Man] (mumbles)
they never come back.
Give it a place
with a lot of food.
It'll keep coming.
- Why so many?
- To protect us,
To protect us from them.
I'll teach you soon enough.
- Stephie you feeling okay?
- Yeah
- We're going to get
you all better okay.
- Yeah.
- Poor thing.
Let's grab our lunch boxes.
Take this one okay.
Did you get a cat?
- What?
- A cat.
- I used to have one.
- They're fixing to
come back and get her.
Do you want to go back with her?
- Yeah.
- If she's good with it.
- Stephie You're going let
Ms.Katie go back with you?
- Yeah
- Okay.
- All right. Stephanie
you ready to come on back.
- All right.Come on.
(music playing)
- (mumbles)
we're gonna draw
some blood okay.
- Okay.
Oh oh. It's going to be okay.
- It's okay. Relax.
- I'm just gonna tie this
around your arm okay.
- [Katie] Hey Steph
you wanna look at me?
- Now see your arm.
- [Katie] Hey. Hey.It's okay.
- What are you doing?
- [Nurse] I'll be quick. Okay.
- [Katie] It's okay.
It's okay
- [Nurse] You doing good.
- [Stephanie] Go ahead.
- [Nurse] All right I'm just
going to clean you okay?
With the alcohol.
- [Katie] It's okay.
It's okay. See that
wasn't so bad was it?
You need to rest up okay.
Come on.
come on.
All right.
(loud drumming)
But if the devils find them
their entrance must be blocked
by something that was
once part of the living.
- [Man] Once part of the living.
Find them
The devils find them.
Hello
Hello. Hello.
All right.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Their entrance must be
blocked by something
that was once part
of the living.
- [Man] Once part of the living.
(coins chinking)
- [Man] I can't wait
to show you the house.
You are loved now.
(door closing)
One
Two
(car garage door opening)
- What the hell?
Stephany
- Brandy wait.
- Stephany
- Brandy just let me explain
for a minute what's going on.
Brandy.
Seriously
Brandy
Brandy.
- [Brandy] First off Katie is
writing this weird devil shit
in her notebook.
I came back to check on Steph,
Katie was asleep in the
house with this burnt up cat.
Crazy as shit we
can't have that.
The girl is just fucking crazy.
- Can you sign this please.
- Listen Stephanie is in trouble
I'm just trying to help her
- She's not your
concern anymore.
It's on this so I don't have
to call the cops please.
- It's gonna be fine
it's too soon anyway
- They must be
taken to the house.
It's the only way to protect
them from the devils.
- [Man] From the devils.
They'll call out for
you if you listen
- [Man] Five
Six
Seven
- [Brandy] Be careful
up Ms. Brenda.
Let's go get ready.
Put your night clothes on get
a shower the good stuff okay.
Here we are.
You got it. Be careful
- Hey.You wanna go
and get a drink?
- Yeah
- Okay let's go get it.
Come on. I have it
outside for you.
I brought you a
special drink outside.
Come on let's go get it.
Come on
Hey look it's right outside.
Look. Do you want it?
- Yeah
- Okay. Let's go.
I'm gonna go get it.
You wanna come with me?
Come on.
Good job
- (mumbles)
- We'll eat later okay.
Okay. All right. Come on
All right girl
Come on we're gonna go this way.
Okay stay on the road.
Wanna get the door for you
okay. Here we go.
- [Man] Listen
- You want some chocolate?
- Yeah
- It's okay.
I'm going to help you
feel better real soon.
I promise.
- [Stephany] Yeah
- Okay.
Okay. Careful. Come on.
Okay.
You wait right here. Okay.
- Yeah.
- Once the person
is in the house,
a flame will draw
the devils away
- [Man] A flame will
draw the devils.
The devils.
(door closing)
- [Man] The devils.
(woman's shaky voice)
One
Two
Three
Four
Five
Six
Seven
Eight
Nine
Ten
Eleven
Twelve
Thirteen
(man groans)
- [Stephany] (mumbles)
- Stephany.
Stephany
- [Stephany] Help
Help.
Please
Help
Someone
- Stephany
- [Stephany] (mumbles)
- Stephanie.
Where are you?
Stephany
- [Man] You will be (mumbles)
There will be many in your path.
- I'm scared.
- They thank you
They thank you but you
will not remember this.
One
Two
Three
Four
Five
Six
Seven
Eight
Nine
Ten
Eleven
Twelve
Thirteen
For a life is given
and the devil is born.
But you will not remember this,