Let's just take it from
the top, Mr. McCall.
Mr. McCall?
I told you, I didn't do it.
Good night.
Oh, fun for you.
See you tomorrow.
What?
Good night. We'll clean up.
I love you.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Whoa! Shit! Maverick, stop.
Jesus Christ!
- No, come on. Get off!
- You scared the shit out of me.
Go away. Come on, buddy. Get out.
You're not supposed
to see me tonight.
Come on, that is a dumb tradition.
You don't believe it.
- No, I don't believe it.
- Oh, shit, you do.
Okay, I kind of do.
What are you doing...
- Okay, ready?
- Okay.
Ladies, oop, and gentlemen...
I'd like to present the McCalls.
- Almost.
- Okay, I gotta get dressed.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, hold on, hold on.
Strike that pose. Right there.
I want to capture our
last night together.
We're not dying.
My dad used to follow us around
with one of these constantly.
My mom gave him so
much shit for it.
I think it's sweet.
I wish I had something like that.
My whole childhood
is kind of a blank.
That's kind of why
I want to do this.
I used to think my dad was so lame,
with all his nostalgia
and all that.
But I kind of get it now.
I kind of want this for us.
I just want a record of all the
important things that happen to us.
And all the random stupid stuff
that we'll forget about.
Mmm, yeah.
Tomorrow, we are officially family.
So, tonight I want to
start our family history.
Family history.
Yeah.
I love that.
Good.
In sickness and in health.
To love and to cherish.
Till death do us part.
With this ring, I thee wed.
And pledge myself to thee forever.
Love me tender
Love me true
All my dreams fulfilled
Whoo!
For, my darling, I love you
I just wanted to say thank
you to Ken and Sally...
for making me feel so at home.
I've never really felt like
I was part of a family before.
So, thank you for being so
welcoming and wonderful.
Dad had the first camera.
He'd carry it on
his shoulder like this.
I wanted you to know that I think
you are a wonderful brother.
I'm being serious! This
is a beautiful event...
and I'm really grateful
that you invited me.
We were in the same foster
home together for a year.
And we were more
than friends. Family.
I hope that you guys
will be happy forever.
So, here's to happily ever after.
Oh, gosh.
Mmm.
- Mmm.
- Are you okay?
Sam...
my beautiful wife.
This was the most perfect day.
I can't believe we're married.
When we watch this
a lot of years from now...
just remember how
good-looking I was.
I love you so much.
I promise I will
always protect you.
Keep you safe.
I love you.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is your captain speaking.
I'd like to welcome you
to the Dominican Republic.
This is gonna be awesome.
- Now, the honeymoon begins.
- Ooh.
Oh, wow!
We're gonna do this
swimsuit issue-type thing.
Oh, God!
- No, no. You're gonna go in the water.
- Uh-huh.
And then you're gonna
come out of the water.
Is that how I'm gonna do it?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Don't worry, I'm right behind you.
- This is gonna go fast.
- No, it's not.
Oh, my God.
Christopher Columbus.
- Oh. Really?
- Yeah.
This is the first cathedral
in the New World.
"The Cathedral of Santo Domingo."
"It's Gothic style highlighted
with Renaissance details."
Oh, my God.
I have never seen anything so
fucking perfect before in my life.
Look at this sea of white.
Oh, my gosh.
What's that?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
That's my husband.
Wake up.
Hey.
Oogum, Oogum, Boogum,
Boogum, Boogum...
Now, baby you're casting
your spell on me
Your high heel boots
In your hip-huggin' suit
You got it right
You're outta sight
What is that?
It's the coolest
wedding present ever.
Mason gave it to us.
It's an adventure cam.
- Oh, good, that's what I always wanted.
- I know.
And now we can go
zip-lining. Come on.
Just get your game face on.
All right.
Hold on. Hold on!
Wow.
Where are we?
Zach, come here.
We're going here.
Whoa. Come on.
Hey, wait up, wait up.
- Welcome.
- Oh, thank you.
- Hi.
- Welcome.
- Have a seat.
- Okay.
I will study your palm.
Okay. Which one do you want?
This one.
I don't think it matters.
I don't know. They're different.
You've had some hard times.
But now, you're so happy.
- You're happy now.
- She's good.
No family.
No past.
You were born from death.
What do you mean?
They've been waiting.
- Do you want to go?
- Yeah.
- They've been waiting.
- Whoa.
- All right.
Thank you. That's fine.
- Whoa.
- They've been waiting.
You are the first.
The first of many.
You will bring the end.
You know what? Let's go, let's go.
Can we get out...
- Ow! Ow!
- You were born from death.
- Let go of me, please.
- Ma'am, let go.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
- Zach, come on.
- Okay.
Hey, are you okay?
What did she say to you?
- Nothing. Fucking nothing. I don't know.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey. Forget her, okay?
She was crazy.
What did she whisper in your ear?
I don't know. It was just
a bunch of gibberish.
She stank of rum anyway. I just
want to get back to the hotel.
I don't remember
this street, do you?
Do you wanna go down this way?
Let's turn around.
Okay.
Jesus!
Let's go.
They don't have any street signs.
Can we head back towards
where the party was?
Do you guys need a taxi?
- Are you are a taxi?
- Yeah.
- That's your family?
- Mi family. Children. Babies.
- Babies?
- Oh, no, not yet.
- No?
- My new wife.
I have lots of babies.
- Yes, lots of babies.
- Someday. One day, yeah.
I take you somewhere fun.
Eh... Fun, authentic.
No, no, no. We're good. Thank you.
We just want to go
back to the hotel.
No, no, no. No worry.
I'll wait for you outside. This place,
eh... Very distinctive. How do you say?
It's special.
- What do you think? One more drink?
- No.
Come on. You're so young.
- Twenty minutes.
Twenty minutes?
Twenty minutes.
It's our last night.
- Twenty minutes?
- How much does it cost?
Oh, it's free, it's free.
Are you guys with me?
- Deal.
- All right, fine. One drink.
This is it. We here.
- We're here.
- Yeah. This looks...
Great.
Oh. Okay.
Your vacation starts right now.
Okay, gracias.
You're welcome.
Come on. It's this way.
- You don't look happy.
- Well, where are we?
I don't know, but
it's gonna be cool.
- Careful.
- Right. Okay.
Oh!
- Look at this little guy.
- Hi, little guy.
Whoo.
Ooh!
I'm right here.
Shh.
The music.
- You hear music?
- Yeah.
It's musica.
Yeah, I hear it.
Wait, this is...
No, Zach, let's go back. This
is crazy. Let's turn around.
Don't worry. Don't worry.
We'll be all right. I'm
right here, I'm right here.
All right, I'm right here.
- Don't...
- We'll go slow.
I'm sorry, what?
Oh, wow. Okay.
It's fine, I promise.
- See?
- Go on. Go on.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
It's special!
This is insane!
Authentic Santo Domingo. Come on
Oh, see how great. Here we go.
Cheers!
Yes! Beautiful!
- Here we go.
- Ah!
- I'm gonna hold my nose.
That's not how you take
a shot. You sipped it.
No!
You gotta do another. One more.
Oh, my God! Congratulations!
Oh, thank you!
- They just got married, too.
- No way!
Yes!
I'm done.
Oh, yes!
Oh.
These men are staring at me.
What?
I said, "These men
are staring at me."
I guess you'll do.
I can't dance anymore.
Hi!
Hey, babe, let's put it away.
- Yes?
- Yes
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Come on, wife.
Time to get up.
- Come on.
- No.
Yes. I'm sorry, but
we gotta get up.
Ugh.
I'm so hung over.
Yeah, no kidding.
Mmm, oh, God, get away with that.
Come on, I'll get you some water.
We gotta get up and
catch this plane.
Okay.
Oh.
Yeah, my head is killing me.
Me, too.
Oh, shit. I'm stuck.
Mmm.
How did we get home last night?
I don't know. The guy in the cab?
Stop. Not right now.
See you later, Santo Domingo.
- Well, we're home.
- Mmm.
Home sweet home.
The honeymoon is over.
Ooh, wait, wait, wait.
- Hold this.
- Oh.
- Oh, sorry.
- Yeah.
- Okay, here we go.
- All right.
Welcome home, Mrs. McCall.
Ugh.
Oh.
- Suzie left the door open.
- Great.
That's great.
Oh.
Yay, home.
Ooh, presents.
Crate and Barrel, Crate and Barrel.
I'll go get the bags.
All right. We got the panini grill.
And that thing from Allison.
And what is this one?
Oh, I don't know. Open it up.
Mav, do you want to open it?
- All right. OK.
- He doesn't care.
This is the juicer that I wanted!
I'm gonna make so much stuff
with flax and probiotics...
and things with kale.
- Kale?
- Mmm.
Kale... kale.
Oh, Mav!
Oh, my God.
- Look at him.
- Oh!
Hey, did you see the "Sold"
sign on the Anderson house?
For real? Maybe someone will
finally fix that place up.
I hope so. It's terrible.
Your husband, he can't
grill for shit.
Sam, come on. You're gonna miss it.
This will be awesome. Ready?
Just like we practiced.
Are you kidding me? Come on,
Maverick. No, no, no.
You're supposed to catch it.
- Zach.
- Yeah?
Come on, ready? Eye on the prize.
Yes, yes, yes!
- Zach.
- What?
Can you turn that
off for one second?
Whoa.
What is that?
Uh...
It doesn't make any sense.
I've taken the pill religiously.
I've never missed one ever.
Whoa, whoa, whoa...
You're pregnant?
- Yes.
- Oh, my God.
We're having a baby.
Holy shit!
Oh, my God. That's so amazing.
I feel good about this
office. How about you?
I feel good. Except that says three stages
of pregnancy, and there's four pictures.
Okay, so this isn't a math office.
It's a doctor's office.
I hope that doctors can do math.
Well, the doctor didn't
make that sign, clearly.
Do you think the doctor made
the "Dirty Area" sign?
- Oh, hello.
- Hi.
Mr. and Mrs. McCall.
Hello, how are you?
- I'm Zach.
- I am Dr. Ludka.
Nice to finally meet. Yes.
- Hello, lucky lady.
- Hi.
- How are you doing?
- I'm good, how are you?
Okay. You ready?
Yeah.
Okay, this is gonna
be quick and painless.
Awesome.
- Sorry.
- "Awesome."
You know you get a copy
of the ultrasound, right?
Oh, yeah, I just, um...
This is his thing.
- It's our thing.
We just want to film a bunch of this
so he/she, whoever, can see it later.
- It's for the baby.
- Okay, sure.
- Is it okay?
- Oh, yeah, perfect.
Okay. Make sure you
get my good side.
- Done. Right there.
- Both sides.
This is gonna be a little cold.
Mmm-hmm.
- A little gooey, huh?
- Yeah. Oh!
- That's great.
- Okay.
- Ah, there we go.
- Oh.
Can you see? There's your
uterus, right there.
And there's the heartbeat.
Huh, um...
What?
Oh, don't worry, I'm just
gonna make a few adjustments.
Is it okay?
Uh...
Ah, there we go.
- So, you're about seven weeks along.
- Ooh.
And everything looks really good.
Honeymoon baby.
The pill is about 99 percent effective,
but, occasionally, this happens.
Okay.
- She winked at me.
- I saw that.
Because I got good sperm.
- This is what you started.
- What? It's good, strong sperm.
I'm gonna prescribe vitamin B...
- and iron, since you're a vegetarian.
- Mmm-hmm.
Yeah, I've been trying
to break her of that.
- It's for the baby.
- Mmm-hmm.
But, overall, you're pretty healthy. I'm
expecting a pretty smooth ride, here.
- Awesome.
- Great.
- Okay?
- Thank you.
One more thing.
Ooh.
Congratulations.
The due date is March 30th.
- Hey, he looks like you.
- He doesn't!
A little jelly bean.
- Ooh, Will you hold this?
- Oh, sure.
- It's our first family video.
- Oh, sweet.
That's awesome.
Sorry. Thanks.
All right, I expect you
guys back in five weeks.
I think Maverick drank my wine.
Aw, Mav, he's such a lush.
Hey, have your ankles and
toes started swelling up?
Oh, my God, with the ankles.
Yes, they're swelling up.
I read in the baby book, it says
that those things swell sometimes.
They do. My entire thing
is swelling right now.
It looks good. You could use
a little meat on your bones.
Mmm-mmm. I don't like it.
- Hey, ew. I mean, whoa.
- What? Oh, God.
- You haven't noticed that?
- No, what is that?
- Oh.
- Does it hurt?
No, I think my body is being
taken over by hormones.
Ugh, this is not supposed to be
happening yet. Don't look at that.
All these weird things
are gonna happen to you.
You're making a person
inside of your person.
Seriously, that's amazing.
- Sam.
- Mmm?
You're making a baby.
I can't do that.
Yeah.
Mmm.
Oh, she woke you up?
Yeah. So, your mother snores.
Even though she
categorically denies it.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
But we now have hard evidence.
So, if she ever denies it again...
Oh, hey. Sam.
Sam, hey.
Jesus, Sam.
Sam.
Hey.
Go to sleep.
What are you doing?
Hello.
They're getting restless.
So, I'll leave it to Sam.
We're having a baby.
Oh, my God!
What?
We get to be grandparents again.
Stop.
Congratulations.
Flip it. Flip that card that
you just had in your hand.
Thank you. Seven,
king, so I get it.
- Tofu?
- What did you think it was?
I wish you wouldn't have
told me it was tofu.
- I mean, did they do a sonogram?
- Oh, yeah.
Did you get a picture?
She wants a picture to show
everybody immediately.
Oh, ultrasound.
If you go with a C-section, your
body just bounces right back.
- Great.
- What?
Natalie, why don't you try to not
micro-manage their entire thing?
I checked under the fridge.
It's not there.
- You lifted the fridge up?
- I looked under it.
We'll find it.
I couldn't find it. When I
do, I'll email it to you.
I hope you find it.
We Will.
I'm just gonna be on
pins and needles to see it.
Oh, my God, Sam, you're bleeding.
- Oh, God.
- Oh, jeez, here.
Sam, here you go. This is clean.
Tilt your head back.
This is where you'll go to school.
I got beat up here a couple times,
but that's not gonna happen to you.
You're gonna be a much cooler kid.
Ah, this is where me and
your mom got married.
Very pretty church.
This is where we walk the dog.
Here's the Anderson house.
It still looks like shit.
Shit, fuck. Maverick!
Maverick, God damn.
Hey, hey. Maverick!
Come here. Hey, no, no.
No, no, we don't live here.
Come on.
All right, come on.
This is your house.
That's your room up
there on the left.
Your granddad says
that it's a money pit...
but it's got good bones. Shit.
- Hey.
Do you think this
looks too mish-mash?
Um...
Do you want the truth?
I'm giving our baby a
tour of the house.
- Yeah? Hey, that's not the house.
- Sorry.
And the grand finale, your room.
Formerly known as
your mother's office.
But now we are converting.
- Thank you for giving up your office.
- Mmm-hmm. Whoa!
- Jeez.
- Watch it, there.
I study on the couch all the time,
anyway, so it's not a big deal.
It's a pretty good room, though.
She really didn't do anything in
it, so I think it's only fair.
It's gonna be kind of cool, though.
You and I are gonna hang in here.
Hey.
- Do you see this guy across the street?
- Huh?
He's just staring up at the house.
- What the fuck?
- Oh, it's creepy.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- How was class?
- Ow!
Ugh. It was fine. I just had
to leave because I'm starving.
I think there's some
leftover Pad Thai in there.
I know, I don't want that.
Okay.
Um...
I'm just gonna eat a
bunch of cookies.
How are you feeling?
Fine.
I'm just hungry.
All right. Whoo! Get ready.
- Hey, no!
- Oh!
- What?
- Hello?
I told you that this was off-limits
until I told you that it was on-limits.
But it's just Emily,
I want her to see it.
It looks so good.
I don't care about
Emily, I care about you.
- Okay. Thanks.
- Great.
Are you guys gonna
pick a color or...?
- One of these days.
- This looks really good, though.
- Oh, look! Oh, my God.
- Yep.
- That's really nice.
- You made that?
It's gonna look way better.
You're doing a great job.
I'm very proud of you.
- Well, here's the crib.
- Uh-huh.
- Hey!
- Oh, wow.
That looks really good.
Yeah, we got it at the antique place
and then I brought it home...
and sanded it down and refinished
it and stuff. Made it baby-safe.
- I know you're big on baby safety.
- Yeah, it looks great.
Cute sheets.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- I got you. Okay.
- Ah!
I got you. Sit down.
Are you okay?
It happened this morning, too.
- This bad?
- Mmm-hmm.
- Hey. Just breathe, okay?
- Mmm.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Lie down, maybe?
Are you sure?
I'll just sit here for a sec.
In...
and out.
Do you see what I'm doing for you?
I'm learning how to breathe.
You might actually have to
know some of this stuff.
I know this stuff.
I know how to breathe.
Okay. I know that you know how to
breathe, but there's other stuff.
Okay.
Stop!
You are strong. You are healthy.
Your body is going through
a beautiful transformation.
That's a load of shit.
I want you all to imagine a
place that's calming, quiet.
Make it a specific memory.
Where are you?
On the beach on our honeymoon.
How old are you?
Are you alone?
Breathe into this memory
that brings you joy.
Okay, everyone, please breathe.
If you're gonna sit up,
sit up slowly.
Very slowly. Keep
breathing, everyone.
Please remain calm.
Sam. Are you okay?
- So, this is happening.
- Yep.
We are buying baby stuff.
Baby stuff!
- Let's go crazy.
- Yeah, let's go nuts.
Ooh! Uh...
Do you want to practice a little diapering?
Get a little wrap around this guy?
- I'm good.
- You don't want to do that?
He's not even in a box.
He's clearly dirty.
Yeah, where'd this baby come from?
I don't know you, baby.
You bent him over, looked at his
ass to see where it came from.
I just wanted to know if he
had a name or something.
Ah...
It's a milk pump!
Not at all.
- No?
- No.
- We need one though, right?
- Yeah, we do actually need one.
I never want to see you
do that ever again.
Probably not.
No, I think we got everything. This
is all a baby needs, right here.
Ow!
Are you all right?
I'm gonna go get the car,
all right? Just hold on.
No, I'm fine.
No, seriously, Sam.
Please, just wait there.
I'll be right there.
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Oh, shit! Sam!
Motherfucker!
What are you doing?
Are you fucking crazy?
- Get away from my car!
- Stop, stop!
It's okay. It's okay.
We're gonna get some help.
It's all right, it's all
right, it's all right.
What happened? What happened?
Breathe. Just breathe.
Just breathe, just breathe.
What is wrong with me?
Something is wrong!
Hey.
You look really pretty
when you're pensive.
I'm serious.
Hey...
Look what I found behind your ear.
Nothing.
- Oh, hello.
- Hi.
Hi, Samantha. I'm Dr. Dylan.
Where's Dr. Ludka?
Dr. Ludka had to take a leave
of absence. I'm covering for her.
Well...
Excuse me. Is she gonna
be back anytime soon?
She filled me in, and
I've studied your file.
Well, will she be back
by the time we deliver?
Yeah, can we talk to her?
I don't think she's gonna be able to come
back. Let's talk about your symptoms.
Oh.
Okay.
Huh.
The baby looks healthy.
But it's turned around.
We're not gonna be able to find
out if it's a boy or girl today.
- It's gotten so much bigger.
- Mmm.
Sam, are you okay?
She just needs a minute.
Sorry, the nausea hasn't
really gotten better.
It actually seems like
it's gotten kind of worse.
Well, it's not entirely unusual.
Um...
She's been getting nosebleeds,
too. Are those...?
Yeah, it can be.
She just doesn't seem
like herself lately.
Is there a history of mental
illness in her family?
Uh, I don't know.
She took some meds during
college for anxiety.
I don't really know what they were.
Um...
We don't really know
anything about her family.
Her parents were killed in a car crash
and they had to cut Sam out of her womb.
I'm sorry. I had no idea.
Hey.
You look beautiful.
I'm really sorry.
- It's all right.
I'm gonna do an amnio now,
just to rule out any issues.
Especially since you don't know
what may run in your family.
Okay.
- Are you all right?
- Mmm.
Okay. Good.
I'm good, too.
Good. I was worried about you.
I know. I could tell,
because you asked.
Uh, is this gonna hurt?
Oh, it's just a little pressure.
It'll be over before you know it.
I need you to stay very still.
Nurse, watch the monitor, please.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Are you ready?
Just relax. Take a deep breath.
Mmm.
Mmm-mmm.
Are you okay?
- No.
- It's okay.
Something's wrong. Can you
get it out? Can you get it out?
- Keep her still.
- Is everything okay?
- No, no. Mmm-mmm.
- Just try to stay still.
- Samantha, we're almost there.
- Can you get it out?
Can you get it out?
Please, get it out!
You're gonna hurt
yourself. Sam, please.
Get it out!
Can you get it out
of her? Thank you.
It's out. It's done, it's done.
Hey, hey. It's done.
It's okay. All right?
It's okay.
I can't do this. I can't do this.
It's all right.
I'm really worried about her.
I don't know what to do.
Do you think she'd ever
actually hurt herself?
What?
No. I don't know, I don't think so.
Just to be safe, we'll be
keeping a close eye on her.
Okay.
I'm gonna fix this door someday.
Yeah, that'll be great.
- Watch your step.
- Okay, thank you.
I'm so glad my sister
bought me that flashlight.
How are you doing?
I feel like a hot air balloon.
- You're going upstairs?
- Mmm-hmm.
- I'm gonna go take a bath.
- Okay.
I'm just gonna check
the score on the game.
All right.
This thing takes
forever to turn on.
We need to get a fucking maid.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh, look.
That's beautiful.
Wow. Nice.
Do you want to take off while
we wait for the results?
Go to a spa, or...
Let's just get out of town.
- It's a good idea.
- Yeah.
I'm just thinking, though, you've
already taken so much time off of work.
And I've got finals and we should probably
be close to the doctor right now.
All right. It's just a thought.
It's a good thought.
I'm gonna be all right.
I know.
One second. Okay.
Surprise!
- Happy birthday, darling.
- Wow, thank you.
Great, son. How are you?
I'm very well, thank you. Hi, Ma.
- Happy birthday, Aunt Sam.
- Oh, my gosh.
Happy birthday!
No, I'm fine, I just gotta rest.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
Why are you guys
hiding in the corner?
Hey.
Looking good!
- Thank you.
- Um...
She's just gonna go upstairs
for a little bit, take a rest.
I gotta lie down. I'll be back.
I'll come up in a little
bit and check on you.
I just need a few minutes.
- I'll clean all this up.
- No, I got it, I got it.
I'm gonna help you, too.
It's fine, I got it.
You guys got everyone here,
I'll clean it all up.
It's no problem. That's
what friends are for.
- Can I have some cake?
- Yeah, here you go.
- Is this too big a bite?
- No.
Oh, that's cute.
- We're the sweetest.
- We're so cute.
How's Sam?
I don't know, I haven't been
up there since she went up.
Honestly, in general,
she has not been herself.
The doctor says that everything is
fine, and we've done all these tests.
But she's just convinced that there's
something wrong with the baby.
- She's adamant about it.
- Wow.
Braedon.
Come out, come out,
wherever you are.
Braedon?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Come on, I know you're in here.
Braedon.
Braedon?
Braedon, come out.
It's not funny anymore.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Braedon.
Get out!
I think I just saw you move.
All right, come on. Do it again.
Lift this back so we can see you.
All right, buddy, let's go.
Ah.
You're sleeping like
your lazy mother.
Lazy bones.
It's all right.
Shh.
Mav, hey. Hey.
You know, we talked about
the summer courses.
So, I figured I'd just get a
couple of classes going...
and then go back to the
full load in the fall.
You don't want to just
wait until the fall?
No, I don't want to just
wait until the fall.
Okay, I was just
thinking because...
I know, it's just that
this has come up and I...
No, I know. But the baby
is coming in March.
I know it's not gonna be easy. But I don't
want to put everything on hold just to...
We're not putting everything
on hold indefinitely.
- I gotta keep working.
- But if I stop doing it now...
then I feel like I'm not gonna
be able to start back up again.
I'm gonna be stuck in this house
and I'm gonna become
some housewife.
Then I'm gonna turn
into your sister.
I'm gonna be Natalie, and
I don't want to be her.
Sam, you're not gonna be
Natalie. It's you and me.
That's what it's turning
into. I know that...
but this isn't what I
wanted to begin with, okay?
I didn't want to get
pregnant and now I am.
And I just want life
to go back to normal.
I don't want to talk about it anymore and
my fucking hair is falling out, okay?
Sam! Whoa.
- Hey.
- Hi. Are you excited?
- Yeah!
- Yeah, why?
- Because today's my First Communion.
- Oh, shoot, my bad.
Hi.
Oh, I'm so glad you're here.
How are you feeling?
Well, well, well.
Are you ready for your
big day, young lady?
- You've got the whole family here.
- Yeah.
- Hello, Sam.
- Hi.
- How are you doing?
- I'm doing well, how are you?
I'm good, really.
So, when is the little one due?
- One month.
- One more month.
- One month. That's good.
- Are you all right?
Do you want a bottle of water?
No, I'll be fine. One month.
That's the home stretch, right?
Yeah.
I've just got something in
my throat. I'm so sorry.
- Excuse me.
- Sorry.
I think that's the nicest
procession I've ever seen.
Boys and girls,
we are so proud of you.
And we are so happy...
to have you here this morning on this
big important day in your lives.
Newest members of our church to gather
round for the Liturgy of the Eucharist.
We are here to celebrate with you
today your first Holy Communion.
Also, the first time...
you receive our Lord Jesus
Christ into your souls.
Uh...
Excuse me.
Uh, this sacrament...
It is a sacrament...
Father Thomas, are you okay?
Where was I?
He needs help!
It's okay, Father. Go call 911.
Thomas, Thomas.
Hey, whoa, Sam.
Hey, hey! Stop, Sam.
Look, it's me.
Hold on. Stop. Stop!
All right. Hey! It's okay.
I don't remember what
happened back there.
With Father Thomas.
Did I...
Did I do that to him?
What? No.
Hey.
What the fuck is wrong with me?
Hey, hey! Stop, Sam.
Look, it's me. It's Zach.
Hold on. Stop. Stop!
All right? Hey! It's okay.
- Zach...
- Let's just go. Let's just go home.
Oh, I am so sorry. Where was I?
Jesus Christ into your soul.
Born from death.
Twenty? Oh, it's free.
- Look at this little guy.
- Hey, little guy.
Yeah, I hear it.
No, Zach, come on.
These men are staring at me.
What?
I said, "These men
are staring at me."
Hey, babe, let's put it away.
- Come on.
- No.
Yes. I'm sorry, but
we gotta get up.
Ugh.
I'm so hung over.
Yeah, no kidding.
Hey, Mason, it's Zach. Um...
Can you come over for a little bit?
I need to talk to you about something.
Thanks. And I'll meet you outside,
in front of the house, okay?
I don't want to bother Sam.
Okay.
Mmm...
How did we get home last night?
I don't know. The guy in the cab?
What the fuck?
He was like our cab driver,
on our honeymoon.
So I came home, looked at all the tapes,
and there's all this mystery fucking...
Look at this.
You sure, man? Maybe it's some weird shit
they do down there to scare tourists.
Whoa, what the fuck?
What the fuck?
It's gone.
What are you talking about?
I was literally just looking at
this shit right before you...
I was looking at this right before
you came in, and now it's gone.
It's empty. It's gone. The
fucking tape is gone now.
Fuck!
- Why don't you just take a breath, man?
- No, I don't need to take a...
Wait, hold on. What the fuck?
We've been monitoring him 24/7.
Uh, do you think I can
talk to him privately?
If he needs anything,
we'll be right outside.
Father Thomas, how are you?
I had a small stroke.
Yeah, we heard.
Are you gonna be all right?
How is Sam?
Um, she's okay. That's
actually why I wanted to...
- I'm glad that she's okay.
- Talk to you. Um...
I saw these weird symbols
on our honeymoon.
And, um, I just don't know
really what they are.
And I thought you might...
because everything I've seen says
they're, uh, religious symbols.
So, uh, there's these ones...
and then there's that.
There's a bunch more.
These are the only ones I've
actually seen in person.
The other ones were all just linked
to it when I started looking.
- John, first John.
- What?
First John, 2:18.
"And children,
this is the last hour."
"You have been told
the antichrist is coming..."
"and so, that there are
many that are coming."
"That is how we know
it is the last hour."
What are you talking about?
These are from early, early religion.
These are...
early religion, there
is a sect, dissident.
They tried to bring the church
down in its early days.
They did rites, and they
used those symbols.
They painted them on the point
of entry and on the nest.
The point of conception
and the point of birth.
- What?
- So that he could get in.
There was ash all around.
There was ash everywhere.
The antichrist is coming.
"So will there be
many antichrists..."
"and that is how we know
it is the last hour."
"They will be coming."
I didn't mean to upset you.
- It's the last hour.
- I'm really sorry.
I don't think you can be here with
that anymore. You have to go now.
- I need you to go now, Zach.
- Yeah.
I'm very, very tired
and I need you to go.
- Put that away.
- It's gone.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I'm really sorry.
I didn't mean to upset you.
You've upset me. Just go.
- Go.
- I hope you feel better.
Now! Go!
Okay, all right.
Nurse? Nurse, can you...
Um this one is from you.
This is from Emily.
There's more to come.
That's just a taste.
Whose is this one?
I don't know. It
doesn't have a name.
Does this belong to anybody?
Well, anonymous.
- It's nameless.
- Anon.
You're just getting
gifts from everywhere.
Sorry, whoever this is from.
Brooke!
What a sweetheart, Brooke!
I didn't read the note, so,
I don't know what's happening.
That's nice of you.
Sam, are you okay?
How was the shower?
Fine.
Did you hear that?
Fuck.
Every window in the house,
but a lot of them in these.
This is really mostly where I see
it, so I don't know what to do.
You know, I have to admit,
it is, uh, kind of weird.
Someone was in here, all right?
Someone broke into our house.
- Wait, hold on a second.
- But, look at the porch.
I can file a report, and call us
if there's any other problems.
That's all I can do for now.
You have a nice night.
Okay, here we go.
- Here he goes.
- You're gonna break your neck.
Uh, uh, uh!
- Oh, he got it! No way!
- Wow, I'm so impressed.
- What's up?
- Take this. I gotta take a piss.
Oh, fuck.
I'm out.
Do you want to come?
Will you hold it for me?
No, she doesn't want to.
Since Jay's gone, do you want to...
Hey, guys! You gotta come see this!
- What is he doing?
- Fucker.
You're fucking me up.
Look what I caught.
- What is that?
- Oh, fuck.
- Dinner is served, y'all.
- Jay, stop.
- That is so gross.
- Oh, what in the fuck?
Please, don't touch it.
Oh, it fucking stinks!
- Hey, take a photo.
- I'm taking a video, jackass.
- It smells like shit.
- Touch it, see if it's still warm.
- You guys, there is something over there.
- You're so fucked up.
Look! Do y'all see that?
- Shut up.
- What?
Wait.
Yo.
Hey.
- What is she doing?
- Ash, stay back.
Ma'am, are you okay?
What the fuck is she doing?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh, my God.
Oh, shit!
Ma'am, are you okay...
What the fuck!
Run!
Come on, man. Get up!
What the fuck! Oh, shit!
No! No!
Oh, fuck.
Hey, are you all right?
Yeah, I'm good. Actually,
I feel a little bit better.
Good. Um...
Do you need anything?
No, I'm good. Thanks.
Okay.
Sam?
Hey.
Sam.
What are you doing?
Sam?
Hey.
What's going on?
Are you okay?
Sam, what the fuck is going on?
Whoa, whoa, whoa...
Don't touch us!
Sam, it's just me. All right?
It's just me.
Stop, stop, stop! Sam!
It's okay, I think you're
dreaming. Hey, stop.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's me. No, it's me.
I got you. I got you.
It's me.
It's all right, I'm right here.
See, see? Look, it's just me. Okay?
Are you okay?
It's okay.
- What's happening?
- Nothing.
You just had a dream.
It's okay.
The McCalls. Leave us a message,
and we'll call you back
as soon as we can.
Hey, Dad, um, it's Zach. Uh...
Look, I think Sam and I need to come
over and stay with you and Mom.
Sam is really freaking out and
it's gotten me really scared.
It's just not normal, okay? And I
know this sounds really crazy...
but I swear, there have
been people watching us.
We just don't want
to be alone, okay?
I think we'd just feel a lot better
if we were with you and Mom.
So, uh, call me back.
Fuck.
Hey!
- Hey.
- Hi.
Thanks for coming over. Sam
is upstairs, she's sleeping.
Is she feeling okay?
Yeah, she's fine. I just need
to take off for a minute.
I didn't want her to wake
up and have no one be here.
- Okay. Where are you going?
- Just don't answer the door.
Okay, bye.
Weirdo.
Hmm.
Sam?
Hey, Sam?
Hey.
Sam?
Samantha?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Sam, Jesus! What are you doing?
Sam, hey, hey! Give this to me.
Stop, stop, stop. Sam, stop.
Give this to me.
Sam!
Sam, stop!
Fuck.
Shit.
Fuck!
Oh, shit!
911, what's your emergency?
I need some help.
Something is happening to my wife.
Please, send someone over.
- What's the address?
- 901 Harrison Street. Please.
Sir, I'm sorry, I can't...
Shit.
What the fuck?
What do you want?
Leave us the fuck alone!
Sam?
Ah!
Fuck.
Shit. Fuck.
Sam!
What the fuck?
Sam?
Oh, Jesus.
What the fuck?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Sam!
Shit! Fuck!
Sam?
Sam, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Stop, Sam. This isn't you.
Please. Please, just come with me.
Please, let's go. We gotta get...
Oh, God.
Suzie?
Suzie? Suzie?
Fuck. No, no.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Fuck.
Sam.
Please. It's okay.
Come on, please. It's me.
Come on. Just come with me, please.
I'm sorry.
It's me, come on.
No!
No! Stop!
Please. Please.
Sam. Sam!
Sam!
What are you doing?
Please, just let me down.
Sam! Fuck!
No! No, Sam!
Sam, no!
Stop! Please stop, Sam!
- Zach?
- Sam.
- Zach.
- I'm here.
What happened? What happened?
It's okay, it's okay.
- Is the baby okay?
- Yeah. I love you.
Is the baby okay?
Yes, it's okay.
Don't worry, it's okay.
I'm sorry.
No. I love you. I love you.
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
No, no, Sam.
Sam.
Sam, no.
Fuck.
Please...
No. No, no!
Stop. Just stop, please.
Just leave us alone, please.
No, leave her alone.
Leave her alone!
No.
Don't, don't, don't...
No, no. No!
So, what did you do with the baby?
They took it.
And this is the same "they" who
killed your wife and your sister?
You know, we checked.
The Anderson house.
It's been abandoned for years.
Completely empty.
And there's no Dr. Dylan at Willow Oak
or any other hospital in the area.
Why don't you tell us...
what really happened?
Mr. McCall?
Look at it. Oh, my God!
I got it, sweetie.
That's so amazing. It's
like a dream come true.
Okay, last day of the honeymoon!
Au revoir, Paris.
All right, let's do one together.
Can we come back next year, baby?
- We are gonna come back every year.
- Okay, good. Promise?
- It's been awesome, hasn't it?
- Best trip ever.
- I love you so much.
- I love you.
Let's get a taxi.
- You got it.
- Perfect.
- Bonsoir.
You want a taxi?
Yes, please.
- Come, get in.
- Okay.
- I take you somewhere fun, eh?
- Okay, yes.
Authentic. Outside the city, but...
- All right, good.
- Let's go somewhere fun.
- It's first time here?
- Yeah, it's the first time.
- And newlyweds?
- Yeah, how did you know?
Oogum, Oogum, Boogum,
Boogum, Boogum
Now, baby you're casting
your spell on me
You got me doing
funny things like a clown
Just look at me
When you wear
your bell-bottom pants
I just stand there in a trance
I can't move
You're in the groove
Would you believe, little girl
That I am crazy 'bout you
Now go on with your bad self
Now mercy, mercy on me
All right
When you wear those big earrings
Long hair and things
You got style, girl
That sure is wild
And you wear
that cute trench coat
And you're standin' and posin'
You got soul
You got too much soul
I just say who got the blues
Say who got the blues
Say who got the blues now
Castin' your spell on me
Once upon a time
When I was in high school
I was in love with you, lady
And you treated me so cool
I was driving a Chevy '72
It had four on the floor,
girl 120 it would do
And I remember Marvin Gaye
Singin' What's Going On
And there was a war, baby
Somewhere across the sea
I don't wanna go and fight, girl
'Cause you were really lovin' me
I remember Martin Luther King
Lord, he was the man, babe
That gave us all a dream
And I remember Marvin Gaye
Singin' What's Going On
Don't play with my love
And I remember Marvin Gaye
Singin' What's Going On
They used to have
sweet music in the park
Lord, up at Monterey straight
down to the Melody Bar
You used to wear, girl
Them hot pants
When you strolled down the hall
All the boys wanted a chance
And I remember Marvin Gaye
Singin' What's Going On
Don't play with my love, oh
I remember Otis Redding
Sittin' at the Dock of the Bay
But then he went away
And I remember Sam Cooke, y'all
So Bring It on Home to Me
From your love I can't be free
I remember Elvis Presley
And them Blue Suede Shoes
Lord, they gave me the blues
I remember Marvin Gaye
Singin', yeah Let's Get It On