These are the facts:
In February 1959, 9
Russian travelers ventured in the Urals
Two weeks later, all
nine were found dead.
Became known as the Incident Dyatlov Step.
- Okay, go.
- My name is Holly King.
I am a student of psychology
at the University of Oregon.
Gathered in a remote area
in the Ural Mountains in Russia
trying to solve the mystery that devastated
the world for nearly 50 years
known as "Incident Dyatlov Step"
thanks to leader
1959 expedition, Igor Dyatlov.
They failed.
But I was struck by the story
and when my favorite teacher,
Dr. Kittles spoke at room
On a project dealing with the
incident, did not believe.
Commented to a friend, Jenson,
a film student here
and he said that we should make a movie
then ask a purse, and...
Achieved.
Okay, then...
What happened?
I heard the first time about the incident
by a Russian journalist, Yuri
who published a fictionalized
version of a book of sci-fi
"The Highest Level of
Complexity Yuri Yarovoi"
Sure he had him killed.
Russian writer Yuri Yarovoi
crashed into a empty road on 01/28/1980.
No matter who has fictionalized the facts
they do not want anyone
talking about Dyatlov.
And I started to use the "incident"
as an exercise teaching in psychology
Because there is a lot to know
what happened in Dyatlov Pass
in such detail
and whole thing still remains
shrouded in mystery.
What explanations usually used?
The most common explanations
call "scientific"
is a disease called dementia hypothermia...
Dementia hypothermia
this is literally the most widely used,
but my preferred
is called...
"Paradoxical undressing".
It's something that happens with
severe hypothermia sufferers,
disoriented, think they are
overheated and bare all.
Holly, 9 were experienced there,
tells me that they all
had hypothermia severe
while the same night?
They were out 3 days ago,
because at that moment?
An avalanche is another frequent response.
This, is even more stupid
than "paradoxical undressing".
Hearing the avalanche would be the
3 hours out camping without boots?
But after entering answers
the question nameless
my students will introduce their own fears
The Russian army?
I hope my students
propose something more believable...
I want to put them in place of those people
to understand why
victims did what they did,
this is the answer we seek.
Let's find out the truth?
- You know you'll never find out.
- What?
There is no truth.
The first leg of our journey will
Eugene-Oregon-Chelyabinsk Russia.
Not going to use those stupid dotted
to show the journey, right?
Wrong!
The last destination is Kholat Syakhl,
literally translated as
"the Mountain of the Dead."
Seriously!
The name takes into account the
numerous mysterious deaths
and disappearances
throughout history, so...
Find an audio engineer, Denise Evers.
The only operator on campus
audio that fills... physical requirements.
Bunch of skinny guys in Audio.
What's wrong with skinny?
Ah, sorry, was wrong.
And then we found two capable guides.
Andy Thatcher, President of
Northwest Trails Association...
Climbed all the mountains of the
USA, and also mochilei by TA.
- Forgiveness?
- The Appalachian Trail,
stretches from Maine to Georgia
I went in the summer.
- So you think you realize that?
- Yes
Why would you do that?
No more I can climb
U.S., is a challenge for me.
- Are you afraid?
- No.
You know, recreate a trip
where 9 people died.
50 years ago, come on?
Not the Snowman.
- Yeti!
- He's gone now.
- And you are?
- Is JP Hauser.
- JP.
- I drew.
You think you're ready for this?
This guy was here
in Himalayas, is ready.
- Really?
- Yes
- I took some time off.
- A long time off.
What kind of Hauser?
Hauser Hall?
Type construction that we are facing?
A itself.
This reminds me of my philosophy,
I take care of children after!
We have our team, it's time to work
:
studied maps, prepare gear and join
chopped and supplies
and then trained in the local mountains,
are excited and eager to go.
- I hate those snowshoes.
- It is so cool with them, Jenson.
Hey, what do you think of these boots?
Almost all hate that.
Shit!
Now, January 25...
Is time to leave.
Still looking for 5 students
missing last month
in the Urals.
Remember that three days
rescuers found items
to be students, tents, backpacks
and other equipment.
Ivan, our Russian correspondent
Channel 24 has more information.
Good afternoon, I'm Ivan Kudryavtsev
and you're watching the Russia-Canal24,
continue following the event that occupies
the attention of the international media
and the news is more
commented in Russia
the disappearance of the Ural Mountains
a group of American documentary filmmakers
that, as you may know, followed the
steps of the expedition Igor Dyatlov
9 whose members died in mysterious
circumstances in 1959.
Experts
raise several theories for disappearances.
I think I made contact with aliens,
a ship or something...
In recent years there have been
several interesting phenomena on site.
The more I study the place, date
mysterious signs and...
And sinister, even mystical,
area is shrouded in mystery, which feeds
such theories, even the mystic
are understandable because has long been
reports that testify objects in the sky
and today this area is common
reports of Yeti footprints.
Also a native tribe, ethnicity
Mansi, have their own theory.
An elder Mansi remember that when
group Dyatlov disappeared,
Native reported noises and balls
of fire over the mountains.
Believe that place...
Is where two worlds collide...
where you can pass from
one world to another...
Is where
enters the world of spirits.
The Canal24-24 Russia continues to inform
recent disappearances
in the northern Urals,
where 5 U.S. documentary filmmakers
disappeared mysteriously
in the same place, in 1959, the group
Igor Dyatlov died.
Thank you, Ivan.
Students recreated the ill-fated journey
seized by Igor Dyatlov
8 and other Russian explorers
50 years ago for a documentary.
The most promising clue is found
equipment team recording
Experts watched the footage without
disclose it in the press, but today,
a group of hackers calling themselves
ConspiraLeaks gained access to footage
and posted on their web-site.
I opened the door and darkness
followed me, and in my dream.
Hey, come on.
Hey, hey, hey.
- It was just a dream, just a dream.
- Excuse me.
Jenson, never leave here.
Excuse me...
One month before
We arrived to Russia and the next
point of our journey is Chelyabinsk
and then to the Urals, into a city called
Ivdel.
- Beautiful tattoo, angel! Has another wing?
- It's unique, and it hurt like hell.
Anything else I should know,
something you want to show to the camera?
Keep dreaming, pervert.
And this phone?
It is equipped with GPS universal,
and where there is no signal,
here GPS navigates
anywhere in the world.
Cool!
Sorry, can not help
know I did not bring fluid.
- Do not do it.
- Talking to the camera?
Chatting with Lucile.
Really?
Type a girl?
Filmmaker
are quite connected in their cameras.
No power, baby, she's jealous.
- Thank you.
- Quite linked...
Thank you.
What do you think? Think will put
backpacks and spend the week?
Is a test, you know?
Man against the elements.
Millennia People survive without
these things happening,
just do everything right,
and I bet you will.
Your confidence is daunting.
Enters those without trust,
you will not return.
And you, JP?
I thought well,
and live only once,
want to try to see and
do as much as possible,
I have everything I need in
backpack for months...
- That?
- For years, maybe. Yes, that.
How many people can say that?
I hope that does not need much.
- Yes, you never know.
- Never know.
We spent Monday in Ivdel,
then we can interview Piotr Karov,
the 10th member of the Dyatlov, who
got sick on the first day and came back,
shortly after he had a breakdown and
came to this Psychiatric Hospital.
Back.
Stop the camera!
Hey, hey,
does not touch the camera!
Turn it off!
- No recordings!
- Yeah, tell that to the camera!
- Go away, please!
- The Cold War is over, we're friends.
We can not interview
Piotr Karov?
- He died. Now go.
- What?
- How did he die?
- Go!
- Friendly, no?
- Holly, in the upstairs window!
What?
Is it?
- I can not understand.
- Oh! Ow!
It was Karov?
What did he say?
- Have you seen?
- What the hell!
I know I look like Jenson, but I
believe I saw Piotr Karov that window,
and I really want to know
what they tried to show,
but could not,
and trains do not go here
Try to ride Vizhaj,
let's start backpacking.
Best Jenson unless U.S. ambassador,
could restart the Cold War.
Okay, these guys say
bar here has a native
then we should give because there
has a native, the family is Vizhaj
are we can get a ride,
sounds good?
- Come on.
- Bar does not sound good.
- It's the wrong way!
- No, this is where we should go.
That's what I was talking about! Jenson
1 0 Andy.
Look, accept dogs,
Company home.
- Hilarious!
- Calm!
Holly, you know because it has no
drunk driver in Russia?
- No. - Yeah, give!
- Hey, a photo! Come on!
- Yes!
- I timer on the camera.
Only available on iPhone 3.
Come on!
- A... - Xis. - Two... - Three...
- West Coast!
Do you speak English?
Course.
- Something to drink?
- Yes, please!
Jenson, looked for a ride.
We are young beautiful people
foreign land who would like a drink.
- Where are they going?
- Vizhaj.
And then that drink?
Vizhaj?
Why?
We are making a documentary about
the incident from Step Dyatlov.
Ah...
So should try it!
- What's in there?
- VIP gentlemen.
- Here comes the shot!
- Shooting? Oh, no.
Owe me a special favor,
anyone have a cigarette?
Looks like they're having fun.
- Beautiful... - Memorable bottle, huh?
- Beautiful bottle.
- God, she smelled?
- Yes!
Fede.
- Maybe not so full.
- Chora!
They are great!
Let us then!
- Then I start?
- Wait, wait!
God, what a mess.
- It's the end...
- Gonna mess with me, kid.
Let the shot!
The success of your trip.
- Thank you.
- "In zdorovje"
What?
I mean, I know nothing about the people,
culture, history or women
Russia but did my duty as
home to good manners.
- So... cheers!
- Cheers guys!
Shit heavy!
You guys are viadinhos?
- What is it?
- Well ..
- Sa-ma-gon.
- Samagon.
Like a drop coaster.
Yes, because it served Samagon?
Serve them right here.
- Before leaving.
- Who? Who are they?
Dyatlov!
Drank it before leaving.
Stop it.
Not funny.
- There is an omen, right?
- No, it's just a coincidence.
- We want another round, friend.
- Yes!
- Get down! - Making a movie?
- That's right.
- And going Vizhaj?
- Yes
Yes, you know how to get there?
'll Take you.
Go?
All right.
Leave tomorrow!
- Yes - Yes
- And take all?
No problem.
I said it would work.
Okay, serve this guy a drink?
- A drink. - What do you want?
- Vodka.
Thank you very much.
No problem, I'm Sergei.
See, not so bad.
- Who let Jenson go ahead?
- At least we have the girls, bro!
- Keep dreaming.
- How far is...?
Vizhaj.
Some 40 miles (65kms).
Forty?
Great.
At least we have enough potatoes for stupid
chew.
- Denise, let's go!
- Guys?
My eyes froze shut!
Not funny.
What do I do?
- Wait, do not move.
- Take it easy on her, Andy!
- Hold on!
- Shit.
Expected, the other!
There is.
Everything okay?
Yes Thanks.
Cold here? I feel that...
You're...
- Feels like... cold.
- Okay, let's go!
No, man!
Not cool.
- I'll give you $ 100 if you lick the bumper!
- I'll give you a dollar sucking JP.
Come on, guys!
Hey, will love it. I found that
Sergei came to visit her aunt.
Wow, that too!
No, she was part of the first
rescuers to see Dyatlov.
- Wait, seriously?
- Yes
- I asked her to speak if they want
- Yes, I do!
- I want.
- I'll be in the movie, right?
- You bet!
- She speaks English?
Better than I!
Can you translate something for me?
- Here, take the camera.
- Yes, of course.
Let's go and find her aunt.
- What's her name?
- Alya.
She is a teacher.
What is this?
Piotr The name arose.
- Like this?
- Yeah, I guess.
What does it mean?
Stay away!
Tell us what happened.
My brother Vallik, father
Sergei, found the first body,
still remember how he screamed,
when he returned later.
Proceed.
Did not take long to find the others,
track...
A trail of corpses...
Find two
and woman
a trail to campfire set up where
there we two
and four, in the ravine.
We were so sad,
but not surprised
when we discovered
there were no survivors,
but it was so weird...
I felt,
people got nervous...
I felt so,
had something wrong with the place,
I left there wanting to get rid of it
,
was when I found two more
on the north side.
There was something wrong with them,
more than others,
and something...
Snow near them.
A machine!
- As strange.
- Excuse me.
Let...
Cut a minute.
So found 11 bodies.
-
Yes - Are you sure?
I know what I saw, young lady,
'll never forget.
But the reports, photos of
scene, all report only 9.
So what?
Believe what everyone tells you to believe
or else believe in your own heart?
'll Leave them a trail next.
Not like we have
thank you, Sergei.
- I told you!
- Did what?
Aliens!
What else can it be?
And the military? You said
conducted an experiment with them.
- Well then change my vote pros aliens.
- Yes, it makes much more sense, Jenson
And you, Andy? The think the
theory of aliens Jenson?
- Stupid.
- It is the silent type, huh?
I do not think Andy agrees with his theory.
Whatever.
Do not get me shoot?
Shoots mountains.
Sounds interesting, JP.
Hey, Andy!
Denise did not take his eyes off you.
Yes, your eyes say:
Oh, Jesus!
What an idiot!
So, guys, it's all what they expected
?
-
Yes - Oh, yes.
!
The words lost?
Is this?
- This what?
- "Kholat Syakhl"
Yes
The Mountain of the Dead!
Jesus!
As you can see, the weather changes quickly
,
and changed.
My racquet again!
Piece of shit.
- We could die here.
- Better go before nightfall.
- The weather will change.
- Jenson!
- Yo! - Just one more picture!
- Come!
Guys, this is too much!
So Mr. Hauser, which tricks
cooking at camp?
Well, I like to do
as simple as possible, so...
You have to Dried Mountain Chili...
delicious.
You know I'm vegetarian, right?
- Really?
- Yes
Do not know...
Have Macaroni and Cheese, huh?
Okay, so let bottled water?
Is using the snow?
We need fresh water, but without
drama: the snow boiling kills bacteria.
- Smell amazing.
- JP, his master cook.
Wait but...
Will burn your mouth.
Idiot!
Because it gave me,
knew it was hot!
- I still do not feel like it.
- Alright.
- Surprise for everyone.
- What?
Chocolate?
- Looks tasty.
- Is it all the time?
I sleep well anywhere.
- I have a surprise too, Denise.
- And what is it?
Cut firewood when I got with the guys.
Thank you.
Cool.
- Life-Size.
- What do I do with it?
- I can show you later if you want.
- Sure can.
How many nights
with these guys?
Two.
Tasty.
How's the pepperoni?
Good
- Want?
- No, thank you.
Oh Jenson
show me your beautiful eyes.
- This is sexy.
- Is sexy?
How's your first experience on a film set
professional?
And this is a professional set?
This? It's the best set
which could start.
It's cool, but what about you?
As thought was backpacking?
- I thought it was good, easy.
- It? - I need sleep...
And gives you backpacking,
and gives you mountains.
Hoped to lead the expedition tomorrow.
Food can not stick with it.
- Think, smart!
- It's a dick, is not understood.
But guess
feel the difference, huh?
Jesus Christ.
And hearing this, 'm satisfied.
- Do not want to hear.
- If called hilarious. - Really?
Is not it beautiful?
What?
The aurora borealis.
Oh, right.
Yeah, well...
Adorable.
- How is your tongue?
- Well
Now, forget the aurora borealis,
Garner Denise is there.
Believe me, I'm not interested
in perverting Denise moment.
Okay, what are you doing?
Week Incident reported
orange lights in the sky,
six witnesses totally different.
- Aliens?
- Is what most think,
the official report was "unusual
atmospheric conditions"
Light of reflected light in
clouds or something.
- But I do not believe it?
- Hey, is not sleep?
Start early tomorrow.
- Okay.
- What?
The big day.
Yes, I'll just...
See this.
Okay.
What was that?
- What was that?
- That Sound!
Forget.
Holly! Arise! Something was here,
gotta see this!
- Is jokingly Jenson?
- Holy shit!
- What the hell.
- Okay. Action
- Denise?
- Do not like it!
Denise, if something happened,
was last night.
Do not know.
I do not see any danger, I know it
is strange and so I want to shoot.
Okay, whatever.
Can you wait a minute?
Thank you.
You idiot!
Okay,
woke up and found something strange:
footprints, located between these
two stones and around the tents,
format is strange,
see how big they are?
And the other... is greater...
Two pairs, two different people.
- People?!
- I speak not of Yeti, Jenson!
Come on, look at the size
of these footprints!
I do not know, a bear, a tiger
Snow!
- What? Snow tiger?!
- The Snow Tiger is extinct Denise!
What is more strange:
Anyone walking in this type
Snow boots need special
need to grip, then use
stakes or gloves well modeled,
but are footprints soft, and is
whatever, were bare.
Andy told us that low
night temperature here...
- Freeze the toes in 10 minutes.
- What explains the Yeti.
- There's your fucking Yeti!
- How do you know? - The damned do not exist!
- Do not know!
- By God, Jenson!
Okay, filming.
No footprints are inside
or outside of campgrounds,
is as if something fell from the sky,
walked barefoot around the stalls
and then rise again.
- Yeti flies too?
- Hey, Mike. - Hey.
Can we go?
- Has snow tiger here?
- No damn tigers here.
Come.
Not have to cross it, right?
No.
- are well? All morning quiet.
- Yeah, all right.
- Do not look fine.
- So for us to fill.
They think I'm filling?
No, we think Bigfoot
was in camping last night.
How could it be fake?
Okay, Holly, nobody ever did
Bigfoot footprints in the snow.
He's right, Holly,
fun is cool, but
look around you,
is the last place
to scare someone.
Do not know what they are talking about.
Left So say we all
the limit this morning.
Holly!
Did you hear that?
The entire team wonders
whence comes this strange sound,
watched the tape and no one can tell where
is
and then found this...
As in camping,
the trail has no beginning or end...
're A little scared.
Holly! Come here,
more footprints!
- What is it?
- A meteorological tower.
The footprints are all over the area here.
The collar measures the wind speed.
No more, probably.
- Hey, what are you doing?
- Following the footprints.
Whatever makes that sound,
is here, and want to know why.
- E?
- Wait.
What the...
- You okay?
- Okay?
-
Yes - Are you sure?
Holly...
A language?
- It's not safe, Holly!
- Yes, that's what I saw.
Seriously, it's a language!
We must go now!
- Denise, can only...
- And the footprints?
- Jenson said it comes from there, listen!
- Voyage of Jenson. Give me a minute?
Hey, come on.
Is filling the bag with this stupid movie
.
Okay?
Is everything okay?
Yes, just scared,
is everything.
But you know, everyone is.
I heard about these steps
mountain in China
where birds fly against walls and
people and animals go crazy and die
and all because the wind generates a sound
4 Mega Hertz
that makes people get mad.
- I think that...
- Wind crazy?
Jenson, all saw the tape and
hear whatever it is.
Please tell me what is?
I heard this before.
Jesus Jenson.
This mountain is really "fantastic".
I stopped someone
mention how much I hate these rackets?
Someone?
No?
- Guys, wait!
- Come on slug.
Guys, wait, is here we come!
- Thank God!
- Are you sure?
I saw the pictures hundreds of times,
this is, was what happened here,
this is Step Dyatlov.
53 years ago today that nine people armed
camping in the same soil,
they had dinner and went to bed
and somewhere between 9 and 11
the night, something that Russian officials
defined as "uncontrollable force unknown"
caused the flight of nine of its
tents in such a state of terror
they tore the inside
and threw the night,
to 17 degrees below zero.
Gonna love this, Andy.
TV socket.
It?
Which one?
A gay.
- It was good.
- Gracinha, Jenson.
Rustem Slobodin, 23,
the first to be found.
Igor Dyatlov, 23,
scout leader and most
experienced of the group,
probably was his idea to try
to go back to barracks.
Kolmogorova Zinaida, 22
just a year older than I am now
was the nearest camping
when the force arrived,
and only victim that showed signal strength
,
was no language and a large portion of your
oral cavity.
Dubinina Ludmila, 21,
Nicolai Thibeaux-Brignolles,
Alexandrovich Zolotarev,
Alexander Kolevatov.
The cause of death for all victims
was defined as hypothermia,
But Rustem and Nicolai also
had serious skull fractures,
and Ludmila and Zolotarev
Alexandrovich also had broken ribs,
but no bodies tried to defend injuries
on the other hand does not have
external injuries...
Somehow, something tried
crush the skull of two men
and broke ribs and Ludmila Alexandrovich
without leaving anything more than bruises.
Moreover, Alexandrovich was positive for
high concentration of radiation.
Hello!
Where here
contracted Alexandrovich much radiation?
And because he alone?
Georgiy Krivonischenko, 24,
Yuri Doroshenko, 21,
when others fled,
they sat quietly near the rest of the fire
Quietly and froze to death.
- What is it, Andy?
- Nothing.
Not sound like anything.
The GPS seems primed,
should not be at this point.
Seems suspect.
Think this is my fault too?
- I dunno, it ruined?
- Not!
She must have moved at my watch
Also, the altimeter burned,
it and see,
compass went crazy, went pro Himalayas with
and it always worked, but here.
I think we should leave.
- What? Just arrived!
- But we have to go back...
're Blind without GPS or reliable map.
- What's wrong with the map?
- There should already be here.
How so?
According map covered 23 kms today
not arrive before midnight.
So what?
We are fast.
Look, let's go and follow
compass to stop freaking out
is obvious that some of the magnetic field
rocks and such
stop elsewhere that no one
would notice the difference.
- I have to finish the images before.
- Forget about the footage, Holly!
Obvious that something
is wrong, we should go,
begin to put it all together, gives
time.
No, no, no, do not want to get
,
but if we start together and we will be
walking in the dark and that's not good.
Guys, it's a night
people live for thousands of years
without clocks and without GPS
I think we got one night,
what was to come.
Okay, let's have dinner.
Thank you.
Hey.
's Going on a date there.
Strange, I feel that I am
sailing.
Just do not understand what she sees
a guy like him.
- It's so arrogant...
- Confident...
- Full of himself... - Arrogant...
- Asshole...
You know, there's a room that
tent, you come in?
Oh, maybe you too,
I'm sure I will someday
boyfriend as cool as Andy, so...
What are you doing?
Nothing, just...
Shit!
Thank you, thank you.
It is one of the reasons why
can not find anyone.
Not find anyone,
so I'm going with you.
In their desires.
You know what Andy said...
About the magnetic field of the rocks?
Yes?
And if not that?
Okay,
tell us what you have there.
So, this is a pretty basic Geiger counter
,
without complicating,
it detects radiation levels.
Like here,
definitely no radiation in this area.
Uranium could be rocks here?
There is nothing dangerous, but
is more than you should.
Yes, the source of it...
Surely comes from there.
Let's check.
- In this direction.
- Beware!
Lucile not like it.
I think I found something.
Hey, Jenson.
See that thin ice there?
-
Yes - Snow...
Yes?
What is?
Looks like someone was here,
type in recent days...
Be careful!
Okay.
Here well up here.
- Holly, beware!
- Okay.
Wait.
Jenson, I think it's a rock.
- Shit! you're Getting this?
- To picking, I'm picking up.
Be careful!
- See that?
- Yes
Continue, continue.
Come on!
- What is it?
- I do not know.
- Oh, my God!
- Oh, Jenson!
See that?
Tell the camera what you see!
What do you see? Let
.
A cave or something...
God, Jenson...
lower the camera and come help me.
- It's a door!
- What?
Lower the camera.
We have to film this!
's So weird!
Of course it is, Jenson, see!
Is a door in the middle of the mountains
!
What are locked from the other side?
Is designed to keep something inside.
- Yes, but what?
- Holly!
Look around, come on!
The Russian government took a long time
building a big solid door
to store something in the
mountain, we must not...
Jenson, and why is she here?
Do not want to know? The unstoppable force
unknown? Yeti or alien or...
One superman designed by the Soviets?
I want to know what is
and the answer is behind the door,
Then could help me, please?
Okay?
Expected.
Is now open,
but is frozen, it seems.
Well, it means that we can open up
derretermos ice.
- Let's call them and get hot water.
- No, Jesus...
- Why not...
- Why?
You want to go here...
This will only scare them more...
And do not want to change
the camping, okay? So...
Count tomorrow
now and then we come back, okay?
Hey, guys!
What's up?
- Let's go to bed?
- Sure.
Good night.
- Goodnight, Holly.
- Good evening.
Good night, guys.
What are you reading?
Slaughterhouse 5.
- Do not like Vonnegut?
- I love this book.
- I thought of him yesterday.
- Good.
I'm impressed!
- Sit, teacher.
- Thank you.
Just take it from here...
Yes, impossible to heat
when sitting in snow all the time.
I think my ass will not know when
crap.
- They found something with the Geiger counter?
- Not totally clean.
Good,
I think, I mean,
hope you find something to your movie.
Still have time?
Love young.
Hope you're right that...
Thatcher is a nice guy, but not
concerning boyfriend.
What?
I think he's cute.
Speaks master to stay on track.
Staying on track?
Yes, let me see, man,
Stay in camping,
a track in the middle of nowhere
especially when it's cold
and the girl needs caress.
A romantic, my God!
- Not the worst.
- He has herpes?
This is not, not.
Know the camera on the phone?
Oh, no!
It records?
Not only is the map panorama reliable,
is also the head by the camera.
No, Denise.
She will fall.
And you, what is your tactic?
Te present to my only friend
"Colonel Whisky".
- Hello, sir.
- Yes, please.
John Patrick Hauser,
're trying to get me drunk?
Is the easiest way to get
paradoxical undressing.
Cool.
- Can you believe that?
- Not power, it's just a flirt on track.
- Just a flirt on track?
- 'Re Filming, Hauser said.
I'm not sure...
This sequence wet.
Lucile Whenever we call, right?
Hey man, you laugh but...
If shoot this illegal in the
state of Oregon, then...
I would not, but unfortunately there is
,
so I have to maintain a
professional relationship she
mostly.
Well, I'm going...
- I'll sleep.
- Okay.
- Good evening.
Sweet dreams.
Sorry for accusing him of faking
footprints.
Okay. Do not know if it was fake, then
thought the same thing.
I jumped into a conclusion unwarranted.
Hoped that hit me,
but you good people.
Well, if you want to apologize...
Such warm me with a caress?
- Really?
- Yes
Yes
are 6 am
guess is...
The third day
and we know Denise.
- What are you doing?
- Huh?
- Our own movie.
- Ready again?
Why are you so surprised?
Surprised me,
with the explosion.
Explosion?
Turn it off!
- What?
- Turn! Off! No!
'll Say I never did
sex at the camera?
- Andy!
- Oh, wait, that's part of the show.
I have to admit it?
- You'll have to admit...
- Andy!
Shit!
What is this?
- What is it?
- Hear that? - Yes!
Guys?
Everyone okay?
What is this?
What the hell is that?
Shit!
- Denise! My God, out soon!
- Guys!
Denise, get up!
Avalanche!
Come on, quick.
Denise!
Run, run!
Come on!
Denise comes!
Denise!
No!
Andy!
Oh my God!
Where's Denise?
- Denise!
- Denise! Denise!
She's gone!
Denise died.
No way, man,
is waiting somewhere!
She's gone!
- I'm sorry.
- She died.
You abandoned her!
- Abandoned her!
- Fuck you!
- Used it for a flirt on track...
- Shut up now!
He's right!
Had not how to do anything!
- Tried to kill her!
- It was an avalanche!
Wake up, man! They tried to kill us and
bury, and think it was an accident?
You crazy bastard,
speaks as if there were no avalanches!
're Talking not seen these explosions?
Choose? Or
explosions were the ghosts of the mountain?
- Do not know what happened!
- What!
Anyone discovers this,
look around!
I asked permission for the trip,
then know our itinerary,
JP, they know exactly where
we are and when we arrived,
just waited for us to sleep,
Jenson is right,
someone tried in kill!
- Holly, you too?
- Oh, God!
Okay, so tell me, who is it?
The military man!
- This is serious!
- Listen, you do not know...
Shut up!
Please shut up,
can not believe Denise died, but true
Now we have to pull ourselves together,
and focus on not losing anyone else.
- Andy, what do we do?
- My first aid kit.
Okay, now what?
'll Have to go back to the place my leg.
Okay, Jenson, get the camera.
- I can do that!
- Take care, Holly!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Sorry, sorry, sorry!
- Andy! Need to cut your pants.
- Okay.
- I'll be very quick!
- Okay
Just do not...
Wait, try to be gentle!
Shit!
Shit, okay.
Need to calm down,
and will be okay.
Okay, okay, I can not cut
, will rip.
Okay, JP,
'll have to help me with something...
Oh, my God! Okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
- God, this is so good. - What?
- Okay, okay, okay.
- I can not, JP!
- It's okay. Leave it to me.
Not bad as she said, is only...
Jenson, take a twig or
something to use as a splint.
- No, no, no!
- Not so bad, it'll be fine.
'll Be fine, I promise I will...
This will hurt a bit
will hurt a bit, okay?
Have to replace it...
Have to replace it now!
- Ready?
- Yes
count of three, okay?
- Three breaths, okay?
- Yes
- Are you ready?
- Make logo!
Okay, on three.
Okay?
A...
It was not so bad.
Not for you!
- I'm sorry, it's over.
- Not! - Okay.
- Okay.
- This thing're on?
Off,
do not want them to see me like this...
This does not work!
I paid for the international plan.
This is stupid! We need help, we turn
flags.
- If we see who did it...
- Nobody... did it!
I do not know, JP, maybe
Jenson is right.
No!
So Andy took the plunge and
bag is too far for someone to see us!
Gotta same record?
No matter the end of it, I
record what happens to us
not done so as
Dyatlov another mystery.
If we do that, we can ask for help before
?
I do not think we can carry Andy.
What is this?
- What?
- That look...
What the hell is happening?
We found something with the Geiger counter.
What do you think?
A port.
What?
Freezing in the damn snow all day
and says he has a fucking bunker here?
But we can not open,
radiation is... strong.
How strong?
It is not dangerous, but...
Unbelievable!
Planted footprints?
No!
Do not planted footprints.
Not believe.
Great, not believe me.
Okay,
if someone started this avalanche,
reason is there, right?
Yes
Light up the flags, so people will
will not have chance to kill us.
Okay.
Come on!
What?
Orange lights in the sky.
JP, I'm sorry,
should have told you
but they were so concerned
with the compass, and...
With the map, and...
And did not want anything to happen that
.
Yes ..
Follow step by step how
they killed nine people,
what you thought would happen?
I do not know.
I just...
Always felt attracted to this place
do not know why,
can not explain.
I do not want that.
Do you think anyone will see the flags?
I do not know.
If to freeze here,
opened that door with radiation or not, ok?
Yes
Okay.
Want blueberry pancakes
or Macaroni and Cheese?
Have to eat blueberries for breakfast...
To grow.
Hey, Jenson!
- What is it?
- Hey, man...
Sorry for Denise
true, think what you want
, but sorry.
Yes, me too.
Oh, shit!
Someone is coming, look!
Help!
We need help!
We saw the flags!
Are you well?
Our friend got hurt.
- No, look, it's a lie.
- What?
Are no backpacks,
as they arrived so fast?
- Are following us.
- I said, detonated the explosives.
- Who?
- The military!
- Go, go, now!
- We will not leave you, Andy!
Go I can not go anywhere.
- Help load!
- I'll get it, we will.
- I can not go anywhere!
- One, two, three.
Okay!
- I can not...
- Shit!
Can not go, can not, will!
Go Now!
- Jenson to the door!
- Come on.
- JP, have to follow us, okay?
- Vai.
Hey, give me the gun signaling
let me.
Quick!
We need to go now!
- Come on!
- I will not!
- JP, come on!
- We have to go!
We'll send help!
Jesus, are shooting!
What the...
Holly!
O Jesus!
- Not!
- Go!
Oh my God!
- Let
- JP! - Get out!
JP, come on!
Come on, Holly!
Arise!
- Open the door.
- Shit! Shit! Shit!
Opens!
It is open only froze shut.
Guys!
- Shit!
- Oh, shit!
Opened enters!
Quick!
Come!
- Holly!
- Close the door, close the damn door
Lock!
Bolt on the other side,
and they have closed!
- My God locked us!
- JP?
- Yes?
- You okay?
No, I'm bleeding a lot.
Press the injury.
- It's okay.
- Stop for a second.
Take the camera,
light on camera.
Good.
Okay, got it!
Oh, God!
What do you see?
Is a tunnel!
- What?
- We're in a tunnel.
Okay.
What do you see?
An alternator...
Alternator power.
- League!
- Okay.
- Works.
- Thank God! - Right.
- Should lock the door.
- Why?
Why lock yourself out,
can come whenever you want.
No one will enter, face,
is wasted forces.
- Is an emergency...
- Looked around?
No one will come to save us.
We are on our own!
They know that in a few
days we will dehydrate
and not have to worry
with any of us.
Then just lock themselves
the door and come back in a week.
Unless if we find an exit.
- Can you walk?
- Yes
- Okay.
- Beware, beware.
Shit!
Okay.
- Let's rectum.
- Okay.
- Jenson, stay close.
Slowly, slowly.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Okay,
better take a break.
Shit, shit!
Another tunnel, another tunnel.
JP, JP...
What?
What is it?
I felt something.
What?
There's something here!
- Follow.
- There's something here, Jenson, I swear!
There's nobody here, Holly!
Come on!
Shit!
- Which way?
- Left.
- Take it easy. Do not stop, do not stop.
- Right.
The lights are still here.
- Stay close.
- Okay.
Shit.
- Not very fast.
- Right.
Jesus!
What is this place?
Is a...
Laboratory or type.
Still is.
What happened here?
Who will know?
Sit down, let me see.
Wait...
Here.
Use this.
I'll Be fine.
Sorry.
It will hurt a bit.
I found an opening.
- Be careful.
- Yes, no problem.
Look at this place.
Holly, come here, look at this
.
- What is this!
- A thick book, I think.
I know that word.
- Yes?
- Yes ..
Saw her several times while researching.
What is the meaning?
Killed in combat.
This all?
Can you read something else?
Only dates.
1945.
1959.
Year in which the explorers were killed
,
and then.
What?
Is a boat.
Is the Eldridge
USS Eldridge,
the Philadelphia Experiment.
Philadelphia Experiment?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Come on, live in the cave and such?
In 1943
the U.S. Government made a
experiment with this ship.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What kind of experiment?
Teleportation.
Oh my God!
There are rumors of people
saw the carcass of the ship,
but no one has ever seen
anything like this,
type these photos are top-top-secret...
Someone could be killed because of it.
Oh God!
Okay.
Let's get out.
- Yes
- JP, can walk?
- No.
- Shit.
I'm not leaving here, okay?
So think of something.
Find a way out, okay?
Okay, and then I'll go back and
carry you out, okay?
Come on!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Jesus Christ!
Is a cave formed naturally...
Do not know if the output is
seems a little wild.
Turned espelelogo now?
See it.
Seems nuclear power for electricity
it has here.
Alexandrovich was here, which was picked
radiation.
You have to have an outlet.
Caution!
Oh, my God!
What is it?
- Still works.
- Yes, give me that.
I knew someone had been here.
Who is he?
A military.
Why is he here?
When killing five Americans want
to keep a secret buried for 50 years
send someone to make sure
that the secret will be kept.
- What are you doing?
- Checking something.
Shit!
A we found at
Meteorological Tower.
Is his tongue?
How did she get there?
Something must have started.
So the door unlocked.
Could be doing an experiment there?
He said he has a lot of it in progress.
My God!
Holly,
looks at the bullet holes,
this is not a laboratory,
is an execution chamber.
Oh God!
Holly, what is this?
Seems one of the soldiers that book.
I do not understand.
- Jenson!
- These things do not...
Not appear normal.
Maybe that's why we left here.
What the hell is that?
Wait!
This door was not open.
What is it?
Be careful!
What is this?
JP?
God!
There's something here, Jenson.
- Oh, no!
- My God!
-It's Blood?
- We gotta get out of here, okay?
- What is it?
- I do not know.
- A type of light?
- No lower.
Let me see that.
Is this the same camera, and still
battery. See what's on it.
- No recordings!
- Yeah, tell that to the camera
- Go away, please!
- The Cold War is over, we're friends.
- I do not...
- Accelerate before the battery runs out.
He died.
Stop!
See what's on it.
- No recordings!
- Yeah, tell that to the cam...
Shit!
This is impossible!
No, maybe not...
Remembers Eldridge,
the Philadelphia Experiment?
He allegedly was teleported
from Philadelphia to Norfolk.
- So what?
- So what...
Reportedly arrived in Norfolk
10minutes before leaving Philadelphia.
I mean that is a
damn time machine?
No, I mean anyone,
elite scientists or the government,
none knows
Nobody knows what is happening or has
notion of how fuck is this.
Holly, all these experiments were abandoned
,
Eldridge's crew, who not
fused to the deck, went crazy,
suffered some...
Change...
Mutations...
People do not mention these things.
JP!
Jenson, come on!
Come on!
JP!
Jenson!
What are you doing?
Get out there.
- Where were they?
- Go back to get me.
Control yourself,
recompose now!
- JP!
- Come!
On the ceiling, the ceiling!
Jenson!
- Jesus Christ!
- Jenson!
- From where?
- I do not know.
Look, it's up there!
- Jenson, where he was?
- I do not know!
- Where was he?
- Catch the JP!
Jenson!
Let him out the door and ran after
, understood?
Understood!
- Run! - Beware!
- Go, go!
- Over here!
- Come on!
Run!
Go!
Jenson, here!
Because let us run?
Why not prevented?
I do not know, we should be dead.
Do not kill us when they had a chance!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What the hell is that?
Like a giant fossil.
- What are you doing?
- Waiting for us.
- JP! I said I would come back for him.
- It can not see what they did with it!
If we open the door, do the same with us
,
're trapped, and they know,
're exactly where they wanted.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Holly saw that?
- Yes
Do it again.
- She recorded this, right?
- Yes
Good.
I knew, I knew...
What!
- Teleportation.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Those creatures,
the way disappeared...
Were intangible,
can teleport
but not through these doors.
Therefore lock from the outside.
There must be a connection between
those things and this place.
They came here,
they came of it.
Makes sense...
Type this is...
A giant...
"Wormhole"
type one...
Carrier.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- How to get here?
- I do not know.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Holly
the Mansi, the natives, all
here for thousands of years,
Do not know how this thing works, but
is what they are trying to say.
So they built a teleporter?
I do not know, maybe just found this thing
the cave and drew,
it may be some kind of alien technology
,
maybe try to turn into a weapon.
And if there are more portals
like this in the world?
If these things come from within it...
Explain all kinds of unsolved mysteries,
the Eldridge, the appearances of
the Mothman in Point Pleasant,
'll know what else!
- The flashlight was already.
- Shit.
- Jenson, I see nothing!
- Okay, stay with me.
Here you are.
Watch your step. Okay.
Without opening the door, not in
reach if we sit here, okay?
Got it?
Right.
Happened...
What?
I opened the door and darkness
followed me, and in my dream.
Hey, come on.
Hey, hey, hey.
- It was just a dream, just a dream.
- Excuse me.
Jenson, never leave here.
Sorry.
The camera is connected?
- I see the light.
- Yes
Okay.
I have an idea.
Enough with the old game, Jenson,
are spending battery.
No.
The portal...
What about"
holes that bend the space time continuum
and cause panic in the human brain"?
This is my plan...
See?
No controls...
Has no buttons...
Which means that it takes
you somewhere specific...
Or anywhere.
Nowhere.
What I think too.
But what if...
You...
Fix a place
clearly in mind,
you concentrate,
so to there that takes you.
As they say, there's no place like home
us, it's easy.
Yes, easy.
And let's not blow
the mountains and such?
Do not know hope not.
We will die here, Jenson.
This is it...
Or laboratory.
Okay.
What do we do?
It will tell you what we'll do,
but I think there should be a place
fresh in his memory,
somewhere close by,
A place whose image is in your mind.
Outside the mountain.
Tells the other side of the door?
It's the most fresh in our minds,
and now that the door is closed
,
protects us from those things, right?
Okay.
I'm scared!
"It's all right, and everybody has to
do exactly what he does"
Where is it?
Slaughterhouse 5.
Never read.
So here we go.
Other bodies.
Vallik!
But I think all the tourists!
Who are they?
- Stay away!
- She heard him move away!
- Stop!
- We did not do anything!
- We just wanted to help.
- Alright...
The army declared quarantine
this site to find out what happened...
Return with others to the city, please.
- Go!
- Okay.
What are you doing?
How will discover what happened if
are removing everything?
- C'mon, Alya!
- Listen to the...
He knows what is best for you,
the situation is under our control.
Do not even know who they are.
Rest.
Left.
- What are you doing?
- Placing them with others.
No, no. Dr. Miktenko
will want to look these.
- Let them separate.
- Why? They are the same from others.
Come on!
Look at these clothes,
never seen anything like this in life.
Put away them fast, fast!
Okay.
Hang them!
- Who are they?
- Perhaps the group Dyatlov.
- Made a mistake coming here.
- No matter,
hurry, let's get out of here.
I hate this place,
gives me chills.
Also in 2013, the world's
leading scientists
are still unable to explain what
happened to the group Dyatlov.
But there are those who believe
that the answers are there,
buried under snow and rocks,
waiting to be found...