Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
Where you going, Violet?
Just to pick some flowers.
Don't wander too far.
♪ My wild Irish rose ♪
♪ The sweetest flower
That grows ♪
♪ You may search everywhere ♪
♪ But none can compare ♪
♪ With my wild Irish rose ♪
Well, hi there.
Do you want one?
You're wondering why
I'm wearing such a funny hat.
I always wear this hat.
So much,
it's a part of my name now.
My friends,
my very, very best friends,
they just call me
Rose the Hat.
It looks like
a magician's hat.
It is.
It's a magic hat.
Do you wanna see?
Nothing up my sleeves.
Nothing in my hat.
Don't worry, that's my friend.
You're missing the trick.
Reach inside.
Wow!
It's so pretty.
Because it's special.
And speaking of special,
you're a little magic, too,
aren't you?
The flower in my hand,
what color is it?
Purple.
Violet,
like you.
You don't eat flowers.
But you do.
But these are special.
Honey, it's the special ones
that taste best.
I should get back to my mom.
No, stay. Stay awhile.
See more magic.
- Ow.
- You are a special
little thing, aren't you?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
No, no, no. Please.
Hey. It's okay, Doc.
It's okay.
There.
All dry.
What happened?
You have to talk to me, Danny.
You haven't talked
since we left...
Please, Doc.
Please.
So,
you ain't talking, huh, Doc?
Weren't talking much
first time I met you neither.
You remember the first time
we really talked?
When I spoke up
inside your head?
Made you feel good, right?
Knowing you weren't alone.
Someone did that for me, too.
And some day, Danny Torrance,
you'll teach someone else.
I won't.
Oh, you won't, huh?
I won't shine, I mean.
No more. It's dangerous.
Reckon it is sometimes.
She found me.
She'll come back and come back
until she gets me.
You're right.
The Overlook's condemned.
Boarded up.
They're starvin' old ghosts,
and they're reachin' out
for you.
Won't stop with her, either.
Pictures in a book.
You said they were just
pictures in a book
and they couldn't hurt me.
Some things,
dark things,
the shining's like food.
The Overlook,
it was always just pictures
to me.
But I didn't shine like you.
Nobody shines like you.
So, you in that damn hotel,
you was like
a million-watt battery
all plugged in.
And it ate it up.
World's a hungry place.
And the darkest things
are the hungriest,
and they'll eat what shines.
Swarm it like mosquitoes
or leeches.
Can't do nothing about that.
What you can do
is turn what they come for
against 'em.
My grandfather,
he was a mean son of a bitch.
Dark inside.
Same type of dark as your dad.
Beat me senseless,
and my grandma, too,
and when he died, I danced.
But he kept on coming back.
Standing in my room.
Suit all gray and stinkin'
from whatever mold was growin'
on him in that box.
So, Grandma,
she taught me a trick.
Gave me a present.
I want you to know this box
inside and out.
Don't just look at it.
Touch it.
Stick your nose inside
and see if there's a smell.
Why?
Because you're gonna build one
just like it in your mind.
One even more special.
So next time
that bitch comes around,
you'll be ready.
Let's get you back to Mama.
Danny!
There you are.
Where did you go, huh?
You scared me half to death.
Don't you do that to me.
You hear?
Don't you ever do that to me.
Don't ever do that to me.
Eh, what's up, Doc?
What's the bit?
What's cookin'?
What's cooking,
little friend? Why, you are.
Me?
Why, yes.
Ouch!
You're killing me!
Agony! Agony!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Let me see now.
It is obvious that this
is no ordinary rabbit.
Therefore, I must dream up
a brilliant master strategy,
ingenious...
You okay, Doc?
Now, what if I lured him...
- Yeah, Mom. I'm okay.
- ...into a rock crusher?
Nah, nah, nah,
too complicated.
Yeah, yeah, too
complicated. But what if I...
Too much detail.
Right.
And what's your name
- again, cutie?
- Dan.
Dan.
You're gonna take
your medicine.
Get off him.
Get up. Get out of here.
Shit.
I think you killed him.
What if you killed him?
I hope you killed him.
You hear me?
Let me kiss it better.
No, no, no.
Whoa. What the... No.
Mommy?
- Mommy?
- Baby.
Here, here.
You can
put her money back, Doc.
You can do that much.
She took mine.
She probably bought
the coke with it.
Doc.
♪ It's still the same
Old story ♪
♪ A fight for love
And glory ♪
♪ A case of do or die ♪
♪ The world
Will always welcome lovers ♪
♪ As time goes by ♪
Henri wants us
to finish this bottle
- and then three more.
- Andi?
Says he'll water his garden
with champagne...
That's right.
...before he'll let
the Germans drink it.
This sort of takes the
sting out of being occupied.
You're prettier
than your picture.
- Doesn't it, Mr. Richard?
- You said it.
And you're older than yours.
Are we staying here
or going somewhere?
Don't you wanna
watch the movie?
I don't see
what the fuss is about.
Chat room romance.
Little gross. Not interesting.
Just watch.
It's interesting, I promise.
Well, it better be,
'cause she's not
all that steamy.
And there she goes.
Aren't you tired?
Sleep.
Okay.
Wait. This is the best part.
I watched her do it
three times now
and it never gets old.
Sleep deeper,
deep as you can.
The pain you feel
is only a dream.
You can explain
a lost wallet
when your wife asks.
But you can't explain this.
This you'll see
every day
when you look in the mirror.
And every time you see it,
you'll say out loud...
"I like little girls."
And the next time
you go looking
for a little girl online,
I want you to remember
that time
you got bitten
by a rattlesnake.
- That is interesting.
- Mmm-hmm.
Excuse me, miss?
Miss. Miss, you left something
in the theater.
You wanna leave me alone.
Well, hi there.
You wanna let me go.
Oh, no, sweetie.
No, I don't.
Mommy, I made this for you.
It's a secret card.
Thank you, Abba-doo.
Does anyone know a magic word?
Hmm. You.
Abracadabra.
That's a great one.
- One, two, three.
- Two, three.
Abracadabra.
I know magic, too.
Sometimes, if I...
Sorry.
Has anyone seen my spoons?
I can do that.
That's nice, sweetie.
- They're on you!
- Oh, they're on me?
What the hell?
Dave...
Abracadabra.
Oops.
Well, hi there, sleepyhead.
Sorry.
I had to sleep you
pretty hard.
You're a tough one.
Willful.
You know, I checked.
Six men in three months
with those little snakebite
tattoos on their cheeks.
Why, you've been busy.
Snakebite Andi,
that's who you are.
So, who am I?
You're some crazy bitch
who kidnapped me.
Just the truth from now on.
You will only speak the truth.
You're the most beautiful
woman I've ever seen.
My God.
Works a little too well,
don't it?
Here's the deal,
Snakebite Andi.
You're a pusher. Hmm?
You can push people.
We haven't had a pusher
around here for a little while
so I'm gonna offer you a deal
I haven't offered anyone
in almost 40 years.
How old are you, darlin'?
Fifteen.
Fifteen?
Oh, God, what an age.
Springtime of your womanhood,
isn't it?
Mmm.
You're not a girl anymore,
but you don't have
a single dent yet either.
Gravity hasn't even
noticed you.
Not at 15.
Men, though...
No, no, no. No shame.
You paid that back,
didn't you?
That's what I'm offering you.
Springtime forever.
Ten years from now,
you're still 15.
A hundred, maybe 17.
Eat well,
stay young, live long.
You like it?
Oh. Sorry. I was just...
That's okay.
People love to look at it.
We used to set this up
in the library.
Community project, just taking
a life all its own.
See, we started with
the clock tower there.
- Oh, yeah.
- Just keeps growing.
Kids call it Teenytown.
The kids build this?
With some help, oh, yeah.
Keep it up,
build the whole town square.
Are you off the bus
or riding your thumb?
Yeah, the bus.
Oh. Not many ride the bus
this far north.
Unless they're looking
for work.
Yeah.
Change of scenery,
or you running away
from something?
Don't mind me.
I hope I'm...
New face is all.
Yeah.
Guess I'm running away
from myself, I guess.
Oh, yeah.
Running away from yourself.
That is a pickle.
You take yourself
with you wherever you go.
- Ain't that the bitch?
- Mmm-hmm.
Rent's 85 a week,
payable up front.
Billy paid your first two,
rest's on you.
No pets, no parties, no noise.
I'm a quiet tenant.
Last guy said the same.
Math student.
Even let him paint the wall
all blackboard,
so he could scribble his
little puzzles up there.
Wasn't quiet. No, sir.
Didn't even paint over this
when he left,
but I'm glad he didn't
'cause I can make this easy
for ya,
so you see it every morning
when you wake.
You sure you wanna vouch
for this pup?
Pretty sure.
It's your ass, Billy.
Bleedin' heart, this one.
I'm downstairs, ground floor,
if you need anything.
Find me tomorrow,
talk about some work.
Why are you doing this?
You don't know me.
No, I don't.
But I know the look,
like I said.
And sometimes I get
this feeling about people.
Hard to understand, I guess.
Easier than you think.
- Thanks.
- All right.
You ready?
She's ready.
Who are these people?
You'll find out after.
That over there
is Grampa Flick,
and he'll lead us.
Lie down.
There.
No fear.
You understand?
We are the True Knot
and we endure.
We are the chosen ones.
We are the fortunate ones.
What is tied cannot be untied.
Here is a woman.
Would she join us?
Would she tie
her life to our life?
Yes.
Say yes.
This one's special.
Her name's Violet.
There's not much of her left.
And she tastes...
like flowers.
Breathe deep.
There. Embrace it.
Embrace it.
No!
No! No!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
They haven't found us yet.
They were used to
hearing him cry
'cause I left him alone
so much.
So they didn't do anything.
And they haven't found us yet.
Mommy?
Oh, hey.
Uh, you said
that you knew my look.
Well, what did you mean?
You're sick.
You're tired.
I can see that much.
I need help.
Come on in.
We'll talk about it.
God, grant me the serenity
to accept the things
I cannot change,
the courage
to change the things I can
and the wisdom
to know the difference.
Well, Bobbie's got
a big birthday today.
Three years.
Three years sober.
Yeah.
Thanks, John.
Well, now for the most
important person in the room.
Is, uh, anybody here a newbie?
Somebody got 24 hours?
Yeah.
New to town, huh?
Yeah, I, uh...
Nothing personal.
I delivered half the people
in the room.
Just new faces pop,
that's all.
This here is Dan Torrance.
- He's fresh off the bus.
- Oh, hey.
Fresh off the ground,
by the look.
Oh.
There's no judgment here,
brother.
I mean, we've all been there.
- And worse, trust me.
- Oh, yeah.
If you're looking
for a wing to climb under,
I can't say
you'll do any better
than Billy Freeman here.
Thank you
for your hospitality. I...
I'm a little, uh...
I guess I'm not used to it.
Well, you know we say,
"You can't judge someone till
you know their whole story."
You might think
you understand,
- but you don't.
- You don't.
So, how are you today?
All right?
Train's still running.
That's good to hear.
You good?
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, good to know you, Dan.
- Yeah.
- Come again.
- Thanks.
- Hope to see you again soon.
I'll come back, yeah.
Really good man.
He's got a gift...
Yeah. Hey, Billy, hang on.
Hey, Doc.
Your watch. Uh...
You lost your watch. You were
worried about the kid with...
Goocher's.
What?
The kid with Goocher's
or Gaucher's. The bone thing.
Gaucher's disease.
Right.
You were washing your hands
in the hospital bathroom
and you left it
on the soap dispenser.
Well, just check
- It's good to meet you.
- Yeah.
How did you know?
I wish I could say. Uh...
Lucky guess.
My ass.
Intuition, I suppose.
Like a feeling in my gut.
Maybe a...
A lucky guess.
What do you wanna do here?
What do you mean?
I mean here in Frazier.
Why are you here?
I don't know. I don't know.
Something different
than I've been doing.
Something better.
You go to church?
Does it matter?
Do you believe in something?
Something...
bigger than you?
Our beliefs
don't make us better people.
Our actions
make us better people.
So, Billy says
you have orderly experience.
That's right.
You workin' right now?
A few shifts at Teenytown.
Helping with the train.
'Cause I do three days a week
at Rivington House,
the hospice.
Good orderly is tough to find.
Tougher to keep.
Do dying people bother you?
No.
We're all dying.
The world is one big hospice
with fresh air.
Hmm.
Wow.
Well, hi there.
You said it didn't hurt.
Doesn't now, does it?
Felt like I was dying.
I know.
You did.
You'll feel better
when you eat.
Am I still human?
Do you care?
Hey. Let him be.
Azreel, leave him be.
Azzie?
Azzie, come on.
Come on. Azzie.
Doc.
That you, Doc?
No, I'm not a doctor.
Do you want me
to get you a doctor?
The cat's on my bed.
Oh, hey, I'll move her.
No.
I knew she would be.
That cat
always seems to know...
when it's time.
- I guess it's time.
- No.
It's just Azzie
being a silly old cat.
Nope.
Been that way
ever since I got here.
The cat knows
when it's time to go to sleep.
Everybody knows that.
I'm gonna die.
Yes.
Let me get you someone.
No.
Known it was comin'.
Doesn't make it less scary.
Yeah.
But maybe
it's just like you say,
just going to sleep.
I mean, there's nothing scary.
It's just sleeping.
You're a strange
type of doctor.
I told you, I'm not a doctor.
Oh, I think you are.
Doctor Sleep.
Doc, I am so scared
it's gonna hurt, or be dark,
or be nothing at all.
And I don't wanna...
Nothing to be scared of.
Just going to sleep.
Finally, true, restful sleep.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you, Doc.
Look, I shouldn't be here.
Let me go get you some...
No, no, no.
You're exactly
where you should be.
Exactly.
I see my wife.
Dan, alcoholic.
Hi, Dan.
I'm not much of a speech guy.
I just thought
I'd hold the chip
and talk about
whatever popped up.
And I'm thinkin' about my dad.
He died when I was five,
so the only way
I got to know him,
really got to know him,
was when I went dark.
When I drank to dull the,
or, uh,
whenever I wanted
to break someone's face,
'cause the drinking
and the temper and the anger,
those things in me were his.
And they were
all I could know of him.
But now, well, now I get to
know him a little different,
'cause he also stood
in a room like this once
wanting to get well
for me and my mom.
And he held the chip
in his hand,
and the chip said five months
and on that day, he...
Before it all...
Well, on that day,
all he wanted in the world
was to stand
where I'm standing now.
And here I am,
so thank you for us both,
I guess.
This is for Jack Torrance.
Hey, Charlie.
Doc?
Guess I don't need to ask
why you're here at this hour.
Do you have pain?
Do you want me to get
Claudette to bring you a pill?
Pill won't matter.
I'm not scared of hell, Doc.
I lived a decent life.
I don't think there is
such a place anyway.
I guess I'm scared...
there's nothing.
We don't end, Charlie.
I know that for certain.
I don't know much else,
but I know that we don't end.
Blueberries.
I can taste blueberries
my mother used to grow.
Can you taste them?
Yeah, I can.
And I can hear Frank
on your old radio.
The one you used to have
on your workbench
next to your tools.
♪ Come fly with me ♪
♪ Let's fly, let's fly away ♪
♪ If you can
use Some exotic booze ♪
♪ There's a bar in far Bombay ♪
♪ Come fly with me ♪
♪ Let's fly, let's fly... ♪
♪ Away ♪
Been a minute, little pen pal.
Abra? School.
Fine, I know.
Hey, Gramps, you seen Rosie?
Watchtower.
You feelin' okay?
Peachy keen.
Hey.
Sorry to interrupt.
Any luck?
- Gettin' closer.
- Hmm.
He's somewhere in Iowa,
I think.
We'll all take
a nice long road trip
once I'm sure I've found him.
Until I do, we...
You gotta open
a canister, Rosie.
We took steam
six months ago, Crow.
Six months is nothing.
That kid in Delaware
wasn't so steamy
and it's already showing.
You see
Grampa Flick's hair, yeah?
Yeah.
I don't think he's well.
Grampa Flick hasn't been well
since Nixon was in office.
I know.
But we need to eat.
All of us.
Are the canisters low?
Course not.
Just no need to waste one
if you're close to the kill.
- Rosie.
- Mmm-hmm?
I might need it
just to find him.
There used to be more steam
in the world, you know?
Oh, don't be daft. Come on.
That's like when rubes say,
"50 years ago, people used to
be more neighborly."
But it's true, Rosie.
There's less steam out there,
and it's weaker, too.
I don't know if it's their
cell phones or diets,
or their Netflix or what,
but I am not picking up
many scents these days
and the ones that I do, Rosie,
are just not that...
I'll open a canister tonight
to tide everyone over.
Thank you.
- You know it, Rosie.
- I know what?
It's why
you're up here every day.
It's why you're always up here
no matter
what you tell the others.
The world's not as steamy
and you are looking
for a whale.
Oh, watch this kid.
Number 19.
That kid is a natural.
He hits the ball every time.
Like he can read
the pitcher's mind.
Hmm. Is that right?
See? You watch,
one of these days,
one of those talent scouts
is gonna get wind of
Brad there. You watch.
Hey, 19,
just saw your game.
You are ready for the majors.
- Well played.
- Thanks.
Hey, you headin' home?
You wanna hop in?
I'll give you a ride.
No, it's real close.
I'm good.
It's okay.
We're friends.
You wanna hop in.
We'll take you right home.
You can take me right home.
You trust me.
I trust you.
No! No, please! No!
No! Please let me go.
Please, I won't tell.
Please. Please!
Number 19.
Kid, you were good.
No!
No, please let me go.
I won't tell.
I won't tell. Please.
It's okay.
Please.
Ah.
Are you gonna hurt me?
Yes.
No!
Pain purifies steam.
Fear, too, so, you understand.
Shh.
Stop.
Stop!
Stop, monster.
Stop. Stop.
What is it?
No! Stop!
Abra! Abra!
Hey, hey, hey!
Sweetie. Sweetheart, wake up.
Wake up, sweetheart.
- Abra, wake up!
- Hey, hey, hey.
- Abra! Abra!
- Stop it!
Jesus.
Okay.
Okay, ready?
They killed him.
- It's okay.
- It's all right.
We had a looker.
Tonight?
Mmm-hmm.
Yeah.
Big steam?
Oh, honey, it was huge.
Where?
East Coast, I think.
You're saying
someone looked in
from 1,500 miles away?
Maybe further.
Boy or girl?
Girl, I think.
She was out of there so fast.
But I swear, Crow Daddy,
I haven't felt power
like that,
raw power like that...
in so long.
Then we need to look into it.
- Sooner the better.
- Yeah.
Case her parents freak out,
send her to a psychiatrist.
You know, they get her on
pills, could ruin the steam.
Might muffle her just...
No, giving Paxil to this kid,
it's like throwing
a piece of Saran Wrap
over a searchlight.
I don't know where she is
but when she comes back,
and she'll be back,
oh, I'll be ready, honey.
I'll be ready.
Morning.
Guess what.
I made a new friend.
His name's Dan.
Abs, are you okay?
Last night, I...
I'm okay.
Sorry about that.
I know that head of yours
is like a radio sometimes.
And you pick up
some weird stations.
Nothing weird like that.
Not anymore.
My God.
I've gotta study.
If I don't study...
Running play.
Hand-off to 11 and...
Coach is gonna kill me
if I don't get these.
Why doesn't he like me?
My hair?
I should change my hair.
The freak
is staring at me again.
What is she staring at?
Freak.
Hey, Abba-doo.
Hey, Dad.
School okay?
How's the book?
Good. Yeah, going good.
I'm writing about
Charleston and Black Bottom.
It's feeling like...
I'm going to
start my homework.
Okay. Good.
That's good, sweetie.
Think Harvard in three years.
We'll see.
Yeah. We will see.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Thanks so much
for shopping with us today.
And remember, we're
always fresh, just for you.
Well, hi there.
Get out!
Get out! Get out of my head!
- Ma'am, are you okay?
- No! No.
Yeah, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
Jesus.
Danno?
Dan? Dan?
Get up. Stand up, Dan.
Come on, Danno.
- What happened?
- Well, you just dropped.
Thought you was having
a stroke. Who's Tony?
What?
You kept saying,
"Please help me, Tony."
Oh.
Well, I'm sorry about that.
Rosie?
We've got a problem.
- Talk to me.
- The looker?
Yeah, she found me again.
- How?
- I don't know.
I don't care.
We have to have her, Crow.
We have to.
Does she know who you are?
Where we are?
No, I don't know.
I don't think...
That's not the important...
Look.
I said she's huge steam,
- right?
- Mmm-hmm.
Yeah, it's even bigger
than that.
I tried to turn around in her
and she blew me out of her
like I was nothing.
Bullshit.
No. Never happened
to me, ever.
I would have said
that was impossible.
Is she food,
or do we turn her?
We don't turn her.
Rosie, are you sure?
If she's what you say
she is, then...
Then we don't want anyone
with that power in the Knot.
Jeez. Think about it.
Have a great day.
You, too.
Hi.
Billy.
You can hear me.
Let's use our outside voices,
all right?
You tracked me down?
It was easier than I thought.
Like GPS, but in my head.
Look, I don't mean
any offense,
but this day and age,
a grown man
sitting with a teenage girl
on a park bench...
I'm Abra Stone.
And if anyone asks,
you're my uncle.
Uncle Dan.
And that's not even a lie.
Not totally.
You're magic, like me.
I don't know about magic.
I...
I always called it
the shining.
And, yeah, we both shine.
Do your parents know?
About my shine?
They don't talk about it.
Or if I use it,
they look at me different.
When I was a kid, I didn't
understand the shining.
I called it "Tony."
I thought he was
my imaginary friend.
I thought you were
my imaginary friend...
for a long time.
How many of us are out there?
There's a lot of people who
have a little bit of shine,
they don't even know it.
They always seem
to come home with flowers
when their wives are sad,
or they do well on the school
test they didn't study for.
But I only met two or three
people in my whole life
who knew they shined.
The baseball boy shined.
His name was Bradley Trevor.
These people...
they look like people anyway,
they took him.
And they ate him.
They ate his shine.
You could feel it?
And they could feel me.
If you could get
something of his,
if you could go to Iowa...
- Whoa, hang on.
- I can help you find him.
Then his parents would know
where he was.
They could bury him right,
at least.
We could also get his glove.
If I can touch that glove,
I can track them.
Easy. Easy.
Because Barry the Chunk,
I think that was his name,
for a while,
before they killed him,
he was wearing it.
Abra, go home.
Don't chase these people.
Don't aggravate them.
And whatever you do,
don't attract their attention.
Find something, anything,
well, almost anything,
to stop that shine of yours.
Keep your head down
and hope to God
that these people
or anything like them,
that they don't see you.
If they see you,
they come back.
Abra, do you hear me?
They come back.
Keep your head down.
Stay safe.
I'm sorry.
Hey, Azzie.
You got your wires
crossed tonight.
That room's empty, Az.
There's no one in that room.
Whoa! Hang on, Doc.
Dick.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I... I... I thought it was...
Thought I was
from the Overlook.
Almost locked me up.
Still getting visits
from them old ghosts?
No, not for years.
Horace Derwent
was the last one,
confetti on his suit.
Said, "Great party, isn't it?"
Shit-eating grin on his face
till I pulled out
a box for him.
That grin went fast.
Hey, it never occurred to me
to ask you back then,
what happens to them
in those boxes?
Do they die in there?
Do you care?
I missed you.
Has it been a long time?
Can't tell.
This world is a dream
of a dream to me now.
Eight years. Little more.
Why are you here?
I'm here because
it all comes 'round.
Ka's a wheel, Doc.
These empty devils
ever found you
when you was a tyke,
if they'd even sniffed you,
you'd be long dead.
They eat screams,
and drink pain,
and they've noticed
that little girl.
They might kill her,
might turn her...
or might keep her
till she's all used up,
and that'd be worst of all.
You can't let 'em.
Why me?
Because she found you.
Because she showed up.
Hell, Doc, why me?
You just walked on
into my kitchen one day,
and I'm still on the hook.
What the hell am I
supposed to do?
Get her what she asked for.
You won't see me again, Doc.
This is my last dream.
It seems to me
you grew up fine, son,
but you still owe a debt.
Pay it.
- Hey.
- Hey, Mom.
You feeling okay?
We missed you at dinner.
I'm okay.
Just had a rough day.
I'm flying out to see Momo
in the morning.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
Abs, is she...
Is she gonna pull through
this time?
I don't know.
I hope so.
Tell her I love her.
Keep sleeping, princess.
You rubes.
Spend your whole lives
making little boxes,
little memories.
Oh, you think
they make you so rich.
You should see mine, kiddo.
Oh, my mind's a cathedral.
Well, hi there.
Hmm.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
He said you'd come back.
And you did.
Good.
No!
Get back! Get back!
You're just a fucking child!
Where are you?
Where? Where did you...
Where...
What did you...
Where did you...
No.
Get out! Get out!
Get out!
Rose?
Trap.
What the hell happened?
Little bitch
set a trap for me.
Oh, my God. Oh, your hand.
Rose! Rose, calm down.
We know where she is now,
right? Now we know.
She was in my head!
- What?
- Stealing!
- What does she know?
- I don't know. I don't know.
- How much does she...
- I don't know!
- I don't know...
- There's a problem.
Not now!
Grampa Flick...
I think he's cycling.
Uncle Dan!
Uncle Dan, I hurt her.
I really hurt her.
I hurt her
and she deserved it,
and that's not the best part.
The best part is...
The best part is
I got in her head.
- Uncle Dan? Are you there?
- Oh, God, Abra.
Can you hear me?
What have you done?
Just talk to the kid.
If we're gonna do this,
then let's do this.
Hi, Abra.
I can hear you.
I don't understand.
You will.
I thought we lived forever.
Did someone
promise you that, Andi?
Did someone say
you're immortal?
I said, "Live long, eat well."
We can live long, very long.
And we do,
most of us.
But we haven't
been eating well.
Not for a long time.
Rosie, he's going.
Rosie.
Yes, love?
I'm scared.
No, you're not.
You watched empires rise
and fall.
Cheered the gladiators
in Rome.
Sailed across oceans
to new worlds
while you fed on
kings, and princes, and popes.
They wrote myths of you,
and made statues,
and they trembled
in their villages, and beds...
and skyscrapers.
So, no...
...you're not scared.
You're a king,
and you eat fear.
Hey, bro.
You know, it's 4:00 a.m.
You've always seen me, Billy.
You have a good sense about
people, is that fair to say?
Yeah, what...
You think I'm an honest man?
A good man?
I do, I do. Dan, I...
I need your help.
The first thing I need is
for you to listen to a story
and try harder than you've
ever tried to believe me.
How's it going?
Oh, hey. Shouldn't you
be getting ready for school?
Yeah, but I wanted
to tag along.
How long
have you been driving?
A few hours or so. We should
get there tonight. Late.
Who's that?
He's my friend.
Maybe my best friend.
You should've seen her face.
She was scared, Uncle Dan.
Scared like
all those kids were scared.
All those kids she's killed.
She was so mad
and so scared that I got in.
That was a new trick.
I've never done that before.
Yeah, me neither.
What was it like?
Like a library.
I guess we're
all libraries inside.
How'd you do it?
Like this. Just a little push.
Abra!
Sorry! Sorry, sorry, sorry!
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to.
It's okay.
What were all those boxes?
Nothing.
Liar.
When I was a kid,
younger than you,
I bumped into
something like these things
that ate like they do.
Only it wasn't a person,
it was a place.
They closed it down after
and let it rot.
But the things
that lived there, they...
Don't go poking around
in there again.
Okay, I won't. I promise.
Phew!
We're almost ready.
We're just loading up.
Good.
Get the caravan on the road
and we'll have her
in a day or two.
I don't think
you should come, Rosie.
The fuck did you just say?
She tagged you.
She got in your head.
Yeah, it won't happen again.
And who knows
how much she got to
before you kicked her out.
She's mine, Crow.
Right now, as far as we know,
you are the only one of us
she could track.
Now, if she sees you coming,
she could run
or set another trap.
You know I'm right about this.
If she pulls a trick on you...
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
But I got some tricks
of my own.
Hey, I think
we're here.
Okay.
I'll see if I can get her.
Abra?
That's the sign.
Pull around back.
She says to pull around back.
And I'll tell you
when to stop.
She'll tell us when to stop.
I gotta tell you,
Danno,
I don't know whether
I hope you're right
or wrong about this.
I mean, if you're wrong,
my friend is crazy.
I mean, full-blown...
mental breakdown,
imaginary-monsters-
killing-imaginary-kids
bonkers.
But, you know,
I... I can work with that.
If you're right, though...
I know.
It's much worse.
You should go home.
What?
No, not you.
I can handle it.
No. We'll take it from here.
Okay, it's just us.
You smell that?
Used to hunt.
I ever tell you that?
No.
Deer.
This one summer,
I clipped this buck.
I was tracking it
for two days.
I got the shot, clipped him.
He ran off, I went after.
Figured he wasn't
gonna last long.
Then he vanished.
Just up and evaporated.
Not a trace.
Truly baffling.
Five days later,
I'm trying a different spot,
miles away.
I come around looking
for a spot for a blind,
then I smelled him.
Smelled him.
Found that buck
holed up to a hollow trunk.
Dead for days.
The smell...
Never hunted a day since.
This is the same smell.
Billy.
Oh, my God!
Fuck.
Fuck, Danno. What the fuck?
They didn't
even bury him deep.
They buried him shallow.
I'm sorry, Billy.
What did you
get us into?
The people who did that...
They're not people.
No. No, they ain't.
Anyone do that
to a little boy,
they ain't people.
Did you get it?
Yeah, we got it.
Is she back?
We're heading back to you.
We'll be back in the morning.
We got a stop to make.
I need you to show your
parents what's happening.
No.
- Yeah.
- No.
They almost think I'm normal.
If I tell them, they'll...
Rose'll go through them
to get to you.
You know that, don't you?
She'll cut them down
without a second thought.
And she's coming, Abra.
They need to know.
So, what's this stop
we gotta make?
You still got
those old deer rifles?
You're Uncle Dan?
- The fuck you think you are?
- Sir...
Hmm? She is 13 years old!
Abra, I told you to show him.
- I told him.
- Well, that's not the same.
I'm gonna kick your ass
before I call the police, huh?
- Hey, hey, hey!
- No, no, no. Abra.
Now, don't you say her name.
Abra...
I'm sorry, Mr. Stone.
I am a friend.
Everything she told you
is true.
No, thanks.
No.
Those people,
they know about my daughter?
They do.
And sooner or later,
they're coming.
We gotta do something.
All right, we're calling
the police, the FBI...
These people have been
around a long, long time, sir.
They're rich, connected.
I don't think they're worried
about the police.
But where are they?
When are they coming?
Where can we go?
Abra can answer that,
if she's ready.
I'm ready.
You sure you wanna do this?
I have to.
I-95.
Barry, the Crow, the Snake,
and a few others.
The trees haven't
changed that much,
so maybe Massachusetts,
- but they're close.
- Rose?
Didn't see her.
But they're coming.
This is the only room she saw?
That's right.
And I made a few changes.
Hid a few things.
All right.
Well, they'll be trying
to track you,
trying to catch on.
And you're gonna let them.
Are you crazy?
Possibly, but you're
gonna let them,
and then I need you to try
and do a little trick.
A magic trick?
They're following us.
Concentrate. You gotta
keep it up until they land.
I know.
This should work.
Good blinds over there,
and there.
They still close?
Getting closer, I think.
This is tough.
I know. I know.
How much longer?
Okay, Crow Daddy,
go get her.
You look relaxed.
You feel relaxed,
don't you, Abra?
I guess.
You should.
Just relax.
We're friends.
You're friends.
That's right.
Just friends.
And we want to take you
to meet more friends.
Good friends.
Well, shit.
The way they talked you up,
I was thinking it'd be
a little harder than that.
The fuck?
Parlor tricks.
Just fuckin' parlor tricks.
No! Get out of there!
Get out of there!
No!
You deserve it.
All of you.
No!
Oh, fuck.
Stop.
I just got one question
for you, sweetie.
Aren't you sleepy?
You're sleepy.
Sleep.
Wake up! Uncle Dan!
Wake up! Wake up.
Wake up!
Fucking men.
Stay back, Billy.
Kill yourself.
No!
Billy!
There is one missing.
I didn't see the Crow.
Where is the Crow?
Hello, Abra.
Abra!
Oh, good, you're awake.
Dan...
Don't bother.
What's wrong with me?
You've been dosed, missy.
More than
I've ever used before.
Might let you wake up
here and there,
but that steam of yours
is fast asleep.
My dad...
What happened to my dad?
Lot of good people
killed today.
Lot of good people.
I'd love to tell you
someone will pay,
some kind of justice raining
down on the sad events today,
but it don't work like that.
We were always gonna have you.
Some of my people are dead.
Some of yours are dead.
Outcome didn't change, though.
Think on that a minute.
The outcome didn't change.
So, their deaths,
all of them,
just a waste.
A waste you brought on
to us all, young lady.
For what?
Please hear me...
Ain't nobody hearing you.
Might as well calm down
and enjoy the ride.
Like I said,
outcome hasn't changed.
No.
Please.
Oh, please, please, please.
Abra!
Abra.
Tony?
Help me, please, Tony.
God.
Okay. Okay.
Okay, okay.
Okay, you always said...
your brain was like a radio.
No one's answering when
you call, so stop calling.
And just listen.
Dan. Dan.
Help.
Hi.
Dan.
Did he drug you?
I'm so sorry.
I'm gonna try something, okay?
But you're weak.
He's blocking you.
I could barely hear you.
You gotta trust me, okay?
Okay?
Awake again, huh?
Might have to dose you
at the next rest stop.
Where are we going?
Mmm, you know where.
Fuck, I feel hungover.
I told you it's good shit.
Haven't felt hungover
in years.
And, you know,
I don't miss it.
Not even a little.
West, huh?
Stayin' off the major roads.
Smart.
Crownville. New York.
Who are you?
I'm the guy
that killed your friends.
It's nice to meet you.
Neat trick.
Haven't seen this one before.
Wanna see one more?
Don't imagine Rose'll be too
happy if you shoot the prize.
I don't suppose Rose will be
happy about any of this.
And when that woman gets mad,
well,
it seems to me you know enough
to know you might
wanna sit this one out.
Count your blessings.
Go on your way.
What's so funny, friend?
Well, it's just arrogance.
It's arrogance, really.
But it makes sense,
if you think
you're gonna live forever.
Stands to reason,
of course you wouldn't
wear your seatbelt.
No!
Dan?
I hope that hurts.
Rosie...
A lot.
You little bitch.
What have you done?
All right, bitch child.
All right.
Sorry.
Dozed off.
No, you earned it.
Where are we?
Ohio.
Where are we going?
Colorado.
Why Colorado?
She's gonna keep coming.
- I know.
- Always.
This only ends if we end it,
and I don't think
we can beat her.
Not by ourselves.
There's a place.
A place that's dangerous
for people like us.
The place you told me about?
The hungry place?
Yeah, that's right.
If it's so dangerous,
why would we go there?
Well, if it's dangerous
for people like us,
I expect it's dangerous
for people like her.
Maybe even more so.
Good.
She's following us, you know.
Yeah, good. Let her.
I'm sorry about your father.
Sorry about your friend.
It's my mom.
What do I say to her?
Hi, Mom.
Oh, thank God!
Abra,
are you okay?
Where are you?
I love you.
When we're safe,
you'll call her
and tell her where to find us?
I will.
Okay.
Not too much further.
Up the mountain.
Here's what we're gonna do.
You're gonna stay in the car,
keep the heater running.
I don't want you spending
a minute inside there
if you don't have to.
She can only come from here.
You can see her
a mile out, easy.
You see lights
on the mountain over there,
you blast me, okay?
But I don't want you going in.
Not until she's here.
You aren't waiting with me?
I can't.
Why not?
I have to wake it up.
Wakey-wakey.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Slow night, Mr. Torrance.
Not for long, I imagine.
You're a whiskey man,
are you not?
I was, most of the time.
On the house.
This was your brand.
Jack Daniel's.
I used to see the bottles
in our home.
Our real home,
before all this.
I smelled one once. It smelled
like something on fire,
which I suppose it was.
I'm afraid you've
confused me with someone else.
It's Lloyd.
Lloyd.
I apologize, Mr. Torrance.
I don't know
where everyone is,
but it'll pick up.
Oh, I know where they are.
And you're right,
it'll pick up.
If you don't mind my saying,
Mr. Torrance, you seem...
put upon.
Put upon?
Pulled into
other people's problems.
I see it all the time,
if you don't mind my saying.
So we lived in Florida.
I'm sorry?
Mom and I.
We never wanted
to see snow again,
so we lived in Florida.
Tiny place,
but it was comfortable,
and we were happy.
I was 20 when she died.
And back then, I saw
when someone was gonna die.
I saw flies. Black flies.
"Death flies," I called them,
circling people's faces.
And in those last weeks,
she was covered,
her whole face.
I could barely see her eyes.
And I...
And I tried to comfort her,
but I could hardly
look at her.
And she saw that.
Maybe something warm to push
away such unpleasantries.
Don't you wanna hear about it?
She was your wife.
I think you've mistaken me
for someone else.
- I'm just a bartender.
- Oh, yeah?
Just Lloyd the bartender,
pouring joy
at the Overlook Hotel.
I'll pour whatever you like,
Mr. Torrance.
Man takes a drink,
the drink takes a drink,
and then the drink
takes a man.
Ain't it so, Dad?
Medicine.
Medicine is what it is.
Bona fide cure-all.
The mind is a blackboard.
And this...
is the eraser.
A man tries.
He provides.
But he's surrounded by mouths.
And a family.
A wife, a kid.
Those mouths eat time.
They eat your days on earth.
They just gobble them up.
It's enough
to make a man sick.
And this...
is the medicine.
So, tell me, pup,
are you gonna
take your medicine?
I'm not.
Dan!
She's here.
Okay.
This place is sick.
Sick like my momo was sick.
It's cancer,
only worse.
What do we do now?
We head inside.
She'll find us.
Well, well, well.
Hi there.
When this starts, run.
Yes, you run, dear.
And then I will find you,
and you will scream for years
until you die.
We'll see who does
the screaming.
Oh, we'll see indeed.
She's right, you know.
You should be afraid.
Why is that?
Because you don't know
where you're standing.
I'm sorry, who are you,
handsome?
You're the one who killed
my Crow, aren't you?
Go.
Clever.
You've made some improvements,
haven't you?
Since the last time
I was in your mind.
How do you know
we're not in yours?
Where are you, pup?
You're gonna die here.
Mmm. Brave words, dear.
Is that what you really think?
You're gonna hurt me?
Yes.
You know,
you remind me of myself.
I can really see it now.
You've got a darkness
in you, dear.
I think the only difference
between you and me is time.
You don't know yet
what you'd do...
for more time.
But I promise you, dear,
oh, you'd be surprised.
Pain purifies steam.
Fear, too, so, you understand.
Hmm.
I was just like you
when I was younger.
I was special,
and alone.
But I met someone who gave me
the gift of purpose,
of community,
and I might have
given you such a gift
if things would have
gone differently.
No?
Defiant, aren't you?
So much like me.
Your mind is so...
This isn't your mind, is it?
This isn't you at all.
You're just the bait.
Enough!
Run.
How the hell did we miss you?
Oh...
You and I should have
met years ago.
Danny.
That's your name, isn't it?
Well, something happens
to the steam
when you rubes get older.
It gets polluted.
Dirty.
You know that.
I see the grease all over you.
You don't shine
quite the same.
Growing up spoils that,
I guess.
Seriously, handsome,
where have you been hiding?
I can make you an offer.
An offer I rarely make.
Oh, yeah? I can't wait.
Such a gifted boy,
hiding his light
under a bushel for so long.
You could live a long,
long time. Live well, too.
Indulge yourself,
no consequences,
no hangovers.
Eat well, live long.
You must be lonely,
being the last one.
I mean,
the last one in the world.
Sweetie, I'm not the last.
Far from it.
I'm just the prettiest.
I assume you know my answer.
Pity.
So, are we doing this or not?
Whew.
Oh, sweetie.
Oh, look at that, huh?
I seem to have nicked
your femoral artery there.
Why, you're gonna
bleed to death, huh?
My, my,
what a temper you have.
So much fire.
Such a waste!
Or maybe not.
Oh, damn.
Even at your age...
it's so good.
You taste like whiskey.
Danny!
Danny boy!
Oh, so much terror.
All your life, huh?
Delicious.
Don't hurt me!
Oh, damn.
What are...
You're not alone in there.
Huh?
What are you hiding, huh?
What's in those?
Something special, huh?
They're not special.
They're starving.
No.
No!
Hello, Danny.
Come and play with us...
forever...
...and ever...
and ever.
Uncle Dan.
Uncle Dan, is it done?
Is she dead?
Great party, isn't it?
Abra!
Try it.
Oh, there you are.
Abra.
You've been very, very bad.
You're not Uncle Dan.
You're a mask. A false face.
Who else would I be?
You're the hotel.
But he's still in there.
Mask is off, then.
Why are you smiling?
Because you don't know
where you're standing.
I know these halls
like my own face, child.
I mean the body
you're standing in.
The face you're wearing.
That's Dan Torrance,
and you don't know him.
Dan Torrance.
Dan Torrance
made one stop
as soon as he got here.
To the boiler room.
There you are.
You were supposed to run.
I didn't wanna leave you.
I'm exactly where
I'm supposed to be.
I can't hold it off
for much longer.
Abra, you need to run.
No.
I'm not going anywhere
without you.
I have to close the door
behind us, right?
Run! Run!
Come on, Uncle Dan.
Get out of there.
Come on.
The fire spread fast,
destroying the hotel.
Purifying it.
I could almost hear it
screaming.
I could hear it dying.
And deep inside, I knew...
I knew you were okay.
I'm sorry I put you in danger.
It was the only way.
I know.
Do you think she was right
when she said
she wasn't the last one?
The world's a hungry place.
A dark place.
Maybe there's more of them
or things like them or worse,
but there are more people
like you, too.
People who stand.
I told you
when I first met you...
that you should hide.
That you should
keep your head down.
Keep your shine out of sight.
But I was wrong.
Shine on, Abra Stone.
You shine on.
Dinner's ready.
Who are you talking to?
No one.
Hmm.
That's not true.
I was talking to Dan.
We go on after.
We go on.
And he's okay.
So is Daddy.
He really is.
Good.
You coming, sweetheart?
In a minute.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org