Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
What are you doing here?
Dreaming.
Well, welcome to paradise.
It's nice.
Paradise may be
inhabited by nesting animals
and two years of dust.
Well, I'm not afraid
of a little work.
It's why we're here, right?
Yeah.
It's nice.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Where's Josh?
Josh...
Hey.
Are you coming in, bud?
I love how they look
right onto the forest.
Makes it easier to see the bears
before they attack you.
Hey, Josh, you're in charge
of smores tonight.
Maybe later we'll get
the fire pit going, okay?
You remember where your room is?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
This is my mom.
Oh, um,
she's very pretty, Josh.
Come here.
No.
I don't play.
I can dance...
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Okay, so we're
going to take this hand.
- Mm-hm.
- And put it right here.
- Okay.
- Okay. Yeah.
Get ready, when I nod,
you press down, okay.
- Okay.
- So...
No, no.
That wasn't nodding.
- Okay.
- Okay, here we go.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Hey, I just want to say,
I'm so happy that...
Go have your own kid!
I'm so sorry.
He's killing me,
I'm going to go talk to him.
Um, no.
This is not a toy.
This stays downstairs,
okay, buddy?
Josh... you know Gail isn't
trying to replace Mom, right?
Okay.
Are you okay, by yourself?
You want me
to leave the light on?
- Josh?
- I'm not a baby.
Okay.
Goodnight.
It's kinda quiet, huh?
Peaceful, huh?
Well, I was gonna
say terrifying but...
You know, I just wanted to say
I know a lot
of women wouldn't...
Thank you, for letting me
into your family.
Mm-hm.
Josh... Josh... Josh...
Josh... Josh...
Josh...
Joshy?
Hey, kiddo. It's me.
Mom?
He's never had nightmares
before, not like this.
Mm... there is a theory
that suggests that we are
all the characters
in our dreams, 30,
if Josh's mom is splitting,
then could be he's just leaving
behind past trauma, so...
Could be a really good thing.
If this is a good thing, I don't want
to know what a bad one is.
Hey!
Hey...
For some reason
this is the only place
you can get a single bar.
And... it's gone.
Well, no news
is good news, right?
Well, he wants a new chorus
and he wants me
to make it more clever.
Alright, well, how about,
go and write your own song.
I'm staying here with my kid...
and my girlfriend. Hmm?
It's catchy but wordy.
Hey... we got you this.
It's just a present.
Josh helped me pick it out.
No, I didn't.
Thanks, Josh.
- I said, no, I didn't!
- Hey.
Look, I'm going to try
to make it back tonight.
But if I can't make it back,
are you two going to be okay?
We'll be fine... ish.
Ooh...
- See, now that's clever.
- Mm-hm.
We'll see you tonight.
It's okay, just forest sounds,
nothing to be afraid of.
How would you know?
Well, you're right actually.
Does Dad love you?
Well, I hope so.
It's not fair.
- What's not fair?
- She's dead and you're...
Go on. Why don't we...
Hey. Josh! Josh!
Hey! Hey!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Why'd you have to pick
our family?
Okay, this is not funny.
I'm going to count to three.
- Go have your own kid!
- Josh!
Oh, my God!
Oopsie.
Okay. Okay, that's...
that's not funny, get out.
Get up! Get up!
That is not funny!
Okay, do not do that again!
Hey, you know, I'm sorry
if I scared you before.
Josh, it's just
you really frightened me.
You can't take a joke.
Wow, this is pretty
awesome, huh?
Did you see
what happened to the trail?
Hey, Josh, maybe don't
go in there.
What does that say?
I don't know,
it looks like Dreamcatchers.
What's this?
I don't know,
some kind of crafty nonsense.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Well, we probably shouldn't be here,
this is somebodys place.
What do you think's in here?
- Tetanus?
- Nope.
There's no tetanus in here.
But lots of stuff for sale.
Some beautiful, some strange,
some a little bit scary,
some yummy.
Ms. Ruth's wild berry jam.
We're just looking for
the trail, actually.
Like what scary stuff?
Do I know you?
You got smart little jack rabbit eyes,
you a little jack rabbit?
My mom and dad used to
live around here.
My mom drowned in a pond.
We should probably go, Josh.
That was your mom?
Come on, we got spirit traps,
let me show ya.
Um, Josh, come on.
I'm not a baby.
No, you're not a baby.
And did you know
that the spirits
wander through these woods?
They like to linger
in old barns.
They visit you in your sleep.
In your dreams.
Do you have had dreams?
Cause a spirit trap
will catch 'em!
Listen, shh.
Oh, my goodness!
They are in here right now!
They're trying
to tell you something.
Something very important.
They are saying,
"Buy Ms. Ruth's
Wild Berry Jam."
Ahh, come on.
I'm just playing with him.
Okay. Come on.
Trail picks up
right over there.
- Great, thank you.
- Yeah.
Hey, hey, hey!
Josh, is that your name?
See you around,
little jack rabbit.
Ms. Ruth was pretty cool.
Uh, well,
she's pretty something alright.
You don't believe that stuff
about spirit traps, do you?
You know that's nonsense.
She said they were real.
She said they catch your dreams.
You know how dreams work,
don't you?
Yeah, they scare
the shit out of you.
Hey, language.
Josh, dreams don't come
from out here, alright.
They come from in here.
It's just your mind's way
of figuring out stuff
that's going on in your life.
So if you're having
had dreams,
it means you're probably dealing
with some stuff that's difficult.
And you could talk about it.
You don't want to talk about it,
you could try drawing it up.
You know, if you can see it,
sometimes it makes it
a little less scary.
Helps you understand it,
and maybe you can figure it out
in your real life.
- Does that make sense?
- I guess.
I want to tell you something,
this is a secret.
You're in control.
Okay, so when
you're falling asleep,
just think good thoughts
about your mom,
you know, think about some
of the good times that you guys had,
and I promise you,
it'll be better.
Okay?
- What did I say?
- I'm in control.
That's right.
Say it a little bit louder.
- I'm in control.
- Okay, scream it.
- I'm in control!
- Yes!
You are.
You're in control, Josh.
- Can I get a dreamcatcher?
- No way.
You're looking at a man
who's just written
16 versions of the same chorus.
Well, I'm not looking at him,
cause you're not here.
Listen, I'm sorry. How's Josh?
He's good. He's been talking
about Becky, which is good.
He's been expressing
signs of anger,
so at least we're talking.
It's raw, but I actually
think it's good.
Luke? Luke...
If you guys
want to come back to the city
- I can arrange for a car...
- No, what I'm saying is
I think it's good
if we stay here.
I think it's good for him.
Luke, can you tell me again,
how Becky drowned?
Joshy.
Hey, kiddo. I've come
to take you home with me.
I told you, she was swimming
and her heart just stopped.
- Why does it matter?
- Well, it's just something
that your neighbor Ruth said,
or maybe it's the way she said it.
Oh, fuck, not Ruth.
Just do me a favor,
stay away from her.
Don't be afraid.
I'm your mommy.
Seriously, do not talk to...
- Gail... Gail...
- Hello?
Luke?
Hey. Hey, Josh.
Hey, wake up.
Wake up, buddy.
Hey, hey. Hey.
It's okay.
It's just a bad dream.
Just a dream.
You okay?
You know it's okay
to be scared, don't you?
Hm?
Josh?
Hey, what are you doing here,
little jack rabbit?
Just trying to find
some spirit traps.
Maybe you better go home.
You come back
with the lady you were with.
Tell her Ms. Ruth
accepts cash only.
Will you please help me?
Are you okay?
Do all these catch had dreams?
Uh, some do,
some catch evil spirits.
Some catch bad energy.
Some catch dreams.
Gail says we control
our own dreams.
She says all this stuff
is nonsense.
She does, does she?
She's a child psychologist.
She knows stuff like that.
- Yeah.
- Anyways, that's why
she's trying to fix me.
- Are you broken?
- Sometimes.
You know what,
sometimes we're all broken.
Take off this pack.
Sit yourself down.
Here, put these on.
I'm going to show you
how to fix some stuff.
So, we use this,
then I won't hurt my fingers,
and I probably won't need to
wear gloves when I do it.
Great job!
I betcha this one will sell.
What do you think?
Why'd you scratch out
the dreamcatchers on your sign?
Well, I don't make
dreamcatchers anymore.
Just spirit traps...
Hey, Josh,
What are you doing here?
Can we please get one?
Okay, wait outside.
Go on.
Well, your little friend
sure wants something.
You know,
some people might find
this kind of thing offensive.
Misappropriating
other people's cultures.
Excuse me,
nobody's got the market cornered
on protecting themselves
from evil.
You know, all cultures
have a way to trap bad things.
This is called a Ojos de Dios.
Here's one from Scotland.
It's called a Rowan cross.
And I have a book to show you.
I know you like books.
People always find a way
to ward off what scares them.
And don't touch anything,
please.
Yeah...
You are nosy, aren't you?
Do you mind putting that back?
Is Noah your son?
Was my grandson.
He's dead, they're all dead!
Just like Josh's mother.
Josh's dad told me
about the accident.
Oh, is that what he called it?
Get out.
Never came back here again,
got it?
Alright.
Are you okay with the light out?
Shut my door.
Once upon a time, there was
a knight named Sir Josh,
and he had a sword.
Shh... shh... it's okay honey.
- It's okay now.
- No, no, no, no, no.
It always starts like this
and then it turns into a nightmare.
- No...
- And then you get all scary and...
No, I'm not a nightmare,
not anymore.
Shh. Now that you
have the dreamcatcher,
I can come home.
Are you really here?
Not yet.
I'm just up here.
I'm not strong enough yet.
Are you hungry?
I'll go...
I'll just eat you.
Dad promised he'd be home.
Well, I know
he'll be back as soon as he can.
We could go hiking again.
Hiking's just walking.
How'd you sleep?
I saw my mom...
in my dream.
She read me a stow.
I'm hungry.
Hey, I make a mean pancake.
So when you dreamed
about your mom last night,
how was she?
She was normal.
She was pretty.
She was happy.
You know, I don't think
there's any pancake mix in here.
I mean,
there's a little mouse poop.
Ow! Ow...
- Why did you do that?
- Do what?
- Leave this door open.
- I didn't do anything.
- Josh.
- I said I didn't do anything!
Hey, hey, hey, come back.
Josh, come on, let's...
let's do something fun.
Well, this is fun.
Dad says not to talk
while fishing.
My mom died here.
Who told you that?
My mom.
What do you mean?
In my dream.
She said that she was sorry
that she had to leave.
But she said
when she comes back,
she'll never ever
leave me again.
Do you want to talk about it?
It's like I know
she's always with me.
But I just feel different.
Is that normal?
It's more than normal.
It's very healthy
and grown up.
You don't have to do that.
Do what?
Act all cheerleadery.
Like you're my mom.
I don't need a mom.
Like I said, she'll always
be in here with me.
- I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
- Ow! Ow!
I'm sorry!
Stop! Let's just pause
for a minute, okay.
Ow...
- Okay.
- I'm sorry.
Alright...
Does it hurt?
I'm sorry I hooked you.
That's okay, sweetie,
you didn't mean it.
That's good.
Ooh, thank you.
Look, this is not a joke,
mis...
Okay, bed time.
Turn it off.
When's Dad coming?
Josh, it's been a long day,
please just turn it off.
Why would you do that
with the photos?
- Do what?
- Don't lie to me, okay.
I swear, I didn't do anything.
Come on,
I thought we were friends.
I didn't do anything!
Door!
Josh, I said no iPad!
Josh... hey.
Dad said Gail loves me.
She wants to kill you.
She does?
Honey, do you love me?
Yes.
Don't you want to see me again?
When are you coming back...
for good?
I'm not strong enough yet.
So I need you to help me.
You need to stop her.
But she's nice,
she took me fishing.
You can only love one of us.
Those are
just the rules, Joshy.
Gail, I'm sorry,
there's nothing I can do.
They're making me
stay another night.
I'm telling you I'm just going
to walk right out of here.
Fuck.
How are you feeling?
Hmm?
I think it's going to rain later,
so it's probably an inside day.
You alright?
It's okay, don't move,
I'll... I'll clean it up.
Don't walk on this.
Sorry, I just...
I'm so tired.
Whatcha been doing
this morning?
Just doing the pictures
like you told me.
Oh...
So, tell me, what's this?
That's Daddy, that's Mommy,
and that's me.
Oh, what's this one?
- This one?
- Yeah.
- That's you.
- Who's this?
That's your dead baby.
Just my mind
working through things.
Um... I'm just going to go
get your sneakers, okay,
so don't move.
Mm, just can't find that extra
pink piece for this.
Does this one go there?
Mm... no.
You okay?
Just a little bit tired.
Me too.
Me and my mom used to do this.
You alright?
Yeah. I think I need to go
upstairs to bed.
Okay, Mommy.
Josh!
Josh! Hey, Josh!
Sweetie?
Hey, hey, hey...
I saw my mommy!
She was killed!
Hey, Josh.
Sweetie. Josh!
Josh. Hey, hey, Josh! Josh.
Hey, you're dreaming.
It's okay.
It's okay, I'm right here.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey...
It's okay. It's okay.
Oh, my God!
Hey, how you doing?
I'm in control.
Yeah, you are.
There's honey in here.
Ruth?
Where is it?
- No, don't go!
- Hey! What?
- Hey, hey, hey,
you can't just come
running in here.
No, he broke into my barn
and he took something!
- Josh?
- Josh!
Don't go away again, Mommy!
Okay, Josh, did you take
something from Ms. Ruth's barn?
Okay, you need to give it back.
No, no!
I don't want it back.
But you need to listen.
It was safe where it was,
but not anymore.
You let it out,
and now you're both in danger.
You need to destroy it now!
I don't need it anymore.
You, stay here.
Just tell me,
what happened to your family?
What happened to Becky,
what happened to Noah?
- Just tell me.
- You're not hearing me, just...
just throw it into the fire.
Burn it!
Okay, fine!
I'll throw it in the fire.
Little Noah...
He was just
a regular little guy.
He was smart, funny.
Was a little bit quirky,
he liked odd things.
He had a collection that
he called his "special stuff"
that had dead animal fur,
bones, dead bugs.
His father would say,
"Get rid of that junk!
Normal boys play sports
and they have friends."
I was his friend.
It was Christmas, and I wanted
to find the perfect present,
and there was a yard sale
down the street,
and I found that thing.
This crazy woman said to me,
"Whoever hangs it in their room
will be protected
from evil forever."
I thought, the perfect present.
Boy, was I wrong.
Protect him from evil?
It was pure evil.
It devoured him,
and then one day he followed
his parents into the woods,
and this little boy
hacked them to death.
Came upon them
all hacked to pieces.
Except for Noah.
Suddenly, he... he just
leapt at me like a wild animal,
and he was waving this axe,
screaming at the top of his lungs.
Make it get out!
And then he killed Josh's mom.
Once upon a time,
there was a boy named Josh,
and he had a hatchet.
As a psychotherapist,
I can tell you
that kids have issues, alright.
And using science,
we just need to treat them
with therapy or with medicine,
and this voodoo bullshit
it doesn't help.
It doesn't help anyone.
And I'm just suggesting
that you just drop it.
Gail, help, I can't move!
Shh!
Sorry.
Hey.
How could you just
leave us here?
I had to go to the city.
Why didn't you tell me
Becky was killed?
What are you talking about?
I read an article, okay.
I don't... I don't like
thinking about that.
Okay, well that's something
that you might
want to mention, alright.
Yeah, I... I know.
I'm sorry, I should have told you.
Hey, hey, buddy!
I missed you.
Uh, listen, Gail and I,
we have to talk for a minute,
so, can you go in the kitchen
and fix me something to eat?
I'm so hungry.
- Mm-hm.
- Okay.
How was it, how's he been?
Uh, not good.
He's been sleepwalking.
Do you guys want some pie?!
Uh, yeah, buddy.
- Sleepwalk?
- Yeah, that's the least of his problems.
He left the cupboard door
open on purpose
so he could hit me
on the back of the head.
He hooked me
with a fishing hook.
Well, I'm... I'm sorry
you had a couple of accidents.
It's not accidents.
I mean, I'm napping, I wake up,
and I am covered
in a sea of Becky photos.
- I don't understand.
- He slashes the scarf that you gave me.
He breaks into Ruth's barn.
She comes here...
I... I told you
to stay away from her.
And... and kids
pull pranks all the time.
When I was a kid,
I... I pulled pranks,
I shoplifted once on a dare.
- This is not a prank.
- And I've slept walked before.
Here, actually.
I woke up in the...
in the fucking woods.
Do you want me
to show you the scarf?
I don't need to see the scarf!
I just want to have a weekend,
with my son
with some quality time,
that's nice, where I can relax!
I understand.
What about me?
Oh, thanks, buddy.
Thank you, Josh.
Can we go fishing tomorrow?
Yeah, we'll see.
Mmm, this is
pretty good pie, Joshy.
Well, I'm glad you like it, 'cause
it's pretty much all we have left.
I'm sorry. It's just...
It's just we've had a few
misadventures, haven't we, Josh?
Haven't we?
Are you okay?
Jesus Christ!
- Did you do this!
- I didn't.
- Gail, come on.
- Answer me!
- I didn't.
- You tell me the truth.
Gail, for God's sake!
I said I didn't!
She hates me!
Okay, we're so out of here.
Tonight!
Josh... did Gail tell you
about the pond?
About mom?
No.
Josh?
I don't want to
get her in trouble.
Goddamnit.
Dad, I didn't do the thing
with the broken glass.
I... I know you didn't, Joshy.
Gail, she's just, uh...
She's just confused
about a lot of things.
She told me
not to dream about mom.
What?
Said it was unhealthy.
And it showed
a sign of weakness.
You just get some sleep, pal.
Josh needs help, Luke.
More than I can give him.
Wait, do you...
you really think
that he did this
to you on purpose?
He broke a glass the other day,
he probably took the glass
out of the trash.
Yeah, what's... what's this?
Huh?
And you told him
not to dream about Becky?
No, I didn't tell him that.
Joshy said that you did.
Joshy says that I did.
You're going to take
a child's word over mine?
'Cause I am telling you,
I'm telling you, professionally,
he needs help.
Kids have had dreams.
Maybe he needs to spend
more quality time with me.
This is based on
your years of experience
working with troubled children?
Based on the fact
that he's my own goddamn son.
I'm telling you,
he's traumatized!
He's experiencing
latent violent tendencies,
and you've got us
stuck here in this house
Where his mother was killed!
Are you fucking nuts?!
No, he's not troubled!
He's confused,
he's six years old.
Oh, Jesus Christ,
he's not six.
- Yeah.
- No, he's not.
No, I mean, I know...
I know he's not six.
Because you would
like him to be six.
No, no, no, no.
No, don't do this.
Yeah. You would
like him to be six...
Don't do this psychoanalytical
bullshit on me.
...because then he could
still be your little Joshy,
and Becky would still be alive.
I get it. I get it.
And we need to get
the fuck out of here.
I'm not kidding!
Honey...
It's time.
She's ready.
Go on.
- I don't want to.
- She took my place.
- Hey, you said you hated her.
- I don't, not really.
It's easy. Watch.
Why'd you do that?!
I didn't. You did.
No!
Hi, Gail.
Luke?
Hey, Luke.
What's going on?
What is this?
I was letting you sleep in.
Because we're getting
on the road, right?
Babe, he's fine.
You're fine, right?
Dad's going to teach me
how to chop some wood.
We'll be careful,
we've got snacks.
Listen, I want to
get out of here.
As soon as we get reception,
I'm calling Dr. Fisher.
I am going to spend
some time with my son.
Twenty minutes,
and then we're out of here.
Are we going to chop
some wood now?
Yeah, Josh, we're going to chop
the hell out of some wood now.
- My turn.
- No, hey... Slow down.
Safety first. Come here.
Put both hands on it.
Okay.
Just little swings.
Nice and easy.
There you go. Okay?
There you go.
Nice and easy.
Good.
Now, Josh,
I said to use both hands, son.
Hey, Josh, I said...
I said use both hands.
Why didn't you tell me
how Mom died?
- Okay...
- A little boy killed her.
Hand that over.
Okay, Josh, that's enough.
You give me that.
Damn it!
Put that down, now!
He threw her body into a pond.
Just a boy.
A boy like me.
Once upon a time,
there was a boy named Josh,
and he had a hatchet.
Where's your Dad?
What's this?
Josh...
Josh!
Put that down!
Okay...
Remember... Can you remember
what we talked about?
Okay, losing control?
Josh?
No!
Oh, my God.
What the fuck?!
What are you doing?
Don't interrupt me.
It's for our own good.
- Josh.
- Josh is dead.
Josh, wake up.
Wake up, buddy.
Josh! Your dad's coming back
and we're going to get out of here.
I don't think Daddy's coming.
What are you talking about?
Daddy wasn't safe
with the hatchet.
It's not Josh.
It's this!
It can't be destroyed,
there's something that is living in there.
It is indestructible.
Josh. Josh!
I saw it.
I saw it last night
in my sleep.
And it was a woman.
A miserable hag.
Okay. Okay, Ruth.
Now you can't possibly
believe this.
She has Noah's soul
for eternity,
but now she has Josh.
We have to kill him, Gail.
You have to kill him.
Or he's going to kill you.
He's going to kill me.
He's going to kill
everybody around us,
and the evil is just
going to keep coming
and coming and coming!
I understand. I understand.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I'm going to help you, alright.
But I can't help you,
unless you untie me.
What's happening?
Get away, I'm not going back in!
Hey, hey, hey, stop!
Where is he?!
Where is he?
Is he in there?
You know where he is.
Is my Noah in there?
Is he in pain?
Of course, he's in pain,
can't you see he's sick?!
He needs a doctor!
You think I'm trapped in that?
That's my home,
we all live in there.
- Waiting...
- Waiting for what?
For a place to play.
But we got Noah.
What fun we had with him.
You let him go!
Don't you hurt him anymore!
Fight it!
Gail. Gail, what's happening?
I don't know.
I don't know, Joshy.
But I'm here.
I'm right here with you, okay.
- Josh, is Noah in there?
- Just stop it!
For God's sake!
What do you want?!
It's not what I want, it's...
it's what that wants.
Little boys just don't
become monsters.
Oh, but they do...
they do, Ruth.
And I'm sorry, I don't know
what happened to Noah.
She knows what happened.
Noah?
At first it kinda tickles
when they're inside you.
But then they start eating you.
It hurts so much.
But when you let them play,
they don't feed on you.
It's why they need us.
You figured that much out.
I did. I did.
Just when I thought that
my life was over he stopped.
I thought he was
going to hug me.
But instead, he grabbed my wrist
and put the axe in my hand,
drew it across his own throat.
I watched him die, Gail.
I killed my own grandson.
I miss your hugs.
Do you mean it, sweetheart?
God, I've missed you so much.
Josh! Sweetie, wake up!
Oh...
Holy fuck.
Josh. Josh.
You're in control, Josh!
Stop! Please!
Josh, no!
Josh, stop.
Josh is dead!
Sweetie... you're in control.
Say it. Say it!
I'm in control.
No, no... No, Joshy, there's
someone else inside of you.
There's someone very sweet.
Somebody who your Daddy loves.
Remember?
Remember how much
you love your daddy
and your mommy?
Sweetheart, they love you.
They love you so much.
I love you.
I love you! I love you!
I just wanted to be your mommy!
Mommy?
Hey, kid.
You alright?
Yeah, just a little tired.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org