Claire...
I miss you.
Dr Weir, report to the
Lewis & Clark in Docking Bay four.
- lon drive set.
- Thank you.
Heading: vector one-nine degrees.
We are prepped for lockdown.
I can't believe this.
It's ridiculous.
I haven't got more than my hand
in weeks, and now this shit.
Why can't we go to Mars, Captain?
I mean, Mars has... has got women.
Smith's right. Neptune...
there's nothing out there.
Yeah, we'll be on our own.
That's the rules.
They drop the ball, we get the call.
Have you got our course plotted?
Locked and cocked.
Mr Justin?
Everything's green
on my screen, Skipper.
- Start countdown.
- lon drive in 10 minutes.
Thank you, Lieutenant. Let's go.
- Smith, follow me.
- Yes, ma'am.
Justin, prep those tanks.
Yes, sir.
Mr Cooper. lon drive in 10 minutes.
Ooh, time to play "spam-in-the-can".
- Skipper!
- Peters.
Captain Miller,
I just wanted to say that...
The clock is ticking, Doctor.
Waiting for a personal invitation,
Mr Smith?
- No, sir!
- Captain, I don't...
Follow the crew to the grav tanks.
We're almost under way.
Square away that bunk, Mr Cooper,
or you're walking to Neptune.
What's the hold-up, Peters?
Loading the CO2 scrubbers, sir.
You stand right here.
Thanks, DJ.
Hats off.
- First time in a grav couch?
- Yeah.
I think your captain has a problem
with me.
Oh, well, don't worry about him.
He just loves having complete
strangers on his ship. DJ!
Yeah!
Nah. Is this necessary?
When the ion drive fires
you'll be taking about 30 Gs.
Without a tank, the force
would liquefy your skeleton.
I've seen the effect on mice.
Claustrophobic?
Very.
Billy.
I'm so alone.
Hello?
Is anyone there?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Billy?
I'm so cold.
Claire.
I'm waiting.
You're all right. Breathe. DJ!
OK, Dr Weir.
Let's get you up. Come on.
I'm fine!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
OK. There you go.
Move nice and slow. You've been
in stasis for 56 days.
You're a little disorientated.
Understand?
I'm all right. Thank you.
OK. Take that. Don't rush it.
All yours.
You OK, Doc?
Want some coffee?
What?
Would you like some coffee?
No. Thank you.
All right. Suit yourself.
What about you, Starck?
Want something hot and black?
- Is that an offer?
- No.
Then how about some coffee?
- Starck?
- Yes, sir.
Why aren't you on the bridge?
- Mind if I get dressed?
- Yes. Let's go, people!
OK, Denny, here we go.
Happy birthday.
Play horsey, Mommy! Play horsey!
Oh! Oh!
Hey! No balls indoors.
- Yo, apologise.
- Sorry, Mama Bear.
- Peters?
- Yes, sir.
I did try to find
a replacement for you,
but it was impossible. I am sorry.
I talked to my ex. He's going
to take Denny for Christmas.
I'll get him for the summer,
so everything's all right.
Smitty!
Excuse me, ladies and gentlemen.
In approximately
2 hours and 23 minutes,
we'll be arriving at Neptune.
I thank you.
Good.
Everything's five by five.
- USAC notified of our position?
- Yes, sir.
All right, people, listen up.
We have an addition to our crew.
Dr Weir, care to join us?
Introductions all around.
This is my XO... Lieutenant Starck.
Mr Justin, Engineering.
The funky spaceman is Mr Cooper.
What do you do here, Coop?
Doc. I'm your best friend.
Life-saver and heartbreaker.
He's a rescue technician.
This is Peters, medical technician.
And my pilot... Mr Smith.
The gloomy Gus in the corner
over there, that's, uh...
DJ Trauma.
All right. All right.
Now, then, I got a question.
What the fuck are we doing here?
Perhaps the good doctor
will tell us.
Thank you. Uh, I want to say
how much I appreciate
this opportunity...
Yes. You appreciate
being here, Doctor,
but understand - we don't.
We were taken off leave
and sent into Neptune space.
We are three billion clicks
from the nearest outpost.
The last time USAC attempted
a rescue this far out...
we lost both ships.
So if you please...
Right. Well, everything
I'm about to tell you
is considered code black
by the NSA.
USAC intercepted
a radio transmission
from a decaying orbit
around Neptune.
The source of this transmission
has been identified
as the Event Horizon.
Yeah. Well, that's bullshit,
for starters.
I lost leave for this?
Thank you so much!
Smitty, sit down.
Cooper, as you were.
Just let the man speak.
What was made public
about the Event Horizon...
that she was a research vessel,
that her reactor went critical,
and she blew up...
none of that is true.
The Event Horizon was
a secret government project
to create a spacecraft capable
of faster-than-light flight.
Uh, excuse me.
You can't actually do that.
The law of relativity prohibits it.
Relativity, yes. We can't break
the law of relativity,
but we can go around it.
The ship doesn't really
go faster than light.
It creates a gateway
to jump instantaneously
from one point to another
light years away.
How?
Well, that's difficult to...
it's all math.
Try us, Doctor.
Right. Well, uh,
using layman's terms...
we use a retaining magnetic field
to focus a narrow beam of gravitons.
These, in turn, fold space-time
until the space-time curvature
becomes infinitely large
and you produce a singularity.
Now, the singularity...
Layman's terms.
Well, fuck layman's terms.
Do you speak English?
Imagine for a minute
that this piece of paper...
Uh, excuse me.
That's Vanessa, and that's mine.
This piece of paper
represents space-time,
and you want to get from "A" here...
to "B" there.
Now, what's the shortest
distance between two points?
A straight line.
Wrong. The shortest distance
between two points is zero,
and that's what the gateway does...
it folds... space
so that point "A" and point "B"
coexist in the same
space and time.
When the spacecraft
passes through the gateway,
space returns to normal.
It's called a gravity drive.
How do you know all this?
I built it.
Well, I see why they sent you.
So if the ship didn't blow up,
then what happened?
Well...
the mission was going perfectly,
they reached safe distance
using conventional thrusters,
they had the go-ahead
to use the gravity drive
to open the gateway
to Proxima Centauri,
and then, they just disappeared,
vanished without a trace. Until now.
Where has she been, Doctor?
That's what we're here to find out.
We've been unable
to verify life contact.
The TDRS did receive
this single transmission.
- What the fucking hell is that?
- Listen to this.
Houston passed the recording
through several filters
and managed to isolate what
appears to be a human voice.
- I'm not sure it is language.
- Latin.
- What?
- I mean, I think...
Well, it sounds like Latin.
- Can you translate it?
- Play it again.
Right there. You hear that?
Sounds like "liberate me"
something or other.
I can't make out the rest.
"Liberate me"?
"Save me. "
All right. Stations, people.
Crossing the horizon. Optimum
approach angle is 14 degrees.
Come around to 3-3-4.
3-3-4.
Make your approach
vector negative 14 degrees.
1-4 degrees.
Locked on Event Horizon's
navigation beacon.
She's in the upper ionosphere,
and it looks like
we're in for some heavy chop!
- Bring us in tight.
- Yes, sir.
- Mr Justin, how's my ship?
- Smooth sailing, sir.
Matching speed on my mark.
Three, two, one, mark!
- Range?
- 10,000 metres, sir.
Check radio.
See if anybody's listening.
This is the USAC Lewis & Clark
hailing Event Horizon.
Event Horizon, do you read?
Dr Weir!
I think you'll want to see this.
- Where is she?
- Dead ahead, 5,000 metres!
- Starck?
- Event Horizon, do you read?
3,000 metres and closing!
- Can't see anything!
- 1,500 metres, sir. Too close.
- Where is it?
- Right in front!
- 1,000 metres.
- Proximity warning!
900! 800!
700!
- We're gonna hit!
- Starck!
God!
Reverse thrusters! Full!
There she is.
Jesus.
Very impressive ship, Doctor.
Thank you.
Mr Smith, are you up for a flyby?
Yes, sir. Yes, sir. I'd love to.
That's the main airlock,
we can dock in there.
All right. Smith, use the arm
and lock us onto
that antenna cluster.
Go carefully here. That's not
a load-bearing structure.
It is now, Doctor.
Everything five by five?
Locked into the Event Horizon.
Light 'em if you got 'em.
Thank you very much, sir.
Starck, give me a read.
The reactor's still hot.
We've got several
small radiation sources,
but they're leaks, nothing serious.
Pressure?
The hull's intact,
but there's no gravity,
and thermal units are off-line.
The crew couldn't survive
unless they were in stasis.
- Find them, Starck.
- Already on it, Captain.
Bio-scan on-line.
There's something wrong
with the scan.
- Radiation interference?
- Not enough.
I'm picking up life forms
but I can't get a lock.
These readings don't make sense.
OK. We do it the hard way...
room by room.
Starck, deploy the umbilicus.
- Smitty, fire up the War Room.
- Sir.
Mr Justin, you're up for a walk?
Yes, sir.
Doctor, I'll need you here.
Captain... I need to be on that ship.
Once it's secured,
we'll bring you on board...
That's unacceptable. I need to be...
Once we've secured the ship.
I need you to guide us.
Help us do our job.
Oh, oh, honey, honey, honey.
You forgot your briefcase.
Stand clear!
Anything gets funky, Cooper...
I'll be on it!
Yo, Baby Bear...
keep your nose clean.
DJ, showtime.
Video feed is clear.
Are you with us, Dr Weir?
Yes, I'm with you.
We are crossing the umbilicus,
making our approach
to the Event Horizon.
You're at the outer airlock door.
Magnetic boots on.
We've got pressure.
Place is a deep-freeze.
We got ice crystals everywhere.
That's the central corridor
that you're in.
It connects the front of the
ship to Engineering at the rear.
Mr Justin, take Engineering.
Yes, sir.
Peters and I
will take the forward decks.
Doctor, what are these?
Yeah. I've got another one over here.
In an emergency, they destroy
the central corridor
and split the ship in half,
and then the crew can use
the foredecks as a lifeboat.
I'm in Medical.
No casualties.
Place looks like
it's never been used.
You haven't seen any crew?
If we saw any crew,
Doctor, you'd know it.
Scanning for life readings.
This place is a tomb.
Oh, fuck me!
Miller. Miller, are you OK?
Skipper's got a case of the willies.
Cooper, back to your post.
Miller, your heart rate
just rocketed.
I'm fine.
I think I've reached the door
to the first containment, Dr Weir.
The engineering decks
are on the other side.
OK. Let's take a look.
What the hell is this place, Dr Weir?
It's to enter the second containment
without compromising
the magnetic fields.
Looks like a meat grinder to me.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I'm on the bridge.
Got some blood here.
There must have been a coolant leak.
Man, this shit is everywhere.
Coolant levels on reserve
but well within the safety line.
Ms Peters, could you
turn back and left?
- What is it?
- Ship's log.
It's stuck.
It's pretty jammed in there.
What the hell happened to his eyes?
Explosive decompression.
Decompression doesn't do that.
Looks like it was caused by...
I don't know, an animal.
Look at the soft tissue,
the massive abrasions.
Corpse-cicle.
I'm scanning for life forms.
Man, I'm getting some really
strange readings in here.
Let me see if I can get
some power up.
That's the core, the gravity drive...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
The heart of the ship.
Justin? Justin, you're breaking up!
Justin, come in!
- What's up?
- The life scan lit up.
Something's wrong. Pull him out.
Oh, shit!
He's in trouble!
- Go, Coop!
- I'm gone!
Boarding party, sound off.
This is Miller. Can anybody hear me?
What the fuck was that?
Pressure emergency!
We've lost the starboard baffle!
The hull's been breached!
I'll contain it
as long as I can! Get out!
We're losing atmosphere!
There are pressure suits
in the airlock. Go!
Here I come!
Hold on, Baby Bear!
I'm almost there, almost there!
I got you! I got you!
Oh! Watch out! Watch!
I got you. What the fuck is this?
Hold on!
Captain Miller! Do you copy? Over!
Smitty, where you been?
We have a situation, sir!
We've lost the starboard baffle,
and the hull's been breached!
The safety circuits have failed!
Time for a weld?
No, sir! We've got 218 litres of gas,
and then we've got nothing!
The oxygen tanks failed.
Sir, we are fucking dead!
What about the Event Horizon?
What?
She's got air and power!
It's our only chance!
There's no way
I'm getting on that bastard!
It beats dying, Mr Smith.
I want all personnel on board
the Event Horizon pronto.
- Meet at the air tanks.
- I'm ahead of you, sir.
Bringing thermal units on-line.
Hold tight. Prep for Gs.
Gravity in five seconds.
Wake up!
Open your eyes, all right?
Dr Weir.
Well, I brought
most primary systems on-line...
for now.
Thank you. Starck, what's our status?
The antenna array is completely
fried.
We've got no radio,
no laser, no high gain.
No one's coming to help.
- This air tastes bad.
- Yeah. Carbon dioxide.
And the CO2 filters here are shot.
Take the Clark's.
That gives us... what?
Enough breathable air for 20 hours,
but after that, we'd better be going.
I'm on the port side,
approaching the dorsal heat sink.
Holy shit.
Captain Miller, do you copy?
Smith. How's my ship?
Sir, we've got
a seven-metre fracture.
We can repair her,
but it'll take a long time.
Negative. 20 hours, we suffocate.
Understood, sir.
What happened here, Doctor?
OK. How is he?
His vital signs seem stable,
but he's unresponsive to stimuli.
I don't know.
He might wake up in 15 minutes.
He might not wake up ever.
Skipper, this sounds weird,
but, I mean,
there was, like, nothing,
and then Justin appeared,
and, um, there was liquid,
and the whole core just turned solid.
It's just not physically possible.
Doctor, please, don't start
in with that physics shit.
I'm telling you, I saw it.
It would mean the gateway was open.
Then the gateway was open.
It couldn't be because the
gravity drive wasn't activated.
I'm telling you what I saw...
It can't start by itself!
Mr Cooper, you are out of line!
Doctor, Mr Justin may die.
Now, whatever happened to him
could happen to all of us.
Mr Cooper says he saw something.
I believe he saw something.
I need an explanation.
Well, in my view, Mr Cooper's
delusional...
but maybe he saw an optical effect
caused by gravitational distortion.
An optical effect!
That's fucking poetic.
I'm sorry. I'm all right. OK.
Gravitational distortion...
what could create that, Doctor?
If, somehow, a burst of gravity
waves escaped from the core,
it could distort space-time.
It could make Justin
seem to disappear.
It could also have damaged
the Lewis & Clark.
However, I think this
is entirely unlikely.
What's in the core, Doctor?
It's complicated.
Well, how much time do you need?
We have...
17 hours and 48 minutes.
What's in the core?
This is the gateway.
Now, these three magnetic rings,
when they align,
it creates an artificial black hole,
which allows the ship
to travel to any point in space.
A black hole,
the most destructive force
in the universe...
and you've created one?
Absolutely. Yes.
Because we can use that immense
power to bend space-time.
Look, it would take the Lewis & Clark
a thousand years
to reach our nearest star,
but the Event Horizon
could be there in a day.
- If it worked.
- Come down. It's quite safe.
So if Justin was sucked through,
he's been wherever
the Event Horizon's been.
Theoretically, yes, but I told you,
the gateway can't just open.
I see. I want this room sealed off.
Second containment is off limits.
Yes, sir.
Captain, there's no danger.
The gateway's contained.
It's perfectly safe.
Safe?!
Doctor, my ship is in pieces,
and one of my crewmen almost died.
No one else goes near this.
Come on.
There's got to be something
on this log.
You can do this.
DJ, where are you?
I'm up on Deck 4.
Mommy.
What is it? You all right?
What's up? You was out there so long.
I'd rather spend 12 hours outside
than another five seconds in here.
It's the final entry
in the ship's log.
I'm very proud of my crew.
I'd like to name my station heads:
Chris Chambers, Janice Reuben,
Ben Fender, Dick Smith.
We've reached safe distance...
That's John Kilpack, ship's captain.
.. we're preparing
to engage the gravity drive
and open the gateway
to Proxima Centauri.
"Ave atque vale. "
Hail and farewell.
What is that?
I'll see if I can clean it up.
It's a power drain.
It's the core.
Stay here. I don't want
anybody else near that thing.
Wait for me, Doctor!
What's causing the drain?
Magnetic fields are holding.
There may be a short
in the fail-safe circuit.
Can you give us a hand?
Justin! Justin, can you hear me?
- He's coming!
- Who's coming?
The dark.
Yeah. That's the one.
Captain Miller,
I've got some problems here!
Be with me...
forever.
Carbon dioxide
can produce hallucinations,
impair judgement.
Goddamit, it was not a hallucination.
Doctor, you were in the duct.
You must have heard something.
You must have seen something.
I did.
About an hour ago, I saw my son
lying on the examination table.
and...
in his legs were crawling...
Ms Peters, it sounds a little like
shock.
You're traumatised...
No. No. Excuse me! No!
I've seen bodies before.
This was different.
She's right.
This... this was real.
I felt... I felt heat.
This is not something
that's in our heads.
Smitty, have you seen
anything unusual at all?
No, I haven't seen anything,
and I don't need to see
anything, sir,
but this ship is fucked.
Well, thank you, Mr Smith.
Yeah, you don't...
OK, OK! All right, Doc.
Breaking the laws of physics costs!
You killed the last crew, now us!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
It's just a fucking ship.
It's just a ship, a hunk of metal.
There's nothing odd going on.
Fine.
OK. Let's see this.
You all right?
Yeah. I'm just... I'm sorry.
There's no fucking chance...
That's enough! I want you cool! Now!
All right.
You're going outside
on the Clark with Cooper
and you're going to repair
the ship. No mistakes.
Mistakes, nobody goes home.
Understood?
Yes, sir. All right.
Get moving.
Miller.
What, Starck?
I ran the bio-scan.
The results were bioreadings...
Of an indeterminate origin. Yes.
Tell me something useful, Lieutenant.
- I've got a theory.
- Let's hear it.
There's a connection
between the readings
and the hallucinations,
like part of a defensive
reaction, an immune system.
I don't have time...
- Listen.
- To what?
This ship is reacting,
and the reactions
are getting stronger.
As if the ship brought back
something with it.
What are you telling me?
That this ship is alive?
You wanted an answer.
I want to survive the next 10 hours.
Did you hear that?!
You heard it. What is it?
Listen to me.
It's DJ, all right?
Neither of us heard anything.
Just calm down. Get your breath back.
- Now, tell me.
- I was...
Make it stop!
Open the door.
No!
Weir, stop!
Stop him!
What are you doing?!
In our current environment,
self-control is an asset.
What is it?
Um... the forward airlock.
Miller, Smith, Cooper,
anyone in the airlock?
That's a negative, Starck.
Justin, no! Justin, open the door!
Miller, come in.
We have an emergency.
What's going on, Starck?
Justin's in the airlock.
Say again.
Justin's in the airlock
without a suit.
- I'm on it.
- No, sailor.
- Skipper, you need me.
- Stay there.
- He's engaged the override.
- Shut it down.
- I'll try.
- Coming to him, Starck.
Justin! Open this door now!
Starck, give me status.
He's engaged the override.
We can't open the door.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- I'll get the kit.
- Justin, open the door!
Justin, open the door.
Did you hear it?
- Keep him talking.
- Yes, I heard it. What is it?
It shows you things...
horrible things.
What does?
The dark inside me...
from the other place.
- I won't go back there.
- Baby Bear, open the door!
- What's happening?
- He won't listen.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
If he opens the airlock
he'll turn inside out.
- Stay with me!
- Almost got it...
Stay with me, Justin! Open that door!
If you could see what I've seen,
you wouldn't stop me.
That's not you talking!
That's not you talking.
That's it, there. Open the door.
Go for that button.
He's activated the door.
It's on a 30-second delay.
Stand by for decompression
in 25 seconds.
Where am I? Hey...
- Open it!
- Open the door...
I can't.
It won't open when
the outside door's triggered.
- Oh, God.
- Mama Bear... open the door.
Come on. Please...
- Captain!
- Patch me through.
- Tell them to open it.
- I can't, Justin.
- I don't want to die.
- You're not gonna die.
Listen, I'll get you out.
Oh, my God.
It's starting. My eyes!
Don't think about them.
Shut them as tight as you can.
Five seconds.
Tuck yourself into a ball.
I can't breathe!
Oh! Oh, God!
Oh, God, it hurts!
I want you to huff and puff
and empty your lungs.
Do you hear me, Justin?!
Do it! Now!
OK, Baby Bear.
Got him. I got him.
Stand by, people.
Stand by!
We've got pressure.
We're coming, Justin!
We're coming!
We're going to need five units here.
Hold his head still.
Give me some more glycerine now!
- One thing at a time.
- Christ, he's bleeding!
I stopped the bleeding.
Stabilised him best I can.
He won't be pretty, but he
should live... if we get back.
We'll make it.
Starck, what's our time like?
CO2 levels will become
toxic in four hours.
All right. Peters,
we've got to find out
what happened to the other crew
before it happens to us.
I can work on the bridge,
but I won't go back to Medical.
- Fine.
- Yes, sir.
Justin said something about...
"the dark inside me. "
What's that mean?
Doctor?
I- I don't think it means anything.
Don't you walk away from me, mister.
I'd like some answers, Doctor.
Why did one of my
men try to commit suicide?
I'd like to know
what caused that noise.
Look, thermal changes in the hull
could have caused it
to expand and contract,
causing reverberations.
It's possible.
Bullshit! You built this ship.
You've given me nothing
but bullshit.
What do you to hear?
You said the ship's drive
creates a gateway.
Yeah.
To what?
I don't know.
Where did you send it?
Where has it been for seven years?
- I don't know.
- That's not good enough.
You're the expert.
I need answers. That's your job.
Now, the other place, where is that?
I don't know! I don't know!
Look, there's a lot of things
happening around here
that I don't fully understand.
I need time.
I see.
Well, that's exactly
what we don't have, Doctor.
Captain!
Don't leave me!
Please!
For God's sakes, help me!
It's in your head.
It's just in your head.
God help us.
I'm telling you,
it was his voice I heard.
He was calling to me... a young
bosun named Eddie Corrick.
We served on the Goliath together.
When the O2 tanks ruptured,
four of us made it to the lifeboat,
but Corrick was still on board
when the fire broke out.
You ever seen fire in zero gravity?
It's beautiful.
It's like liquid.
It slides all over everything.
Comes up in waves.
And they just kept hitting him,
wave after wave.
He was screaming for me to save him.
What did you do?
I did the only thing I could.
I closed the lifeboat hatch,
and I left him behind.
I swore I'd never lose another man.
I've known you a long time.
You never told me that.
That's just it, DJ.
I never told anybody.
But this ship knew about it.
It knows my fears.
It knows my secrets.
Gets inside your head,
and it shows you.
I wasn't going to tell you this.
I've been listening
to the distress signal,
and I, um...
think I made a mistake
in the translation.
Liberate tutemet...
Go on.
I thought it said "liberate me"...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
"Save me. "
But it's not "me. "
It's "liberate tutemet"...
"Save yourself. "
And it gets worse.
Liberate tutemet ex inferis.
There.
I think...
That says "ex inferis. "
"Save yourself...
"from hell. "
Look, if what Dr Weir
tells us is true,
this ship has been beyond
the boundaries of our universe,
of known scientific reality.
Who knows where it's been,
what it's seen...
and what it's brought back with it?
From hell.
You don't believe
in that stuff, do you?
Whoever sent that message,
he sure believes in hell.
Captain Miller!
It better be good, Coop.
Ready to repressurise
the Clark and get out of here.
On my way.
Come on, baby. Don't let me down.
Hello, baby.
Papa's home.
She's holding.
Oh, shit.
Skipper, we're still venting
trace gasses.
Give me 20 minutes to plug it.
Cooper, you are the life-saver.
20 minutes and we're under way.
Shit.
Got any coffee?
Yeah, but it's cold.
Great.
Liberate tutemet ex inferis.
We're leaving.
No, we can't leave.
Our orders are specific.
Rescue the crew, salvage the ship.
They're dead, Doctor.
Your ship killed them.
- We came to do a job.
- We're aborting!
Starck, download the files
from the Event Horizon's computers.
DJ, get Justin prepped
and ready to move to the Clark.
There's stuff I want from Medical.
- Move him to the tank.
- No problem. Do it.
- Peters.
- Yes, sir.
Get the CO2 scrubbers.
Take Smitty with you.
Don't do this.
It's done.
You can't leave my ship!
I have no intention of leaving her.
I will take the Lewis & Clark
and launch TAC missiles
at the Event Horizon.
No.
Captain, bio-scans
just went off the scale.
The core's draining power
from the rest of the ship.
Get the files.
Vacate. I want off this ship.
You can't leave. She won't let you.
Just get your gear
or you're walking home.
I am home.
Let's go!
Ready?
Shot.
Come on. Come on.
Ready?
Shot.
Shot. OK.
Can we go? This place freaks me out.
- You wanna breathe going home?
- No! Let's go!
Shit! 25! Come on!
We need 25! Peters!
Come out! Got it!
Oh, no, Peters.
Oh, God.
It's me. I'm home.
I'm home.
I know I wasn't there
when you needed me, and...
I'm sorry I...
I let my work come between us.
God, Claire, no.
I'm begging you.
Please, please don't.
Not again, please.
I've been so...
Billy.
It's all right.
I've been so alone.
You'll never be alone again.
You're with me now.
You're with me,
and I have such wonderful,
wonderful things...
to show you.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Damn, I'm good!
Coop, how long are you going to take?
You can kiss my ass, Smith. I'm done.
Just let me collect my tools,
and we can go.
- Two minutes, tops.
- Roger that.
Dr Weir, get your ass
back on board now! Weir!
Shit.
Captain Miller, do you copy? Over.
Go ahead, Smitty.
I've just seen Weir messing
around on the Clark, sir.
Stand by, Smitty.
I wanna check something out.
- Smith, get out.
- Come again, sir?
Explosives are missing.
Weir's put it on Clark.
No, sir. No way.
I've just put it back together.
Get off there, Smith!
Where the fuck are you?
Got you.
Hang on, Smitty! I'm coming!
No!
Shit!
Where the fuck am I going?
Why does this shit happen
to me? Fuck.
All right, think, Coop. Think. Think!
Get back to the ship.
Blow my air tank.
I'll blow my air tank.
All right. Fuck.
Oh, this better work.
This shit better work.
Here I go. One, two, three.
Come on. Come on!
Come on! Yes!
Yes! Yes!
Here I come, motherfuckers!
What was that?
Clark's gone.
Smitty and Cooper are dead.
What the...?
You spot Weir, take him out.
Understood.
Be careful, DJ.
Don't worry about Weir.
I'll take care of him.
DJ! DJ, answer me!
OK, Dr Weir.
You don't wanna leave your ship?
You never will.
It's OK.
I'll get you out of here.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Easy.
Oh, my God.
What happened to your eyes?
Where we're going,
we won't need eyes to see.
What are you talking about?
I created the Event Horizon
to reach the stars,
but she's gone much,
much further than that.
She tore a hole in our universe...
a gateway to another dimension...
a dimension of pure chaos...
pure evil.
When she crossed over,
she was just a ship,
but when she came back...
she was alive.
Look at her, Miller.
Isn't she beautiful?
Your beautiful ship
killed its crew, Doctor.
Well...
now she has another crew.
Now she has us.
What do you think
you're doing, Doctor?
You wanted to know
where the ship has been...
so now you'll find out.
If you miss me,
you blow out the hull.
What makes you think I'll miss?
That's right! I'm back!
I'm... oh, shit! I can't stop! Hey!
Hey! Fuck.
What?! Who the fuck?!
Who the...? Oh, shit!
No!
Give me your hand!
- Come on!
- I can't!
I'm not leaving you!
Forward airlock.
It can't be Weir.
I'm not taking any chances.
You watch your back.
Yo! Don't hit me!
Take it off! Take it off!
I can't breathe. I can't breathe.
You're OK. You're OK. It's over.
No, it's not.
Weir's activated the gravity
drive. We got to shut it down.
- How? The bridge is gone.
- What about Engineering?
Dr Weir was the expert.
I don't want to go
where the other crew went.
We'll blow it.
- Blow it?
- Like Weir said.
Blow the corridor,
separate us from the ship,
use the foredecks as a lifeboat.
TDRS should pick up
our emergency beacon.
We put ourselves in stasis,
and stand by for rescue.
I'll manually arm these explosives.
Skipper, will this work?
Go activate the emergency beacon
and you get back here.
- Yes, sir.
- I'm coming.
You stay here.
Close this door behind me,
Lieutenant.
Gateway opening
in T-minus five minutes.
Emergency beacon activated.
Yes.
Blood?
Oh, fuck me.
Fuck me.
Run!
Gateway opening
in T-minus three minutes.
Detonator release is authorised.
The main corridor is now armed.
We're armed. She's ready to blow.
I repeat. She's ready to blow.
Miller. Miller, can you hear me?
We have to get out of here now.
You let me burn!
Gateway opening
in T-minus two minutes.
You left me behind.
No, you're not Edward Corrick.
I watched him die.
Weir?
The ship brought me back.
I told you she won't let me leave.
She won't let anyone leave.
Did you really think
you could destroy this ship?
She's defied space and time.
She's been to a place
you couldn't possibly imagine.
And now...
it is time to go back.
I know. To hell.
You know nothing.
Hell is only a word.
The reality is much, much worse.
Now let me show you.
Help me!
No!
No. No. No.
You see?
No, they're not dead.
They're not dead.
Not yet.
You - won't -
take - my - crew!
They're not your crew any more.
They belong to the ship.
Gateway opening.
Take me.
You take me! You leave them alone!
No.
There is no escape.
The gateway is open,
and you are all coming with me.
Do you see?
Do you see?!
Yes...
I see.
No!
This is Rescue One. We have contact.
Approaching the wreckage
of the Event Horizon.
Prepare to board.
I'm entering the grav couch bay.
It doesn't appear to have been
damaged in the explosion.
There appear to be three survivors:
Cooper, Justin, Lieutenant Starck.
Justin seems to have suffered
massive injuries,
but he's still alive.
The grav couches still have power.
I'm opening the first tank now.
It's all right. It's OK.
You're safe now.
Justin. Cooper.
They're fine. They're fine.
They're with us.
You're with us.
Starck.
Stay calm. It's all right.
Starck, calm down. It's me.
Breathe deeply. Breathe deeply.
I need a sedative here now!
I got you, Starck..
It's OK.
Sedative now!
Starck, we're safe.
OK, OK! I need it now!
We're safe.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
...guess what...