Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hello?! Is anyone in there?
Oh, thank God! Let me in!
Please let me in!
Sorry, lady, we just closed.
No, No! Please!
- 911, state your emergency.
- You've got to help me!
- They took them!
- Took who?
My boys! Oh, God.
We were just here, and they took them!
Ma'am? Ma'am? I need you to calm down
and give me your location.
Can you look around
and tell me what you see?
There's a gas station, on the highway...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What the fuck?
Whoa!
- What the hell's going on?
- Well, we're not sure, boss.
This here is a... weird one.
Store clerk here said a woman,
brunette, like 30,
shows up around midnight,
she's acting irate,
banging on the door here
and wants to use the phone.
- And then...
- Then what?
I think I'll let the boy
tell you himself.
Now, sheriff, I'm not gonna lie to you,
I've done a lot of hallucinogens
in my day,
but what I saw last night,
that shit was out of this world.
Straight up.
Nancy McPherson.
Where did you go?
I know, yeah, I won't forget.
In the garage. Don't worry,
I'm using a wide angle lens.
Never mind. Mom? Ok.
Mom, I gotta go. I'm packing.
Mom, I'm getting off the phone now.
Ok. I love you, too. Bye.
- Mom busting your balls again?
- Yeah, she's driving me fucking nuts.
Are you sure you want to come with me?
I could just take the photos
and come home tonight.
No, I'm coming with you
and it's gonna be great.
It's been a brutal semester, God knows
we both deserve some R and R.
If you say so.
It's gonna be fun. We can go on a hike,
little small campfire,
look up at the stars. And then...
I will make you my bitch.
Or I can be your bitch,
I can be your bitch, too, if you want.
You're already my bitch.
Dad, what do you want?
Hey, April!
- You actually see me over there?
- Hey, dad. Yeah, I can see you.
I can't talk for long, ok?
We're just getting ready to leave.
I still can't believe your mother's
making you go all the way out there.
Couldn't she just have gotten the real estate
agent to take the damn photos?
I don't know, she said it was gonna
cost too much. You know mom.
Cheapest woman I ever met. She's just
selling it to spite me, you know that right?
As if getting the goddamn house
wasn't enough.
Dad, are you drinking?
It's like eleven in the morning.
You know what they say, the only cure
for a hangover is to keep it coming.
Dad, seriously. Slow down.
I worry about you.
Did you catch the game last night?
Dad, I really can't talk for long,
we're, like, almost out the door.
Well, wait, wait. I...
I need you to grab some things
for me while you're out there.
Two fishing rods in the garage,
and a tackle box.
You'll find it behind the work bench.
Ok, fishing rods, tackle box. Got it.
Oh... and my shotgun. The double barrel.
It's in the basement.
If your mother wants that, she's gonna have
to pry it out of my cold, dead hands.
Got it. One shotgun, dead hands.
Ok, dad, I'm gonna go now, ok?
I love you, I'll talk to you later. Bye.
Ok, how do I turn off...
I feel like I'm seventeen
all over again.
Did your dad find a new job yet?
He's been looking,
but he's not in very good shape.
Jesus, what now?
- Hello?
- Yo, bitch!
Are we doing this shit, or what?
- We'll be down in a sec, chill.
- Well, it's hot as fuck down here, Kyle,
my balls are sweating
like a motherfucker. Let's go!
Who is that, is that Seth?
Ok, I probably should have
told you this earlier,
but I might have invited a few people
to come with us to the cabin.
- Kyle, seriously?
- April!
- Hey, Mel.
- Come on, April, let's do this shit!
Time is money.
I got places to go, people to see.
It's gonna be fun, I promise.
Oh, yeah, hey April, can I come upstairs
real quick? I gotta take a fat shit.
I so hate you right now.
- Come on, come on!
- Seth, watch it!
Watch this shit!
Motherfucker!
Don't fucking do that again.
Don't be such a fuckin' pussy, man.
There's nobody on the road!
- Oh, fuck.
- If he searches us, we're fucked.
I gotta tell you,
that is pretty high on the list of
stupidest things I've ever seen in my life.
Yeah, I'm really sorry,
officer. I'm an idiot.
I'm glad you're aware of it.
License and registration.
Yeah...
Where you kids headed?
My mom owns a cabin out here.
We're just staying at it for the weekend.
Well, we've had some
disturbances around here...
some break-ins, vandalism,
animals being killed.
Obviously, you kids wouldn't know
anything about that, would you?
No, nothing. We just got here.
- You're just visiting.
- Yes.
See, we get a lot of that. Kids coming down
for the weekend, getting drunk,
thinking they can do whatever they want.
I'm here to tell you that's not the case.
While you're in my town you best behave,
or you're gonna have to deal
with me and you don't want to do that.
- Are we clear?
- Yes, sir.
- I'm gonna give you a warning.
- Thank you.
No more fuckin' around. Got it?
Yes, thank you.
We're not gonna be a problem.
Yep.
Remind me to punch you
in the dick, Seth.
Wow, this is amazing!
It's beautiful out here.
Yeah, April,
when you said cabin in the woods
I thought this
was gonna be a total shithole.
Oh, yeah! Fuckin' A!
This is what I'm talkin' about!
This is such a trip.
Last time I was here,
we were in middle school.
Yeah.
We used to come out here every summer.
I'm gonna go grab my camera,
hopefully I can get all the rooms
- before it gets dark out.
- Do you need any help?
- No, it's ok baby, I got it.
- Alright.
Hey, think fast, fuckhead!
Bottoms up, motherfuckers!
I figured it was coyotes,
so I replaced the whole damn fence.
Now I don't know what to think.
Well...
it doesn't look like coyotes, Rick.
It's too perfect, too clean.
If this keeps up,
I'm not gonna survive the season.
I'm gonna get animal control down here,
get things cleared up, ok? You take care.
I'm over here at the Riseman farm,
got another animal mutilation
- same as the others.
- Copy that, sheriff.
What the hell is going on in this town?
- No.
- Yeah.
Oh, my God, I can't believe
you slept with that guy.
- Yeah.
- No!
- Yeah!
- He was, like, forty and so guido!
Oh, whatever. He was hot.
So...
NYU probably has a pretty
good writing program.
You know, it would probably
be easy to transfer there.
- What?
- For Kyle.
If he wanted to go with you.
Melanie, I put a lot of thought into this, ok?
I just don't see it happening.
I don't know, it's just that there are
a lot of douchebag guys out there,
and Kyle isn't one of them.
- You guys are great together.
- I know we are, I just...
I don't want to be one of those girls
that marries her high school sweetheart
and then pops out three kids
and wonders what could have been.
Look, all I'm saying is that, you know,
maybe you should just think
about it a little bit more.
What? What is it? What the fuck?
What the fuck's your problem?
Rusty, stop being so aggro.
Fucking... Rusty, come back here!
- Rusty!
- Fucking dumb dog.
Rusty!
Fuck. I think he's back there.
Really, Mel?
Don't be a square. Come on.
Wow. What a shithole.
Fuck, I think he's back there.
Holy shit, Melanie, look.
Oh, my God.
Score!
Thank you, God, thank you, God.
Ok, remember,
we're here to find the dog.
What dog?
Oh.
Sweet Jesus, it's a miracle!
Melanie, put it down.
Come on. This is sketch.
It's probably some drug dealer's stash.
- Can I just take one bag?
- No! I don't wanna get killed!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Ok, fine. Fine.
There you are! Don't do that again.
Come on, let's go ok? Oh, my God!
What are you doing on my property?
We weren't trying
to steal anything, I promise!
You're trespassing!
No, no, no, my dog just ran back here
and we came back to get him!
Who sent you? Who sent you?
My parents own a cabin
right down the road!
April?
I know you?
Hell, I haven't seen you since you
were knee high to a bait pail.
Remember? Your dad and I
used to take you fishing out on the lake!
- Travis?
- Yeah!
Sorry for spookin' you guys back there,
I don't get many visitors.
I see somebody on my property,
they're usually here lookin' for trouble.
Is this you?
Oh, yeah, a little green
behind the ears in that one.
So... were you in, like,
Vietnam or whatever?
'67 through '71.
Brave as shit.
I've seen things...
things your generation
just wouldn't understand.
Hey, what's that thing?
My motion activated thermal cameras
picked this one up last week.
What is it?
What do you think it is?
Secret military air craft!
They've been using this whole area for test
flying ever since the end of the Cold War.
Maybe things have been heating up.
Just last night I tracked one of these babies
going about 2400 clicks an hour,
it stopped right on a goddamn dime, did a 180
quicker than any aircraft known to man.
You had to see it.
- No way!
- Way.
Oh, you guys are so young,
you have no idea
what's going on out there.
Why should you?
When I was your age,
I thought the world was...
a good and fair place.
I've seen some shit since then.
People nowadays live in their naive,
comfortable bubble worlds,
and the men behind the curtain
want to keep them that way.
The last thing they want is an informed,
public cable free-thought.
Free. Yeah.
People out there, they think they're free,
but they couldn't be further from the truth.
That's why you gotta stay off the radar.
Keep off the grid.
'Cause they're out there,
and they're watching.
So... can I buy some weed?
Of course you can.
So then, I was like "oh, my god."
And I was, like, freaking out and I felt
super dizzy and out of it, and I mean,
I was having a full on panic attack
in the middle of the club!
All of my friends were totally TTYL,
I didn't know what to do.
So anyway, out of nowhere, he comes over
and he's all like "hey, are you alright"?
He takes me to his dorm and he takes care
of me all night and he gives me water
and I just knew he was
the right guy for me.
So yeah, that's how we met.
- Wow, that sounds amazing.
- I know, right?
Hey... can I talk to you for a second?
- Just, like, upstairs?
- Yeah, ok, sure.
Actually, could you close the door?
- Are you ok? You're acting really weird.
- Yeah, no, I'm fine.
So, I...
I don't know how to say this, really.
Say what?
You know that I care about you
a lot, right?
Yeah, of course I do. What is it?
Ok, here goes.
April...
we know each other inside and out,
and the last three years have been
the best three years of my life.
I love waking up next to you, and...
and I want to keep waking up
next to you for the rest of my life.
So...
What are you doing, Kyle?
April, what do you say?
You want to keep waking up
next to me, too?
Kyle, are you serious?
Is that a yes?
I don't know.
You don't know?
Oh, fuck.
You can't leave me hanging here.
Kyle, I...
- I can't.
- But why?
Fuck, I haven't told you this yet. I...
I didn't want it to be like this.
- I got a job offer in New York.
- New York?
- Yeah.
- When does it start?
The middle of May.
That's like a month away!
When the hell were you gonna tell me this?
This weekend, but then you ended up
inviting a bunch of people over here.
That's right in the middle of the semester,
I can't transfer that quickly.
What, did you not want me
to go with you?
No, Kyle, I didn't say that.
I just... I...
Oh, my God. You're breaking up with me.
No, no Kyle, I just...
I don't know if I'm ever gonna get another
opportunity like this again.
- Oh, I'm such an idiot.
- No, Kyle.
- I'm such a fucking idiot.
- Kyle...
Kyle, don't walk away.
Surprise!
Let's get this motherfucking
party start...
Fuck off, Seth.
- You said no?
- Seth!
That is some cold ass shit.
Welcome to the gayest
surprise party ever!
Not only did the surprise
completely backfire,
but there's no TV,
there's no cell phone service,
and I just got the worst news
that my chick is on the rag.
In this corner we have Kyle,
who has just taken a merciless beating
from April and could be out for the count.
Hey! Say something
for the camera there, champ!
Come here, you fuckin' dumb dog.
Oh, yeah, gimme this shit.
What are these dirty sluts up to?
Fuck, I just wish it didn't have to go down
like that. I fucking care about him.
Are you filming this?
That is some fucked up shit. I mean really,
who says no to a guy on one knee?
Seth, fuck off.
I just, I'm trying to understand
the situation.
- So am I.
- Seth.
I thought we were happy together.
It's "April and Kyle", remember? We're in it
for the long haul. Where you go, I go.
- He fuckin' loves you, April.
- Enough.
Seth, get the fuck out of here.
- I care about you, but...
- But what? But what?
I fucking love you and you love me.
I don't even think I believe
in the concept of marriage, Kyle.
Look how well it turned out for my parents,
they can't stand each other!
But you are the one for me.
Kyle, that is just something
we are raised to believe
that we're supposed to want, ok?
The one, you know?
Like it's some magical fucking thing
that is going to complete us and it's crap!
- Are you listening to me?
- What are you talking about?
I'm saying that at the end of the day,
we're all just alone in the universe.
April, that is the worst
fucking logic...
What the fuck is that?
What the fuck?
Holy fuck!
Oh, my God!
- We gotta go!
- Leave this shit! Let's go!
No way, man!
- What the fuck, April?
- Melanie!
Shit!
What the hell is that?
Are we really fucking doing this shit?
Fuck sakes man, I'm too fucking drunk
for this shit, man.
Come on, hurry the fuck up.
Fuck.
Oh, my God.
- What the hell is that?
- It's an airplane, right?
I don't know, maybe man,
but what's with the red light?
- I don't fuckin' know, man.
- Seth!
Is that what I think it is?
Oh, my God, this is fucked up!
What is this?
I know one thing for sure it's not,
this is definitely not an airplane!
No way.
This is so light, it's like tinfoil.
Do you think it's a military thing
like Travis was saying?
- It has to be.
- Ok, seriously, fuck this!
This is not fucking happening!
I'm going back to the car.
Yeah, yeah, yeah baby,
I'm with you. Yo, yo guys, let's go.
Come on, let's go!
Seth? Look at this!
Yo, yo, yo! Come check this out!
Get over here!
Come on.
Holy shit.
Are those footprints?
Seriously?
Fuck.
Hey, you got the video?
I want to see the video.
I know one thing for sure it's not,
- this is definitely not an airplane!
- This is so fucked!
I knew this shit was real, man.
That fuckin' Roswell Area 51 shit is true.
- No, it's gotta be something else.
- Look at it, for Christ's sake!
It's a UFO! It's a fucking crashed UFO!
I think we should pack our shit
and get the hell out of here, you guys.
Let's just drive until we get reception
and then call someone.
Who the fuck are we gonna call? 911?
They'll think it's a fucking joke.
- I don't know, but we can't just stay here!
- You guys! She's right.
Those footprints...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
they were headed in this direction.
Alright, calm down.
Everything is gonna be fine.
You've got to be kidding me!
Ok, guys, it's ok. The power's gone out here
before when the weather was this bad.
- It's probably just the breaker.
- Well, where's the breaker?
Come on, hurry the fuck up.
- Alright, where is it?
- It's over there.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Where?
- Here.
I think it's the ground line.
Are you ok?!
- Yeah, yeah.
- Oh, my God.
Oh, shit.
What the fuck is he barking at?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
There's someone in the house!
Yeah, or something.
There's a gun. There's a gun down here.
It's unloaded.
Oh, my God, let me do it.
Where did you learn how to do that?
My dad and I used to hunt.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God, Rusty!
Come on.
Oh, my God.
Quick, shut it!
Do you see anything?
No.
Is it still in the house?
Oh, shit.
Watch out, watch out, watch out.
Anything up there?
Come on.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
You see anything out there?
No. Whatever was in here,
it's definitely gone now.
Oh, my God.
Hello?
Did I just hear a gunshot?
Is that blood?
What the fuck is that?
Jesus.
Dude, that's a dead fuckin' alien.
Kyle, it's cold! Drive faster!
Do you guys realize what we just saw?
I mean, do you realize what this means?
I don't care, I don't care.
I just wanna get home.
No, no, no, we gotta come back
in the morning and take pictures!
- Oh, my God, are you fucking kidding me?
- Think about it! We're gonna be rich!
We're gonna be on TV and shit! We have
proof that life on another planet exists.
Give it a rest, babe. Fuck!
Kyle, slow down.
Great. Perfect.
- Just drive over it, man.
- It's too big to drive over.
Can't you just, like,
move it or something?
Move it? Look at it.
This thing probably weighs two tons.
Kyle, look at this!
What did this?
Was it lightning?
This is the only road back into town.
What're we gonna do?
Well, at least it stopped raining.
What the hell?
Oh, my God!
Jesus Christ, what the fuck is that?
Get in the car!
I'm getting the fuck out of here!
- What the fuck are you doing?
- Get back in the car!
What is she doing? Let's go!
Oh, my God!
Get in the fucking car!
Oh, my God, no!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Sheriff's department. Open up!
Hello?
We're finally here, at Echo Lake,
it is unbelievably gorgeous,
and it's Matty's first time fishing.
One, two, three, go!
I'm gonna catch a fish
that's even bigger than this!
- Say hi to grandma!
- Hi, grandma!
Live it up, I want to live that dream...
- Oh, my God, what is that?
- Are you filming this?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Honey, is that a plane?
Matty, what are you doing?
Get back in the camper!
Mom, I can see something up there.
- Oh, my God, Matty!
- Jesus! Matty!
Oh, God.
Anybody there?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Don't hurt me!
Ma'am, I am not going to hurt you.
I'm here to protect you.
8732, I'm over here at Dudney Trunk,
I am requesting immediate medical assistance.
10-4 sheriff, we're on our way.
Ma'am, what happened?
Who did this to you?
They took Jeffrey! They took my Matty!
Took them where? Who took them?
Who do you think?
They do tests, experiments.
They want to know everything about us.
They'll show you things.
Put things in your mind.
Terrible things.
Ma'am. You're safe now.
They held me down!
I couldn't stop them.
They held me down.
Oh, God.
Oh, shit. What the fuck?
What the fuck is happening?
What the fuck was that?
They just fucking took her, man!
They just fucking took her!
We are fucking here!
- We're in the middle of fucking nowhere...
- Seth, calm down.
Don't! Just don't touch me, ok?
- I said get the fuck off me!
- What the hell is your problem?
Guys, guys, guys! Stop! Look!
It's Travis's place.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Come on. Let's go.
- Yo, you sure this guy's cool?
- Yeah, he's totally on the level.
Nobody move! Or this one will be dead
before he hits the floor!
Travis, please don't hurt him!
It's just me!
April?
What the hell are you doing,
sneaking up on me?!
We thought you were dead!
No, no. I've been sleeping
with one eye open for years.
Yeah? You want to let go
of me then, please!
Oh, I'm sorry, son.
Old habits die hard.
I was watching the dolphins
and niner's Super Bowl game and...
must have dozed off.
We didn't mean to scare you, we just...
didn't know where else to go.
We're in trouble and need help.
Trouble?
Seth, show him the video.
Video?
What video?
You're gonna want to add this one
to your collection.
This is definitely not an airplane!
Aliens.
I should have known.
See, everyone within the inner circle
knows that the US government
has had a treaty with the extraterrestrials
after since Roswell.
We don't have time
for this conspiracy theory bullshit!
We need to get help! Now!
Seth! Let him talk.
What kind of treaty?
Well...
The powers that be
turn a blind eye to them
abducting civilians and doing
whatever the hell it is they do with them.
And, in turn, we get to run around
down here as if we own the place.
It's a basic simple agreement
with one cardinal rule:
Do not engage. And you...
you engaged.
What do you mean?
Sweetheart, you shot one of them.
Broke the treaty.
Now they're out for blood.
You guys, what does this mean?
It's them.
It's gone, right? Did it fly over us?
- No, they landed.
- What?
Landed, what do you mean landed, man?
Oh, my God.
It's time to move.
Where are we going?
If you guys go that way,
you'll find a path back to your place.
Wait, aren't you coming with us?
Look, nobody invades my property
without expecting a fight.
I'm American. It's my right to defend
what's mine, and nobody,
not even little green men,
are gonna take that right away from me.
Now you go, go on. Go on.
Come and kiss my ass.
What the hell?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Where are you, you son of a bitch?
Shit.
So we want to play hide and seek, do we?
Yeah. Yeah.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Got you.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Time to get your friends.
- You have to help the others.
- What do you mean?
They bring most people back.
Like they did with me.
But not everyone.
There's hundreds of people
still alive up there.
Some of them
have been up there for years.
Maybe even their whole lives.
You've gotta do something.
It can't be.
I hope the boards hold.
I think we're gonna be alright.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What was that?
Ok, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- What do you see?
- I can't see anything.
- What?
- I'm telling you, I can't see shit.
Move, let me see.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
What? What? What is it?
Oh, my God, it's right outside the door!
It's going to get inside!
Oh, my God, they're coming!
Down! Get down!
Get on your knees! Get down!
- Don't shoot!
- Put it down!
Do it now! Back up!
- Officer, we need your help!
- Back up!
- Shut up, both of you!
- Hands against the wall! Now!
You need to help us! We didn't do anything,
alright? This is fucking bullshit!
This one's breath smells like whiskey,
sheriff, and he's belligerent!
You, face me. We found your car
abandoned on the side of the road,
do you mind telling me what the hell
is going on and why your friend
- just tried to kill us?
- We were attacked.
- We are not safe here!
- Quiet! He isn't talkin' to you!
Cool it, Mitchell.
You said you were attacked.
What happened?
Look, I know that this is
gonna sound crazy, ok,
but we saw something crash in the woods.
We thought it was a plane,
but it was, like,
this disc shaped craft...
It took our fucking friend.
It was a UFO!
I mean... it abducted our friend!
- And it was a fucking UFO!
- She's telling you the truth, I swear!
Listen to me for a second, listen to me.
There are fucking aliens everywhere, man!
It was right outside the cabin,
we thought you were one of them!
Why do you think I shot at you,
you dumb pig?
Why do you think
we boarded up all the windows...
Put your hands against the wall!
Come on! Aliens? UFOs?
Are you fucking listening to this shit,
sheriff? I mean, take a look around.
There's booze and narcotics everywhere!
You cannot possibly believe
this load of shit.
Sheriff, I bet we search the basement,
we'll find us a full-on meth lab,
- won't we, you little shit?
- We can prove it!
One of them was in the house.
I shot it. It's in the pool.
Show me. Both of you.
- You stay put. Go on.
- Ok.
Get up, kid.
Oh, my God. It was right here, I swear.
It wasn't dead.
You guys have another friend
hiding back there?
No. It's just us. I swear.
Get back in the house. Now.
Sheriff's department.
If someone's in there,
come out where I can see you.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh, my God.
So, when they took you
on board their... space ship,
did they give you one of them...
you know, anal probes?
Oh, yeah, very original
you fucking idiot,
I already told you it was my girlfriend
who got taken, not me!
Hey!
You know, you ain't got to go
into outer space to get probed.
You'll be getting plenty of that
in the shower every day
from a big guy named Mootombo.
Sheriff, you have got to get a load
of this kid's story.
The boys back at the station,
they're gonna love this!
Sheriff? Hey, you with me?
They're tellin' the truth.
You see? I fucking told you!
You can't be serious.
I mean, come on man,
these kids are obviously high as kites,
makin' this shit up! UFOs?
Alien abductions?
I mean, this is horseshit!
It's because of this, isn't it?
It's been ten years, Alan.
Now look. I mean no disrespect,
but it is time to face reality, man.
She left you.
People have been trying to
convince me that she just split town,
just took off with another guy.
People have been saying it so long
I almost believed it myself
but now I know what happened.
What the hell are you talkin' about?
She would have never done that to me.
We were in love with each other.
That night I went to bed sleeping
next to her and I woke up...
and she was...
she was gone.
She didn't take any of her clothes,
didn't leave a note.
How could she lock the front door
without taking her keys?
I don't know,
but I think you need to accept the fact
that she ain't never coming back.
If it had been her choice,
Mitchell, then I would.
But I don't think she had one,
she was taken from me!
Kidnapped, abducted, whatever you
want to call it, but goddammit,
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
what happened to her is what's happening
to these kids right now!
And we gotta get 'em outta here.
Whoa, what the hell is that?
What the hell is that!?
Oh, shit! Start the damn car!
Don't do it!
Fuck!
Fuck! Shit! Shit!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Are you ok?
Get me out of this fucking car!
Get these things off me, man!
Get 'em off, get 'em off!
- What the fuck happened?
- Shit!
They made him do it!
They got inside his fucking head,
and they made him blow
his own fucking brains out! Oh, shit.
Shit, they're gonna take control
of all of us!
- Just stay away from me!
- Seth. Calm down, ok?
We can't stay here, ok? We can't stay here
'cause this shit, this shit
is not gonna do anything, alright?
We are gonna die in here.
- Give me that cop's gun.
- What?
I said give me the fucking gun!
- Shut the fuck up, Melanie.
- Put the fucking gun down.
Oh, my God!
I'm the one with the gun,
so you listen to me, ok?
Do you understand that, tough guy?
- Seth!
- Back the fuck off!
Ok, everyone, just calm down, alright?
Ok, ok, just let me think.
Just let me think, ok.
Those fuckers are not gonna
get inside my head.
Just give me a second, alright?
Just... everyone just fucking calm down.
Let me think. These fuckers are not
gonna get inside my head, alright?
So this is what we're gonna do.
We're gonna make a break for town,
you're coming with me, you get up,
you're coming with me.
You stay put, because this is your fault.
They want you!
So if they want you,
they can fucking have you!
You're out of your fucking mind, Seth!
We're not leaving without her.
Is that right? Is that right?
Well, to hell with you.
You can all stay here and rot.
Have fun on your fucking honeymoon!
Oh, my God, are you ok?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
I can see why you
didn't want him to come.
You guys?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What the fuck was that?
- Get away from the window!
- Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
We gotta get to the basement!
Go, go, go, go, go, go! Go, go, go!
Kyle, let's go!
- Kyle, what're you doing?
- I'm not letting them get you, babe.
No, Kyle! Open the fucking door!
- No, I'm gonna be ok!
- No, Kyle, please don't do this!
Babe, there's no other choice.
I have to, I'm sorry.
You are gonna get out of here,
and you're gonna survive.
No! What about you?
I'm full of surprises!
Kyle?
Kyle, No! Kyle! Kyle!
Ok.
Hey! I'm up here, you motherfucker!
Up here! Come on!
Shit! Shit!
Fuck. Shit.
No, no, no. Fuck. Fuck! Shit!
Ok, alright. Fuck.
Who's there?
Who's out there!?
Fuck, who's out there?! Huh?
Fuck you!
You motherfucker!
You're not taking me!
You fuck! Shit! Shit!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Fuck! Fuck!
No! No!
No, no, please, you can't take me!
You can't...
You remember when we came out here
that summer before high school started?
Yeah, it was right before
my parents broke up.
We raided your parents' liquor cabinet
and got so drunk.
And your dad took us
fishing the next day...
And you threw up all over the boat.
And you covered for me,
you said that I was just sea sick.
We were only on the lake.
That was the best summer ever.
I think I took too many.
No, Mel. No, Mel, why did you do that?
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
I don't want to go up there.
I don't want them to take me.
No. No, it's ok.
I'm really tired.
I think I'm gonna close my eyes
for a little while.
No. No.
No, Mel, no, no! Please, no!
Mel! Wake up!
Mel, wake up! Don't do this to me!
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Kyle?
No. No!
No!
No, wait!
No! Don't go!
Come back, please!
Come back!
Come back! Come back!
No, please! Come back!
Come get me!
I'm right here, please!
No, please.
I'm sorry, Kyle.
Oh, oh, shit!
Help! Somebody, help!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Fuck!
Oh, my God.
Kyle!
Oh, my God, Kyle!
I'm gonna get you out of here!
It's ok.
No. No!
No. Kyle!
Oh, God, I'm so sorry.
Oh, God.
When you proposed, I should have
said yes, I was just scared.
Well, I'm not scared anymore.
Because what I said about us being alone,
I know that's not true.
So wake up. Wake up!
You're not dying!
No, you're not dying! Wake up, Kyle!
No, wake up, Kyle! Kyle, wake up!
Wake up!
Kyle! Kyle, wake up! Wake up!
Oh, my God, it's ok!
Just breathe! Just breathe!
April! What're you doing here?
It's "April and Kyle", remember?
Where you go, I go.
I didn't mean outer space.
What happened?
I don't know.
You came back for me.
You're fucking crazy, April.
You just realized that now?
The book of love is long and boring
No one can lift the damn thing
It's full of charts
and facts and figures
And instructions for dancing
But I,
I love it when you read to me
You
You can read me anything
The book of love has music in it
In fact that's where...
Wait, wait, wait.
Do you hear that?
What is that?
It's over there!
I love it when you sing to me
Hey! Over here!
Help us!
No! No, wait! Wait, wait, wait!
That's the last of them.
Good. Do we know anything yet?
Intel is still coming in, but it looks like
the storm caused the crash.
Like the one last year in Portugal.
- Fatalities?
- Fairly minimal.
Stories are already being prepared.
What should we do with the bodies?
Same thing we always do.
When I die and they lay me to rest
Gonna go to the place that's the best
When I lay me down to die
Goin' up to the spirit in the sky
That's where I'm gonna go when I die
When I die and they lay me to rest
Gonna go to the place that's the best
Prepare yourself, you know it's a must
Gotta have a friend in Jesus
So you know that when you die
He's gonna recommend you
to the spirit in the sky
Gonna recommend you
That's where you're gonna go
when you die
When you die and they lay you to rest
You're gonna go to the place
that's the best
Never been a sinner, I've never sinned
I got a friend in Jesus
So you know that when I die
He's gonna me send me up
with the spirit in the sky
Oh, send me up
That's where I'm gonna go when I die
When I die and they lay me to rest
Gonna go to the place that's the best