Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Well... womp-womp.
Hey, come on.
Stop it.
I can't.
I-I can't.
I just wanted it to be natural.
It will be natural.
Just let me call him.
Look, he's one of the top five
fertility specialists
in the world.
As a woman,
this is the one thing
I'm supposed to be able to do,
and I can't do it.
Well, let's just find out
if we can get pregnant.
And if we can't, then, you know,
we'll blow the college fund
on some of the best vacations
of our lives.
Call him.
Really?
Oh.
You're gonna love him.
Wow.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- You must be Lucia and Adrian.
- Yes.
- Um, I go by Lucy, but...
Can we get a name change
from "Lucia" to "Lucy," please?
Oh.
I'm Dr. Hindle's
head nurse, Dawn.
Let me just get you started
with some paperless paperwork.
And Rita...
can help out with refreshments.
Do you want a, uh,
espresso or something?
Sure.
Enjoy it while you can.
Go ahead.
Take a seat.
I'm changing
the file name now.
Thank you.
Here.
Rita recommended that for you.
Mmm.
Gonna be good.
Adrian.
Hey.
So nice to see you.
Yeah, it's been a long time,
hasn't it?
Yes, it has indeed.
Hello, Lucy.
- Hi.
- Lovely to meet you.
Such a pleasure to meet you.
So... you two need
a little help.
- Uh, y-yeah.
- Yeah.
We've been trying pretty hard
for two years.
Yes. I know.
Adrian told me.
I don't get it.
I... thought I have been
doing everything right.
I eat well.
I exercise.
I haven't even had a drink
for two years.
I don't want you
to have to question
everything you're doing.
I will give you
the best possible chance
of getting pregnant.
How does that sound?
That sounds great.
Good.
Oh, thank you, Dawn.
Hm.
Did you know that Adrian
was the most talented surgeon
I ever taught?
Oh, God.
Stop it.
There was this one woman,
she had breast cancer,
and the hospital wouldn't pay
for a post-mastectomy
augmentation.
So your husband,
he just goes and does it
without telling anyone.
Well, I-I told her.
Yes, and the board wanted
me to let you go.
I told them, "If he goes, I go."
I was sick of teaching at
the hospital anyway, so I quit.
We should've started our own
practice right then and there.
Yeah. Would've been great.
Lot of work, though.
Mm, I know it's hard.
Sometimes I wish
I could clone myself.
It's the only way
I'd get the job done.
Okay.
- Your architecture is great.
- Oh.
Problem is low hCG levels.
We'll give you a little boost
post- and pre-insemination,
monitor your numbers from there.
That's it?
Yes.
Really?
I've just been tested
so many times.
All these women...
All these women here
had troubles.
Some... Some worse than you.
All happy mums I've sent home
with babies.
We have IUI and IVF.
IVF makes babies in a test tube.
IUI makes them inside of you.
I've invented a method
that's a little of both.
I like to call it, um,
in utero Hindle fertilization.
You can help me with that one,
as you're the marketing genius.
Okay.
Oh.
Well, then, thank you, John.
- It's a pleasure.
- Yeah.
Thank you so much, Dr. Hindle.
Thank you.
Luce? Got five?
Dirk's considering making you
lead on the Wyth account.
Oh, my God!
- Are you serious?
- Yes!
Mihail's managing four clients.
I've got six, and I was like,
"What about Lucy?"
Greg, you said that?
Thank you so much.
Of course.
He wants to see Bryon's ideas
before pulling the trigger.
Of course.
But you're what this pitch
needs.
Some female intuition.
Although I like to think I cover
a little of that myself.
Now, if this works out,
it's gonna come
with more responsibility.
Travel, more money.
Luce, I'm fighting for you.
Also... I'm thinking
Dig In for lunch.
What do you think?
I'm obsessed with Dig In.
- I'll start an order.
- Great.
I'm gonna do the, uh,
grilled tofu market bowl
and a side
of wilted beet greens.
- Yum. I'm gonna do the same.
- Mm.
Is there anything else
I can do for you?
No.
Uh... thank you.
Okay.
Lucy, would you like to watch?
- Oh. No.
- Here you go.
Perfect.
Okay.
- Mm.
- Rita.
Good work, son.
This is powerful stuff.
Mm.
Oh.
Brilliant.
Hmm.
She looks like a smart shopper.
Why are you fighting me
on this?
Okay, Luce,
what do you think of her?
She's kind of too runway.
I think of Wyth as more
"girl on the subway" hot.
Thank you.
That's what I said.
We need subway hot, not runway.
Subway hot?
Okay.
What about this one?
Um...
I'll be back in a second.
You are...
100% pregnant.
Oh, my God!
Oh, thank you, Doctor.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Thank you.
Thank you, Dr. Hindle.
Come on. Stop it.
I'm almost done.
Alright.
You go.
- After all that?
- Yes.
Okay. Fine.
If we have a girl...
Mm-hmm.
...Wendy.
Oh, Luce.
That's perfect.
We can make Wendy
a little Peter Pan costume,
in honor of your mom.
- That would be nice.
- Mm.
Okay.
I'm only gonna do boys' names
from now on.
Okay.
What about...
Adrian?
As in Junior?
Kind of cool, right?
Hey.
Um, I will take orders
in just a couple minutes, um,
but I wanted to talk to you
about something.
Sure.
Are you, uh, feeling nervous
about the pitch?
Actually, I wanted
to let you know that I...
am pregnant.
I knew it!
I seriously have some sort
of women's-intuition thing
going on.
You have been glowing!
Oh. Thank you.
Alright.
What's up?
- Oh.
- Tell him.
Go on, tell him.
Okay.
I'm pregnant.
- Yes!
- Aww!
No wonder you've been glowing.
That's what I just said!
I literally said that
to my wife last night.
I was like, "Lucy is glowing."
You guys, thank you.
That's so sweet.
Hey, let's get
a really good lunch today.
Whatever you want.
Even better than Dig In.
What about Wyth?
You know,
it might not be a bad idea
to let them know
you're expecting.
Make them feel bad
if they don't hire us.
Yeah, and, I mean,
if you're not showing by then,
we'll just plump you up
with a pillow.
Yeah.
Wyth has really nice pillows.
That's right.
Mm-hmm.
Thank you, Dawn.
Oh.
Wonderful, wonderful.
Hm.
Right.
Here we go.
Oh, my God.
Is that a...
Yep.
And there's the second.
Twin set.
Males.
We have twin boys!
Twins.
And... the third.
Female singlet.
Wow.
Just relax.
Water, please.
Relax.
This is absolutely normal
for how aggressive we boosted
your numbers.
I was not gonna send you home
empty-handed.
So, we've got twin boys
and a female singlet,
total of three.
Now...
selective reduction.
Far be it from me
to tell you what to do,
but with your history
and these elevated numbers,
we're looking at an increase
of possible complications.
Preemies or,
worse, miscarriage.
By reduction, uh, you mean...
an abortion?
We'd be making a sacrifice
to ensure a successful birth.
Either the boys, because they
share the same sac, or the girl.
Now, I would strongly recommend
we keep the boys.
They look healthy.
And the girl?
Well, she's a bit small.
Um...
C... Uh...
Could we...
Like, is there...
- It's okay.
- Sorry.
I-I just don't want to make
the wrong choice.
Lucy, Lucy, Lucy.
I will not let that happen.
Yeah.
The odds of you having a baby
have just increased 100%.
But yes.
You do have a decision to make.
Thank you.
Adrian, can I have a word?
Okay.
I know, sweetie.
It's a lot to think about.
Yeah.
Thanks.
I heard we have
a celebration this evening.
We did it.
I'm pregnant.
Yes, we're pregnant.
Come on.
It's expensive.
Do you want to talk about it?
I'm still processing
the whole thing.
Aren't you?
Yeah.
But I agree with Dr. Hindle.
I think we should have the boys.
You do?
You said you've always wanted
a sibling.
You know, a lot of your quirks
are from being an only child.
Uh...
Two at once is a lot.
Look.
What do you think
the chances are
of us being able
to get pregnant again?
Slim.
I-I'm saying that for myself,
'cause I'm getting
up there, too.
What about Wyth?
I'll just take on more clients
if you want to quit work.
I don't want to stop working.
I'm just starting to get ahead.
Babe, we've always talked
about having more than one.
Yeah, that was before
we couldn't have any.
Yeah, which is why I'm saying
that we should have...
You asked me my opinion,
so I gave it to you.
I want the girl.
I've always seen her,
pictured us lying together
in bed, staring at each other.
And she would see through me
with these clear eyes,
right past me to some
better version of myself.
Come here.
I hear everything
that you're saying.
I just don't want you to regret
your decision.
Are you serious?
Would you like to hear
this evening's specials?
Uh, yes.
That would be great.
Tonight we have
a pan-roasted duck.
It is in a persimmon glaze
served with a side of roasted
local root vegetables.
We also have a homemade
tagliatelle pasta
with black-pepper cream sauce
with foraged mushrooms on top.
I'm sorry
if I made you feel bad.
It's okay.
Let's have Wendy.
It's what you want.
Are you sure?
I mean, if you are.
Oh.
Thank you. I love you.
I love you, too.
What?
John wants me to present him
with some big award.
Probably just wants to embarrass
me with a story or whatever,
but...
Well, you have to do it.
That's some real exposure.
Yeah, then I have to write
a speech, then I have to...
I'll write it for you.
Duh.
Are you serious?
Of course.
He got us pregnant.
You owe him.
- Yeah.
LUCY:
Well, can't argue with that.
Lucy, you're not gonna be
doing this on your own.
You should join a mommy group
or something.
- That's a great idea.
- Yeah.
I wish one of my friends
was pregnant.
You know, Eden doesn't even have
that boyfriend anymore,
and Alyson is like...
Alyson's Alyson.
Come on.
You know you love them.
They're just...
Loud?
I was gonna say young,
but they are also loud.
Mm.
So then I got into
part-time food styling.
I was just like, "Fuck it."
- That's awesome.
- Good for you.
- Yeah.
- That's great.
Um, well, I'm Corgan.
Uh, I'm a paralegal,
and I'm 17 weeks pregnant
with Rafe,
like "Ralph" but French.
Oh. Cute.
My husband, Brad, is a lawyer
at Goldman, in house.
Um, and we're just so excited.
We did a bunch of rounds of IVF,
and, you know,
third time's the charm.
- Oh.
We tried two times,
and this one finally stuck.
Good, good.
I kind of went
a little off the deep end.
Mommy brain is a real thing.
Oh, girl.
We did IVF, too.
Oh.
Who'd you go to?
The Hindle Women's Center.
Oh, my God.
I was on a wait list there
for a year and a half
before we gave up.
Oh. Wow.
Can I ask how long
you had to wait?
Um, I actually didn't
because my husband, uh, was
his student in medical school.
- Oh, my God. How lucky.
- Wow.
Well, what kind of doctor
is he?
Adrian is a reconstructive
surgeon at Sloan Kettering.
Uh, does he do
mommy makeovers?
Yeah.
Can you get, like,
a Hindle C-section
and a tummy tuck
all in one shot?
I never thought about that,
but I'm gonna ask him.
I would really like
to get in on that plan, right?
- Uh, yeah.
- Can we get a family discount?
Yeah. But you're so tiny,
you probably won't even need it.
- Oh.
- You are gonna be huge!
Thank you.
Lucy.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
There's no need
to be worried, Lucy.
I've done this procedure
thousands of times
over the past 30 years.
Dr. Hindle is an innovator
in the field.
You are with truly the best
in the biz.
I swear I didn't tell her
to say that.
You are in good...
and hopefully warm hands.
Okay.
You're gonna feel
a little pinch.
Just breathe deeply.
Very good.
Breathe.
Deeply.
In through your nose.
And out through your mouth.
Breathe.
I've perfected the technique.
Do you think she can hear us?
No, no, no, no.
She's out cold.
She'll get
her fairy-tale ending.
Wendy.
Wendy, it's time to go,
sweetheart.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hey.
You zonked out on us.
How are you feeling?
Okay, I guess.
Well, you can just rest up now.
Lucy, I want you to think
of this as a fresh start.
Okay?
- Okay.
- Good.
Oh, Dawn.
Okay, sweetie.
You might not want to tell
anyone about this.
You know,
there's so much judgment
and misinformation out there.
Yes. You feel free
to call us any time.
Visit any time you wish.
What happens to... the twins?
What do you mean?
The, um... reductions.
Reduced fetuses
attach to the placenta
and get extracted
with the afterbirth.
So they won't affect Wendy?
No.
No, no, no.
She's all taken care of.
Thank you so much, Doctor.
Oh.
Let's have a hug, shall we?
There we go.
Mm!
You rest now.
Adrian?
- Thanks, man.
- Yes.
Good man.
And when is she gonna start
calling me John?
- Well, that's up to...
- Oh.
- Thank you, John.
- Bye, now.
Try to enjoy
some quality mom time.
You deserve it.
Remember, you're pregnant.
You know, I...
thought I heard these weird
things during the reduction,
you and Hindle talking about...
I don't know.
Really?
Must've been dreaming.
Right up here, Mohammad.
Thank you.
Yeah.
The Internet is full
of misinformation.
I don't want you
getting paranoid.
What you have is called OHSS...
ovarian hyperstimulation.
Actually, it's a good thing.
Your uterus is making room,
so it stretches,
sometimes a little too thin,
and it bleeds.
So you're not concerned?
No.
Now, there'll be
no more googling.
Understood?
The choices Wyth have made
are subtle but powerful,
elevating yourselves in
a marketplace full of basics.
We here at Liegler want to
re-fashion your consumers,
your "fans," as co-creators.
You fucking killed it!
I did, didn't I?
I've known Coraline
for decades,
started a crew together,
and she's a, um...
How do I say it?
Let's say, uh, tepid.
Exactly.
For her to say, "I like it"?
- Wow!
- No, no, no, no.
She said, "I like it very much,"
and that it was very smart.
That's a big compliment
coming from a...
let's say genius.
I didn't even
hear you come in.
Okay.
Guess what.
What?
I nailed the pitch, and
I get to lead the Wyth account.
That's amazing.
Am I gonna be one
of those women who has it all?
My career, my kids,
my old man by my side?
Who you calling old?
Whoo!
Oh, my God.
That's so scary.
Apparently, umbilical cords
are supposed to have
two arteries,
and mine only has one,
because of course it does.
I'm so sorry.
Half the babies born with this
have all sorts
of awful complications.
I mean, horrible things
like deformities.
- Oh, God.
- I just can't...
I just...
Dr. Davis says I essentially
have to be on bed rest
from here on out, which...
I guess is okay,
'cause I can quit now
and not have to waddle into work
for the next five months.
You're... You're gonna quit?
Oh, Brad and I decided.
I mean, if something happened
to baby Rafe
and I hadn't done
everything that I could,
I wouldn't be able
to live with myself.
Maybe you could do
a little work from home.
Oh, please.
I'm so ready to check out.
At least you won't have to
figure out where to pump.
Right?
Like, "Oh, excuse me, guys.
I'm just gonna go pump
in the broom closet real quick.
Pump on the toilet."
I'm actually gonna pump
on the subway
'cause it's less awkward
than at work.
Oh, thank you
for making me laugh.
Do you have your notes?
Yes.
Thank you, by the way.
Use them.
Don't read them.
Yes.
I know, I know.
Just get that centered.
Did you hear that?
Yeah.
I'm gonna take a look.
Nothing.
Oh.
What can you say about a man
who has fundamentally
changed fertility?
The truth is,
you can't really say enough.
Not in words.
But you can see it.
You can see it in the eyes
of a mother
looking at her newborn
for the first time,
seeing her purpose, her destiny.
You can see it in the giddiness
and that nervous energy
of new parents
bringing their baby home,
full of wonder and awe.
I'm filled with
an enormous warmth tonight,
being with John's peers,
of course,
and honoring him
for the fifth time in a row.
Dr. John Hindle.
Good evening, ladies and
gentlemen and honored guests.
Basic science.
The fundamental foundation
of our economic, social,
and environmental progress
is under attack.
Hi, Mama.
Hey, Daddy.
I got you something.
Adrian.
We are nowhere near
being able to celebrate yet.
I don't want to jinx it, mister.
I'm celebrating...
because we've been through
so much already.
It's different this time.
Adrian.
You deserve it.
These are difficult times,
challenging times.
But there is no greater reward
than to see a young mother
who has toiled with
a burning desire to give life
and who now lies before me
with her infant on her breast,
spent with exhaustion
and euphoria of birth,
to look into that child's eyes
and to know that I've been part
of their existence in this life.
That is the true gift
of my work.
I'd like to put it on you.
Okay.
It is... very beautiful.
Honestly, thank you so much.
We are building a generation,
progressing families,
and giving mothers
their fairy-tale ending.
It's why I'm here.
Tonight... and always.
On behalf of all the families
whose lives I am now
forever part of...
I humbly accept this award.
Does your doctor claim
to know more about your body
than you do?
That your body is high-risk?
Hey! Whoa. Hey.
Relax.
- What are you doing?
- I th...
I thought I-I heard someone.
Oh.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
It's alright.
Come here.
Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
We managed to get
a second opinion,
and we're feeling so much better
about Rafe and everything.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
- That's such a relief.
- It is.
Oh, I'm so happy to hear that.
How are you?
I'm good.
I'm okay.
Are you?
I-I just...
I'm starting to feel nervous.
Oh.
A little... crazy.
I-I'm seeing things.
Honey, me too.
I'm having the wildest
mommy brain lately.
I don't...
I don't think it's mommy brain.
Something's... not right
with Wendy.
What do you mean?
Did Dr. Hindle say something?
No.
I-I-I think Dr. Hindle...
did something to Wendy.
Lucy.
No.
I mean, that's...
You're just...
This is a lot.
Have you talked to Adrian
about how you're feeling?
- I really think...
- No. I think Adrian's in on it.
In on what?
That's why I'm... I'm thinking
of using this midwife instead.
Lucy.
This is not like Rafe.
Unless something
is really wrong,
you should not be making
sweeping changes
to your birth plan.
Yeah.
Hey.
This pregnancy shit is no joke.
- Right?
- Yeah.
Okay, it's really scary.
But you are not alone.
Thank you, Corgan.
I'm gonna hop on the bike.
If you want to pass out
before I come back in,
I'll be quiet
when I come back in.
- Okay.
- Alright.
Unless you want me to stay.
No, no.
Enjoy.
Alright.
Does your doctor claim
to know more about your body
than you do?
That your body is high-risk?
Do you feel disenfranchised
by what swirls around us
regarding motherhood,
trying to get pregnant, work,
your birth plan?
Feeling connected
to your changing body,
longing for
a deeper experience?
Hi.
I'm Grace Singleton.
And I believe
that women are gifted
with the highest-potential
purpose for humankind.
I became a midwife because
I wanted women to connect
with this planet's most powerful
and phenomenal instrument...
their bodies.
We have a spiritual current
that flows through us.
We are vessels
for a cosmic feat.
That privilege makes women the
strongest people on the earth.
Modern gynecology stands
on the shoulders of men
who thought the womb
was an unruly creature
inside a woman's body.
Doctors said labor was traumatic
and that we needed
to be subdued.
Suddenly, we can't handle
the pain as our ancestors did,
billions of women before us,
as if birth was broken
before these men came up
with the solutions.
They fear, loathe,
and covet that power,
and always under
the guise of concern.
We've been robbed
of experiencing
the richness of this process
in all its messy,
complex, awesome entirety.
Letting them make
the decisions for us...
That's what I call high-risk.
Lucy, how do you feel right now?
I feel like
my head is spinning.
Confront whatever it is
that's blocking you from you.
Let it out.
From your gut.
Go.
Go, Lucy.
Let it out.
Remember how
you're feeling right now.
Empowered.
Free.
Lucy.
You alright?
Yeah.
I thought I heard you scream.
I-I...
I must've been dreaming.
Okay.
Um...
Well... time to turn off
your iPad.
Go to bed, you millennial.
Well, most pregnant people
have had medicalized entry
into care,
especially if you've
had IVF or IUI.
Pregnant people are not ill.
They're pregnant.
How is that even within
the realm of possibility?
Thank you.
Well, we sent the portfolio
two... over two months ago.
Yes.
Lucy.
Dawn.
What are you doing here?
I came to get the magazine.
With Dr. Hindle on the cover.
Oh.
Well, he's been working for...
oh, for 30 years
to get on that cover,
and he doesn't appreciate
you taking it.
I was only borrowing it.
I'll bring it back.
Oh.
Mommy brain.
Totally fine.
Really? You don't need
to s-see her or...
Nope.
Responding normally.
Reflexes, heartbeat.
You'd be surprised
at how resilient they are.
It was very good
that you came in, Lucy.
There you go.
I'm really sorry
about the magazine.
Mm.
Well, I'm sorry about Dawn.
She's very loyal
and proud of my work.
Dawn has worked for me
for the past 18 years
and fiercely defends her family.
Mm. I'm so embarrassed.
I really only meant
to borrow it.
Oh, I know that.
Yes, there's a lot of voodoo
out there.
We just want to make sure that
you get the best possible care.
Thank you, John,
for seeing us so last-minute.
Oh.
Thank you, buddy.
Yes.
Okay.
Have a good night, hon.
So?
So...
after talking
to Mihail and Dirk...
we worry about losing momentum.
We think Bryon should lead
on the Wyth account.
Really?
You're gonna need time.
It's a marathon.
Luce, you don't want this to be
your first one out of the gate.
Are you using m-my deck,
my ideas?
They loved you at Wyth.
We love you at Liegler, Lucy.
Come on.
Don't take this the wrong way.
We just want to make sure
things go smoothly.
I think I'm gonna need
at least a three-month buffer.
Yeah.
Well, she's gonna need me.
Huge change, yeah.
J... Hey, you know what?
Uh, c... can I call...
can I call you right back?
Thanks. Bye.
You okay?
No.
Well, what's going on?
They're using my deck
and my ideas.
I got the Wyth account, and now
I'm not allowed to work on it.
It's okay, it's okay.
I just had to get
out of there and come see you.
I got you something.
- Lucy...
- It's really, really good.
We got it at work the other day.
I can't believe
we haven't had it yet.
What the hell's going on?
What?
I can't bring my husband lunch?
You just brought me lunch.
Mommy brain
is a real thing, Lucy.
Prepartum depression hits
about one out of five women.
Listen to Dr. Hindle.
You should be enjoying
this process.
We now know that Xanax is safe
at .25 milligrams
starting the third trimester.
This won't affect Wendy?
Wendy?
Mm, no.
No, no.
Try and take care
of yourself, Lucy, hmm?
Can you do that for me?
Smile, Lucy.
It actually makes you happier.
It's scientifically proven.
There you go now.
Lucia Martin?
Yes.
Oh, my gosh.
I can't believe
I'm actually meeting you.
I'm a really big fan
of your words and your videos.
Your whole thing inspires me.
It is highly unusual
for me to take on a client
this late in the process.
But you seem vulnerable.
This time should feel special
and exciting,
not a constant uphill battle.
You have a lot to unpack.
My mom died a few years ago.
And I've been hoping that,
with Wendy,
I might get a piece of her back.
But maybe it's wrong to put
that kind of pressure on her.
See yourself with Wendy,
loving her, nurturing her.
Laughing with her.
Giving her all the strength you
have been given, have earned.
And look at her.
Strong little lady.
Hey. How you doing?
You're all set.
Room 1992.
Thank you very much.
- Hi.
- John.
Ohh.
Room 1992.
I found this in Adrian's safe.
What is this?
Read this.
Do you see that?
I-I-I'm part of a study?
What study?
I-I didn't sign up.
Do you see that?
An injection.
Of what?
Look at... Look at this.
Look at these photos of me.
I-I know they did
something to Wendy.
I've known it the whole time.
This is crazy.
I am not crazy.
They're trying to make me
think I'm crazy.
Can I take this
and show this to Brad?
Why?
To get a lawyer's perspective.
I mean, he's gonna need
to see this for himself.
He'll know your rights.
Right. Okay.
Thank you.
Just until we know
what this is,
you have to act like
everything is normal.
Hey!
Hey, look at me.
You okay?
What did you do?
I think I s...
I swallowed water.
There's no shame in it.
Morning.
What's happening?
I'm gonna quit.
Eating?
My job.
Everything.
Even Dr. Hindle.
You're joking.
No. I-I want to see
Grace Singleton.
Sorry. Who?
She's this midwife I found,
and I saw her yesterday,
and, Adrian, she was magical.
She was just... amazing.
She's just more natural.
Hindle and them, they feel so...
Ugh, like...
Yeah.
Look, Luce, we've been
seeing him for months.
I've known John for years.
He... He's the one
that got us pregnant.
He got me pregnant, Adrian.
I don't know. I'm just
more comfortable with Grace.
Dr. Hindle gives me
a bad feeling.
So you're basing this all
on a fucking feeling?
And what am I
supposed to tell John?
I don't know.
He's your friend.
No.
No, no, no.
I-I-I have to draw
the line somewhere.
Well, not around
my birth story.
Your birth story?
So, what, you saw a post,
and now you're...
you're basing
our entire baby's life
on a fucking Instagram trend?
Let's not forget, this is my
baby we're talking about, too.
Um, I invited Eden and Alyson
to the shower.
It's gonna be really fun.
- Mmm.
- Oh.
- This is delicious.
- So that's it?
Yeah.
Do you want some?
Did you send the sonogram
over to Grace?
Yeah, I told you.
John is really mad
and disappointed.
Oh, my gosh.
- Oh! Oh, my gosh.
- Take it.
That is gorgeous.
To Lucia from me.
Oh, thank you.
What is this?
It's a first-edition copy
of Peter Pan.
It's the same one
that your mom read to you.
I just wanted to do a little
something besides the shower.
Thank you.
Luce?
Earth to Lucy!
How did you know
my name's Lucia?
What?
I'm sorry.
Is it baby brain
or is it mommy brain, right?
Lucy, are you okay?
Hey.
Is... Is everything alright?
You go to John.
What?
I've had three miscarriages
and tried IVF three times, Lucy.
I didn't have a choice.
When did you go?
We were really worried
about you,
and... and when I told Adrian
about my complications,
he got me in.
After everything I told you,
you went to Adrian?
You were scaring me.
You were obsessing, and...
and you seemed really not well.
I just thought that
your husband should know.
Wait.
You gave him the file.
That was my proof, Corgan.
Lucy...
Adrian said there is
no safe in his office.
Oh, my God.
Push!
Here she comes!
Here she comes, here she comes,
here she comes.
It's a boy.
Oh. Oh.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Oh, my God.
You're crowning again.
Okay.
Oh, God.
I'm having the twins!
You need to go to the ER
right now.
She's experiencing
a full placental abruption.
You need to go.
Now!
- You're doing great, baby.
- Doing great, Lucy.
Just push now.
Push.
- Push, Lucy, push.
- You're doing great.
It's amazing.
You're doing just amazing.
It's coming. It's coming.
The baby's head is crowning
right now.
Push.
And here he is.
Our second baby boy.
This is hard, and it's
difficult to understand,
but we will work
through this together.
But these are ours, and it is a
critical time to create a bond.
You know, we have
been through... a lot.
And...
this is not, um...
You've been through a lot,
Luce...
these last couple days, and...
It's overwhelming.
I know it seems hard right now.
But this is a good thing.
Wait till you see
how special these boys are.
Such beautiful blue eyes.
I can't believe
this happened to me.
I know, I know.
It's crazy.
What happened to your office?
Wasn't it more culturally, uh...
Weren't there, like...
masks and...
Even your outfit
looks... different.
No.
Nothing has changed.
Really?
Mm.
I am not your mystical
Negress, Lucy.
I'm sorry.
Fuck.
I don't even know what to do
with myself.
Be better.
How?
I don't have the answers.
It's not my job.
It's yours.
I need to talk to John.
Do you have an appointment?
I need to talk to John
about reducing the wrong...
This way.
You have two babies
and a wonderful husband.
If I were you, I would go home
and spend every minute
with them...
mothering them.
Just let Adrian and Hindle
do the good work
they're trying to do.
What?
Oh.
He didn't tell you?
Oh. I thought you two
were closer than that.
Uh, Rita, can you bring in the
Martin-Hindle paperwork, please?
Oh.
Hm.
Thank you.
Mm-hmm.
Adrian's joining the practice.
Just think of all the good work
they're going to do.
Welcome to the family.
You poor thing.
What Grace did,
morally reprehensible.
And for her not to have
an affiliation with a hospital
should be illegal.
I just want Wendy.
Okay?
This world just breaks
my heart at times.
I don't know what's going on
with people these days.
We've got pedophiles
running the government,
terrorism in our schools.
Sometimes I feel like
there's no hope,
no containing the onslaught.
Most people don't understand
what's best for them.
They search for solutions,
but God, money, magic...
none of these things
can fix our problems.
None of them cure disease.
Science does.
We have a saying around here.
"God doesn't make babies.
I do."
Oh, my God.
When you and Adrian
came in here,
you said you wanted a baby.
I gave you
the best genes there are.
My own.
You raped me.
Oh, please.
Lucy.
There's no need for hysterics.
All I wanted was a daughter.
All I wanted was Wendy.
Mm.
Yes.
Well, I'm sorry about the girl.
But these boys...
these boys will spread the seed.
Now, I wish I didn't have to
do this, but it's for the best.
Don't worry.
It'll be painless.
Ohh!
I trained myself
not to have a gag reflex.
Lucy!
You're gonna want to find
a new doctor.
Wendy, I'd so like if
you'd sing me a song for sleep.
Close your eyes, Michael,
and I'll sing.
Funny the thoughts
I have at night
So different from
the thoughts I have by day
The moment Mama
switches off the light
A thousand different
questions come my way
And stay
Who am I?
Was it all planned
in advance?
Or was I just born
by chance?
Oh, who on earth am I?
Did I ever live before
As a mountain lion
Or as a fly?
Someday I'll die
Will I ever live again
As a rooster or a hen
Or a lion in a den
Or a robin or a wren
Or a fly?
Oh, who
Am I?
Oh, my God.
What happened?
I know what happened.
You knew we were having
the boys.
No.
He, uh...
He said he was gonna
take care of us.
This deal, this is gonna be
a good thing for us, Lucy.
Mm.
Lucy.
Go.
What am I supposed to do?
Go!
Funny the thoughts
I have at night
A thousand different
questions come my way
And stay
Who am I?
Oh, who on earth am I?
Did I ever live before
As a mountain lion
Or as a fly?
Can I be the only one
Who thinks these
Mysterious thoughts?
Someday I'll die
Will I ever live again
As a rooster or a hen
Or a lion in a den
Or a robin or a wren
Or a fly?
Oh, who
Am I?
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull