( music playing )
Man: Fear...
a little death
that consumes you.
From the common
to the abstract,
everyone is scared
of something.
I got a cockroach.
Somebody kill it.
Kill it. Ohh!
I was always taught
you had to live with it,
accept it.
I watched as others fought back.
Agoraphobia, nyctophobia,
hydrophobia, acrophobia.
There are literally thousands
of classified phobias.
I figured out a way
to give my patients a fresh
start
without the inhibitions
and restrictions
their phobias had placed
in their lives.
Oh, the chamber here
animates your phobias
in the form of hallucinations.
- ( squeals )
- No!
Total immersive exposure
therapy,
that's where I went...
pushed to the edge of science
and sensory deprivation.
We had the technology
to find a cure all along,
but everyone else
was blind to it.
Smarter men than me all failed,
but not me.
My agenda was pure,
and I figured out the key
hiding in plain sight,
which they all had overlooked,
the amygdala,
the portion of the brain
which feels fear.
( growls )
Everyone else
had danced around it
and treated it
like something sacred,
but I took a slightly
different approach.
The amygdala also acts
as a kind of projector
in which the signal
can easily be received
and, most of all, bounced back.
It was working.
Round after round,
I was fighting fear and winning.
No! ( screams )
Some of my colleagues
tried to debunk my theories,
calling me insane,
dangerous, outrageous,
but they were just jealous.
But something,
something went wrong.
( monitor
beeping steadily )
Dr. Andover:
Now close your eyes,
and just concentrate
on the sound of my voice.
( silverware clinking )
( overlapping chatter )
( no audible dialogue )
Which one do you want?
Strawberry?
Vanilla?
Chocolate? What?
- Vanilla.
- Vanilla?
( crowd screaming )
( gunfire continues )
Don't do this.
Please don't--
( gunfire resumes )
( muffled gunfire )
Dr. Andover:
Talk to me.
I need you to tell me
what you see.
Nothing.
Tell me what you see.
A door.
Good.
Is it the door to the diner?
I don't think so.
( distorted voice )
That's it, Paige.
Focus on the sound of my voice.
Paige, you're not listening to
me.
Focus!
Paige...
- ( panting )
- focus!
( distorted voice)
That's it, Paige.
- ( gasps )
- Focus on the sound of my
voice.
I'm scared.
( panting )
- Paige.
- No!
Paige, it's just a
hallucination.
All you need to do
is open your eyes.
Let me in.
Paige! Paige!
(distorted voice )
Open the door.
Andover: All you need to do
is open your eyes.
Open your eyes, Paige.
Paige, open your eyes!
( screams )
Paige.
Paige!
( woman screaming )
( scream echoing )
( thunder crashing )
( banging on door )
( banging resumes )
( knocking )
Woman:
Sara.
Sara, are your lights out, too?
I'm fine.
Really?
Why, 'cause you lit
a couple candles?
You know what?
I think I have bedbugs.
Could you check my neck?
It's really itchy.
I feel like I can feel
them crawling on me.
It's just gross.
Right there.
Relax. Relax. Relax. Relax.
( groans )
Damn it.
Nothing.
- Really?
- Nothing except lice.
Oh, fuck you.
Why don't you light
some more candles?
Shut up.
So you got
your hot date over there?
He's warm enough, I guess.
Remember that friend of his
I told you about?
No, I don't.
You don't know what you're
missing.
No! Just let me finish grad
school
and worry about all
of that other stuff.
It's all about sacrifices.
Sacrifices for the greater good.
I know. You can spare me
the speech. Thank you.
Shut up.
I'll have the last laugh
when I'm a horribly underpaid
teaching assistant.
( sighs )
Thank God.
Now get out, itchy bitch.
I have school in the morning.
You could teach this kid
a thing or two.
- Get out.
- What?
Get out! Come on.
Oh, come on.
He's kind of hot
and edgy and dark.
I know you like 'em dark.
The darker, the better, bitch.
( thunder continues )
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Okay.
( screams )
( panting )
Oh, God.
God.
( dials )
( line rings )
( rings )
( ringing continues )
( rings echoing )
( ringing stops )
( doorbell buzzes )
Hello?
Man:
It's not my fucking job!
I'm not a fucking magician
or mortician.
I am...
Osborn, are you fucking nuts?
For the past few days,
I have gone above and beyond.
I-- yeah.
Well, you know,
it's just a matter of time
before the checks start
fucking bouncing.
( cellphone rings )
( rings )
- Hey.
- Woman: Oh, my God.
Where the fuck are you?
I'm-- I'm at the clinic.
Please tell me you're
getting an abortion.
Look, I-I'm sure I'm fine.
I just-- I wanted
to talk to Andover.
What, you couldn't call?
You had to drive four hours?
Yeah, well, the place
looks like shit.
I'm not sure the fear business
is doing too well.
And I overheard Bauer
on the phone.
I think that something
happened here.
God, I hate that convict creep.
He's so rapey.
Listen to this shit.
I saw this article
about this bug from Japan.
It flies and shoots acid
into your eyes.
Listen, I gotta go, okay?
I'll be home later.
Great.
( door creaks )
Hello?
Dr. Andover?
( knob rattles )
Dr. Andover:
Now, we discussed
how important it is
for you to revisit
these images, right?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Okay, just concentrate
on the sound of my voice,
- and breathe.
- ( screams )
- Stop!
- ( screaming continues )
Sara, it's not real!
( scream fades )
Dr. Andover?
( water dripping )
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Dr. Andover.
We're closed.
Woman:
Come on. Come on. You're okay.
Come on.
- ( groans )
- It's okay. Come on.
- ( panting )
- Come on. Come on.
( dripping continues )
( car engine approaches
and stops )
Yo! Yo, can I get
some help over here?
- Excuse me?
- Yo, lady,
I just drove five fucking hours.
I just need you to come...
Wait.
You're Dylan Dunn, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's me.
( snaps fingers )
Yeah, you're Sara.
I remember you.
Caylee's outside,
and she's really sick.
She needs to see
the doc right away.
Caylee's here?
What's wrong with Caylee?
We gotta get her in a room.
We gotta get her to see the doc.
( wind whistling )
Hey.
Caylee.
Why aren't you eating?
I-- I just can't.
Hey, listen,
I'm gonna go get a drink.
Yeah. I got her.
Caylee, you were doing so well.
Tell me, why aren't
you really eating?
I know.
I know you saw it.
You saw him, too.
What?
Hello!
Can I get some help?
Caylee, are you okay?
- ( Caylee vomits )
- Here.
What the hell is this shit?
Get her prepped, please.
( gags )
We're closed.
- Caylee. Caylee.
- Here. I got her.
I got her.
Come here. come on.
Come on.
Get up. Get up.
We got you.
What makes you think
you had a fear aftershock?
I mean, but it was so...
real.
Like the mask, the gun.
I could smell the gunpowder.
Okay, within days of being
in the chamber, Sara, sure,
but you haven't
had a session in a year.
It's-- it's unheard of.
There hasn't been
one documented case
of fear aftershocks
reemerging
since he built
the chamber 20 years ago.
I don't understand
why I can't talk to Dr. Andover.
You know, what was that thing
that he was in?
Don't worry about that.
It's always been a secret part
of his process.
What do you mean?
Even though he
can't see what you see,
it still takes a heavy
emotional toll on him.
Well, then why doesn't he just
go
into the chamber himself?
Because it'd be
counterproductive,
I mean,
possibly even dangerous.
He's the only one
who knows how to run it.
He'd be the first
to tell you, Sara,
he has no fear to treat.
I don't know what's
going on here,
but our fears
are coming back.
And what is this black stuff
she projectile-vomited
all over me?
At first, I thought
it was stomach bile,
but it's thicker,
more viscous.
All I can tell you, Sara,
is we've never seen
anything like it at the clinic.
Is there something
you're not telling me?
It's Paige.
Paige Peterson?
She's dead.
What do you mean?
She was better. I--
She was better
for a while.
She came back months later
insisting on talking
to Andover.
Just like me now.
Did she die
in the chamber?
I-- Sara, I can't give you
any more details, Sara.
I've already said too much.
And I'm afraid you're
wasting your time here.
Look, I can't go backwards.
I put up with those
hallucinations
in the chamber.
I slept with the lights on.
I did everything.
Caylee is clearly sick, okay?
I'm not leaving.
S-Sara.
Reporter:
Rewind. When did you know
that you could take the lead
and finish it out strong?
Dylan:
From the beginning.
I don't question it.
You just keep riding hard.
You stay focused.
You keep doing it,
you're gonna win,
and that's what I do.
Done. Did it.
Another trophy
for your mantel...
Try to relax, okay.
Fans out there.
Yeah, I'm talking to you.
We're gonna get you something
for your pain, okay?
Just relax.
Okay, I'm afraid
Caylee is much sicker
than when we
initially treated her.
Her sitophobia and
body dysmorphic disorder
have reached a point
she could die
- if she doesn't start eating.
- I don't get it.
She was cured
when we were here last year.
Why can't you treat her
with traditional means?
I'd have to run
more tests to find out.
Why don't you just put her
in the damn chamber?
It's not an option,
apparently.
Why? That's the reason
why we came here.
Where the hell's the doctor?
He's supposed to be here.
- Why won't he see her?
- I understand.
Listen, between us,
I'm working on a backup plan
and hoping Andover
will get onboard.
Caylee's life may depend on it.
He needs to get his head
out of his ass.
- I'm aware.
- Listen, I'm gonna stay
and help with Caylee.
You don't have--
maybe a clean shirt
and a few vacancies?
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
Uh-huh.
I have done
as you asked, and...
you promised me.
You promised me.
Give me what I want.
Please. I need it.
Paige Peterson, addendum.
This afternoon, I just...
( door opens )
You have time
for a bubble bath,
but not to talk to me?
I'm sorry. I just...
I don't understand
what's going on here.
You and me both.
Things have been rather trying
around here lately.
I heard about Paige.
It was an accident.
- Right?
- No.
I was responsible for her, Sara.
I wanted to help her.
I wanted to help all of you.
You did help me.
You saved my life.
I saw the shooter.
The shooter?
No, that-- that's
never happened before.
Prolonged aftershock, I know.
Osborn schooled me.
I think it's time
for one more session.
Paige was just
one more session.
Everything was just fine,
and then she somehow
lost her way.
She lost me. I--
she was beyond my reach.
Sara, I nursed her for months.
She didn't require oxygen.
She didn't need life support.
How's that possible?
I could tell.
I could see
that she was still suffering,
that she was still terrified.
How did it end?
I simply closed her eyes.
( scoffs )
And she was gone.
I really appreciate
your wanting to help.
I really do, but-- ( sighs )
I just can't do this anymore.
So if you'll excuse me,
I have some things
I need to do.
Do you know that Caylee
is throwing up
whatever black stuff
that is in your vial?
You'd know that if you
came out of your office.
And unfortunately,
Dr. Andover,
I'm not leaving.
The Fear Clinic
is open for business.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Nobody can find out
about this,
or we're in deep shit.
Dang! Fuck!
I hate that fucking shit!
Well, that's Osborn's problem.
She can break it to the doc.
( groans )
Son of a bitch.
You stole millions
of dollars worth of power
juicing up illegal grow farms.
You mean to tell me
this is a challenge?
You know what?
Your fucking mama is a
challenge.
Here's what I think.
Why don't we just get
this son of a bitch back
upstairs,
and I'll piggyback
the breakout box?
Ah, fuck no.
Look, for one,
Andover destroyed the--
whatever power supply
was up there.
You need to figure
something out, and fast.
How much you say she was
cutting us a check for?
So much we'll never
have to work here again
or do anything that winds us
back in the joint.
Well, that's a good thing.
¶ Ooh, sexy bitches ¶
¶ Are my favorite kind
of bitches. ¶
( laughs )
You dumb-ass.
- I hate that song.
- ( laughs )
I daisy-chain a couple,
three gennies together,
I can have this thing
up and running by dinnertime.
- Boom.
- I'll be back.
Yes.
Hey. Baby, listen.
They're gonna keep you here
overnight for observation.
Well, they're gonna
make you better.
They're gonna fix you.
They're gonna do it without
that Fear Chamber.
No.
You have to get me in there,
no matter what it takes.
You want to lose me?
Huh?
Fuck no, I don't want
to lose you.
God, I feel like I've already
lost too much of you.
I-- all right.
All right, I'm gonna
get you in there.
I'd do anything for you.
( sighs )
I like that.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
( screaming )
( sobs )
( sighs )
( gasps )
( joints crack )
Paige?
- W-where are we?
- ( joint cracks )
What happened to you?
In the chamber,
what happened?
( echoing ) You thought you
were building a box.
You built a door instead.
Door?
What door?
A door for me.
Every time you put someone
in that thing...
( joint cracks )
it made more cracks,
so I peeked through
the cracks you made...
( cracks )
became a little easier to turn.
I won't let you through again.
( cracking )
( gasps )
Paige Peterson, female,
age 26,
deceased.
This black substance
seems to induce hallucinations
upon contact,
which leads me to believe
that it's some kind
of phobic residue,
a fear waste, if you will.
Why hasn't it manifested
itself before now?
Man:
Caylee.
( lights buzzing )
Show me.
Where?
I understand.
If that's what you want.
( sighs )
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Ooh. Mwah.
I am fucking hungry.
How are you feeling?
You hungry?
Caylee:
You know my mom's doing
that whole dinner thing
tonight, right?
Yeah. I gotta eat something
before then, though.
Maybe we could just go grab
something somewhere close.
- What's up, buddy?
- Hey, hey. What's up, dude?
I just saw you on the video.
Oh, yeah?
How'd my hair look?
I don't know. You were wearing
a helmet, stupid.
- ( laughs )
- Oh, you're so...
- It was so cool, though.
And when are you going to teach
me
those awesome flips?
No way. Your sister would fuck--
freaking kill me.
Can't do that.
Hey, brat, you want
a milkshake over at Eli's?
Are you kidding?
It's freezing.
Hey, come on.
Don't be a wuss.
It's warm in there.
Come on.
What do you say?
- Uh...
- Milkshake?
- Fine.
- Done deal.
- Ooh. Come on.
- Let's go.
( bird caws )
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
( gunshot )
Ah, shit, honey.
Sorry about this.
Hate these damn things.
Always chewing up my wires.
( grunts )
Hey.
Know how you catch
a unique squirrel?
Unique up on him.
( laughs )
( sighs )
( tone chimes )
Bauer: Osborn, please come
to the reception area
for patient intake.
Osborn.
Osborn:
Mrs. Patton.
I'm Osborn,
the head therapist here,
specializing in PTSD.
So happy you could make it out.
Mrs. Patton:
Of course.
Hi.
I'm Sara.
He hasn't spoken
since the shooting, I'm afraid.
Osborn:
Blake.
Why don't we get you
in an exam room
and get you
all settled in, hmm?
Bauer.
Till then, you want
to have a seat?
I have to admit,
this is not what I expected.
Wasn't always like this.
You've been here before?
I came here after
the incident myself.
Dr. Andover really helped me.
He cured me of my scotophobia.
I'm sorry.
It's fear of the dark.
So why did you
bring Blake here now?
Well, at night...
just for a few minutes,
not every night,
it's like he sees something
and it really scares him.
He sees something
relating to the incident?
I don't know.
I know nothing can
bring him back now,
not the way he was.
But I can't stand the thought
of him being terrorized
by something
and then not
knowing what it is.
I think he's in the right place.
( sighs )
Do you know that that kid
can barely move,
but hurts himself every night,
he's so scared?
Yes, I promise you
we are gonna help Blake.
How?
By giving him fucking fluids
- and a lollipop like Caylee?
- Keep your voice down.
No! This is bullshit,
and you know it.
That kid is suffering.
Caylee is on the brink of death,
and he's too chickenshit
to use the chamber?
Sara.
He said he'd never
fail us, right?
Well, he's failing us
right fucking now.
( sighs )
Before you get angry...
this is your life's work.
I had it repaired for good
reason,
and two of them
are in the waiting room.
What you and
this box have done
for me and
my claustrophobia,
for all the people
you've helped,
it is not over,
and you know that.
( sighs )
In over 20 years,
I've never had reason to doubt
that this was anything but a
cure,
a magic bullet.
( chuckles ) I thought
I did everything right.
And you did.
It was a terrible accident.
Paige was a tragedy, and it's--
it's not gonna happen again.
I don't want
anyone else hurt.
We can save this boy,
another victim
of that shooting,
one that was hurt so badly,
he flew under our radar
all this time.
Can't we give his mother
some peace
and let her know
what's tormenting him?
I don't know if I can. I--
I don't know.
You can.
You can,
and then you'll see
there's nothing
to be afraid of.
Don't worry, Doctor.
Have a little faith.
I don't understand.
- Why are we taking the stairs?
- Elevator's out.
And why is it
in the basement?
Elevator's out.
All ready to leave you
to it, Doctor.
No, please, you stay this time.
Given the-- given
the patient's condition,
this is new territory
for both of us.
- Certainly.
- Thank you.
Right this way.
The chamber is a very private
experience for our patients.
It's imperative for Dr.
Andover's
concentration
that he has no distractions
during the session.
Well, aren't you going
to put him to sleep?
We don't deal in dreams here.
At no time are our patients
ever asleep.
Now close your eyes,
and just listen
to the sound of my voice.
I need you to relax
and listen
to the sound of my voice.
We're going back,
back to the restaurant
on the day of the shooting.
The restaurant
is full of people
eating dinner.
Blake, what do you see?
Blake,
are you there yet?
- Blake, focus.
- Paige: Don't do this.
Please don't-- ( screams )
( gasping )
Focus, Blake.
Blake, you're not focusing.
His heart rate is elevated.
Do you want to stop, Doctor?
No. Blake.
- Blake!
- ( plastic thumping )
Mrs. Patton:
What's happening?
Bauer, would you
come get her, please?
- Is he okay?
- It's okay.
Ma'am, I need you
to come with me.
Penlight.
Osborn:
It's okay, Blake.
We're gonna get you out of here
in just a second.
Bauer, his chair.
( gasping )
Osborn:
We got you. We got you.
Hey, you've reached Megan.
Leave a message,
and I might call you back.
Megan, will you please
call me back, please?
I'm really starting
to get worried.
- Fuck.
- Girlfriend trouble?
Listen, I need access to a car.
Well, I could probably do that.
But it'll cost you.
Fuck off.
Is there a problem here?
Oh, no, sir. We're just--
- we're just kidding around.
- I can't find Megan.
It's been, like, six hours.
She's not answering her phone.
Mr. Bauer,
you will go get the young lady.
Now.
Yeah, okay, sir.
All right.
Sorry, sir. Sorry, sir.
Sorry.
Thank you.
I don't fucking get you guys
with this chamber thing.
You guys are all
freaking obsessed.
You don't get it.
Everything fades
once you're in there.
You don't have to be afraid
of anything anymore.
Dylan:
It's bullshit.
Caylee:
What do you mean?
All right, fear is
a primal thing, right?
Hey, babies were born with it.
It's part of our
damn genetic code.
We've evolved
and we have survived
because of it.
I know all about fear,
and it's got no place
in my world.
And now you've got some fucking
guy
who builds this box,
and he wants to play God,
and he wants to start
digging around
in our heads and shit.
No way.
No. I'm pure instinct.
I don't need no fucking box.
Yeah, well, you're
not getting in mine.
- You were a patient, right?
- No, I wasn't a patient here.
I was in that thing once.
I was only here one time.
It's just she used
to show us videos
of all that crazy shit
you did with bikes.
Oh, yeah? Well, what's he got to
say
about his first ride?
Now, that wasn't very nice,
now, was it?
Hey, don't be an asshole.
Ah, yeah, we're gonna go
back and eat inside.
All it takes is one
trigger-happy fuck,
and next thing you know,
you got nobody to push the
buttons
on the control panel.
Caylee:
Have a little respect.
Just a little.
Guess he wasn't as lucky
as the rest of us that night.
( fluttering )
( chitter )
( gasps )
- ( buzzer )
- Help. Hello.
Somebody, hello.
Bauer: Megan, your old room's
waiting for you.
There you go.
Super!
( chuckles )
I missed you, Megan.
You're like a ray of fucking
sunshine in my day.
As usual, you guys corner
the market on hospitality.
( chuckles )
Hospitality.
I'll fucking show you
hospi-fucking-tality.
( heavy metal playing )
- ¶ Sexy bitches... ¶
- ¶ It's way past midnight ¶
¶ There's a howling wind,
oh, God what can it... ¶
( sighs )
Oh, thank God.
Ow.
I was so worried about you.
Are you okay?
Yeah. I don't know.
I just thought it would pass
on its own, I guess.
I've got so much to tell you.
( crickets chirping )
Hey, babe.
I'm gonna take a shower.
I'll see you after
your session, 'kay?
Come here.
- Come here.
- What's up?
You okay?
No.
No? What's wrong?
Come on.
Now just focus
on the sound of my voice.
Now you're going back.
You're going to return...
to the restaurant.
Are you there?
Are you in the restaurant?
You see your boyfriend.
You see Dylan.
I'm safe.
Caylee:
I see them.
Andover:
Caylee, I need you to tell me
exactly where you are.
- ( Caylee sighs )
- ( bird cawing )
I'm safe.
Good.
So now it's just
a few moments
before the incident.
Do you see anyone
approaching the door?
Caylee:
I can see him.
- Can you see your brother?
- ( gunshot )
( woman sobbing )
Do you see little Kevin
sitting opposite you?
( sighs )
I-I can see him.
What's he wearing?
Picture it, Caylee.
What are you eating?
Picture everything.
Caylee: I don't want
to remember everything.
I can't. That's not
what I'm supposed to do.
Yes, that's precisely
what you're supposed to do.
Now trust me.
Now look to your brother.
- ( gunfire )
- Caylee: No!
I can't.
Caylee, look at Kevin.
Get me out of here!
I want you
to picture everything.
( gunfire )
Caylee:
Get me out of here!
( Caylee gasping )
Caylee. Caylee,
I know it's painful
for you to relive that day,
but you can't hide from it.
I'll have Gage help you
to your room, Caylee.
- Just relax.
- What the fuck was that?
That wasn't supposed to happen.
He promised me!
Come on. Come on, hon.
- Let me help you out.
- You fuck.
Get off of me!
Get off!
- Okay.
- I'm not a fucking cripple.
I'm not the one
in the wheelchair.
- Okay.
- Move!
Move!
That wasn't about food
at all, was it?
No.
No, it certainly was not.
( thunder crashing )
( knock on door )
Hey.
You mind if I come in?
It's okay.
You want to know a secret?
I was always
afraid of the dark...
ever since I was a little kid
in my bedroom.
And then when
the shooting happened...
( screaming )
the guy followed me,
you know,
like me and only me
when he started
shooting out the lights.
And, you know,
at that moment,
I wasn't even scared of him.
( thunder resumes )
I was scared of the dark.
I was scared
of monsters in the dark.
Anyway...
Dr. Andover really helped me.
Until lately.
I'm starting to think
maybe it's smart
to be scared of the dark.
- ( inhales )
- Huh?
S'okay.
S'okay, be...
- ( gasps )
- S'okay.
I se--
I see monsters...
too.
I see mons...
( laughing )
Blake.
( knock on door )
Sara, Dr. Andover would
like to speak to you.
Hey. I'll be right back.
( laughs )
Blake.
Blake, are you okay?
What's wrong, Blake?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
( moaning )
Ow. Fuck!
Take it easy.
Yeah.
Hard. Hard.
Hard.
Hurt me.
Fucking hurt me. Fuck!
Harder. Oh, harder.
Hard--
Caylee, what the fuck--
fuck is--
fuck is wrong with you?
Fuck, can't we just
be normal for once?
Get out.
Get out!
You're fucking useless.
This is fucking bullshit.
Get out.
Sara: He's moving again.
He's talking.
I know.
Blake moved.
( thunder resumes )
His brain activity has tripled.
Why can't you see
that that's amazing?
Because, Sara, what's happening
here to Blake
simply isn't possible.
The chamber wasn't designed
to work that way.
The chamber doesn't
cure gunshot wounds.
It simply opens a door
into a portion of the brain
that most people keep
locked away. That's it.
Then why did you
tell his mother
that you thought he
was going to be helped?
Yes, I thought
perhaps we could improve
his function a fraction
using sensory techniques.
But this? Oh, no.
This is impossible.
This is dangerous.
Or it's a miracle.
Or and if it's not a miracle,
it's a really fucking
great side effect.
I honestly
don't understand why
you're not calling
medical journals
and telling them
that it works again.
Because I invented
the goddamn thing.
I know what it's capable of.
( sighs )
Look, maybe this will make
sense.
( gasping )
Blakey?
- Blakey?
- ( yells )
Blakey! Baby, are you okay?
( yelling )
Oh, baby.
What? What?
What do you see? What?
What, honey?
What's the matter?
You're okay. You're okay.
You're with Mommy.
Mommy's here.
- Mommy's here.
- ( wails )
Mommy's here.
This is the amygdala.
It's the part of the brain
where the emotion
of fear is generated from.
And until today--
until today,
Blake's entire frontal lobe
was severely damaged
by that bullet--
utterly, totally unresponsive.
I think this is
about the chamber.
I think it's doing
something to all of you.
I think it's doing it for a
reason.
( chuckles )
Sara. Sara, don't look
at me like that.
Listen, I know
this sounds crazy,
especially coming from
a man of science, but...
I'm truly afraid
that there could be
a malevolent entity
at work here.
You can't quit.
It's not an option.
Besides, what reason would
a malevolent force have
for making Blake smarter?
( thunder resumes )
( Sara on recording )
...what reason
would a malevolent force have
for making Blake smarter?
So that he can be made
to feel fear again.
( slurping )
( gasps, winces )
How bad is it?
It's not that bad.
I need you to take
a deep breath.
All right, Megan?
I'm going to have to cut this.
- Okay?
- Okay.
( moans )
Okay, just take
a deep breath, okay?
Just relax. Breathe.
- Breathe.
- ( winces, groans )
You're gonna feel
some pressure now.
All right?
I have to squeeze it.
Oh, God. Ow.
- It hurts.
- I know, sweetie.
Just take a deep breath.
Please stay still,
Megan, okay?
Calm down, sweetie.
( crying )
- It itches. It--
- I know, sweetie.
It's like there's
something inside.
I know. Just breathe.
Just breathe.
Stay still so I
can clean this, okay?
Okay, sweetie.
- Oh, Christ.
- Take a deep breath.
It hurts. It--
( crying )
It feels like there's something
crawling in there.
Is there something in there?
Oh, what the hell is that?
What is that?
( crying )
( knock on door )
Hey.
You mind if I come in?
( stammers )
Sure.
I didn't know
you had tattoos.
( chuckles )
Did that hurt?
I-I don't know.
Do you remember anything?
What do you remember
about that night, Blake?
( stammers )
Sara.
I get flashes
in the chamber.
It's-- it's not like you guys.
I don't...
When does your mom
come to get you?
( laughs )
I don't know.
I don't care.
She seems
a little overprotective.
Yeah.
That's one way to put it.
She cares, though.
Can we please just
not talk about her?
S-- I'm sorry.
You know what would have
been really nice?
Just if we could have
known each other
before any of this...
sh-shit happened.
I would have liked that.
Corner lamp,
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
patient room 2A.
- Hah! ( laughs )
- Fuck!
It's me, fuck-nut.
Jesus Christ, Bauer.
What are you doing?
Where'd you get
that creepy-ass thing?
It's cool, right?
I found it in the basement.
No, it's goddamn weird.
Gives me the heebie-jeebies.
All right, all right.
Put your fucking vagina away.
Fuck you! You scared
the shit out of me, boy!
( laughs )
Goddamn jokester
motherfucker.
Aw, horseshit.
Don't know how to do
your job, old man?
I do my job the same way
I do your mama,
- eight hours a day.
- ( laughs )
Might have to switch me up
some circuits in here.
God damn it.
Ah, we're gonna
need to be ready
for emergency lighting anyway.
That storm's coming up strong.
- ( woman screams )
- What the fuck?
I'm glad you and--
you and Sara
are getting along.
So how are you feeling?
Good. Thank you.
Now, Blake, during your session
in the chamber,
did you see anything strange?
Hear a voice other than mine
trying to speak to you? Hmm?
May I?
Ah. Oh.
The mask from the diner.
Is that what you saw?
I understand how traumatic
that could be for you
to remember, Blake.
It's scary.
Blake.
It's-- it's a scary mask.
Blake...
it's just a mask.
All of us wear masks every day.
We hide behind social masks.
We need to wear them.
We couldn't survive without
them.
What frightens you isn't this
mask.
What scares you
is what it represents.
Blake, I need
to ask you something
that may make you
feel uncomfortable,
might upset you.
Go ahead.
I need to know
exactly where you were sitting
in that diner.
I don't know.
All right.
What were you wearing, hmm?
You remember that?
Talk to me.
What did you have to eat?
I don't know.
French fries?
How did you get there, Blake?
Who did you come with?
All right.
What was your meal that day?
What were you wearing?
- I don't know.
- Blake, you can do this.
Talk to me, Blake!
You look at me,
and you don't know anything.
Doc. You gotta come with me.
Were you even there that day?
Doc.
The basement.
It's the bug chick.
It appears Blake's
developed necrophobia.
I think it's a good idea for me
to go prep her room,
prepare for
a worst-case scenario.
( chuckles )
I'm not even sure
I know what a worst-case
scenario
is around here.
I know, but I don't know
what else to do.
She will claw herself apart.
At least in here,
we have a chance to reach her.
You can reach her.
Or something else
may reach her.
Sweetheart, I'm gonna need you
to close your eyes.
Megan. Megan.
Megan.
( wailing )
No!
( yells )
( thunder resumes )
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
( gunfire )
- ( grunting )
- ( gunfire continues )
( panting )
( gasps )
( static buzzes )
A masked gunman
has opened fire
inside a popular
restaurant tonight,
killing six people,
including
a seven-year-old boy.
Police are still looking
for the suspect,
who is said to be wearing a mask
and is heavily armed.
( no television audio )
Get the hell on,
you annoying son of a bitch.
Hey, you know what's going on
with the lights?
Obviously,
there is a power surge.
Dr. O thinks my time
is better off spent
putting beds together
for goddamn crazy people.
By the way, your friend's
down in the chamber.
She freaked out.
Who? Megan?
That's the one.
Can you take me to her, please?
You know what?
I am goddamn tired
of being a chambermaid.
I need to reroute power
to the emergency lights
anyway. Come on.
I'll take you there.
Sara:
Shit.
Megan.
Megan. Megan, talk to me.
- Open it!
- I'll see what I can do.
Can't you open it?
Megan. Hey.
Hey, Megan.
Talk to me. Look at me.
Look at me.
Hey.
( groans )
Bauer, get your ass down
to the chamber now!
Let's get her out of there.
Get her head down there.
What the hell
is wrong with her?
Listen, I can't find
Andover anywhere.
- He is fucking gone.
- Oh, Jesus.
What's wrong with her eyes?
God, she doesn't even blink.
That's trippy.
Don't touch her.
I saw the same thing with Paige.
Her heart rate
and blood pressure
are impossibly low.
By all accounts,
she should be dead.
Sweetie, come on.
It's okay.
Don't close her eyes,
even for a minute.
You guys, she needs
real medical attention,
more than I can give her here.
Under normal circumstances,
I can cover RN duties,
but nothing is normal here.
We need to get her
to a hospital
before her body
goes into shock.
I can carry her out.
No. Someone's got to go
to the hospital.
That ain't gonna happen,
all right?
All the doors and windows
are jammed tight with this tar
shit.
It's impossible.
Yeah? Well, hold on.
Hold on. Hold on.
( groans ) I still don't
have a damn signal.
I ain't got one either upstairs.
Whether it's that storm
or this shit,
I don't know, but here's
what I'm thinking.
We're fucked.
Okay, I need
more medical supplies.
When this sedative wears off,
if she even comes out of this,
we need extra blankets to raise
her body temperature,
and there's not enough
down here.
I'm gonna go get supplies,
all right?
- No. No, no, no.
- I'll be back in a minute.
Honey, wait a minute.
None of us know
what the hell's going on
around here, all right?
Everything's gone up shit creek.
I don't think you should be
running around there
all by yourself.
I'll take my chances.
God damn, that is creepy.
Paige.
( echoing )
Please, help me.
( groans )
( screams )
I know who you are.
( joints crack )
I won't let you through again.
Paige:
The door is closed.
You were taking
so much food off my table.
I'm going back.
( distorted )
You're home now.
( groans )
( Andover on recording )
Her body temperature
and vitals say she--
she should have expired,
but she's beyond my reach.
It's as if something else
is holding on to her,
not letting her die,
keeping her in a state
worse than death,
a kind of fear loop.
( tape rewinds )
( Andover on recording )
I stupidly tried to eradicate
a fundamental and necessary
human function,
the oldest human emotion.
And now fear itself,
now it wants to live
and breathe on its own.
I think--
I think an entity
is coming through
into our world,
and now fear itself,
perhaps planning to use all of
us
as a host, a vessel.
( door opens )
'Bout time you get down here.
Can you give me a hand?
Lazy fucker.
Come on. Quit looking
for your girlie magazines
and get over here.
Help me out.
Thing ain't gonna jury-rig
itself.
Fuck.
What the fuck is this?
What in the fuck?
( racks shotgun )
( gunshot )
Look, I know the sounds
of gunshots.
We need to get
the hell out of here.
And how are you
gonna do that?
I'm gonna find a way.
Fuck! Fuck!
( gasping, growling )
( warbles )
What's going on?
Did you find him?
Bauer, can you please
go find Andover for me?
- Yeah. I mean, it wants me.
- Please?
It needs me to--
it wants me to join.
- Bauer.
- I'm not in.
- I don't want--
- Bauer.
- I don't want to be in.
What is going on
with you?
- Bauer?
- This is the door.
Bauer? Bauer!
You really think he's gonna let
me
leave here, don't you?
"He"? Who the hell
are you talking about, babe?
He's coming.
Bauer, can you please
go get Dr. Andover for me?
What-- what is
going on with you?
- ( laughing )
- Bauer!
( laughing )
Bauer?
You still don't get it, do you?
Oh, no, no, no.
You don't--
- He's coming.
- No, no.
- That's how you leave!
- Bauer?
- Hear him, baby?
- No, listen to me.
You're talking crazy.
The window.
I pushed on the--
It pushed back!
- Look at me.
- It's not letting me leave.
- ( screams ) No! No!
- Bauer, it's okay.
- No! No!
- It's okay.
It'll all be over soon.
No, I got an idea.
I have this.
Caylee!
( whimpering )
( screams )
Bauer!
( growls )
( creature wails )
( Caylee gasping )
You promised me.
You promised me
I could be with him.
you'd get me out of here.
Go away!
( distorted )
I keep my promises.
You want to see Kevin?
( Andover on recording )
Worse than death,
a kind of fear loop.
( growls )
( groans )
( screams )
( gasps )
( sobs )
( Andover on recording )
My hundreds of sessions
curing the phobic
are starving
this thing somehow.
It's relentless and,
worst of all, patient.
It needs to feed,
and it won't be
denied its meals.
( crackling )
Dr. Andover?
Have a little faith.
Is that-- is that you?
Are you okay?
Everything's
going to be okay.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
( wails )
Worse than death,
a kind of fear loop.
( screams )
( gasps )
( groans )
Andover?
Andover!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
( gasps )
Please.
No! God!
( yelps )
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
( screams )
( gurgles )
( roars )
Sara,
you were right
about one thing.
Sometimes it's smart
to be scared of the dark.
No!
( crying )
Blake.
Blake, it's not you.
Blake, this isn't you.
Then tell me, Sara,
why does this mask
feel so familiar?
You're not wearing a mask.
Look.
Feel your face.
Mrs. Patton:
You killed all those people!
You should be dead!
I do remember you.
( screaming )
( whimpers )
It was me.
I did it. I'm so sorry.
( gurgling, wailing )
( winces )
Blake, we have to go.
( gasping )
No. No.
Sara:
How did it end?
I simply closed her eyes.
( groaning )
( wails )
( gasping, gurgling )
Fuck!
( roars )
( shell rattles )
( groaning )
Andover:
Dylan.
Entity:
You want to see Kevin?
( wails )
( screams )
No! Megan!
Stop! Get off me!
There's nothing left to fear.
( screams )
It's just us.
I know.
But it'll be back,
and it'll be stronger.
Fear never dies.
It wanted you all along.
Was my fault.
I opened the door.
Then let's change the locks.
Maybe it's time for one more
session, Doctor.
Dr. Andover:
Fear, it is relentless.
It needs to feed,
and it won't be denied its
meals.
After seeing what it did
to get to me,
my concern is that fear itself
will use me, my clinic,
and the chamber to feed,
to-- to consume...
all of us.
Now close your eyes.
Concentrate on the sound
of my voice.
( heavy metal playing )
( distant screaming )
( evil laugh )
( screaming continues )
¶ It's way past midnight ¶
¶ There's a howling wind ¶
¶ Oh, God, what can it be? ¶
¶ Something out there evil ¶
¶ Is coming straight for me ¶
¶ The house is dark and very
cold ¶
¶ I know there's no one here ¶
¶ Why am I scared to death? ¶
¶ Just petrified with fear ¶
¶ 'Cause I'm shaking,
and I'm thinking ¶
¶ Of something evil lurking ¶
¶ Waiting for me in the house ¶
¶ 'Cause I'm shaking,
and I'm thinking ¶
¶ Of something evil lurking ¶
¶ Waiting for me in the dark ¶
¶ The dark ¶
( laughs )
¶ When I opened up the door
and snapped on the switch ¶
¶ The room was filled with light
¶
¶ Then something black
and very fast ¶
¶ Flit upon my sight ¶
¶ What I feared most as a child
¶
¶ Was the coming of the night ¶
¶ Now my horrors
have become quite real ¶
¶ My nightmares breathe new life
¶
¶ 'Cause I'm shaking,
and I'm thinking ¶
¶ Of something evil lurking ¶
¶ Waiting for me in the house ¶
¶ 'Cause I'm shaking,
and I'm thinking ¶
¶ Of something evil lurking ¶
¶ Waiting for me in the dark ¶
¶ Dark ¶
¶ Yeah ¶
¶ What is it in the house ¶
¶ That the darkness
brings to life? ¶
¶ I sense their eyes upon me ¶
¶ As I grab a butcher knife ¶
¶ Whatever it is
that waits for me ¶
¶ It hides beneath my bed ¶
¶ And if I try to sleep tonight
¶
¶ By morning, I'll be dead ¶
¶ 'Cause I'm shaking,
and I'm thinking ¶
¶ Of something evil lurking ¶
¶ Waiting for me in the house ¶
¶ 'Cause I'm shaking,
and I'm thinking ¶
¶ Of something evil lurking ¶
¶ Waiting for me in the dark ¶
¶ 'Cause I'm shaking,
and I'm thinking ¶
¶ Of something evil lurking ¶
¶ Waiting for me in the house ¶
¶ 'Cause I'm shaking,
and I'm thinking ¶
¶ Of something evil lurking ¶
¶ Waiting for me in the dark ¶
¶ Yeah ¶
( vocalizing )
¶ Yeah, 'cause I'm shaking,
and I'm thinking ¶
¶ Of something evil lurking ¶
¶ Waiting for me in the house ¶
¶ 'Cause I'm shaking,
and I'm thinking ¶
¶ Of something evil lurking ¶
¶ Waiting for me in the dark. ¶
Dr. Andover:
Fear never dies.
( gasp echoes )