Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Hey! Stop! Hey! Hey!
Hey! Hey!
Stop! Stop!
He's coming.
Hold on.
- He's coming!
- Let me go! No!
Stop!
You're making it worse! Stop!
- Don't tie her down! Stop!
- Go ahead.
The medicine
makes her a zombie.
Of course she's going to try
to wean herself off of it.
It doesn't make
any sense.
Here's your checklist,
Rain.
It's been years,
and that's the best you can do?
- Yes.
- You're a doctor.
Jumping to anger isn't helping.
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
It's just... She said
she was feeling better.
We see that regularly
with schizophrenia.
Patients take their medicine,
feel better,
and then think
they can go off it.
But it can't be cured.
She's gonna be an adult.
And then what? We're supposed
to lock her in a room
- for the rest of her life?
- John.
What? Is there...
another way? What?
Short of admitting her
into a psychiatric facility...
- No!
- Absolutely not!
Her psychiatrist
can try switching her over
to an atypical antipsychotic,
which may have
fewer side effects.
Hey, baby.
Is this happening?
John, she's awake.
Hey, baby.
- Hanging in there?
- Yeah. Okay.
Again, for maintenance staff,
please call extension 405.
Can I get you anything?
Rain?
Didn't you say you wanted
something to sketch with?
Um, wait.
Could I have a pencil?
- We can't give...
- Just a soft sketch pencil.
I'll get you some crayons.
Dr. Lin,
you got 447, Dr. Lin, 447.
I don't know what to say.
Whatever comes to mind.
Nothing?
Too much.
Well, let's start with what
you remember then.
Do you recall anything
that triggered it?
Um...
I'm... I don't...
I don't... I remember...
going upstairs and then
being on the bus.
But you never left your house.
I was in the woods,
though.
There was a man chasing me.
Rain, these episodes
get increasingly worse
each time you try
going off your meds.
You just... you don't...
you don't understand. I...
I get that the medicine
could make me,
like, more stable or whatever
but I...
It makes me feel like a zombie.
And I... I can't paint,
if I can't feel anything.
We can try experimenting
until we find
- the right com...
- Experimenting?
I'm not... I'm not a lab rat.
Not taking it is not an option.
One more misstep and the state
is going
to institutionalize you, Rain.
It's not fair.
People see and hear God.
No one thinks they're nuts.
That's not the same thing.
Why not?
Is everything okay?
Yeah, monkey.
Everything's fine.
Jack of all trades.
Yeah. Master of none.
Mom, what's wrong?
It's been a rough week.
- I'm sorry.
- No, no, no.
It's just... your dad
and I handle things differently.
Let me know
if you need anything.
Looking forward to having
you back in class, Rain.
Grandma and grandpa?
Who else?
It didn't work.
I'll let you tell them that.
And for what it's worth,
they sent me good luck balloons
when I told them
I wanted to open
my own restaurant.
Yeah, look how that ended up.
Sold out.
Rain?
Hey, baby.
It's gonna be okay.
- Just...
- Stop! Get off!
Hey.
Don't worry about all this,
okay?
I'll get it fixed up.
Oh, it's okay, monkey.
It's okay.
Hey. Why don't you stay
in the guest room
till I'll get it all
put back together.
All right?
This is my fault.
You have not lost me, brother.
You like strawberry pomegranate?
Are you cool with that?
Yeah. Just a normal PBJ
is fine, Dad.
It's normal,
it's just, like, spruced up.
- Dad, I'm sure it's fine.
- I put my magic touch on it.
Hey...
- I know you're...
- I've missed this.
...you're on your way
out the door and stuff.
- Dad.
- But I want you to know that
- if you need to chill...
- Dad.
- ...and maybe going to school...
- Dad, Dad.
...you might feel a little bit...
Dad, I love you
and I understand
that you're worried...
but I'm good.
You've got to let me try, okay?
Okay.
It's not like I'm on drugs
or anything.
Best jelly I ever had.
It's jam,
it's made from fruit pulp.
Have a great day, sweetheart.
- Love you. Bye.
- Bye. I love you.
Uh, okay. We've got
a lot to cover if any of you
have a hope in hell
of passing your finals.
Welcome back, Rain.
Care to join us? Come on.
So, I gotta see more quotes
in your essays.
I mean, you can't just say
"Heathcliff is a psycho."
I mean, uh...
Uh, well...
you can't just say,
"Heathcliff is a sadistic ass
because he spent his entire life
pining after his childhood crush
and plotting against the man
she ends up marrying."
And I'm not disagreeing
with you.
But back up your claims.
Let's get textual.
Okay? Got it?
Do we see nodding heads?
Yeah, please.
Good. All right.
Let's get going.
Chicken and guacamole.
Sorry, it's just...
I have a strict diet.
Medical stuff.
I don't know.
I was just so annoyed...
Hey. I tried calling you
the other day.
I like your necklace. It's cool.
It's a choker.
Do you mind if I sit
with you guys?
Oh, no room. Sorry.
Not for all those personalities.
- That's not what...
- Be careful.
She might go all Carrie on us.
Whoa.
Yeah, you wouldn't even believe
half the things I've seen.
I heard she tried
to kill herself.
She's just desperate
for attention.
Hey.
I'm Caleb.
You wanna pick a card, any card?
I know it's cliché,
but come on,
do it anyway.
Come on, Rain.
you know what, just take...
You know, it's Tarot,
so it's a little more...
difficult. Do you remember it?
- Mm-hmm.
- Throw it back in the deck.
Really gotta stop talking.
I don't like magic.
Well, you're in luck
because this isn't magic,
this is skill.
Tap the top of the deck.
Just give it a little...
See, this is the really
interactive part
where I just distract you,
that way you're really impressed
when I swap it out
and you flip over your card
and that's yours.
What? It's not yours?
No, no. I'm kidding.
I know that.
I just gave you that one
as a gift to, you know,
balance out your own,
which is under your bottle.
Where you from?
Why haven't I seen you around?
What is this, 20 questions?
Five, so far actually.
Um, I've been out sick.
I mean, you're new.
Where are you from?
Uh...
Texas, Louisiana, Arizona,
Arkansas, New Mexico.
Uh, must suck,
leaving your friends.
Uh, I got to go do a bunch
of makeup work.
'Cause I've been out.
Sorry. I gotta go.
All right. Well, hey,
if you ever, you know,
you wanna hang out sometime
and grab a cup of coffee,
that'd be...
Oh, I can't drink coffee.
Caffeine makes me...
Well, me neither.
So, yeah, you know,
if you ever wanna hang out
and grab a cup of non-coffee,
that'd be... That'd be fun.
Rain?
I was just saying hi.
Looks like you're up.
Hi. I'm picking up
for Rain Burroughs.
B-U-R-R-O-U-G-H-S.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Yeah, as much
as I would love to,
I don't... I don't think
now's a good time to be...
to be starting up something
like that, so...
Yeah. No, I've been wanting
to get back into it.
It's just work's been hectic
and...
I should probably
be around here.
Thanks, though.
Thanks for thinking of me.
Dad, who is that?
Oh, hey. It was nothing.
It was Phil.
He's... catering some events
this month,
wanted to know
if I could help out. That's all.
You're not going to?
No. I don't... I don't have time.
I mean, no, you should go.
You haven't cooked in forever.
- I cook for you all the time.
- Yeah, Mom and I don't count.
You sure?
- Really?
- Yes.
- I don't have to do it.
- We'll be fine.
Rain?
Honey,
your father will take the door
off the hinges
if you keep locking it.
Yeah, I know.
It's a habit. Sorry.
- Did you hear anything?
- Mm-mm.
So, how was your first day back?
It was great.
Yeah, everyone thinks
I'm a freak.
Oh, I doubt that.
Isn't it cool
to be different nowadays?
Not recently hospitalized
for psychosis.
It's like the biggest event
of the year for them.
It's ridiculous.
I mean, everyone knows.
- Even my teachers.
- It'll blow over.
Someone will get a bad haircut,
or Alexa will make out
with someone's boyfriend, and...
they'll forget all about it.
No, she just...
won't talk to me anymore.
She's got whole new friends
who love hearing horror stories
about the crazy girl.
Stop calling yourself that.
It's like I'm a social currency.
Whatever. I mean, I don't care.
It gives me more time to paint.
I think that's what
I wanna study.
- In college?
- Mm-hmm.
You don't think I'll get in?
No, I just...
I didn't know
that's what you wanted.
I think...
I think that would be wonderful
for you.
How long is this going to take?
Well, it's me.
I'm a spectacularly talented
daughter,
who's one to spend hours
memorializing me.
I can actually feel
myself aging.
Yeah, you're right.
A lot of wrinkles.
Who knows how long that'll take.
Hmm.
Bring your sweater.
It's 90 degrees outside.
I'm already roasting.
- It feels good.
- Yeah, for a sauna.
Bye.
Ready, guys?
And go.
Hey, I'll walk with you.
No, thanks.
We don't wanna catch your crazy.
Hey, wait up.
Hey!
- What are you up to?
- What are you doing?
- Cutting class, I guess.
- Well, stop.
Why? It's just P.E.
Gonna end up
in the nurse's office anyway.
I mean, stop following me.
Are you okay?
No, I'm not okay. My best friend
won't even talk to me anymore.
- Why not?
- I don't know.
There's got to be some kind
of reason.
When I said I don't know,
I mean I kind of know,
I just don't wanna talk
about it.
Oh.
You wanna get out of here?
Maybe I could take you home
or wherever.
Wherever?
Yeah.
Okay.
We're gonna be pedaling
this thing like the Flintstones.
Yeah, sorry,
I'm still restoring it.
How long has it been?
A while.
It wasn't running, so I had
to rebuild the carburetor.
I've got new rotors, brake pads,
change the starter
and then replaced the rack
and pinion.
It's been about six months,
But, you know...
I ran out of money
before I got to the body.
- At least it's running.
- For now.
Oh. So, is that what
you wanna do?
- What?
- Be a mechanic?
No. Well...
car mechanics
and quantum mechanics
aren't closely related.
They're more like homonyms.
You know, like,
a wave versus two wave.
If that makes sense.
- That's cool.
- Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
Okay. We're gonna have to...
- stop here.
- What? Why?
Uh...
My... My windshield wipers
aren't working.
We're gonna be stuck here
for a minute.
Do you have to do that?
- What?
- Just magic. Right now?
I already told you
it's not magic. It's skill.
It's puzzles, sleight of hand.
Everything is contingent
on the sleight of mind.
Everything's an illusion.
Get out while you can.
Back to weather
on the seven.
Please, please stop.
Are you okay?
Mm-hmm.
Well, you're fidgeting,
and your face is flushed,
your breathing's
shortened, so...
What are you afraid of?
Nothing. You're just...
You're just talking really fast.
I guess I can have that effect
on people sometimes.
It's just because I don't like
about inconsequential stuff
like the weather.
Which would be ironic actually.
- Hmm?
- If it was the weather.
You know, like,
Rain afraid of rain.
Run now. Rain, run!
No. I just... I just...
I just wanna go home.
- Right here?
- Yeah.
It's okay.
Oh, you didn't have
to get my door.
I did. The passenger door
doesn't open from the inside,
so it's...
- Sorry for wasting your day.
- Oh, you didn't waste it.
You don't have to protect
my feelings either.
This was actually the...
One of the best days
I've had in a really long time.
We didn't do anything.
Yeah.
- Have a nice night.
- You too.
Look, there's something
I need to tell you,
I don't want you
to get freaked out or anything.
I'm, like, sick.
No, I mean,
not like cancer. Like...
in my head.
Hey, Rain?
Oh, hey. Okay. This thing's
gonna go really late,
and I got my guys working,
so they're gonna handle
the cleanup.
I'll be home as early as I can,
I promise. And I have my phone.
Okay.
Where's your phone?
Do you have it?
Yes, I have my phone.
All right.
I literally just told you
not to lock the door.
Rain, I'm not gonna tell you
again.
- Where were you?
- I...
I was at the library. I was...
studying and...
Mm-hmm.
- What's his name?
- Who?
You forget your father and I
were study buddies.
That's gross.
His name is Caleb.
It's a nice name.
I got to call your grandparents.
You should help your father
finish loading up.
Help!
It's not real, it's not real.
- It's not real, it's not real.
- Rain? Hey.
- Did you hear that?
- What?
There was a girl...
A girl next door,
a tiny little girl.
- Wh... Where?
- She was...
She was screaming for help.
Did you hear?
Um, no. I...
I didn't hear anything.
Where did you see her?
In the...
Over there in the window.
- Rain, there's nobody out here.
- No, she was there. I swear.
She was standing there
and then she... She grabbed her.
- Who?
- Ms. McConnell?
No. I don't know!
I couldn't see.
Oh.
Rain, use your checklist.
Is it possible?
No. She doesn't even have kids.
Yeah, I know, but that...
That's the point, Dad.
Oh, this is ridiculous.
- Honey.
- All right.
Why don't you try to go to bed
and then, we'll go over there
tomorrow and...
we'll check it out, okay?
- On or off?
- On is good.
- Mom?
- Yeah, baby?
- Can you stay with me?
- Of course, baby girl.
- You having second thoughts?
- No.
- Are you sure?
- Dad.
Oh!
- Good morning.
I wasn't expecting guests.
Yeah. Can we... Can we just
talk to you for a sec?
Yeah, sure. Come on in.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sorry about the mess.
I'm still fixing her up.
You should see my place.
I've seen your yard.
So, what can I do for you?
Okay, this might sound
a little bit weird,
but um, Rain has been hearing
these noises,
and we just thought that
we would come by
to make sure everything was...
Everything is good.
- What kind of noises?
- A little girl.
Little girl?
Uh, the folks across the street
have kids.
That's probably what you heard.
- She's lying!
- Rain.
There's a little girl
in your attic! I saw her.
In my attic?
I have an attic,
but there's no one up there
as far as I know.
I'm happy to bring you up there.
No, no, no, that's... We're good.
- Thank you for the offer.
- Yeah. I want to.
Oh!
Okay. Well, this does not
make me look good.
- Quite a collection.
- Yeah.
I have not been up here
since Gram passed.
She made each one by hand.
Their clothes were much nicer
than anything she ever made us.
Yeah, it sure does
bring back memories.
Oh! Oh, jeez.
Don't... I definitely don't even
worry about it.
Jeez.
- Hey.
- Yeah?
We'll get out
of your hair.
You good, Rain?
Thank you for humoring her.
That's not a problem.
Humor me, Dad? What?
Do you think this is a joke?
No, I don't.
She's lying!
Did you see the Almanacs?
- There's one up there from 2018!
- So what, Rain?
She said
she hasn't been up there.
Who gives a shit whether
she's been
in her own attic or not?
Well, you never believe me!
You listen to someone
you don't even like.
Hold up. I get it! I get it!
She's wacko, okay?
But she sounds
a hell of a lot more logical
- than you do right now.
- Can you just give me
- the benefit of the doubt!
- Give you the benefit of the...
Have you been listening
to yourself?
- You can't, I'm crazy, right?
- No, no, no, no.
- No. Rain, please stop it!
- I hear things, I see shit...
Stop it!
Just stop it for a second.
Everything is fine over there!
When are you get that
through your head?
What if that was me up there?
Oh, my God.
There's no one up there.
It's your mind.
Your mind
is just playing tricks on you.
Please stay away
from that house, okay?
If she files
another complaint...
the state is gonna put you
in a hospital.
Can you promise me?
Okay.
Come here.
So how have you
been feeling
since you've been home?
Better than being
strapped down
and experimented on.
I can't sleep, even though
I'm taking my medication,
which I don't really need
in the first place.
We've been through this before,
Rain.
It's not helping.
And I just wanna feel
like myself.
You realize if you choose
to go off your medication,
you're likely to end up
in an institution
where they'll force you
to stay on it.
I'm so sick of this.
I know things are happening,
and no one believes me.
And then it makes me question
whether it's just in my head,
even though I know it's real.
Is there anything in particular
that you're unsure of?
Do you think I'm stupid?
Do you think I think
you're stupid?
I know they tell you things.
Who's "they?"
They told you
about the little girl, right?
What girl?
My neighbor is keeping
a little girl in her attic.
Rain, this is not like
your other hallucinations.
This is a serious accusation,
one that'll likely have
equally serious consequences
for one of you.
I heard her screaming.
Have you run
through your questions?
Mm-hmm.
Did anybody else react to her?
No. No,
she's keeping her hidden.
- Why would she do that?
- I don't know! I think...
I think she kidnapped her,
and she's keeping her
chained up,
and she screams for help.
Do you think it's possible
that you might be projecting
your own fears
of feeling confined
or restrained?
Projecting your own fears
of feeling confined
and restrained?
Help me! Help me!
Get me out of here!
Help, help!
Yeah.
What's that?
Yeah, I guess
it could be possible.
- I'm sorry, sweetie, you okay?
- Oh, yeah. It's just a cut.
I was worried you were Mom.
I'm making her dinner
to cheer her up.
That's nice.
What's that?
- It's ranch.
- Buttermilk aioli?
And I see some pan-roasted,
leavened bread
with herb-infused tomato puree
and a blend
of artisanal cheeses.
Dad, she's coming! Distract her.
- Right.
- What's going on?
Nothing, Mom,
please don't come in.
Okay, okay.
The singularity is near.
We're all gonna merge
with artificial intelligence.
Not me, "we."
- But them, "we." I'll be fine.
- How's that?
Just no social media.
No cell phone.
You don't have a cell phone?
No. Otherwise I would've asked
for your number.
But I don't.
"Do-nut" forget to vote for me!
- Will do.
- Thank you.
Nice kid.
Where do you even learn
about all that stuff?
Oh, you know, online.
You can find out anything,
if you know
what you're looking for.
It's actually pretty
hypocritical for me to say.
- I figured...
- Idiot!
- What?
- Loser is freaking me out.
- Get out of here.
- You know.
Stupid!
Why didn't she just
die?
- Stupid.
- Freak.
What are you feeling?
Can we go outside?
Yeah, she parked to the side.
- Rain?
- One foot, right?
- Shh! Shh!
What are you...
What are you doing?
- They're gonna take me away.
- Who?
The cops! My neighbor,
she called the cops on me.
I think they're just on patrol.
You don't believe me?
No. I mean,
I don't know, I guess.
But why would she call the cops?
She needs to get rid of me,
my neighbor.
She kidnapped a little girl.
She's keeping her in her attic.
Have you told the cops that?
- No, I can't.
- Why not?
- They're on her side!
- Dude, this is insane.
Yeah. I know! I know.
Okay. You're telling me
that your neighbor
kidnapped a girl
and has her chained
in her attic right now?
And she called the cops on you?
- Do you realize how that sounds?
- Yeah.
I know. Okay.
But have you seen the news?
Look at Dahmer, no one thought
that could happen.
He had neighbors.
But people are demented!
Okay.
I just need you to trust me.
I do. All right. I...
- If this is true, you gotta...
- It is true. Okay. I...
I just need proof.
All right, well, maybe I can...
Maybe I can help.
Meet me here after school,
all right?
We... we'll figure it out.
Yeah.
My mom's here.
I gotta go.
All right,
see you tomorrow.
Hey, get in.
Okay.
- Hey, girl.
- Hi.
Hi, Rain.
It's Dr. Pangloss here.
I'm checking to see
if you're gonna make it
to your appointment today.
Hey, where are you going?
I thought you left.
I did. I had to fill up.
Sorry. Here. Get in.
Oh, my...
Sorry. I kind of crushed it.
No. It's actually...
It's for you.
I made you a little something.
- What is it?
- Open it.
Is it magic?
No. You don't like magic.
It's a neuron.
- Really?
- Yeah. You know, I...
It's kind of nerdy,
you know, but...
I don't know, I guess
I just like your brain.
I love it. Thanks.
That's her place.
- That's nice.
- She inherited it.
Okay. How are we gonna do this?
Uh...
We just wait, I guess,
and watch,
figure out her schedule.
She works Monday through Friday,
from 7:00 to 4:00,
and has a night class at HCC
from 7:00 to 11:00.
That's gonna be our prime time.
What? Did you just think
I was gonna wait
for someone else to fix this?
I'm not breaking
into somebody's house.
I need to know.
Shh.
Come on, come on, come on.
Why can't we come back
Wednesday when she's at work?
Who knows what could happen
to her by Wednesday!
This is new. It was open before.
Well, then, let's just go.
We got to find a screwdriver
or something!
- Hey, look.
- So?
Maybe she does have a kid.
I found one!
- What the hell, Rain?
- What?
You said she works
Monday through Friday.
It would've been helpful
to mention it was at our school.
It's not okay.
This is really bad.
Walls don't bleed,
walls don't bleed.
Walls don't bleed.
- Mom?
- I'm sorry. It was just...
- You scared me.
- I didn't mean to.
Just wanted to see
what you're seeing.
Be careful what you wish for.
So, when am I gonna get
to meet this Caleb?
Probably never.
- Why?
- Lie.
- It wasn't a lie.
- I didn't say it was.
Yeah, well, I know
what you're thinking.
What?
You wanna know if he's real.
Honestly, I don't know
if he is or not.
I don't care. I like spending
time with him,
even if he's an illusion.
It's not healthy for you,
though.
How do you know, Mom?
You have no idea what it's like
to have no one to talk to.
I finally have someone
to keep me company.
And he's not hurting me
or anyone else.
So, I don't understand
what the problem is.
It's just...
It could be a trigger.
And you always have me talk to.
That's just not the same.
Why? Because I'm real?
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have said that.
I just...
I wanna get better.
I really... I do.
Sometimes I'm just afraid
to lose it all.
I know, baby.
I know.
Hey!
Let's skip class
and go back to her place.
- You're joking, right?
- No.
Rain, I'm not about to break
into my teacher's house!
Well, you kind of already did.
Well, I'm not doing it again.
Can't we just hang out
and do something normal?
Hey, let's go back
to the school.
I have an idea and this time
it doesn't involve
anything, you know, illegal.
I've been looking online
for two weeks.
You're not gonna find her.
Well, you are severely
underestimating my skills here.
- How old would you say she was?
- Three or four.
There's so many of them.
The world's full of monsters.
All right. Well,
we're just gonna have...
- to start in Florida.
- Okay.
And just move out from there.
No. Scroll down.
You can't even search by gender.
It's just...
Um... Okay. Try, like...
Try Georgia or something.
- Any of these look familiar?
- Go to that one.
- This one?
- Yeah.
No, that's not her.
- What about any of these?
- No.
You know, that kind that looks...
Okay, no. That's not it.
Okay. Go back. Try, um...
Try South Carolina.
Keep going. Scroll, scroll.
No.
Go back. Try Alabama.
I'm telling you,
she had this really curly hair.
Hmm?
Mm-mm.
Try North Carolina.
Wait, wait, go back up.
Oh, my...
Oh, my God. That... that's her.
That's the little girl.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, I'm sure.
Malia Robinson
missing from Pender County
since February.
Believed to be abducted
from her home.
Oh, my God. This is... this...
You're ama... Oh, my God.
We need to call her parents.
And tell them what?
Well, tell them
that we found her, like...
Are you sure that's a good idea?
I'm like...
I'm like freaking out right now.
I need to... Um, I need to grab
a drink of water a bit.
I'll be right back. Uh, find...
Find her contact information,
and I'll... I'll be right back.
Why are you taking it out on me?
I'm not the one who left.
Hello?
- God.
- Is everything okay?
My parents...
they just won't even
speak to each other.
I have no way
of paying for college.
And it's not just fair,
you know.
I don't wanna get stuck here.
It's not my fault!
I... I feel like I can't breathe.
No, wait, I can help.
- We can grab a...
- Stop!
Get away from me!
I think she's having
a panic attack.
Just because
you're schizophrenic
doesn't mean the rest of us
are messed up, too!
- Hey.
It doesn't bother me, you know.
I just wish you would've told me
what it was.
They've diagnosed me
with so many things,
I don't really know
what to believe anymore.
If you don't wanna be friends
after this, I'll understand.
You wanna grab something to eat?
I don't wanna be
insensitive or anything,
but what it's like?
What do you mean?
You know,
do you see things?
Do you hear things?
I don't know.
I wanna know everything
about it. You know, I...
Okay, that's a lot.
Sorry,
I'm being rude here. I...
No, it's fine. Um...
Number one, I don't have
multiple personalities.
A lot people assume that,
but it's completely different.
All right. So it's just Rain.
I mean, not exactly.
There's a lot of voices
that say the worst things
you could possibly imagine.
I mean, or that I could.
I mean, to be honest,
it gets kind of scary
not really knowing
if I can trust
what I see or hear.
But a lot of people,
they don't have
visual hallucinations,
just auditory ones.
But I have both, so...
Sorry. I... I know
it's kind of...
- weird.
- No.
It's what makes you you.
You know, I...
I'm different, you're different.
Why should we have
to apologize for that, you know?
I don't see anybody else
apologizing for having
diabetes or tuberculosis,
you know.
Look, Rain, it's...
it's okay if she's not real.
- I'll see you later?
- Yeah. Bye.
- Hey, you're home late.
- It's only 7:00.
Did you do anything today?
Mom, if I can get out
and socialize, you can, too.
I'm proud of you.
Hey, Monkey,
I've got a surprise for you.
Ta-da.
What do you think?
Yeah, it looks good.
You remember that day?
Yeah. You and Mom looked
so happy.
I think I'm gonna stay
in the other room for now.
Oh, okay.
Mommy!
Do something.
Help me.
Mom?
Mom, what are you doing in here?
What's wrong?
Is it something I did?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I messed up.
No, baby.
- No, it's not you.
- It's not you.
I'm gonna try to be better,
I promise.
I'm sorry.
Just like taking a candy
from a baby.
Right, Ms. McConnell?
No one's reacting.
He's not real.
Rain?
- Idiot.
- You're stupid.
Stupid, stupid, stupid.
Rain. Rain.
Rain? He's not real.
What were you thinking?
You're stupid.
Don't forget to turn in
your papers,
if you haven't done it already.
Like whatever.
Rain?
What are you doing here?
- You've been ignoring me.
- Yeah.
Yeah. And...
I wasn't expecting
you would admit that.
Yeah. Well, I did.
And I've been ignoring you
- because you're not real.
- I am real.
No, you're in prison.
You're a prism.
What?
Okay. Number one,
is it possible?
No. The answer is no.
No one like you exists
in real life.
I do... And what makes you
think I'm not real?
You're just too perfect.
What? Okay. That's a first.
No, I...
You're like perfectly imperfect.
I really don't wanna keep
talking about this with you.
Well, too bad because now
I'm not going anywhere. I mean...
This is bad enough
to find friends out here,
much less...
Stop. You need to go,
whether you're real or not.
No, I am real.
And you're a little different,
yeah.
I don't care about that.
I mean, I do, I...
I care about it. I just...
I like you.
- What was that?
- What? You heard her?
- I heard something.
- It was Malia!
- Well, it could've been a cat.
- No, it wasn't a cat!
We should call the police then.
- No, I can't!
- Why not?
You just said
it could've been a cat.
And if I'm wrong,
they'll put me away.
Okay. Well, what do you
want us what to do?
We're good.
Through here. Come on.
Hey. I think we can
get in through the garage.
What's going on?
- Enough is enough, John.
- Dani, what's going on?
It's one thing
when she's having issues,
but now she's vandalizing
my home
and making accusations
that could end my career.
Slow down. What? What did...
I've worked my ass off
for my retirement,
I cannot afford
to have that jeopardized.
What do you want me to do?
- You know what you need to do.
- No. I really don't.
You need to take her
into the hospital.
Do you want me
just lock my kid up
and just sweep her
under the rug?
You know, I get
that you're in a tough place,
but if you don't take her in,
I'm filing charges.
Excuse me, hold on a minute.
- Dani, seriously.
- No, I... I'm done. I'm done.
- Excuse me. Dani.
- I'm done!
- Dani, just...
- I can't.
Please, just...
I told you
not to go over there.
- What were you thinking?
- John.
She has a giant doll house
in her garage.
Yeah. She's got 100 dolls
in her attic.
She's weird.
Who the hell cares?
This is all part of her plan.
She's gonna trap her in there.
- Are you listening to yourself?
- That's what she wants!
She wants you to think
I'm crazy,
so that can send me away.
You broke
into somebody's house, Rain.
I didn't break into it,
- Caleb broke the window.
- Oh, Christ!
This... This again.
No, she only reported
seeing you.
Well, she maybe just
didn't see him,
but he was there.
He heard her scream!
Caleb doesn't exist, okay?
- Seriously, you need to stop.
- Stop? Stop what?
If I wasn't sick,
you would never even be saying...
- You are sick!
- But I'm not my sickness!
Yes, you are! We all are!
You're going to Westbrook.
- Don't you dare say that!
- What? No!
I've had enough of this.
You're both out of control.
Have you been taking
your medicine?
Yes.
Have you?
It doesn't matter
what I say anyways,
- you don't believe me.
- Come here. Come here.
- Stop. Get off!
- Come here.
Get your fucking hands off me.
Take your medicine.
Already taken it today.
- Take another dose.
- No! Dad, stop!
- What are you... Stop!
- Take it!
Is this what you want, Dad?
You want me to take them all,
- get out of your hair for good?
- What are you doing?
Okay.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry.
Don't say that.
Don't ever say that again.
I don't know what else
I'm supposed to do.
I'm sorry.
Sorry doesn't make it okay.
- What are we gonna do?
- Nice of you to show up
after your disappearing act.
What? You ran, I ran. And...
Well, she called the cops.
She's filing charges
to have me sent away.
What? Where?
- I gotta go to class.
- No.
If you leave,
what's gonna happen to Malia?
You mean the cat next door?
So, what's your plan?
We can climb up the ladder
and break through the window.
While she's home?
That's not gonna do any good.
She will call the cops,
get us arrested.
We have to do something
before she kills her. What...
What makes you think
she's gonna kill her?
She knows that I know!
She's gonna kill her
and it's all gonna be my fault!
and I'm gonna be the one
who just sit
and even do anything to save her
or...
- Rain!
- I can't...
We need to come up
with a coherent plan, okay?
Panicking is not gonna help.
Let me get you some water,
all right?
Wrong one.
You take all these?
Not exactly.
They're constantly
changing them up
to see what's most effective.
I can't sleep
on any of them, though.
Studies have found strong links
between insomnia
and intellect, so.
And I'm sure that's what it is.
Just me being a genius.
How can you
be playing cards right now?
It helps me when I'm nervous.
Here...
try it again, pick one.
Nope.
You pick one.
Yeah? What are you gonna do
with those?
Just pick a card.
- Rain?
- Yeah, Mom?
Hey, hi.
I'm sorry. Who is this?
Um, this is Caleb.
Caleb, this is my mom.
Wait, you can see him?
Of course I can see him.
I was so nervous of...
Never mind.
Don't let me interrupt
your date.
It's not a date, Mom.
- We're just friends.
- Mm-hmm.
I don't think we should wait.
Let's go Wednesday, after...
You know, actually, I...
I gotta go.
But I'll, uh...
I'll see you tomorrow. Yeah?
Okay. Yeah.
Did I ruin your date?
All right. All right,
guys, come on. You're late.
Come on in. Take a seat.
Let's get started.
I told you.
- I told you.
- Rain?
He's not real.
I told you.
- Loser.
- Rain.
Kill yourself.
Rain?
No, no! Rain.
Rain, are you okay?
Rain, can we talk for a moment?
You should just die.
No one likes you.
Freak. Freak.
Freak. Freak. Freak. Freak.
You're a freak.
You should kill yourself.
Rain?
I think you need to go
see the nurse.
You're crazy.
Hi. You've reached
the Burroughs residence.
Hi, I... I need to talk
to Dr. Pangloss.
She's over at the hospital,
Ms. Burroughs.
But I can let her know
you wanna speak to her.
Um, no, I need to see her now.
- Sorry.
- She's not here.
Dr. Pangloss! Dr. Pangloss!
Dr. Pangloss!
Rain!
- Save me.
- Rain. Rain.
♪ Rain, Rain, go away
Come again another day ♪
You're crazy.
- You're crazy.
- Get it together.
You're losing it.
She's not real.
She's gonna die
and you're gonna be locked up
where you belong.
They're better off without you.
Get it together.
- Stop!
Stop!
Rain, honey?
Rain.
Rain, sweetheart.
I saw a man
with yellow eyes.
He wants to take me
as his prize.
Cries. Cries. She cries.
Cry me a river
and watch me drown.
- No sound, it's all too loud.
- No, no, sweetheart.
Put it down. Put it down.
Okay. All right.
You're okay.
You're okay, you're safe.
You're safe. You're safe.
Sweetheart, you're safe.
- Wait, Malia, Malia.
- No. No, Rain. Rain!
- No, I won't let you.
- Won't let me what, Mom?
This is your fault
in the first place!
I wouldn't be dealing
with any of this,
if you hadn't made me sick!
I'm... I hate you.
Rain, please.
Please, if you go over there,
they will take you away from us.
I don't care. What if it was me?
I'm not just gonna sit here
- and wait.
- No. No. Rain!
- Rain? Open the door!
- Mom's making a big deal
- out of this, and I've got this.
- We need to talk.
Move away from the window,
please.
I'm not gonna jump, Dad!
I was just...
- Honey, listen to your dad.
- You ruin everything!
There's no one there.
Yeah. She is! She's right there.
Your mom...
She's not here.
She passed away
three years ago, baby.
No. That's not true.
- It's true. I'm sorry.
- Why are you doing this to me?
I'm not doing anything to you.
You need to know the truth.
What about at dinner?
She was there.
We were all there.
Was anyone else reacting?
Yes, Dad. Yes, you were.
- You were reacting.
- Because I was trying...
Dad, she's coming! Distract her.
- Right, right.
- What's going on?
Nothing, Mom.
Look...
I was just trying to...
This whole time?
Mom's coming.
I didn't know
what to do...
Right, right.
...when you started
seeing her again.
- Nothing to see here.
- Nothing, Mom. Don't come in.
Coast is clear.
I tried to remind you
that she was gone,
but it was really, really hard
seeing you relive that loss
over and over and over again.
Yeah, Mom?
But after a while...
your reality with her
was just so much...
It was so much happier...
than mine without her.
And I was... I was...
I was so afraid.
I was just so terrified
that you... That you...
That you would wanna go...
to be with her.
How do I know
you're not lying to me? Hmm?
- Rain...
- How do I know you're not
- just messing with my head?
- Why would I do that?
Why'd you lie to me
in the beginning?
You're just trying to get
to my head.
- Stop fucking with my head!
- Just stop! Stop!
- What are you doing?
- I'm calling 911.
- No! Stop!
- Rain! Rain! Come back!
Rain!
Malia is already dead!
Don't listen to her.
- She's lying.
- This is your fault.
- Do something.
She's lying.
Help me.
Shit.
Malia?
Help.
- Help her!
- You can still see her!
Malia?
It's okay.
I'm here to help you.
Save me.
- Save me.
- Stop.
No, no, you're not real.
I need to save Malia.
There is no Malia!
It's always been me.
You should kill yourself.
No, no, no, no. She's real.
She's real.
- You did this...
- No, no.
...to me.
Look at me.
You can't leave me.
I don't want to.
I'm sorry.
I don't want you to go away.
I don't have to.
I don't wanna be crazy, Mom.
- Help me.
- Malia?
She's made up, Rain.
No, she's not, Mom.
You are.
Hi.
Here's your order.
Thanks.
- Keep the change.
- Have a good one.
It's too late.
It's too late. She's dead.
It's too late. It's too late.
- You killed her.
- It's too late.
- No.
- Wait.
- You're too late.
- Save Malia.
It's not too late.
- Don't do it.
- Go back.
Keep going.
No. Stop! Stop it!
Malia, are you here?
Malia. Malia, hi.
I'm gonna get you
out of here, okay?
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay. Okay.
Ah!
Hello?
Is anybody down there?
Oh! Oh.
Oh, gosh. Rain,
you scared the hell out of me.
Oh, gosh.
Oh! Here, let me help you.
Don't trust her.
Here.
Rain, take my hand.
That's right.
I don't want anything
to hurt you.
- You can't trust her.
- You can trust her.
- It's okay.
- You're just gonna die.
She's not real, Rain.
- There's no one there, Rain.
- She's lying.
There's no little girl there.
- Either one of you.
- Save Malia.
Malia, Malia, come here,
come here. Come here, come here.
Wait. Don't do this.
She's gone.
She's not real, Rain.
You made her up in your head.
You're gonna die.
Don't you do this.
- Listen to me.
- Liar!
- She's a liar, Rain.
- Put that down.
There's something wrong
with you, Rain. Just...
- You're the crazy one.
- You're crazy.
- You're gonna die.
- Let me help you.
Come on. Come on.
Come on. Let me help you.
Does your dad know you're here?
I don't... I don't think so. No.
I don't have to tell him.
We can just keep this
between us, okay?
Why would you do that?
Because I know what happens
when they
institutionalize people
and I don't want that
happening to you.
You have been through
so much already.
I just don't know
what to believe anymore.
You've seen that she's not real.
There's no little girl.
You can just go on home
and we'll keep this between us.
- Okay?
- Rain?
Caleb, don't come down here.
Who are you talking to, Rain?
There's no one there.
This is your head.
This is...
Go, Rain,
get her out of here!
Make a decision, Rain.
A figment of your imagination,
or the real thing?
No, no! No!
You think I was gonna let you
get away with this?
I would've let you go.
I don't want anyone to die.
But you couldn't let things be.
Get her out of here, Rain!
Rain.
Hey, hey, hey. Hey, hey, hey.
It's just me.
You're safe.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
She's real?
Come on, come on, come on.
I need to go back inside.
Caleb's...
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I got you. I got you.
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
I need to go back inside.
- Caleb...
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
He's not real, Rain.
He's not real.
Call EMT.
Hey, there.
You all right?
He is real.
Check out
the neighbor's house.
Hey, we got
another one over here.
I love you.
I'm so proud of you, monkey.
Hey, it's gonna be okay.
They're gonna
take good care of you,
get you back to your mom
and dad. Okay? I promise.
You're such
a brave girl.
Hi.
When you said
that wasn't a date,
what did you, uh...
What did you mean?
Because it felt kinda...
I don't know, datey to me.
- Did it?
- Yeah.
I mean, granted I don't have
that much experience...
with that sort of thing, but...
You mean, like, dates?
Yeah.
But maybe
we can have some more of them...
when I'm out of this?
Hmm.
We could maybe arrange that.
I'd like that. Personally.
For the first time,
I can feel the medicine working.
I can finally tell
the difference
between what's real
and what's not.
But do you still hear
the voices and...
Yeah. They're still there,
but not as, like...
But yeah.
What about mom?
Do you still see her?
No.
I miss her.
- Hey, Dad?
- Yeah?
I think I'm gonna move back
into my room.
Oh, okay.
Sounds like a plan.
I'm here, baby girl.
I love you so, so much.
I love you, too.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull