The 117 citizens of Roano Secretary Island suddenly disappeared.
The island left a mystery letter, <>
Year 1872, Alantic Ocean.
The Mary Sylas was found floating in the middle of the ocean.
All of it's crew were missing.
These few words were hurriedly written down in the ship's log :
4th December. My wife, Mary.
- Did you find anything?
- Nothing.
- You?
- Same.
- Continue searching.
- Yes.
Careful!
This island sure freaks me out.
But this island is also part of Japan.
Where did all the island's people go?
You guys check over there. Quickly.
Let's go this way.
Come on.
Go in.
Forward.
What the hell is this?
It's still warm.
Not only this. The rest of the things in this house are the same.
Captain. Come in.
- What?
- There is someone. From the island.
We found someone on the outside. Come quick!
- Is he alone?
- Yes.
Where are the others?
I can't hear what he is saying.
You. Tell me where are the others.
Where did the others for this island go?
Tell me. What happened on this island?
Siren.
What?
Three times.
The third warning.
There is no choice. Take him away.
Danger!
You can't go outside.
When the siren sounds, you can't go outside.
What?
When the siren sounds, you can't......
Forbidden Siren
Are you still thinking of Tokyo?
I understand your feelings, this is only temporary.
I understand. Its for Hideo.
Heard it's a new house
provided by the company.
Its quite a big isolated house.
Isolated?
From what I heard.
It comes with all the furniture and a big garden.
Its something that Tokyo could never have.
Hideo, don't run around.
You will get sick if you do.
Hideo.
It would be great if he could run around freely.
Look!
Is that it?
Yame Island.
Excuse me, is Minamida here?
I am Minamida, sorry for coming late.
Sorry to disturb.
This is Minamida from the local clinic.
Nice to meet you.
Sorry to trouble you.
Say hello to uncle.
My apologies. Hideo.
Hideo.
The university hospital already informed me.
The child is better than I expected.
But can he get better just by staying on the island?
Don't run around, you'll get sick.
Hideo.
Wait.
This doesn't look like Japan. This Yame Island.
I heard a big part of it is history.
The people that came to Japan a hundred years ago
started gathering on this island.
Hideo.
After the war, this was the American soldiers' burial ground
It affected this place a little.
That makes sense.
Hideo. Come.
We will be leaving.
On the left is where you will be staying.
I'll see you later at the clinic.
Thank you. Sorry to trouble you.
Dad.
We should at least buy some new furniture.
Why? All these furniture can still be used.
We are not staying for long anyway.
Hideo. Stop fooling around.
Take out your own luggage.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Osnan.
Is something the matter?
I'm sorry, let me help you with these.
It's alright, we're neighbours anyway.
Why would you come such a secluded place?
A change of environment, for my brother.
Oh, must be hard.
If you need to know anything about the island, feel free to ask me.
Thanks a lot.
Coming from Tokyo, you might not know this.
On this island, everyone's relationship is very good.
I see.
Also, don't go out at night.
Especially the metal tower in the forest.
There are wild beasts around, very dangerous.
Oh yeah, one more thing.
When the siren sounds, don't go out.
Siren? What's that about?
Its nothing much, just an old island's folklore.
But its also the islanders rule.
Is that right?
The child has been hardworking all along.
The neighbour has also been very helpful.
Correct.
Life... No problem.
All the house's furniture are in check.
Beautiful sunlight.
The ocean's smell.
Wonderful
No problems.
The draft will be done soon.
From today onwards,
I will keep a close eye.
That's all for today.
Let's observe for a while.
Alright.
Hideo.
I have something to talk to the doctor about. Will you wait outside for me?
Don't go too far.
I can stop worrying now.
Hideo is afraid of doctors.
But he seems to like you.
Is that right? That's great.
Doctor.
Will he really recover?
But before this...
Don't forget, this isn't Tokyo.
Let us cure him slowly.
This island has its own timing.
I'm very worried.
I don't know if he will be cured on this island.
Actually, the people on this island
are more introverted. They might seem a little cold.
But they are not bad people.
Yuki, you will start to like this place.
That's good to hear.
Don't worry, I'm here if you need me.
Wind?
The wind in this place has a sound.
Is it because of this island's complicated geography,
that causes the wind to have a sound?
Maybe,
it will be taken away.
Taken away?
Where does the sound come from?
From near the metal tower,
but very few people from the island have been there.
It's dangerous there.
- Pay respects
- Inside the precious mirror
- Is the real reason
- Only the transparent mirror
- The dogs will become Gods
- The living will become evil
Hideo. Hideo,
Hideo.
What happened...
Why isn't there anyone...
Hideo.
Hideo, quit fooling around.
Hideo! Where are you?
Year 1976. Interview dairy.
Wind's here. Siren will sound.
Second time the siren sounded on the island.
Sound is like a police siren.
The meaning of the siren.
Fisherman's tale.
Fear watches over the islanders.
The siren comes from the metal tower?
August, 2nd. Late night.
In the middle of a blackout.
After the third siren, the island started to change.
What are you doing here.
Siren.
When the siren sounds, you cannot leave the house.
Let me go!
You can't leave the house.
Hideo.
Why did you come here?
- It's only inside the precious mirror
- The real truth
- Only the transparent mirror
Hideo, stop singing this kind of songs.
What happened?
It's nothing.
You're going out?
I want to take some night shots in the forest.
I see...
The metal tower is dangerous. Do be careful.
I will be back by morning... You go ahead and sleep.
I'm leaving.
Impossible.
Come over here...
Come over here.
Hello?
Who is this?
We are... Your surroundings.
If the siren sounds...
Who is this? Hello? Hello?
Hideo.
Siren is sounding, you can't go out.
What strong winds.
Okay.
Dad.
Mr. Amano.
Even the islanders will get lost in the forest at night.
I hope nothing has happened to him.
Have you reported this?
I did.
But they said it wasn't very serious,
and that he will be back soon.
Let's just wait.
Do you want to ask the islanders to search together?
No.
Why not?
I keep getting the feeling
that the islanders cannot be trusted.
Siren.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
It must be because Dad went out when the siren was sounding.
Someone told me
that when the siren was sounding, you must not go outside.
Doctor?
Doctor Minamida?
Dad.
What's that?
What.
Look at the mirror...
Dog is God.
Life is evil.
Unchanger.
Immortality through life.
Dog.
Life.
Who's there?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Dad.
Wait.
Don't be alarmed. It's me.
Where did you go? You made me so worried.
You...
Are you sure it was over there?
Doctor. Come over here for a while.
Is it there?
Dad.
You're here.
I tripped and fell real bad.
Luckily, I had only minor injuries.
Were you worried?
Yeah.
Sorry to let you worry.
Hideo, it's your sister.
Please be quiet.
Hideo.
Sister will protect you.
Osnan?
Dad.
Have you seen Osnan?
I don't know.
Osnan?
This is Dad's.
Is that all?
Please take a closer look, Doctor.
Dad didn't fall. Someone attacked him.
Attacked?
I keep getting the feeling
that Dad wasn't normal after he came back.
And Osnan, he has never left like that.
You're just being sensitive.
No.
It must have something to do with the siren the other day.
Miss Yuki...
What's is it with the siren?
After the siren sounds, what is it that will happen?
Its nothing more than the island's folklore.
How about that diary?
Diary?
Something must have happened to Dad.
Okay, stay calm.
Tell me more about the diary.
I'm home.
Yame Island
The Roanoke Incident.
Mary Sylas Incident.
The Missing Incident.
A long time ago,
during the 15th Century,
an epidemic disease was brought from a foreign land.
The infected
were isolated on Yame Island.
The frightening disease
brought the people of Meiye Island infinite disaster.
One by one, the islanders fell
and died.
A very long time ago, there was an old saying,
A mermaid's blood and flesh can give you an immortal life.
The people captured the mermaid.
The mermaid was eaten clean.
Mermaid's Tale
Sirene.
Year 1976
With the exception of one survivor,
the people of Yame Island vanished.
In a middle of a blackout.
The third siren.
The islanders started to change.
Siren...
The third siren...
The siren is sounding, do not go outside.
The siren is sounding, do not......
The only survivor
commited sucide afterwards.
Hideo.
Come here quick.
Leave that person alone.
Hurry.
Siren.
Hideo.
His forehead is hot...
Mirror.
Dog is God.
Living is evil.
Only those who don't change
will lead an immortal life,
and live beyond the human world.
The siren is sounding, do not go outside.
You will be eaten by them.
They are here.
Don't come in here.
You will be eaten.
Run!
Stop the siren!
Hideo.
Hideo, do you like sister?
Do you trust sister?
That's good. Listen well.
We'll hide in the ship at the harbour.
We will leave this island first thing in the morning.
Leave this frightening place.
Hideo hates this place too, right?
Then, listen to sister...
Sister will protect you...
Dad.
The photo taken after the islanders dissapearance.
This house...
It can't be...
All the islanders are...
It's coming... The siren.
Hideo.
Who's that?
What are you doing here!
Dad!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Don't!
Don't come over here!
Policeman. Help!
Help!
No place to hide.
Where should we run...
The metal tower.
The siren is coming from the tower?
Are you okay?
Yuki, where are you?
Miss Yuki...
Come out...
Are you over here...
Ah. I found you.
Hideo.
Don't let go no matter what. Close your eyes.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What is that?
Hideo, don't fall down.
Turn around.
Kneel down.
Hold tight.
Close your eyes.
It's no use. The siren will still sound.
Don't come over.
I don't trust you.
There is no siren.
It's all in your mind.
Only you can hear the siren.
Yuki, hold my hand.
Don't run anymore
I hear it clearly...
Come here.
Hideo.
Don't come over.
Hideo. Hideo...
Hideo is not here anymore.
Hideo...
Hideo died a long time ago.
Hideo. He...
died?
Hideo.
Hideo is afraid of doctors.
But he seems to like you.
Is that right?
She's better than I expected.
Yes.
Don't run around, you'll get sick.
Don't run around like that, Hideo.
What if you get sick?
No way...
But
Hideo and I...
Hideo, I'm your sister.
Hideo.
Have you remembered?
Hideo is not here anymore.
Shut up!
Yuki, it's dangerous. Come here.
Hurry.
Yuki.
Come here quick.
Hideo.
Yuki, it's dangerous.
Come over here quick.
Yuki.
It's dangerous.
Yuki, come over here.
Don't go anymore.
It's dangerous, come here quick.
Hurry, Yuki.
Beautiful.
It's a miracle
to survive after falling from such a height.
But
why does she hear the siren?
It's most probably a hallucination.
It was the same 26 years ago.
At that time, there was a man that lived on this island
who could also hear the siren
and started murdering the islanders.
You're saying
that's the real reason for the islanders' dissapearances?
So it seems.
But
The people of Yame Island believes that
when the siren sounds
one should never go outside.
What this actually means
is that those who can hear the siren should never go outside.
This time we are lucky.
My wife has died a long time ago.
From that time on,
that child has always played her mother's role,
taking care of Hideo.
She...
treats Hideo's death as her own fault
thinking it was her own responsibility.
She keeps blaming herself.
Hideo's death
was a great blow to her.
My daughter...
will she recover?
Whether she can see her own reality
all depends on her.
- Hell's gate
- has already opened...
The forth siren sounded.
I must kill them all!
Subbed by Sunnydown