Subtitle Extraction from : Youtube
Edit sync By : D.LUFFY
Calm down!
He won't hurt you!
What are you doing?
Put the knife away! Put the knife away!
No! Leave her!
Leave her! Leave her!
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it!
I'm watching over you.
FOUR HANDS
20 YEARS LATER
Hey, sis.
You're right.
Okay?
I'll get some help again.
Sorry about the last few weeks.
I'll go and knock some socks off.
-You do that.
Your phone.
Hello, Ms Tauber.
This is Routers Attourney's office.
You wanted us to let you know
and now it's happened.
The offenders were released last week.
Both the man and the woman.
If you have any...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh dear... Crazy enough
to listen to the competition too?
She made a mistake.
They got out.
Sometime this week.
Okay, now sit down.
They're not dangerous.
They've served their time.
They don't even know us.
Okay?
This audition is very important to me.
You have to calm down, Jessy!
They'll live in this town again.
-They're not dangerous.
You're just scared. Just calm down.
Let go of me.
-Okay...
Sit down. It's fine.
-Sorry, you're...
Just sit down.
Look at me.
Look at me. Let him be, Jessy.
Okay, thanks.
-Let him be.
Thank you. Now get home safely.
Ms Tauber?
Are you there?
Something's come up. I'm sorry.
She's sorry.
Keys.
How can you think about playing piano
when they're running free?
I won't let anyone hurt you.
Shut up!
Get in.
Hey!
Help me, please!
-Take it easy...
Okay, okay...
Stop! Stop!
Let go of me!
Hello?
Hey, hey. Stop right there...
Take it easy now. Come with me.
Where's my sister?
-Take it easy now.
Are you in pain?
Do you know where you are?
Do you understand me?
Where's my sister?
Take a seat.
This isn't my ward,
but I'll find the doctor in charge.
I'm sorry.
I want to see her.
You need some rest.
-I want to see my sister.
Did you understand what I said?
This isn't my ward.
And I didn't treat your sister.
Please.
Wait a moment.
She died before we could do anything.
Can I call someone for you?
AUTHORISATION FOR CREMATION
Ms Tauber?
Okay.
No one is to blame for the accident
and I can close the case.
There's another matter.
I saw Maria Uchwat today
and told her she could press charges.
She didn't want to.
-What do you mean?
"If you don't leave town
as soon as you get out of prison,
you'll pay for it."
My sister wrote that.
It's her handwriting.
So there won't be
any more letters like this, then?
Could you hand this in for me?
My sympathies.
I'm watching over you.
Hello.
Catching some fresh air too?
Or running away?
Fresh air...
But it's too chilly, huh?
Exactly.
-Shall we go in?
Can I grab you for a sec?
What shall we do about patient 305?
I'm not on duty right now, actually.
Maybe ask Beate.
She'll know.
-Okay.
Will do.
It fell on the floor.
Frankly,
I wouldn't let you go yet.
I'm just a bit...
Want something to help you sleep?
Okay.
That thing with the cigarette...
That was pretty mean.
Well, it's kind of a habit of mine.
Because the brain only saves moments
worth remembering.
So every day, I try to have...
a kind of mini adventure.
Firecrackers may be childish
but you remember that kind of crap.
And life consists of memories.
And with more memories
I'm kind of extending my life.
And other people's lives.
If they let you out tomorrow and...
you have no one to talk to...
then just get in touch, okay?
Martin.
-Yep.
Sophie.
-Okay.
Thanks for the second chance.
You should thank
our inability to organise.
Please begin.
It's always a question of balance,
between reception and reflection.
But everything in life is about balance,
so what I said is nonsense really.
Welcome to our team, Ms Tauber.
Thank you.
-You're welcome.
Lucky we brought our parasol, huh?
-You thought of everything.
Listen, no bikes, no motorbikes...
So does this count as an adventure?
-Of course.
YOU HONK, WE DRINK
Must be your most unpleasant date ever.
-Sure is.
But you won't forget it, huh?
Being afraid of flying
isn't embarrassing.
Not embarrassing, but...
But I'd like to have seen
a bit more of the world.
What might possibly be embarrassing is...
Sinistrophobia.
Fear of left-handed people.
Yes. Just imagine...
Any person you meet
could be left-handed.
Everyone is potentially left-handed.
So...
Are you left-handed?
Give me your hand. Give me your hand.
-Why?
You can see it.
-How?
By looking at a person's fingers.
Ah, right.
What's wrong?
What's up?
Sophie!
I'll find you...
Ms Tauber, you can't take out any more.
Your account's overdrawn.
But there should be
over 3,000 euros.
If you want to withdraw more,
we need to talk about a loan.
We have to apply for one and see
whether your monthly income
will cover it.
Are you okay?
OSTPARK STREET
Hello?
-Finally, I've got through.
I wanted... I wanted to say sorry.
-For what?
For yesterday.
Sophie?
I kept wondering what I'd done wrong.
-You didn't do anything wrong.
Coffee?
No. Hot wine punch disguised as coffee.
So...
did you black out
before or after you kicked me?
We were kissing,
you kicked me and then ran off.
Have you slept much since the accident?
Not much.
Get yourself checked over tomorrow, okay?
Of course.
I'm pretty normal otherwise. Honest.
Okay.
You're playing it cool
because you're through with me?
I got into big trouble at the hospital
for taking you to the morgue.
But...
Everyone reacts differently
to losing someone.
Take that and you'll sleep like a log.
Sleep works wonders.
Thanks.
I'd be more relaxed
if you didn't hit me when I kiss you.
Well...
We couldn't get hold of you, Ms Tauber.
-I'm sorry. My phone was...
... playing up.
But I take it you'll be
at the rehearsal tomorrow?
Yes. Absolutely.
Okay. Tomorrow at 9,
as keen and alert as ever.
Ms Tauber?
-Okay, see you tomorrow.
GPS TRACKER
SAVE ROUTE
I'm sorry.
Hey, Sophie.
I already know where one of them works.
Leave her alone!
Stop it, stop it, stop it!
What does she want?
-She wants chloroform.
I want it today.
-Today?
Morning.
Come here, please.
Take it easy. Come on out here.
No, not there. Over here.
Okay... Now tell me
why you were at the kindergarten.
Did you want to break in?
Into a kindergarten?
A kindergarten? Seriously?
Or did you think you lived there?
No surprise.
You were totally drunk.
Sorry?
I don't understand you. What?
What?
Oh, no. Let me see that.
Now take it easy...
Wake up.
Hello?
Are you okay?
I found your spray.
You have asthma, right?
Just calm down.
Now, slowly breathe in.
Slowly breathe out.
Take it nice and easy.
Everything's fine.
Your airways are clear.
You can breathe just fine.
The human body is very simple:
Everyone has their limits.
Fear, stress, repressing things.
The body makes it clear
when you reach your limits.
What you have right now
isn't caused by asthma.
Are you done with her?
I can't force you,
but I'd suggest
we check you over at the hospital.
We have a psychiatric ward.
I'd like to do a few tests and... Ms...
RECONSTRUCT ROUTE
ST. MARTINUS KINDERGARTEN
Stop right there.
Just stop right there.
I just wanted to say sorry.
This is where I came as a child.
-Okay, you've said it. Now leave.
Could you help me out a bit?
I can't remember what I was doing here.
What you were doing here?
You attacked a policeman.
You were shouting like mad.
You didn't know what you were doing.
I...
Now listen: if you come here again,
drunk or sober, I'll press charges.
It won't happen again.
Take this back.
You went crazy when you lost this.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
You have one message.
First message.
What can I say, Ms Tauber?
This is my third call. You're not here.
I'm sorry, but we'll have to
go with another candidate.
Yes?
Elly.
Hey, Sophie...
I know where one of them works already.
I'll find out where the other one lives.
I know...
I can't make everything okay again.
I... can't bring our parents...
back to life.
But I can make sure you're safe.
I'll make sure you're safe,
once and for all.
And no one will ever guess
it was us who did it.
CHILDHOOD TRAUMA
DISSOCIATIVE IDENTITY DISORDER
IDENTITY DISORDER
PSYCHOLOGICAL TRAUMA
DIFFERENT PERSONALITIES
Hello.
-Hey.
Okay... so tell me what's up.
Why...
Who's the reason
for the sleeping tablets?
My brother.
He drowned. He was drunk.
I'm sorry.
-No, it's a while ago now.
So, how do you manage...
Because you said it takes a while...
to accept what happened.
How...
-Okay.
How close were you two?
Too close.
Which means?
My sister was really ill. Paranoid.
She thought every stranger was a danger
and was always worried I'd get hurt.
When we were in your car...
I was happy she's dead.
For the first time ever,
my life is about me.
And it feels good.
But...
But somehow she won't let me.
My brother wanted me to pick him up.
He always said life was one big party.
I always picked him up.
Every time, wherever he was.
That one time, I didn't.
I phoned him on his mobile and said,
"Find your own way home. Screw you."
The word "mourning" always sounds
so selfless, but it's totally selfish.
Basically, you're just trying to carry on
without feeling guilty.
And it works.
It gets easier from month to month.
I thought we could pretend
it's your birthday.
It was funny. I'll be back in a sec.
-But the idea was pretty...
Hey!
The toilets are back there.
Has something happened?
How many times have you
been out together?
I don't want you to see her anymore.
-Who?
Stop calling her.
Don't contact her anymore.
Take it easy.
-She doesn't give a shit about you.
Hang on, Sophie...
If you contact her ever again,
I'll kill you.
Understood?
Where's the fucking money?
What are you doing, Sophie?
I like you.
And I'd never find anyone else...
Stop pissing me off.
Stop pissing me off, will you?
Shut it!
Here. Where's the money?
Hello? Hello!
What do you want?
What are you going to do to me?
Hello?
What do you want?
I'm just out for a walk.
Where's the driver?
I don't know. He's gone.
I just saw the accident.
Please, help me.
They locked me in here.
It's locked.
-Please, go and get the police.
What should I tell them?
-I've been tied up.
But I got the gag off my mouth.
And who did it?
I don't know. He came from behind
and drugged me or something.
And then I woke up in here.
Hello?
Help! Help!
Don't move.
Maria Uchwat?
You sent me that letter.
I was locked up for 20 years
because that arsehole went berserk.
Please...
Why us?
You were rich.
And didn't have any neighbours.
We wanted to get in quick.
Grab some expensive stuff.
We'd done it loads of times.
It's completely harmless.
But this time the father was home too.
We thought he wasn't there.
He went for us.
My mate...
He...
He beat him to death.
And the mother?
She'd... seen his face.
I didn't want that.
Did you do anything to the children?
-No.
To the dark-haired one?
-No, we didn't even see them.
The other one...
Does he have a child?
Well...
We'd had day release for a few years.
So it's possible.
You're going to leave town.
Move somewhere far away. Got it?
Okay.
If you go to the police...
or set foot in this town again,
you're dead.
Okay, okay.
-Okay what?
I'll never come back again.
I won't go to the police.
If you do, I'll kill you.
I need all the files, though.
I'll give you the new ones now.
The old ones are down in the archive.
Can I take the files home?
-Yes, the copies.
I don't want to get your hopes up.
Some files are away being digitised.
How long ago was it?
-Twenty years.
Oh! Let's see.
Looks like you're in luck.
Sophie Tauber, five years old,
is alert and lucid
and has no cognitive
or mnemic impairments.
She has processed the incident
far better than her older sister.
As they hid,
Jessica covered Sophie's eyes and ears,
so Sophie wouldn't see
their parents being killed.
Whenever we talk to Sophie, Jessica
stands in front of her protectively.
Jessica shows signs of severe paranoia
and is constantly worried
something will happen to Sophie.
Weeks later we established that this fear
is accompanied by a deep sense of guilt.
Jessica admitted
that a few days before the break-in
the perpetrators
had turned up at her kindergarten.
What's that?
What is that?
-Hey, Jessy!
That's mine! I found it! Hey!
Hey!
How are you?
What's your name?
Have you eaten yet today?
I heard they have my favourite food
at your kindergarten.
Strawberries with sand.
But nettles and sauce are even better.
Yum!
What did you have?
It's not even lunchtime yet.
Oh, you're right!
Do you eat here at the kindergarten?
I always eat with my mummy.
What do your parents do?
-My mummy plays the piano.
And my daddy's a dentist.
A dentist. Oh...
I have to go to the dentist soon.
Does your daddy work all week?
No, he's off on Wednesdays.
Where do you live then?
Ahornstrasse 8.
But my daddy works at Schwanleite 6.
Yes, I know that street.
I've got to go. Bye.
All therapeutic measures
to ease Jessica's sense of guilt
about the death of her parents
have failed to date.
Come on!
Drive!
Just leave me...
Fuck!
Maria Uchwat?
Is she here?
-What?
Maria Uchwat?
Doesn't work here anymore.
Where did she go?
-How should I know?
Zip up your jacket
or you'll catch cold.
When we get home, you're off to bed.
-Why? -It's half past eight.
That's early!
Why do I always
have to go to bed so early?
Hang on a minute.
She's over there!
I know what you want.
You want a nice, normal life.
You want to forget. And you should.
I want you to have a nice life,
but you have to be safe first.
I messed up. He recognised me.
But he won't get away next time.
Leave me alone! This is my life!
Just leave me alone!
What do you want?
I need your help.
You need help.
But this is too screwed up for me.
Wait!
You don't exist. You're dead.
Have you slept at all?
Since I gave you the pills...
She's leaving messages
on my answering machine.
She knows...
stuff that only Jessy and I know.
I'm taking you to hospital now.
-No, I don't need to go there.
You want help, right? I'll get you some.
-I can cope with that on my own.
I just have to know
how to get rid of her.
Get rid of her?
-She's still inside me.
I have to...
-You have to sleep.
I just want her gone.
Since I've known you,
you've been repressing her death.
Jessy's dead. I'm not repressing it.
-Give me your car keys. I'll drive.
I can cope, Martin!
-You can't cope!
You can't cope!
Did you hear what you just said?
Do you realise what you said?
Do you realise?
Okay...
Wait here. I'll get one of my colleagues.
-You'll tell them...
Sure. Don't worry.
If...
If I was normal,
we might have had a chance, huh?
First you have to get better, okay?
You don't need to lie to me.
Who's crazier? The crazy girl
or the guy who's fallen for her?
I can't be normal myself
or I'd have dumped you already.
If only for your crazy tattoo.
Why are you chained up?
I'll take the gag off
and then you can tell me why.
Help!
Come on. Finish up.
Help! Help!
Sophie? Sophie?
Leave me alone! This is my life!
Just leave me alone!
Are you still there?
My deepest sympathies on the death
of your sister, Sophie Tauber,
born in February 1990 and
deceased on October 13th this year.
We will now lay her to rest.
It didn't take you long to...
True.
It's only been around two months.
-True.
What will you do next?
We'll see.
Are you auditioning again?
On piano?
Know what my adventure was today?
I don't know what you want from me.
Listen up: I'm not the hospital.
I don't know what's crazy or normal.
Or which one of you
I'm talking to right now.
But I'd be happy
if you'd call me sometime.
One, two, three, four...