[camera reel whirring]
[grass rustling]
[distant shouting]
- My name is Dimitri Asna,
and I'm a graduate
of the All-Union institute
of Cinematography in Moscow.
I was entrusted
by our great leader,
Joseph Vissarionovich
Stalin,
to film the heroic deeds
of a distinguished
reconnaissance unit
under the command
of Sergeant Novikov.
I am proud to be a part
of this mission
in the Great Patriotic War.
Long live motherland,
and long live Czarevitch Stalin.
[militant percussive music]
[men singing in Russian]
[gunfire]
[plane engine screeching]
- [speaking indistinctly]
[chuckles]
For you.
[camera reel whirring]
- Very good, Seryosha.
Very good.
Very strong.
Ivan.
Ivan, don't--
Very good.
Look where you go.
Don't trip up.
Vanya, yes, very good.
Very good.
No, too much.
Too much, Vanya.
Sacha!
Hurry up there!
I need to use the other camera.
[clanking]
How many times must I tell you,
eh?
Be careful with it!
Give me.
Turn it on.
- There is the sniper's nest.
It's crucial
that we destroy this nest.
It's a potential death trap
for our advancing troops.
Vassili, Alexei,
you flank it
from the right and left.
Ivan and I
will divert attention.
Let's get as much gear off
as we can.
We need to be light.
Sacha, you stay here,
and you guard the gear, huh?
[shouting and gunfire]
- Take cover!
Kill him!
[shouting and gunfire]
Grenade!
- Whoa!
- Grenade!
[explosion]
[camera reel whirring]
[distant gunfire]
[wind whistling]
- Ah, shit!
God--
[grunts]
Fuck off, Dima.
- Um, can you go behind me?
I can't see a thing.
[distant howling]
Jesus Christ...
- Sir!
Over here!
- Keep the fucking noise down,
boy!
- What the fuck?
- Ooh...
- Fucking hooligan.
- I don't give a shit.
We're here to help
our comrades.
Let's go.
- Bear Cobra 3-1-9
calling Mother.
Do you read me?
Over.
Bear Cobra 3-1-9
calling Mother.
Do you read me?
Over.
[static crackling]
Dima, you think you got
some good shots today, huh?
- Can I ask you a few questions,
for the folks back home
in Russia?
You don't sound Russian.
Where are you from?
- Krakow, Poland.
I escaped east
when the Nazis invaded.
Here.
She is why I'm here.
- [whistling]
Seryosha, get over here.
- You think it's worth it?
- Maybe.
- [panting]
[dog barking]
[shouting and gunshots]
[dog yelps]
[people screaming]
[gunshot]
[woman screams]
[people screaming]
[woman screaming]
[muffled screaming]
- [muffled singing]
- Dima, it's only--
[men shouting]
- Moscow Jewboy!
Where are you?
[excited shouting]
You're a liberator!
[laughter]
- You Polish cunt!
You are going straight
to military tribunal!
Give me the camera!
If you don't get off
that fucking bicycle...
Sacha!
You drunken--
- [laughing]
[muffled whirring]
- [snores]
[indistinct radio chatter]
- This is Tiger Bear 3-0-3.
We are trapped.
Does anyone read me?
Over.
This is Tiger Bear 3-0-3.
We are trapped.
Does anyone read me?
Over.
- Misha?
- This is Tiger Bear 3-0-3.
- Misha,
I've got something.
- [coughing]
Hello?
Tiger Bear 3-0-3?
We read you.
Over.
- We are trapped.
We can't hold out much longer.
Our position
is 51-17-28 north
by 13-22-04 east.
Do you read me?
- Hello?
Tiger Bear 3-0-3.
What is your situation?
Over.
- We can't hold out much longer.
Our position
is 51-17-28 north by 13--
- They can't hear us.
- What one is it?
- Some mining village
in the middle of nowhere.
We're not far.
If we get a move on,
we could be there by noon.
- Don't you think it's strange?
Who is Tiger Bear?
I thought we were
the only reconnaissance.
- They're Russians--
our boys--
and they need help.
What more do you need to know?
You better inform Mother.
- I wish I could.
That crazy message
is the only thing I've received
for two days.
- Dima, pack your stuff away.
We won't wait for you.
- Eh?
Here's one, shot already, eh?
Fucking fritzie.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Let me...
Ugh...
[sighs]
[explosion]
- [gurgling]
- Shit!
Shit.
Damn you!
- What's going on?
- Nothing.
Nothing.
Nothing is going on.
- Do me a favor
and stay with the squad.
[camera reel whirring]
- Is that it?
- There's a lot of damage.
There's been fighting here.
Do you see anything?
- Nothing.
No Russians.
No Germans.
Not even a stinking goat.
- All right.
We're going through the trees
very slowly, huh?
And you stay at the back
and keep out of the fucking way.
- Dima!
Come on.
Get down, you idiot!
- I don't get it.
That's artillery damage,
not aircraft.
We don't have artillery
within 50 kilometers of here.
Who did this?
- Let's move down to the church
and take it from there.
Move.
[crow cawing]
- I don't care who did this.
They're bastards,
whoever they are.
- Oh, God.
They are nuns.
- [gasping]
- Oh, God.
One is still alive.
Who did this, huh?
Who did this to you?
It's the Nazis, right?
Say it's the Nazis.
Say it!
- For God's sake, Dima.
- Say it!
Say--say--say it.
- [moaning]
[squishing]
- Whoa!
[panting]
- Are you all right?
- I fell into a fucking grave,
but I'll be all right.
- Hey!
- What was that?
[camera reel whirring]
[door creaking]
[dramatic music]
- What kind of church is this?
- This is more like a factory.
- Fuck...
Sacha!
None of your stupid games here,
huh?
It could be dangerous!
- Sacha.
Sacha, go down there,
see if you can find
a light switch.
- Why?
- Because we need more light.
Go.
[glass shattering]
Sash...
Sash!
- What?
- See if you can get
the generator started.
- Why?
- Don't argue.
Just do it.
[electronic whirring]
[metal creaking]
One...
- [grunting]
Ugh.
[electronic whirring]
[electricity crackling]
- Hey, camera-with-legs,
come over here.
[electricity whirring]
[steam hissing]
Hey,
look at what we have found.
- What's going on?
Sacha, is that you?
[electricity humming]
- Misha...
- Don't you think this is--
- No, no, no, no.
Don't touch it!
[electricity zapping]
- Uh!
[crunching]
- [panting]
[electricity cracking]
[breathing heavily]
[electricity zapping]
- What the...
- [gasping]
- Vassili, don't--
- Don't touch it, Vassili!
[indistinct radio chatter]
- Can you hear me?
I think it's blind.
I don't think it can see us,
huh?
[cracking and gurgling]
What are you?
Can you hear me?
- [breathing heavily]
- Let's put you
out of your miser--
[saw buzzing]
- Misha!
- Novikov!
- Get it!
[shouting indistinctly]
- Vassili!
Vassili, get it!
[saw buzzing]
Get it out!
- Get it off!
Get it off me!
- [growling]
- Kill it!
Kill it!
Get it off him!
Get it off!
[gunfire]
- [groaning]
- Oh, my God, Misha.
Just relax.
Just stay still.
Here, here.
Okay, I'm not going anywhere.
I'm not going anywhere.
- [groans]
- Don't move.
Don't move.
Sacha, for God's sakes,
turn that thing off!
- [gasping]
Ugh!
- Calling Mother.
Do you read me?
Over.
[sighs]
We're being jammed.
It's the only explanation.
It's been days
since I got a scratch
out of the damn thing.
- What if we used the tower?
- That's not a bad idea.
Not a bad idea.
- Vasja.
Vasja.
We are here now.
You heard that Mayday.
Our boys need help.
- Where the fuck are they,
then, eh?
- Listen, we need to search
the village properly.
Otherwise,
Novikov has died for nothing.
- [sighs]
He's right, Vasja.
Take the others.
I'll stay here with Sacha
and their gear.
Go to the village,
find someone, anyone,
who can tell us
what is going on here.
- Correct me if I'm wrong,
Seryosha,
but I'm next in command
after Novikov.
- I don't think so.
Look at the stripes.
- Who gives a fuck
about stripes?
I have been with this unit
longer than anyone.
- That doesn't mean
you're in charge, Vasja!
- Oh, no?
[chuckles]
Well, let's ask the others.
- Vasja, Sergei is right.
- Shut the fuck up,
you Jewboy!
You're here
just to make pretty pictures.
- Vasja, you're too smart
to be in charge.
Let Seryosha have his fun.
We can always slit his throat
later.
- Alexei?
Sacha?
You want him
to be in command?
The fucking radio hand?
He's not even Russian.
Okay, have it your way.
But don't come crying to me
when he leads us
into some fritzie trap.
Stop fucking filming!
- Comrade,
control your temper.
- Make another sound,
I fucking shoot your balls off!
- Alexei,
where are you going?
[muffled whimpering]
- Dima,
be safer outside.
Do not get in my way.
[muffled whimpering]
- We might have found
some dinner.
Mmm.
Come here, little bunny.
Come over here.
Ah! Ah!
[dogs whimpering]
- Guys, look!
There is someone here!
[gunshot]
- No, Alexei, no!
[dogs barking]
Alexei!
Alexei.
We're supposed
to get a prisoner, remember,
to interrogate,
find out where our boys are,
yeah?
- Sie sind--
Sie sind meine Hasen.
- What's the crazy old tramp
saying, eh?
- Something about
stealing his rabbits.
- Oh, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
I'm liberating your rabbits
from fascist oppression.
What is this place?
- I don't understand.
- What is this?
- Vasja, if you let me,
I--I have experience
in this sort of...
interviews.
- Interviews, yeah?
This, I want to see.
- What is going on here, huh?
Where has everybody gone?
- Everybody's dead or run away.
- What were they running from?
- That's a weird camera.
Ls that a microphone?
Are you recording sound?
I've never seen a camera
like this before.
- [sighs]
What were they running from?
- I-I-I...
From...
From things...
- What things?
- The doctor makes.
Where is the doctor now?
- Shut it!
Who gives a fuck
about this doctor?
We want to know
about Tiger Bear 3-0-3.
Ivan, hold him.
- Comrade, listen.
There was obviously some sort
of secret project going on.
- Oh, that's obvious, is it?
- Tiger Bear
must have been sent here
for that very reason.
Vasja, if you find the doctor,
we'll probably find--
- That's fucking fascinating,
comrade.
Now get the fuck
behind the camera.
We have wasted enough time.
Where are the Russians?
- Ah!
- Where?
- I don't know!
[screaming]
I just feed the animals.
- Where--
- Ah!
I'll--
I'll take you there.
- Oh, if you take me there,
you will never have to worry
about getting hurt ever again.
Come on.
Let's go.
- [grunting]
- Keep moving!
- Vasja,
do you think this is wise?
- Shut up.
- What if there are more
like the ones in the church, eh?
- Here.
Ah.
It's down there.
- The Russian soldiers
are down there?
- Yes.
- Down there?
- Yeah.
You--you go.
You'll see.
- It's not safe here, Vasja.
Let us take him back
to Seryosha.
- I'm in charge here,
so fucking do what I tell you.
Show us.
- No, no, I wouldn't--
- No, you fucking show us!
Come on.
- Ah! Ah!
- Vassili,
keep an eye on him.
How far is it?
Ah, this way?
You go fir--
Fuck.
Where has he gone?
I told you,
keep an eye on him!
- Where the hell...
[distant rumbling]
- Now you go ahead.
[distant banging]
- Ivan, check that side.
Alexei,
over there.
Where the hell is he?
[electricity humming]
[shuffling]
What?
- What?
- Shit.
What the...
- [snarling]
- Get out of the way!
[gunshot]
[metallic clanging]
- [roaring]
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
[gunfire]
- Don't shoot!
You're gonna shoot me,
you idiot!
- Get out!
Get out!
- Go, go, go, go, go!
Shoot it!
Shoot!
- Help!
Help!
Alexei!
Fucking help!
- Let's get out of here, now!
Get out of here!
- Which way?
Go, go, go, go!
- [roaring]
- [shouting indistinctly]
Ahh!
- [wailing]
- Agh!
- [screeches]
- Shoot it!
Kill it!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Get the hell out of here now!
- [roars]
- One more!
One more!
- Get out!
[gunfire]
- [screeching]
- Okay, let's get out of here!
[air raid siren wailing]
- Over here.
This way!
This direction!
Here!
- Oh!
There's one more!
There's one more there!
Go, go, go, go!
Out! Out!
[saw buzzing, gunfire]
- Watch it!
There's more, more, more!
- Guys, where are you?
Close the door!
- Over here.
- Close the door!
- Ah!
- Oh, no!
- [screaming]
- Shoot this motherfucker!
[gunfire]
Kill it!
Shoot it!
[gunshot]
- [shouting]
- Shoot it!
God!
[gunshots]
- [screeching]
[gunshot]
- Right now, get away!
Get away!
- [growling]
- Run!
Run, run, run!
[explosion]
[coughing]
- [shouting]
[air raid siren wailing]
Get it out.
- No.
No, I don't think
that's a good idea.
- Please...
- Don't fret, my friend.
I'm not giving up on you yet.
- Leave him.
He's finished.
We're getting out of here.
- Get back to your post!
You're supposed
to be keeping watch.
- Fuck you!
Those things,
they appear out of nowhere.
They could be all around us,
and we wouldn't even know.
Fuck out of the way.
I'll finish him off.
- Ugh!
- Ah!
Oh...
Fuck.
- [panting]
- Vasja!
- I'll fucking decide
when I'm finished
and who finishes me off.
Where's that freak?
- Who?
Dima?
- [laughing]
No, you idiot.
That tramp...
set us up...
Trap!
"I just feed the animals."
[laughs]
[shallow gasping]
- This is your fault.
You were supposed to bring
a captive back here.
[nose blowing]
- Sacha.
All quiet here?
- You're an educated man,
Dima.
What do you think
is going on here?
- I am...
not sure.
I think we have stumbled upon
a new Nazi weapon.
- [exhales]
Only the Nazis would think
of something like this...
Sewing dead people together
and giving them knives
for hands.
It's insane.
- Or brilliant.
- [sighs]
No, Dima.
It's insane.
[water dripping]
We'll move in the morning,
and then we'll find
this Tiger Bear 3-0-3.
- They're dead,
and we will be too
if we hang around here
any longer.
[gunshots]
- Sacha, go down!
Sacha!
[shouts echoing]
- Go around!
Sacha!
- Hands up!
Hands in the air!
Come on!
Hold your fire!
- [gurgling]
- Hold your fire!
- No, no!
- Against the wall!
Over there!
- [grunts]
- No, that is a girl!
That's a girl!
- No, no, no, no!
- Get over here!
- Vasja!
- No, no, no, no!
- [whimpering]
- Enough!
Enough!
Where are the Russians?
- Please...
- Where are the Russians?
- You are Russians, no?
- There where other Russians
here.
Yesterday!
- I--I don't know.
We've been hiding.
- Just the four of you?
- Everyone else was killed
or ran.
It was a massacre.
- Who killed them?
- The undead ones.
Listen, the gunshots
and your firelight...
We must hide
before they come looking.
- Where do they come from?
- Dima, leave this to me!
How many were there?
- We don't know.
He keeps making more.
We must hide now.
Please.
- This is bullshit.
Let's just kill them.
- No--
Du darfst mich schiessen!
- Nein, nein!
Bitte, bitte!
Du darfst mich erschiessen
statt ihr.
- What did he say?
- [whimpering]
Fritz says it's okay
if you shoot him.
He'd rather be shot
by a real man
than ripped apart
by those things out there.
- Let's just kill them.
Keep the girl.
Come here.
- No, no, no, no.
I am a trained nurse, ja?
Look!
I can help your friend.
- A trained nurse?
- I can help your friend.
[panting]
I will help your comrade, ja?
- Here.
Just breathe.
Vanya, breathe.
Well, can you get it off?
- I don't know.
- You get it off,
and we'll let you live.
Deal?
- I...
I can try.
- You heard him, bitch.
Get on with it.
- Okay, Vanya,
what we'll do--
- [coughing]
- Breathe.
- [gurgles]
- Slowly!
Slowly!
Breathe!
- [gasping, coughing]
- Ivan...
- [gurgling]
- Ivan, look at the nurse.
- [grunting]
- Don't move.
- [gurgling]
[crunching]
- [gasping]
I'm sorry.
- Well,
that was fucking useless.
- No, no!
We must work together.
We're all human.
Please don't hurt me.
Please!
No, no!
[grunting]
- Vasja!
- No! No!
- Ah!
- Enough!
[banging and screaming]
- Alexei!
[drill buzzing]
- Shoot that thing, somebody!
- Shoot it, Sacha!
Shoot it!
[gunfire]
Alexei, hold on!
[men shouting]
[gunfire]
- Shoot it!
[bullets clanging]
Shoot it!
Someone stop it!
Stop it!
Sacha!
Sacha, follow me!
- Dima, careful!
Where is it?
- [panting]
- [roaring]
- Shoot!
[gunfire]
- Shit!
- [roaring]
- [screaming]
Sacha!
Sergei!
- [roaring]
- I'll get the camera!
I got it.
I got the camera.
Dima, I got the camera!
- Ahh!
- Grenade!
Get down!
[explosion]
- [roaring]
[gunfire]
- Dima!
Dima!
[explosion]
[crashing]
- Are you all right?
- [roaring]
- My eyes...
- Sacha.
Sacha, give me the camera.
- Take it.
- Here!
Down the hole!
Quickly!
[bullets clanging]
- Eva!
Eva!
- No, no, this way.
- This way, Dima!
Sacha!
Dima!
- [roaring]
- Come on, Vasja!
Grenade!
- Hey!
[explosion]
[camera whirring falters
and stops]
[radio static crackling]
- Does anyone read me?
Over.
We are trapped.
We can't hold out much longer.
Our position
is 51-17-28 north
by 13-22-04 east.
Do you read me?
Over.
- I don't fucking believe this.
- Sergei.
Comrade.
Let me explain--
[grunting]
- What's going on?
- Why don't you ask
Comrade Dima?
- What?
- Tell them...
before I blow
your fucking brains out.
- You don't understand.
- Tell them!
- There's no Tiger Bear 3-0-3.
- I don't get it.
- Here.
It's a radio-jammer.
I couldn't understand
why we were getting
no signal before.
This is why.
Our comrade here
was blocking us,
cutting us off from Mother.
- And I was carrying
the fucking thing!
- He could use it
to transmit the message
from his pack to the radio
and...
- And lead us here.
So there is no...
- No Tiger Bear,
no Russian soldiers
needing our help.
- Fucking bastard!
- Oof!
Ah!
- Wait, Vasja.
Don't kill him yet.
First I want to know why.
- We are not going anywhere.
[coughing]
Not going anywhere.
- That fritz must know the way.
We'll follow him.
- That fucking old fascist?
- You don't understand.
[chuckles]
We are not leaving.
That's an order.
- An order?
I'm going to cut his balls off--
- Here, here, here, here.
- Oof!
- Read this document.
I'm a full captain,
your superior officer.
I have a list
of every man in this squad's
family and loved ones.
If something happens to me...
- What?
- You know what will happen
to them.
- [breathing heavily]
- Right.
- Dima...
Tell me...
Why didn't you just tell us?
Huh?
Why the trick?
- This is a top secret mission.
The bureau was afraid
there might be a leak.
- So you let us come unprepared?
- No, I did not know
the exact nature
of the work
that the doctor was working on.
- He's not a doctor.
He's a madman.
- My orders are to capture him,
if possible.
If not, kill him.
- Capture?
What does
the glorious motherland...
- Listen!
- Want with that madman?
- Listen to me!
This is none of your business.
You do your job;
you go home safe and sound.
Do you understand?
- Is there even film
in that camera?
- Yes, yes.
The film is real.
I need a record of everything
just in case
we cannot take him alive.
Now, Fritz,
we are going
to the doctor's base,
and you--
you're taking us there.
Which way?
- [coughing]
- This is the lift
up to the church.
- If these things
are a Nazi weapon,
they've turned on their master.
Not so brilliant, huh, Dima?
- Ah, fuck.
- [heaving and gagging]
- Fritz,
you used to work here,
right?
Where is the doctor?
- Hey!
Which way?
- Den Gleisen.
[coughs]
Folgen.
- Dima,
you can't be serious.
You want to go to the base
of this thing?
It's suicide.
- I thought I made it clear.
Our job is to find and capture
the doctor.
- Or kill.
Captured or killed, you said.
- Yes, yes, yes.
Moscow wants him alive.
- They're here!
- Go!
Get out, Dima!
[gunfire]
Run, Dima!
For God's sakes!
- [roaring]
- Get in!
Close the door!
- [screeching]
[men yelling]
- Gun!
- Get the fucking gun!
- Go!
- Come on!
[gunfire, bullets clanging]
Run faster!
- Get in.
- Close the door!
- [roaring]
- Come on, let's go!
Forget the gun!
Get inside!
[all shouting]
[banging]
- Lock it in,
you fucking idiot!
- What the fuck?
- No, leave it!
It can't hurt us.
- [grumbling]
- This one can't hurt us.
At last,
we're getting somewhere.
- [chittering]
- Nein! Nein!
- Little fascist...
[metallic clanging]
[gunshot]
[camera reel whirring]
[distant roaring, saw buzzing]
- Sacha, go down there
and take a look.
- What?
You crazy?
- I've got a better idea.
Vasja, get the boy.
- Right.
In you go.
- Nein!
- "Nein!
Nein!"
Come on.
- Wait!
First we'll take you down,
then we'll bring you back.
- In you go.
- Nein! Nein!
[struggling]
- I've got you!
- Hans, tell me what you see!
- [screaming]
- Pull!
Pull!
[shouting]
[metallic grinding]
- Pull him up.
- [groans]
- Ugh!
- [growling]
[men yelling]
[gunfire]
[rotors whirring]
- Shoot it!
Just do something!
God damn it!
- Sacha, the wire!
Try and cut the wire!
Get back!
[gunshots]
Cut the fucking wire!
The wire!
[engine rumbling]
Cut it, Sacha!
[engine dying]
[flames whooshing]
- Down!
- Get down!
[explosion]
[high-pitched buzzing]
- [coughing]
- You all right, Captain?
[laughing]
Thanks, Seryosha.
- Okay, let us go down there.
We can fix a rope.
I told you,
the doctor's lab is down there.
- Of course, Dima.
After you!
[thumping]
- Ahh...
- So, Dima,
you want to continue
your secret mission?
You do it alone.
I'm taking my men
out of this mad hole.
- Bye-bye, Jewboy.
Oh, sorry, I mean,
Captain Jewboy.
- [grunting]
- Don't forget
your precious film.
- Traitors.
Fucking traitors.
All of them.
Comrades!
Come back!
I order you, come back!
[flies buzzing]
Screw you,
Czarevitch Stalin.
Screw you, party slaves!
Soul of the proletariat,
my ass.
You will all be shot anyway!
You'll all be shot anyway!
[panting]
Fucking retard.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Oh, God...
I'm going to hell.
[rumbling]
- [growling]
- I am in hell.
[grumbling]
[screeching]
[mechanical whirring]
- [growling]
[alarm blaring]
[distant rumbling]
- [breathing heavily]
[high-pitched buzzing]
Mama, Papa,
this is my last roll of film.
Do not trust what they tell you.
I made a deal
with the government.
They promised to let you go
in exchange for the doctor.
[breathing heavily]
I don't think
that's happening anymore.
I'm sorry.
I love you,
and I'm gonna miss you.
- [roaring]
- [gasping]
Oh, fuck.
[rubber squeaking]
[horn music playing]
[exhales]
- [pained moaning]
[alarm blaring]
- [coughing]
[woman moaning]
[alarm blaring]
- Oh, God...
- [coughing]
[chuckles]
[mumbling indistinctly]
[gasping laughter]
[mumbling]
[coughing]
Nein. Nein.
Bleibt hier.
[wheezing]
Du musst mich toten.
Ich bin schon.
Ich bitte dich.
Du bist Arsch.
[shouting in German]
[crying]
Wirklich!
Ich bitte dich!
Nein!
Nein, nein, nein!
Ich bitte dich!
Nein.
Ich bitte dich.
Nein!
[shouting in German]
Ahh!
Nein!
Ich bitte dich!
[crying]
Ich bitte dich.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Okay...
[breathing heavily]
- [growling]
- [roaring]
- [screeching]
- [chittering]
[saw buzzing]
- Oh, God...
- [hissing]
[door squeaks open]
- Okay.
Okay.
[metallic banging]
- [roaring]
- Ivan...
Ivan, it's me, Dimitri.
Ivan.
Whoa!
Hey!
Ivan! Ivan!
What--
[crunching]
[cracking]
[high-pitched buzzing]
- Okay,
give us something good.
[dogs barking,
chickens clucking]
No, no, not my finger.
Not my finger.
[dog whining]
[Ride of the Valkyries playing]
[camera reel whirring]
Is it filming?
Yeah?
Good.
Here.
It's good.
Eat this.
It will make you strong.
It's Eintopf.
- I'm not hungry.
- Eat.
[glass shattering]
- [sputtering]
- I need you to be strong.
- [gagging]
- Do you like it?
It's really good.
I have added some
of my own ingredients in it.
- [coughing, gagging]
- I need you to be strong
to make a record
of my work here.
- Your work?
- For posterity, you know?
- [sputtering]
You're Dr. Frankenstein?
- Do you think you can do this?
Do you think you can do this
for me?
- [gagging]
- Swallow.
Swallow.
Swallow!
- [coughing, gagging]
[camera whirring]
- Are you filming?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Come in.
Go, go, go, follow.
Come.
Oh, don't be shy.
My father said
man would be more efficient
if they have hammers
and screwdrivers
instead of fingers.
Here, use this.
When I tried to do it
with cats,
he told me
it was a sin against God.
He--he beat me.
It's not a sin.
It's simple mechanics,
engineering.
[sniffs]
Ugh!
Well...
After Father died,
the Nazis closed the factory
and sent me to a camp.
Someone told the Sturmbannfhrer
about my cats.
He asked me
if I could do the same
with people.
So I used Grandfather's notes.
His techniques were quite crude.
He needed thunderstorms,
but now I can do it
with a generator!
- That's fascinating, Viktor.
Can you explain
how your automatons
receive and follow orders and--
- What did you say?
They are not machines
or puppets...
- Sorry, sorry.
I-I-I--
- Like the toys
my father built!
Each one is still alive.
- I see.
- They even need to eat.
Go, hurry up.
I feed them
with the same Eintopf
I gave you.
- Yes.
- Ah, fuck you!
Fuck you!
- Here they are.
- [laughs]
- At least one is still alive.
- Fuck you!
Fuck you!
- Don't do this to me.
- Fuck you all.
- Fuck you!
- [spits]
[spits]
Fuck you.
Son of a...
- God...
- He'll be fine.
I'll take care of him.
Come, come, come.
- [grumbling]
- Incredible.
- Come!
I want to show you something.
Come in!
- Yes, yes.
I'm coming.
- Come here.
I want to show you something.
This is the generator.
- I see.
- Look.
[electricity surging]
- It works.
[laughs]
it works!
- Genius.
This is genius!
- Come with me.
Come.
I'll show you something else.
- Doctor...
- What?
- Listen.
[distant explosion]
Listen!
Can't you hear it?
- What was that?
- It's us,
the Red Army,
our artillery.
- How far away
would you say they are?
- 15 kilometers?
They could be here
in a matter of hours.
- You're telling me this
because...
- I am here
to offer you a deal.
Our military leadership
is very interested in your work.
- Of course.
I'll give you my weapon
to use against Western Allies
to turn the whole world
into a socialist utopia, right?
- Yes, I think we understand
each other very well.
- And if I refuse?
- We'll bomb you and your army
back to the Stone Age.
- [mumbling and laughing]
Very nice.
How fucking cozy.
- [muffled mumbling]
- In experiments,
the fresher the specimens,
the better.
[indistinct radio chatter]
And if I can use flesh
that is still alive,
I can perform miracles.
- Still alive?
- Tell me,
which of these two
is a better Communist?
- Wha--what?
- Which of these two
is a better Communist?
- This one
is a better Communist.
Don't!
No!
I--
- [gasping]
- Hans!
[indistinct radio chatter]
Ready?
- Yes.
- So, Sturmbannfhrer,
we meet again.
- Viktor, bitte.
Es tut mir leid dass
wir versucht haben lhr
aufzuhalten.
- Hush now, Dieter.
You don't have to apologize.
I'm going to make it all okay.
- Doctor, there's no time.
The Red Army is almost here.
If you want to work for me,
you need to tell me now.
- Enough!
I said I would think about it.
Now focus.
- Nein.
[saw buzzing]
[muffled]
Viktor.
Nein. Nein.
[muffled screaming]
[saw buzzing, grinding]
- Dima...
[panting]
- Hey.
Hey.
I told you to film.
- Sorry.
- [humming]
- What are you doing?
- Don't you see?
I can--
I can end the war
by creating a new being
that brings them together.
- Are you serious?
- I can make them stop.
I can make them understand
each other.
I'll be right back.
- Dima...
Help me.
Help me...
Help me, please.
Please...
- I can't, Seryosha.
I have to bring him back
no matter what.
- Dima...
[groans]
Don't you understand?
He's crazy.
Dima, he's insane.
- I told you--
I told you, I can't.
I promise you this, Seryosha,
when I return to Moscow,
I will personally ensure
you're awarded
the Hero of the Soviet Union
medal.
- [shouts]
- Your sacrifice
will not be forgotten.
- Dima!
I swear, I'll kill you.
I swear, I'll kill you!
[panting]
- [humming]
[saw buzzing]
[grinding]
- [screaming]
[crashing]
[screaming]
Dima!
- As you can see,
the two halves of the brain
have been grafted together.
On the left side,
the Communist's.
Hold on.
Yeah...
On the right side,
the Nazi's.
Yeah.
That will be...
That's too much here.
Okay.
I think--
Oh, shit.
Shit, come on.
Okay, that's fine.
Let me fix that.
The patient
is no longer breathing.
Now...
For the final step.
Drei!
Zwei!
Eins!
Jetzt!
[electricity surging
and zapping]
- [gurgling, screeching]
- It's obviously suffering
from a little
readjustment problem!
I can build more!
- Ahh!
- What are you doing?
What are you doing?
- How does that work?
I need a different lens.
How do you operate this camera?
- Doctor, we had a deal.
Listen,
we had a deal, eh?
You will be safe in Russia.
- What deal?
- I have--
I have people there.
Orders...
Enemies of the state, eh?
You will be safe.
What about our deal?
- I am afraid
I am going to have to refuse
your generous offer.
- You are signing
your own death warrant.
If we don't kill you,
your own people will.
You understand that?
- Oh, yes, I know.
I was in a prison camp,
remember?
But I have other plans.
- No, no, no!
Don't--don't leave me!
Don't go!
Ah!
- I'll be leaving momentarily.
But there should be time
for one last experiment.
- No, you can't.
You can't.
- I can.
I can.
Come here.
Now, what shall we do
with you?
Maybe...
Maybe I will build this camera
into your skull.
That might be fun.
[grunting]
- You fool.
- A man--a man of vision
is always misunderstood.
But the film in your camera
will convince the doubters.
- You're insane!
You're not a doctor!
You're sick!
- Oh, yes.
- You hear me?
You're sick!
- Oh, yes, I'm sick.
Everybody's sick!
The Nazis.
Communists.
Capitalists.
Everyone!
The sickness
cannot be cured,
so it must be cut out,
and my creations will do that.
- Your creations
are fucking insanity!
Look at them.
They're fucking cripples!
- Okay.
My father...
Tried to have me locked up.
He said
I was emotionally crippled.
- [sobbing hysterically]
- I had no choice.
I injected him with a drug
that paralyzed him,
but his eyes could still move,
so he could watch as I--
- No, no, no!
No, no, no!
[explosion]
- What was that?
- That is the beginning
of the carpet bombardment--
- I will not have time for you
after all!
- [laughing]
That is--
that is my comrades
coming to wipe you
off the face of this planet!
[explosion]
The deal,
the deal I offered,
I will make it better.
Anything! Anything!
Tell me what you need.
I'll guarantee it!
- Okay, okay, okay.
I am afraid after I go,
my soldiers
may become a bit crazy.
[metallic ringing]
- What--what are you
talking about?
- They obey only me,
and I cannot take them
with me,
so after I go,
they will turn out
against each other
and anything else
they find nearby.
- [panting]
- I would love to tell you more,
but I have got--
I've got to go.
So good luck, comrade.
[groans]
The film...
Proof for the doubters
to make them believe.
- Gah!
- But it won't reveal
my real secrets.
Do you know why?
Look at me.
Because they are all locked up
in here.
So I'm going to take your camera
with me.
[gunshot]
Ugh...
- No!
Sacha!
You fucking idiot!
Idiot!
Well, don't just stand there!
Let me loose, you fuck!
- [screaming]
- Sacha.
Sacha.
[stammering]
Sacha!
Sacha, no, no, no, no.
Sacha, come on.
Sacha!
Sacha, no, don't leave me!
Please, please, please, please!
Sacha!
[struggling]
Don't leave me.
[explosion]
Sacha!
- [roaring]
- Sacha.
- Sacha, thank God.
Sacha, thank you.
Sacha, listen!
I was only trying to help
my mother!
- No, I cannot.
I'm sorry.
I promised to bring them
this camera, Dima.
- [roars]
- I will make sure
that you get
the Hero of the Soviet Union
medal.
- Don't just stand there!
Please!
- [roaring]
- Help!
Help me!
Sacha, do something!
- [screeches]
- No!
- [bellowing]
- Ahh!
[militant percussive music]
[men singing in Russian]