Created and Encoded by --  Bokutox -- of  www.YIFY-TORRENTS.com. The Best 720p/1080p/3d movies with the lowest file size on the internet. Come and say hi to me; World of Warcraft - Outland PVP (EU) - Bokutox (name)
from the very beginning...
it was the children
who gave me my power.
The Springwood Slasher...
that's what they called me.
My reign of terror
was legendary.
Dozens of children
would fall by my blades.
Then the parents of Springwood
came for me...
taking justice
into their own hands.
When I was alive, I might
have been a little naughty...
but after they killed me,
I became something much,
much worse--
the stuff nightmares
are made of.
The children
still feared me...
and their fear gave me the power
to invade their dreams.
And that's when the fun
really began!
Until they figured out
a way to forget about me...
to erase me completely!
Being dead wasn't a problem.
But being forgotten--
now, that's a bitch!
It's only a dream!
Die, motherfucker!
I can't come back
if nobody remembers me!
if nobody's afraid!
I had to search the bowels of hell...
but I found someone...
someone who'll make 'em remember.
He may get the blood,
but I'll get the glory.
And that fear is my ticket home.
Mike?
Is that you?
All right, fuck you, then.
I'm heading in.
Mike?
Come on, it's not funny anymore.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
No!
Jason.
I should've been watching
them, not drinking...
not meeting a boy
at the lake.
I deserve to be punished.
We all deserved
to be punished.
Jason.
My special, special boy.
Do you know what
your gift is?
No matter what they do to you...
you cannot die.
You can never die.
You've just been
sleeping, honey.
But now the time
has come to wake up.
Mommy has something
she wants you to do.
I need you to go
to Elm Street.
The children have been
very bad on Elm Street.
Rise up, Jason!
Your work isn't finished!
Hear my voice and live again!
Make them remember me, Jason.
Make them remember
what fear tastes like.
I've been away from my children
for far too long.
Marry, fuck, or kill?
Your choices are--
your choices
are the Three Stooges.
Go, Kia.
Oh, God...
Which one had
the super-bad toupee hair?
Harry, Mar--
No! No, no, no.
It was Moe.
Either one, I'd kill him.
OK, who'd you fuck, then?
This is stupid, y'all.
Come on. Come on.
Oh, God. Whatever, look.
I'd fuck the bald guy,
and I'd marry Larry.
Jesus. Is this what
we're doing all night?
'Cause, y'all,
this is really stank.
Hey! Gibb, what are you doing?
I thought you were gonna quit.
I only smoke when I drink now.
But you're always drinking.
Yeah, well, I'll work
on that next.
Hey, OK.
I got another one.
Fred, Scooby, or Shaggy?
Oh! I'm not answering that
and neither is she.
Do you guys think
I should get a nose job?
Oh, my God.
Oh, please, Kia, what you need
is a lobotomy.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I think I'm gonna
get some candles.
I'm gonna get some beer.
Do you guys want anything?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Are you sure you
should be driving?
I'm so under the limit, Lori.
Surprise.
Oh, Trey.
You answered my prayers.
Thank you.
Whoa, babe!
What'd I tell you
about kissing me...
after you've smoked, huh?
Lighten up.
They're menthols.
Yeah. I brought Blake.
Where's Linda?
It's Lori.
This is her house,
so don't be a total cocksmith.
Whatever.
Where are the ladies?
Relax, they'll be here.
I'm relaxed, man.
I'm just wet.
Did you know they
were coming over?
Listen, you gotta be quiet.
Hey, we knew you were be here
all alone this weekend.
Blake's cute.
He's not my type.
Oh! Who is? No one's
ever gonna live up...
to the fuzzy memory
of your first love, Lori.
You were fucking fourteen,
so get over it.
Yeah, I know
we were young...
but what Will and l
had was real.
Well, correct me if I'm wrong...
but didn't Mr. Real
just drop-kick your ass...
without so much
as a good-bye handshake?
He ever even call or maybe even
write to you after he moved?
Send you an e-mail?
No.
You see my point?
It's time to leave
the convent, Lori.
You need to meet a guy.
Hey, Lori...
I like the...
flow of your place.
Got good feng shui.
Yeah.
You know about feng shui?
Oh, oh!
Oh, you should see her bedroom!
-Hmm?
-Great flow in there.
Lori, why don't you go upstairs
and show Blake your feng shui?
Shut up!
I got a kink in my neck.
Come on.
You can massage it out for me.
I think I need
a few more drinks...
before there'll be
any massaging.
What do you see in him?
I don't know,
but he has a cute ass.
Babe, don't make me
ask you twice, OK?
So, Lori...
am I gonna get that
grand tour or what?
Yeah.
You know, why don't you
start in the kitchen...
and get us some beers?
Cool.
Oh, my God, Kia,
he is a total idiot.
Get him out of here.
Oh, Lori, come on,
give him a chance.
I don't like him.
You know what?
You don't like anybody.
I mean, Lori, you've
barely gone out since--
Since what?
Since my mom died?
Yeah, well, you know what?
My dad needs me.
So I can't just go out
with guys all the time...
and if I did, it would not be
with somebody like Blake.
Yeah, fuck me, baby!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Your back door was open.
I closed it.
Mmm.
Babe, you know I don't like
to be touched after, OK?
Fine. I'll go have
a shower then.
Good.
Your hair smells like
menthols, anyway.
Asshole.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Trey!
What the hell are you doing?
Help us! Help us!
Oh, my God!
Over here!
Please help us!
Help us!
You kids need
some assistance?
What the fuck
do you think?!
We need to lock this down now.
Keep it contained, you hear me?
Killed in bed.
Jesus.
It's even the same damn house.
1428 Elm.
It's gotta be him, right?
It's gotta be
Freddy Krueger.
Hey! Don't even say...
that son of a bitch's
name out loud.
Let's just keep it together.
We've been through too much
to let this thing spread now.
Take all the kids
down to the station.
Keep them separate.
Do it now.
Yes, sir.
We'll be in touch.
Thank you.
Let's go home.
So?
She doesn't know anything.
None of them do.
I'm pretty sure we're good.
Pretty sure?
You better make damn sure...
none of those kids
knows anything...
or I'll send your ass up
to Westin Hills with them.
Knows what?
What do you mean?
Good work there tonight, Stubbs.
Right place, right time.
But we'll take it
from here, all right?
Your father's on his way.
Do they know who did this?
No, not yet.
But I thought I heard...
one of the officers
mention a name.
You know, to tell
you the truth, Lori...
I--I just moved here
about a month ago...
but if they have a suspect,
I'd be the first to know.
But they asked me all these
really weird questions...
Iike about my dreams--
What was the name?
Freddy.
Hello?
Are you OK?
His name is Freddy Krueger...
and he loves children,
especially little girls.
Freddy's coming back.
Soon he'll be strong enough.
It's OK to be afraid.
We were all afraid.
Warn your friends.
Warn everyone.
One, two, Freddy's
coming for you
Three, four,
better lock the door
Five, six, grab a crucifix
Seven, eight,
try to stay up late
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Nine, ten, never sleep again
One, two, Freddy's
coming for you...
Blake, we have to talk.
What the hell were you
doing over there?
You were supposed to be
watching your sister.
Were you drinking?
My best friend was
just killed, Dad!
So how about giving me
some fucking space?
You watch yourself, boy.
I'm gonna get him for you, Trey.
Cop let it slip.
It was somebody named Freddy.
I'm gonna take him out
myself, Trey.
I swear to God.
Who is that?
Someone there?
Jesus.
I'm OK. I'm all right.
Not strong enough yet.
Well, I will be soon enough.
Until then...
I'll let Jason have some fun.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Dad?
Hypnocil.
What does this shit do, anyway?
How come we all
have to take it?
It keeps you nice and docile
while I kick your little ass.
I'm fine with that.
We interrupt this program
for a special report.
After tonight's murder...
in this neighborhood
of Springwood...
the Sheriff's Department
has confirmed...
that there is one victim...
Hey, turn that up, man.
Remain sketchy,
but the sheriff--
Sorry, Will.
You know the rules.
Turn that back on.
I know somebody
that lives in that house.
Come on, turn it back on, man!
I never ask for anything.
Just turn on
the fucking TV, please!
Fuck you, man!
What the fuck is your problem?
What are you doing, man?
You want 10ccs of that pink
tranquilizer in your ass?
That was Lori's house.
They said something
about a murder.
I gotta go to her.
I gotta see if she's OK.
Back to Springwood?
Do you want me to start
having nightmares again?
Don't start with that
dream demon shit again.
OK? You know that's all
just in your head.
Yeah, yeah, and who are you,
the poster boy for sanity?
You're the one
that told the cops...
Lori's dad killed his wife.
Yeah, right, and now it
looks like someone else...
got killed in the same house.
You think that's
a coincidence?
Two murders in one house?
Kurt, how many times
do I have to tell you, man?
I don't do checkers.
I'm an UNO guy, all right?
So go grab the fucking UNO deck
and we'll play, OK?
Please. Thank you.
Look at us, Will.
Look around you, man.
We're institutionalized.
We're stuck here.
We're not going anywhere.
I do miss my family, man.
I mean, it's been four years
since I've seen 'em, you know.
All these years,
and you're still convinced...
you saw her father do that?
I know what I saw, Mark.
Fuck what the doctors try
to get me to believe.
I need to know if she's OK.
You want to play?
Sweet dreams, monkey boy.
What the hell
was that for, man?
Heh heh heh!
You're a fucking lunatic,
you know that?
I know you are,
but what am l?
Are you sure
you didn't see anyone?
No, Dad, none of us did.
I already went over this
with the police.
It's just...
I don't know what
I'd do without you.
You're all I have left.
Dad, I'm not going anywhere.
I promise.
Look at you.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
You're exhausted.
Lori.
We need to get you to bed!
I don't want to
go to sleep, Dad.
I just want to see my friends.
I don't think it's a good idea
for you to go to school today.
You've just been through
a very traumatic experience.
Dad, please...
I just need to get
out of the house, OK?
I'll be fine.
I promise.
Well, at least drink your juice.
Will Rollins
and the Davis boy...
escaped from Westin Hills
last night.
Oh, Jesus.
It's all coming apart again.
Don't worry.
We'll find them.
Keep this thing contained.
Lori!
Oh, my God! God, you guys,
I'm so glad you're here.
Blake's dead, too.
What?
Yeah, he--
He was stabbed
to death late last night.
Same with his dad.
What?
Shit, shit!
This is bullshit!
The police are blaming
everything on Blake...
Iike its some kind
of Columbine thing or something.
They're saying he went crazy.
Killed Trey, killed his dad,
and then took his own life?
This is so fucking messed up.
This is messed up.
Excuse me. Sorry.
Lori?
What is it, Linderman?
Um, well, I heard
what happened,
and I just wanted to
express how, um...
well, to tell you
how sorry I was.
Thank you.
That's sweet.
Right. Actually if you need
anybody to talk to or maybe--
Whoa, Linderman,
let me give you a tip.
Place your hormones
back in the box...
and quit while
you're ahead, OK?
We don't have time
for Date-a-Dork right now.
Thanks.
Right. Sorry.
I swear, every day
it's the same thing.
He's like one of those
fucking froufrou dogs...
that keeps humping your leg.
Give a couple to some ladies.
Thanks, man.
I see what
you're saying, Gibb...
but that's exactly
why you should go.
I mean, be amongst friends,
where it's safe.
There's gonna be a whole lot
of loving there for you...
and my boy Trey, all right?
Yeah. Yeah, you're right.
I should go.
I could use a few dozen drinks.
That a girl.
Let your freak flag fly.
See you there.
You want to go?
No, I don't think so.
I--I didn't get much
sleep last night...
and when I did sleep...
I had the most
terrible nightmares.
Lori, you had to sleep
at a police station.
I'd have nightmares, too.
No, no, no,
it wasn't like that.
I mean, this was really real.
I mean, there was this man...
but he more like
a monster really...
and they kept
calling him Freddy...
-and he was so real.
-Shh!
What did he look like?
He--he had this...
dark brown hat, and...
his skin was
terribly burnt...
and on this right hand
he had this like these...
razor fingers, and--
You must be tripping.
No, no, no!
And then there were
these little girls...
It's OK.
It was a bad dream.
They were singing like
this--this song like--
One, two, Freddy's
coming for you.
You know why they sing that?
Because that's when
he comes for you...
in your dreams.
You're lucky to be alive.
Who is he?
He's a child murderer...
that some parents
from around here burned alive...
but then he came back.
Back for revenge
in our nightmares.
Funny no one ever
told us about him, huh?
-OK, thank you!
-No!
You want some free advice?
Coffee.
Make friends with it.
Mark!
That's enough.
You're scaring her.
Will?
Hey.
I thought you might
be in trouble, so we--
Lori! Oh, my God!
Lori, honey, wake up!
Someone get help, please!
Someone get some help, please!
The principal!
Will, let's go, let's go!
Please, somebody help her.
Lori?
How much longer
is it gonna take?
-ls she OK or what?
-Shh!
Tsk!
For nose jobs,
what kind of anesthesia...
do the doctors use?
They put you
all the way under, right?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Got your nose!
Strong work, man.
I came to make sure she's OK...
and you put her
in the infirmary.
What were you
thinking about...
telling her
all that stuff, man?
I mean, we're not in group.
Because I'm thinking
for the first time in my life...
that maybe I'm not crazy...
that my brother wasn't crazy.
She had the same dream, Will.
Will Rollins!
Mark Davis!
This doesn't make any sense.
There's nothing on Krueger.
Not his arrest, his death,
not even a birth certificate.
Whole sections of
the records are gone.
Look at all these
blacked-out obituaries.
January eighteenth.
That's the day my brother
committed suicide.
Why isn't that in here?
I don't know!
But I'm sure there's
a good reason.
Remember in group
when they told us...
not to jump to conclusions?
Listen to yourself.
You're holding onto
that psychobabble bullshit...
Iike it's some kind of
security blanket, man.
Let it go.
They've covered him up, Will.
They never told us
about Freddy...
because that's how they
decided to beat him.
They treated him like he
was a fucking disease...
and they locked up
all the kids...
who had made
contact with him...
so they wouldn't
infect the others.
That's crazy.
Is it?
How come we were
never allowed...
to call any of
our friends, man?
How come none of our
friends ever called us?
We were in a fucking
quarantine, man.
That's what
Westin Hills was for.
Well, even if all
you're saying is true...
then why didn't
Freddy kill Lori?
Maybe he's not
strong enough yet.
My brother said it's our fear
that gives him his power.
Yeah, well,
you sure as hell...
spread enough fear
today at school.
Holy shit.
You're right.
They wanted to forget Freddy so
they wouldn't fear him.
What if I screwed up
the town's plan?
Fuck! This fucker's gonna spread
like the plague, man!
Kids are gonna start
falling asleep, it's gonna--
Let's leave, man.
Let's leave right now.
No, I can't leave.
Why not?
I gotta go talk to Lori.
I gotta see if she's OK.
Well, is she worth dying for?
Because if you fall asleep,
you ain't waking up.
If that's the case,
how come you're not dead?
Or any of the freaks at Westin?
When's the last time
you even had a nightmare?
I don't know.
I can't remember
my dreams anymore.
Look, just give me
one night, OK?
Just let me find Lori,
and then we're out of here.
I swear.
All right.
If your ass isn't back here by
dawn, I'm gone.
We clear on that?
This baby's my brother's
pride and joy, so be careful.
Oh, shit.
Linderman!
Shack, I don't drink.
Hi, Lori. Didn't think
I'd see you here.
Can I get you
something to drink?
Smooth opening, but, you know,
we're already taken care of.
What happened
to your clothes?
Oh, this.
I was playing
a drinking game...
with some
of the lower primates...
and I guess I'm penalized
for my ability...
to read above
a fourth-grade level.
Linderman, you know,
I always pictured you...
as a straight up bedwetter.
You know what, Kia?
I used to think you hated me...
because you thought
I wasn't good enough for Lori...
but that's not it.
You tear me down
to make yourself feel better...
because you really
hate yourself...
which is kind of pathetic
when you actually...
stop and think about it,
assuming, of course...
you can think
with all that makeup...
weighing down your head.
The cops said Blake
committed suicide.
Apparently,
it was grief over Trey.
No, man, that's bullshit.
I heard some guy Krueger
killed them both.
Said his name to my parents,
they almost shit themselves.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, man,
and I heard...
that Freddy freak,
he used to live here.
Fucking gutted Trey like
a Goddamn turkey, man.
Like I heard his intestines and
shit was on the floor--
Oh, shit. I'm sorry.
Oh, my God.
Look who's here.
Look who's here!
What are you looking at?
Come on, come on, let's dance.
Come on, Linderman, let's go.
Where have you been, Will?
Didn't you get my letters?
What letters?
They must've never
even mailed them.
Who?
The...doctors at Westin Hills.
I've been in
a psychiatric hospital.
Mark was with me there.
Some other kids, too.
I don't understand.
Well, I saw on the news
the other night...
I mean, that kid that was
killed at your house.
I mean, I needed to know
that you were safe.
What happened?
I don't know.
Nobody knows.
Nobody saw what happened...
and the police have been
acting really weird...
Iike they know something...
and I heard them
mention some name.
Some...
Freddy. Freddy Krueger.
Where was your dad?
Out of town.
Are you sure?
What is going on, Will?
Well, look, four years ago,
I thought l--
Enough with
this bullshit talk.
Let's go shake our ass
on the dance floor.
Come on!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I'm dead one day...
and you're already out
getting shit-faced?
Same old Gibb!
Trey, l--
I can't believe it.
Come on, let's go.
Babe, don't make me
ask you twice, OK?
Now!
Trey?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
No!
Open the door!
Please, the door--
No! No!
You're the one
that killed Trey!
Oh, don't worry about
my little errand boy.
The only to fear
is fear himself!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
No!
She's mine.
Mine! Mine!
This everclear
is kicking my ass.
This--
Check out this fucking guy.
Well, hey, Jethro!
This is a rave,
not a Halloween party.
Why don't you go
find yourself a pig to fuck?
Yeah!
Invite only, cornpoke,
and you weren't invite--
Son of a bitch.
Yeah!
Burn, motherfucker!
No!
Run, man, run!
Freak!
You killed my brother!
Gibb! Oh, my God!
Oh, Gibb! No!
Let's go!
Let's go, come on!
Was that him?
The guy you were talking about--
Freddy Krueger.
No, that wasn't
the guy in my dream.
That was somebody else!
Who cares about some
fucking dream guy, OK?
That psycho
in the hockey mask was real.
Dude, that goalie was
pissed about something.
We need to find the police.
No, no! Fuck the police!
Just take me home, Will.
Gibb, l--
I can't believe she...
I know.
Look, call me later, OK?
Please.
Just to check in.
Bye, Will.
Be careful.
Will, I'm gonna go inside now.
I think that's the last thing
you should do right now.
Oh, Will, please.
After everything
that's happened...
I just want to go to--
There's more
to it than that.
Look, I tried to tell
you this earlier.
The reason
I was sent to Westin...
is because I saw
your dad kill your mom.
Will, my mom died
in a car accident.
No, that's what he
wanted you to believe...
but I was there, Lori.
I was sneaking up to your room,
like I used to do.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Only you weren't there.
I saw him kill her.
Dad!
Get out of the van.
Get out of the van!
Where were you?
What are you doing?
I've been looking
all over for you!
Get away from her!
You're in a helluva
lot of trouble, you know that?
Like I give
a shit anymore.
Get in the house!
You! I'm taking you
back to Westin.
No! No way!
You can't trust him, Lori.
Whatever you do,
don't go home with him!
No, listen to me!
He was the one
who had me committed!
You didn't understand.
You still don't.
You were confused!
Stop it!
Both of you, stop it!
Damn it, Will!
I am not gonna let you...
endanger my daughter again!
Not after everything
that's happened!
Stop it! Stop it! Fuck!
Lori!
I--l--
Did Mom die
in a car accident?
Yes. Of course she did.
Prove it.
Show me a death certificate.
Show me an autopsy report.
Lori, I don't think now
is the right time--
Really, Dad?
Because I think
it's a perfect time!
Why didn't you tell me
about Westin Hills?
Do you work there?
Because I thought you were
a fucking general practitioner!
Yes, l...
I do some consulting
there now, but...
it's--it isn't
what you think.
Oh, my God.
So you knew about Will
this whole time.
Lori, listen to me.
You're upset.
We both are.
Now I think what you need now...
more than anything
is to get some rest.
Why don't I give you
some pills...
and that'll help you sleep...
and then we talk
about it in the morning?
I don't want
to sleep, Dad!
I want to know why
you've been lying to me!
We'll talk about it
in the morning!
Now do what I say!
Lori! Lori!
Open this door.
Open this door!
Go away!
Damn it, Lori!
Let me in!
Goddamn it!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
It's OK, it's me.
It's me, shh! Shh!
You OK? Are you OK?
It's me, all right?
I don't know how your father's
connected to all this...
but I think
Mark was right.
There's some kind of cover-up
going on here with Krueger.
We can't trust the police.
We can't trust
any of the adults.
So what do we do?
We gotta get to Mark.
He's the expert in all of this.
He'll know what's going on.
You always looked out
for me, bro.
Hey, Mark.
I gotta stay awake.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Shit!
Hey, Mark.
You didn't forget
about me, did you?
Oh, God.
Oh, that's right!
Everyone forgot!
That's why they weren't
afraid anymore!
That's why I needed Jason
to kill for me...
to get them to remember.
But now he just won't stop,
that hockey puck!
This isn't...real.
Somebody, please, wake me up!
Please!
Mark! Mark, wake up!
I need you to send
a little message for me.
That's all,
just a little message.
I'm not gonna do it.
I won't do it!
No?!
I won't do it.
I'll have to pass that message
myself, won't l?
Oh, my God!
Let go of me!
Help...me.
Mark!
Pass on a little
message for me, will ya?
Sheriff,
I've been compiling info...
based on eyewitness reports
of the hockey mask killer.
We already know who did this.
Sheriff, we closed
down the school...
and set up a curfew
for anyone under eighteen.
Good.
Now I want twenty-four-hour
roadblocks set up.
Nobody leaves town,
nobody gets in.
We're gonna contain
this son of a bitch...
before he spreads any further.
Yes, sir.
Sir, shouldn't we have
the F.B.I. come in and--
No outsiders, Stubbs.
We can handle this.
We've stopped him before.
OK, I'm a little lost here.
Stopped who before?
We don't say his name out loud.
You're not from around here.
I don't expect you
to understand.
With all due resect, Sheriff...
I think we have a copycat
of the old Jason Voorhees...
Crystal Lake killer
on our hands--
You listen to me.
We do things around here
a certain way for a reason...
and that's given us
four years of peace.
So you either do your job
and keep your mouth shut...
or, so help me God,
I will lock you up!
Do you understand me?!
Yes, sir.
Why don't we all just leave?
No, even if we leave,
Freddy can still get us.
We all know about him.
We're all afraid of him.
It was our fear that
gave him his power.
We're marked now.
Man, screw that clown.
I mean, what kind
of a pussy...
comes after you
in your dreams anyway?
Now, that big-ass mother fucker
back at the cornfield...
all right, that's who
we should be afraid of.
Tell me who
the fuck that was.
His name was Jason Voorhees.
Shit, man...um...
How'd you know
we were here?
Nothing personal,
but the Scooby van out back...
wasn't exactly subtle.
And never keep
your keys in the door.
Great, so now we're
completely fucked.
No, you're not.
I'm here to help you.
Now, this Jason Voorhees
supposedly drowned...
at Camp Crystal Lake
back in 1957...
when he was
eleven years old.
The counselors weren't
watching him...
then they made the mistake
of killing his mother.
The legend has it...
that Jason kept returning
from his grave...
to punish whoever
returned to the camp.
I think we're dealing
with a copycat here.
No. No. No, no, no.
He's not a copycat.
I've seen what he can do.
He's the real Jason.
That's impossible, Linderman.
Jason is dead.
You'd better start thinking
outside your little box, dude...
'cause somebody's
definitely breaking...
the fucking reality rules, OK?
It makes sense in a way.
I mean, what if Freddy
brought Jason back...
because he was too weak
to go after us on his own...
so he used Jason.
I mean, he knew that
we'd think it was him...
that we'd spread
the fear again.
And now that it's working...
it's like he can't
shut Jason back down.
Wait a minute.
Freddy died by fire,
Jason by water.
How can we use that?
I think we should
concentrate on Jason first.
But I thought we decided...
that Freddy was the one
pulling the strings.
Shouldn't we go
after him first?
I don't know, maybe
what we need to do is...
to offer Freddy
a sacrifice.
Yeah, yeah, totally.
Like a virgin, right?
Someone pure.
Dude, don't look at me.
Even if you pay for it,
it still counts.
Oh, come on.
Look, we all know who
the real virgin is here.
-Kia!
-Oh, come on, Lori.
I know you never
made it with Will.
Why would he want to when
he can fuck somebody like me?
Let's tie the bitch up.
What?
Don't worry, angel.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
You've still got me.
Come on, give daddy a kiss.
Your eyes say no-no...
but my mouth says yes-yes.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Lori, are you all right?
You fell asleep.
Oh, shit!
I pulled that out of my dream.
How is that possible?
Anything is possible now!
God, you just don't get it!
Oh, God, y'all, two killers?
We're not safe awake or asleep.
It's not the sleep
that's killing us...
it's our dreams.
At Westin, Mark and l
never had dreams.
Were you on any drugs?
Yeah, but there's
something called hypnocil.
They never told us
what it was for...
but everyone there
was taking it.
Experimental drug...
not even approved yet
by the F.D.A.
Oh, shit.
Used for...
suppression of dreams.
We need those pills,
enough for all of us.
Can you get us
back to Westin Hills?
All right,
this isn't it, guys.
Come on, let's go.
Hey, dude.
Let's take a little
J-break, huh?
No, man. He's a cop.
Come on. What's he
gonna do, arrest me?
Hold up.
Hang on a second.
Fuck.
That's better.
Where's Freeburg?
Come on. Come on!
This is "D" wing.
These are the ones
who wouldn't stop dreaming.
Are they dead?
They're in a coma.
It says they were given
too much hypnocil.
Who would do this to people?
Your dad's name
is at the bottom...
of both of these charts.
Cool...yeah.
What the fuck?
Nice.
Oh, yeah.
Hold up, man.
What?
What do you want?
No, I don't know where
the hypnocil is, OK?
I can't pour these
down the drain.
We need this stuff.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Freeburg!
What are you doing?
We need those drugs!
Dude, no! Dude--
Go on! Get out of here!
Go!
What was that?
Let's go check it out.
Let's go.
Get back! Shit! Hell!
Fucker!
Help me!
Shit! They're all empty!
We gotta keep looking.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Maybe there's some down here.
Damn, it's gotta
be here somewhere.
Freeburg, come on!
Come on! Come on!
What are you waiting for?
Come on!
Freeburg, time to go.
We gotta go!
Now! come on!
Let me handle this, bitch.
What?
Come on, come on!
OK, let's go!
Let's go.
No, wait, wait!
Look.
Come to Freddy.
These are my children, Jason.
Go back where you belong!
Fuck you!
Linderman...
These are my children, Jason.
Go back where you belong.
Jason...Jason.
My special, special boy.
I'm disappointed
in you, Jason.
You disobeyed me.
You were supposed
to come back home...
just kill a few of them!
But I blame myself.
I should've known...
you wouldn't be able
to stop killing!
You are like a big, stupid dog
who can't stop eating...
even though your master
said you've had enough!
Now it's time to put
this bad dog to sleep...
for good!
Not my arm!
Welcome to my nightmare.
Penny for your thoughts, chief!
Oh, scary.
Tilt.
Why won't you die?
Come on. Come on!
So you are afraid of something
after all, huh?
How in the fuck did I let y'all
talk me into this?
Why don't we just
try and do it here?
Why go all the way
to Crystal Lake?
Best-case scenario: Jason wins.
He'll already be home,
back where he belongs.
I mean, why follow us anymore?
And if Freddy wins?
At least Jason
has home-field advantage.
Aww...how sweet.
You ugly little shit.
Now there's a face...
only a mother could love!
Yeah!
Now we're getting somewhere.
Let's see
what really scares you.
And dig a little deeper.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I'm dying to see what skeletons
are hidden in your closet.
We're seriously running
out of tranq here, guys.
I got maybe one dose,
plus enough for Lori.
Well, we're almost there.
Then I better get going.
No, no, just...
I don't want you to go.
I'm coming back.
Just give me fifteen minutes,
then wake me up.
I'll bring that bastard
Freddy back through.
Just make sure
Jason's waiting for him.
Now I lay me down to sleep.
Freak show! Freak show!
Bull's-eye!
Freak show!
Freak show! Freak show!
Try this on!
Freak show!
Freak show! Freak show!
Stupid!
Aren't you gonna help the kid?!
Can't you see I'm busy here?
You mean you're not coming?
It's not my fault this bitch
is dead on her feet.
It's been five minutes.
Well, that was the last
of the tranq, OK? We're out.
Calm down, OK?
Just relax!
Heeeeelp!
Wait! Give me your hand!
Give me your hand!
Help!
Jason?
Jason Vorhees?
Y'all...y'all...
Y'all, something's wrong.
It's like he's drowning
or something.
Freddy must be killing him.
We need him alive!
Dude, what do you
want me to do...
Iike, give him
mouth-to-mouth or something?
Hell no.
Why are you--
No! No, I'm not
gonna do that. No!
Kia, look, I would
do it myself...
but I've had asthma
since I was six, OK?
I don't have the lung power.
No.
Kia, he has asthma!
Ooh! Ooh...
Look, you can do this, OK?
You can do this.
You just--
Shut up! You're not the one
that has to do this.
I know, but l--
Shut up!
Oh, my God.
Ohh, God!
Oh, man.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
You!
What's wrong, Lori?
Miss your wake-up call?
Wake me up!
I got him! I got him!
No!
Lori, come on! Wake up!
Lori, wake up, please!
Look!
Guys, look.
We're almost there.
Help me. Come on.
We gotta get her up.
Come on. Start running.
Start running.
Wake me up!
Daddy, don't!
Daddy!
No, daddy, don't!
Freddy!
It was you!
I've always had a thing...
for the whores
that live in this house.
Lori, wake up!
Oh, shit.
It's him. He's here.
Lori, come on!
You gotta wake up!
Oh, yes.
My God!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Come on, Lori, wake up!
Lori, please. Wake up!
Lori, please.
Go! Go, go, go!
Lori!
Oh, you fuckin' asshole!
Goddamn it!
Welcome to my world, bitch.
I should warn you, princess...
the first time tends
to get a little...
messy.
Get away from her!
Linderman.
Oh! Oh, no!
Die, you little bitch.
Jesus, Linderman.
You--you're really hurt.
No. No, no, no.
Don't worry about me.
Just a scratch.
Just go get help, OK?
What? You don't think--
Look, I'm just gonna
rest here a minute.
-Linderman--
-I'm fine, Kia.
Really.
Now get out of here.
-Go get help.
-But you--
Just go.
OK, but I'm gonna be back
as soon as I can.
Lori!
Think you're so smart,
huh, bitch?
Freddy!
How sweet...
dark meat.
-No! Kia!
-Let's go!
Nooo!
So you're the one
everyone's afraid of?
Tell me something.
What kind of faggot...
runs around
in a Christmas sweater?
I mean, come on. Get real.
You're not even scary.
And let's talk about
the butter knives.
What is with the butter knives?
You trying to compensate
for something?
Maybe coming up
a little short there...
between the legs,
Mr. Krueger?
Hmm.
I mean, you got these
teensy-weensy little things...
and Jason has got this
big ol' thing that's like...
Kia!
-No! No!
-Come on!
Come on, Lori.
Let's go.
We can't help her anymore.
No! I'm staying!
Are you crazy?
You got what you wanted.
You pulled Freddy out,
and now he's fighting Jason.
Come on!
What more do you want?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
He killed my mother, Will!
It was Freddy.
My dad covered it up
to protect me.
He didn't do it.
Look, he has taken
everything from us!
He has ruined
both of our pasts...
and I am not leaving
until I see him die!
Man the torpedoes.
Hey, asshole!
Up here!
Aha!
Yeah.
Ah, give me a break.
Oh, no.
Ohh, noooo!
Lori, get the tanks!
Give it up!
Freddy!
Go to hell!
It's OK. It's OK.
You...
Welcome to my world, bitch!