The itsy-bitsy spider
Crawled up the waterspout
Down came the rain
And washed the spider out
Out came the sun
And dried up all the rain
And the itsy-bitsy spider
Crawled up the spout again
Jesse, you get in
this house right now!
Oh, Mom.
Right now.
No!
Who are you?
Well, I'm Mrs. Voorhees,
an old friend of the Christys.
No, no. They're all dead.
They're all dead.
All right, I'll go look.
Please don't leave me.
He'll kill you too!
I'm not afraid.
No!
Did you know
that a young boy drowned
the year before those
two others were killed?
The counselors weren't
paying any attention.
They were making love
while that young boy drowned.
His name was Jason.
I was working the day that
it happened. Preparing meals.
Here. I was the cook.
Jason should have been
watched, every minute!
He was...
He wasn't
a very good swimmer.
We can go now, dear.
No!
My sweet,
innocent Jason.
My only child.
Jason.
You let him drown.
You never paid
any attention!
Look
what you did to him.
what you did to him!
No!
Kill her, Mommy. Kill her!
She can't hide.
No place to hide.
Get her, Mommy. Get her.
Kill her. Kill her.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Two of my men pulled you
out of the lake. We...
...thought you
were dead too.
Do you remember
very much?
The boy.
Is he dead too?
Who?
The boy. Jason.
Jason?
In the lake.
The one who attacked me.
The one who...
...pulled me
underneath the water.
Ma'am, we didn't
find any boy.
Then he's still there.
God!
Hello?
Hi, Mom.
I know. I'm sorry.
I meant to call earlier,
but I fell asleep.
Really, I'm fine.
I need a little time
alone, that's all.
I know you and Dad worry,
and I appreciate that.
Come on, Mom, we've
been through all of this before.
I just have
to put my life back together,
and this is the only way
I know how.
Look...
Mom, please.
It's getting late,
and I really don't
want to get into it.
I'll call you
tomorrow. Bye.
Mom!
Hello?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh.
Cute.
You want something
to eat?
Hmm?
All right,
keep your eyes peeled.
I think we're
getting close.
Hey,
there's a gas station.
Okay,
let's call Ted.
Hey,
Teddy, buddy!
We just rolled in.
Yeah, yeah,
Sandra's here.
Hi, Ted!
Hey, so you gonna come down
and get us or what?
Yeah, okay. Okay,
give me the directions.
Here, wait, wait, wait. All right.
Okay, go ahead, I'm ready.
All right,
Old North Road,
and then look
for a Dairy Queen?
Okay. And then
over...
I told the others.
They didn't believe me.
You're all doomed.
What?
Oh, no, nothing.
No, go ahead.
No. All right.
So... All right,
covered bridge.
Okay. Then what?
All right, so, then past an old cemetery.
All right.
And then...
Left down an old dirt road
for half a mile.
Oh, my God!
They're towing us!
Shit! Ted,
I'll call you back.
Hey, wait!
Hey, mister!
This is my truck! Come on!
This is my truck!
Asshole,
this is my truck!
Shit!
Welcome to
God's country.
You rat shit!
Thanks, Max!
Max owns
the gas station.
He's crazy too.
I should have known.
It's great to see you.
It'll be like old times.
Yeah, that's what
I'm afraid of.
Help me load my gear
and we'll split.
So, Ted,
what's the scoop?
I know that guy Paul that's
running the course. He's okay.
He's kind of
macho, though.
He takes the whole thing
very seriously.
Senior
camp counselor, of course.
We'll probably all get a
Brownie badge if we survive.
If we survive?
That's right.
Didn't I tell you you're
gonna be a second assistant?
Oh, no!
Wait, listen, listen.
A bear and a rabbit are in the woods.
Both are taking a dump.
The bear looks down
at the rabbit and says,
"Excuse me, Mr. Rabbit,
does shit stick to your fur?"
The rabbit says,
"No, Mr. Bear."
So the bear wiped his
ass with the rabbit.
What the heck
is that?
Where did this sucker
come from?
I don't know.
Let's move it.
This place is spooky.
It looks like
somebody dragged it here.
Yeah, but
what for?
Hey, you guys,
look at this.
It's Camp Blood.
This place is on the same
lake as we're gonna be.
Camp Blood?
Isn't that the place...
Let's get out of here.
Can't we take a look? No way.
What's the problem?
You don't wanna hear about it, man.
Believe me.
Not before lunch.
Need some help?
Oh. Uh...
No, it's okay. I got it.
Thanks, anyhow.
Ow!
Okay, let's
settle down.
It's great to have you here at our
new counselor training center.
You've all worked as counselors
at one camp or another.
Terry, Vickie, you were
upstate last summer, right?
Scott! Hi! Good to see you here, buddy.
You need it.
And, Mark, I know we worked a
season or two together, right?
Okay. The rest of you I'm sure
I'll get to know soon enough.
I'm also sure there's one thing
I don't have to tell you.
Being a counselor isn't the gravy
summer job everybody thinks it is.
And what we're gonna do
over the next two weeks,
if the rest of my staff
ever shows up,
is go back to basics.
Survival, first aid, boating,
archery, rifle range, all of it.
What the hell...
I'll be right back.
Hi! I'm late.
What is this crap? You're
supposed to be my assistant.
Everyone else
got here hours ago.
I said I was sorry.
You did?
I'm sorry. Okay?
But my car's sick.
You could have called.
Paul, I tried, but your phones
aren't even working yet.
Oh.
Okay, get your gear stowed
and help me outside, okay?
Paul, look, the course
starts today, right?
Well, here I am.
And I promise you, I'll never, ever
be late again in my entire life.
Is it a deal?
All right, all
right, what the hell.
Uh...
Ginny, I was starting
to worry about you.
Bullshit, Paul.
Ginny, put your car
on the lot, okay?
This place looks
like a Burger King.
Where was I?
You were about to give your "Let's
keep our shit together" speech.
Mr. Holt.
Right, Ted. Right.
Okay, look, a few words
about safety.
Axes, knives, lanterns, saws.
They can all be trouble.
Their misuse is the main
cause of camp accidents.
Take care of your equipment,
and it'll take care of you.
Now, a word of caution about
our friends in the forest.
Among other things,
this is bear country.
And contrary to what everybody
hears, bears are dangerous.
That means no food fights.
Aw!
Change often. Food odors
cling to clothing.
If you're a woman,
don't use perfume.
And keep clean during
your menstrual cycle.
Having trouble?
You gotta
treat them gentle.
Just like kids.
Use a little of that child
psychology you're majoring in.
Try it.
It's more fun using that
child psychology on you.
You're such a sucker
for it.
Thanks much.
I don't want to scare anyone,
but I'm gonna give it to
you straight about Jason.
His body was never recovered
from the lake after he drowned.
If you listen
to the old-timers,
they'll tell you
he's still out there.
Some sort of
demented creature,
surviving in
the wilderness.
Full-grown by now.
Stalking.
Stealing what he needs, living
off wild animals and vegetation.
Some folks claim
they've even seen him,
right in this area.
The girl who survived that night at
Camp Blood, that Friday the 13th,
she claims
she saw him.
She disappeared
two months later.
Vanished.
Blood was
everywhere.
No one knows
what happened to her.
Legend has it that Jason saw his
mother beheaded that night,
and he took
his revenge.
A revenge that he'll
continue to seek
if anyone enters
his wilderness again.
And by now, I guess you all know,
we're the first to return here.
Five years.
Five long years,
he's been dormant.
And he's hungry.
Jason's
out there
watching.
Always on the prowl
for intruders.
Waiting to kill.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Waiting to devour.
Thirsty for young blood.
Hey, come back!
Come back!
Okay, look, now that we've
got that out of our system,
I don't want to hear
any more about it.
It's ancient history. Jason
drowned, Mrs. Voorhees was killed,
and Camp Crystal Lake
is off-limits. You got it?
Got you, huh?
What did you think?
The second act
needs work.
- Too bad.
- Come on.
You got him. You got him.
You got him now.
Go on.
That's luck.
That's luck, all right?
Thanks a lot.
Next.
Hi, Terry. Do you
wanna dance?
No, thank you.
Hi there. How about you?
Do you wanna dance?
So there I was, sitting in this
fast-food joint, thinking to myself,
"Scott, old boy, what are you gonna
do with the rest of your life?"
I'm striking out
all over the place.
Well, I think
I've got you. Check.
Wrong, white man.
Checkmate.
Well, what next?
I could get my arm
broken by Mark,
my brains Ponged by
our electronical wizard
or bed.
Good night, Paul.
See you in the morning.
Jeff, I just gotta
see that place.
What place? That camp.
Camp Blood.
You're crazy.
I've just got to. Maybe there
is something to that legend.
I'm serious.
No way. You're not
getting me out there.
Besides, Paul said
it was off-limits.
We'll see.
Hello?
Who's there?
Paul, God damn it!
What do you...
Hey, hey, hey.
Calm down.
You'll wake
the natives.
I'm not supposed to be
fraternizing with the staff.
I won't tell.
I missed you,
Ginny.
And I really was worried when
you didn't show on time.
Oh, Paul, there's something
I think I should tell you.
Come on! Come on!
What's the matter, guys?
Jeff, the women
are showing you up.
What's the matter
with you?
Hey!
We've got about a half a
mile, then we're gonna have lunch.
Try to stay on this trail, because
there's a lot of poison ivy along here.
How far are we
from camp?
Hey, you guys,
don't trip on that.
Mr. Holt. What are
we gonna have for lunch?
Ted's
probably gonna cook.
All right, after lunch,
we're gonna do some more running.
Here you go, Ted.
Thank you, dear.
Come and
get them!
I'm here.
Muffin?
Here, girl.
Muffin.
Muffin?
Terry, lunch!
Okay. I'm coming!
Jeff.
What?
You ready?
For what?
Camp Blood.
I thought we weren't supposed
to go near that place.
Come on, it's only a short walk.
They'll never know we're gone.
Jeff, I'm serious.
I really wanna see it.
Look, when we
get back to the city,
we can tell everyone
we were there.
Oh, come on,
you chicken shit.
Okay, let's go.
Okay, you guys.
I got one. Ready?
What's green and red and
moves 100 miles an hour?
What? A frog in a blender.
Ha-ha. That
wasn't funny.
What's brown and
sits on a piano?
Your face.
Beethoven's
last movement.
Ew!
God.
This must be it.
Yeah.
Oh, my God!
What is it?
It looks like a dog.
It's too mangled
to tell.
What do you think
did it?
Wild animal, I guess.
What are
you kids doing out here?
You're gonna have to keep your
people away from that place.
It's condemned.
Next time I catch anybody
there, I'll run them in.
He told us...
I'll handle this, Jeff.
I might just get a warrant against you.
Oh, really?
Look, Holt, people say what you're
doing with these kids is great.
You've got a
good reputation.
But if I was you, I'd have
located in the next county.
You're too close.
Things have been quiet for five years.
That's the way we want it.
So do I, Officer.
So do I.
Okay, you two, take off, and
I'll talk to you at dinner.
We'll never
do it again, sir.
Thanks, Mr. Holt.
You're not even
gonna reprimand them?
No punishment?
What kind
of place is this?
Ginny?
Yes, Paul?
No seconds on dessert
for Jeff and Sandra tonight.
You okay?
Should we tell Terry? You
know, about what we saw?
No way. As far as I'm concerned,
we didn't see a thing.
Hey! Hey, you!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh, my God.
- Oh, no.
- Anybody want...
Who made this shit?
Okay, people.
Today was fun
and games, right?
I like to start
you out slow, ease you in.
Tomorrow,
we'll get serious.
Anybody who wants a last night
on the town, now's your chance.
Okay, who else?
We only have two cars.
By the way, our wanderers have
volunteered to stay and watch the camp.
Isn't that
nice of them?
I think I'll stay too.
Muffin may show.
Well, I'm gonna
go change, you guys.
You know,
I'm pretty tired.
I think I'll
stick around too.
Get me another cup of coffee?
Sure.
Don't drink too much.
Bye-bye.
Hey, you staying?
Yeah. Nothing spoils a party faster
than a drunk in a wheelchair.
That's crap. Look, we can
go together if you want.
I appreciate that,
but I'm in training.
Then I'm staying too.
Suit yourself.
So how about it, second-in-command?
You coming?
You buying?
Sure.
You got a deal.
Got the keys?
Beer time!
Take it easy. Have fun.
I'll have a Jack for you.
See you later!
Bring back
my truck in one piece.
I'm going
for a walk.
We'll wait up
for you, all right?
Go, scooter.
Now I know how you can
afford tuition to grad school.
You always find some fool to fix
your car and buy you a beer.
You got it.
Muffin?
- Here we are!
- All right.
Everybody, get out
for some beers! All right!
Come on, Mark.
Come on.
You're gonna lose.
All right!
Hey!
Cheater.
Okay, okay, okay.
Two out of three.
All right.
Jeff, don't
wear yourself out.
You wanna wrestle,
come with me.
Later, scooter.
Wanna take me on?
Sure. Have a seat.
I only want
your fingers.
What?
Take your pick.
They're Ted's.
It's okay with him.
Football and hockey.
Which one
do you prefer?
The one
with the puck.
You mean hockey?
Is that
what you call it?
Okay. What do you
wanna play for?
Position.
Looking for something?
Come and get it.
Give me my shirt, Scott.
If I get my
hands on you...
Scott!
It's no longer
funny, Scott.
Help! God damn that Paul!
Him and his
wilderness bullshit!
What can I do?
Get me down, that's what!
I'll have to get a knife
to cut the rope.
Well, hurry, okay?
I ought to let you
hang, you pervert.
Come on, Ter.
Give me a break.
You gonna cut
the crap?
Sure, anything.
I promise.
Okay.
Don't go anywhere.
Very funny.
Where is she?
Scott, I'm gonna
cut you down.
But I swear, if you ever do this
to me again, I'm gonna kill you.
Scott?
Look at this.
I think
I'm in love.
No, no, it's just
tremendous affection.
Are you sure you don't
want me to clear those?
No, I'm
collecting these.
Have it
your way, honey.
I just don't want the bar
to fall down on you.
Thanks.
I think
she likes you.
I think so too.
This whole thing's
ridiculous, really.
Two of our kids got hauled in
today, because five years ago
some girl panics and falls
out of a canoe.
It's absurd.
What if there is
a Jason?
Oh, bullshit, Ginny.
No, what if there is
some kind of boy-beast
running around
Camp Crystal Lake?
Let's try to think beyond the legend.
Put it in real terms.
I mean, what would he
be like today?
Some kind of out-of-control
psychopath?
A frightened retard? A child
trapped in a man's body?
Let me out!
He'd be grown
by now, right?
Right.
And, you know, the only person
that ever knew him was his mother.
He never went to school,
so he never had any friends.
She was everything to him.
Yeah. Deranged killer.
No, no, no. You're
missing my whole point.
I mean, I doubt Jason would have
even known the meaning of death.
Or at least until
that horrible night.
He must have seen
the whole thing happen.
his mother killed,
and all just because
she loved him.
Isn't that what her revenge
was all about?
Her sense of loss,
her rage at what
she thought happened,
her love for him?
Bizarre, isn't it?
He must be
out there right now,
crying for her return,
her resurrection.
Well, what do you think?
I think
you're drunk.
I'll drink to that.
Hit us again, sweetheart.
Not me.
You know, Paul, I'm really
serious about this though.
Jason's a
legend, Ginny,
a legend.
Your turn. Three goals
or you're gonna lose.
I've heard
that one before.
Mark, what happened that
you have to be in a chair?
Motorcycle accident,
paralyzed my legs.
Is it permanent?
The doctor thinks so.
I don't.
I don't intend to be in this
thing the rest of my life.
Just your legs,
huh?
Is everything else okay?
Oh, I do all right,
one way or another.
Toke?
I'm in training,
remember?
For what?
What does
the winner get?
the winner want?
Guess.
Want to stay
together tonight?
I was
just about to ask you.
My cabin or yours?
Ted's in mine. I don't
think that would work out.
We've got the whole camp.
We'll find our own cabin.
Just give me a few minutes
to get some things, okay?
Sure.
I'll be right back.
Oh, damn it.
Terry, you turkey.
There you are.
Vickie?
Vickie, is that you?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I looked up "ugly"
in the dictionary.
There's a picture
of him.
I got to get some sleep.
I'm tired.
You guys quitting already?
Ted, you'd have me out
till breakfast.
I'm gonna ride with
you, okay? Okay.
Good night, Ted.
Good night, Ginny.
When this place closes,
come straight back to camp.
Yes, boss. And let Maggie
drive the pickup.
Yes, boss.
Okay, let's
make a run for it.
Move it!
I'm going! I'm going!
This thing
had better start.
You fixed it.
I know, that's
what worries me.
Are there any after-hours
places around here?
Sure are.
"Sure are."
Mark?
Mark, where are you?
Is anybody still here?
Sandra?
Jeff?
Sandra? Jeff?
Sandra.
Sandra?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Sandra.
No! No!
No!
No! Stop!
Nice night.
Yeah, for a duck.
God.
What the hell are
all the lights on for?
Paul, they wouldn't have
left the place like this.
Think something's wrong?
I'll check upstairs.
These kids smoke
better dope than I do.
Paul!
Yeah, Ginny, what...
What is this,
a joke?
They wouldn't do
anything like this.
Ginny, come on.
Wait for me.
Kitchen light's
still on. Must...
Must be
the main fuse again.
Paul, what's going on here?
Nothing.
Where is
everybody?
I don't know.
The rain's stopping.
We'll go look for them.
Paul, there's
someone in this room.
Paul, there's someone
in this fucking room!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Paul?
Paul? Paul?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Paul?
Answer me!
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
God, please, keys,
be there. Keys, be there...
Come on, car!
Please start. Please start.
Please start.
Start!
Oh, shit!
Oh, my God!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Please help me.
Oh, God...
Jason!
It's all done, Jason.
You've done your job well,
and Mommy is pleased.
That's a good boy.
Now, come to Mommy.
Come on.
Mommy has a reward for you.
Jason, Mother
is talking to you.
Come on.
That's my boy.
Come.
Kneel down.
That's a boy.
Kneel down, Jason.
That's my good boy.
That's a good boy.
Good Jason.
Ginny!
Come on. Let's go.
Ginny.
Jesus.
Come on.
Paul!
I'll carry you.
It's all right.
Hey, you're
all right. You're all...
God! Oh, God!
No, you're okay.
You're okay.
You're okay, Ginny.
You're all right.
It's all right.
Oh, Muffin!
Muffin.
Oh, Muffin.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Come here, Muffin.
Paul?
Where's Paul?