It's like this.
We live in claustrophobia,
a land of steel and concrete,
trapped by dark waters.
There is no escape,
nor do we want it.
We've come to thrive on it
and each other.
You can't get the adrenaline pumping
without the terror.
I love this town.
You've been listening to WGAZ,
the electricity of Manhattan.
This request goes out
to Crystal Lake,
to the senior class of Lakeview High.
That's us!
They'll be graduating
on the 13th of this month
and we wish them the best of luck
and success
when they come to visit
our seductive city.
Our lure is a great one,
young friends, but beware -
the city of lights
casts many shadows indeed.
- I love you.
Got to throw the anchor over.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
Come on, Jimmy,
something's bothering you.
We're near that summer camp
where all those murders took place.
- What murders?
- You don't want to know.
- Tell me.
- Forget about it, Suzi.
The guy's dead now,
somewhere at the bottom of this lake,
if you believe the stories.
What stories?
There was this boy
named Jason Voorhees.
He drowned in Crystal Lake
about 30 years ago.
None of the counsellors heard him.
Help!
A bunch of years went by,
everyone forgot about it
and that's when the murders started.
Jason did it?
His mother blamed the counsellors
for her son's death
and she tried to kill them all
but she got her head chopped off
by one of them.
Legend has it that Jason came back
to get even,
vowing to kill every teenager
in the area.
And every now and then,
the murders just start up.
Forget about it,
they're just stories.
CRYSTAL LAKE CAMP.
- Did you hear that?
- Hear what?
Come on, I'm serious.
All right, I'll go check it out.
Jim?
Stop screwing around. I mean it.
Got you good, Suzi.
All right, so I'm a major ass.
- You'll never do it again?
- Never again.
- Forgive me?
- No.
Jason?
No. Please, no!
Toby's gone awful quiet back there.
Yeah, I guess he's a little nervous
about the trip.
Here.
Go on, open it.
Stephen King supposedly used it
in high school.
I don't know what to say.
Rennie, you are the best student
I have ever had.
You have a real gift.
If there's anybody that can
make use of that pen, it's you.
- Charles.
- Colleen.
This cruise was your idea
so at the very least
you could show up on time.
- Has everyone checked in?
- No.
Jim Miller and Suzi Donaldson
never showed up
and I'm very concerned.
They probably decided to explore
each other rather than New York.
That's nice. We're running
five minutes late already.
There's someone else coming, too.
You never should've brought her.
It's up to Rennie to decide
what she wants to do.
She doesn't know. She never had
a stable life till she lived with me.
She certainly doesn't have one now.
I'm her legal guardian,
not you or anybody else
and I know what's best for her.
End of discussion.
I think it's just the beginning.
Have you decided on
your departure protocol?
I thought I'd leave that honour
to my son.
That's not necessary.
Relinquishing command
of the motor vessel Lazarus
to Captain Sean Robertson.
But before you take the helm,
take this.
Something old and something new.
I used that sextant
when I was your age.
Now those goddamn computers
do all the work for you.
Have you decided on
a plan of departure, Captain?
How about we start up the engines
and come around 180 degrees?
Aren't you forgetting something?
Send out
the international maritime signal,
followed by a broadcast
warning other ships
that we are underway.
This voyage is doomed.
Tell me about it.
- Have fun in New York!
- Bye!
LAKEVIEW GRAD CRUISE.
- Rennie.
- Hi, Sean.
I heard you weren't coming.
We changed our minds.
- I got you a present.
- But I didn't get you one.
Forget it.
It's a dumb little thing anyway.
I love it.
I thought when we got there we
could hike to the top of the statue,
if you felt like it.
It's supposed to be 22 storeys tall.
That sounds wonderful.
Mr Robertson,
your father was looking for you.
I guess I'll see you later.
What are you doing here?
We've already been through all this.
I'm sorry, Uncle Charles.
Please don't be upset with me.
I'm not upset, I'm just concerned.
Is this axe awesome or what?
Too cool, JJ.
Your parents really came through.
No lie. I hear there's
this big power room downstairs,
we can get supreme
concert hall echo.
Come down and shoot a basement
tape.
I've got to get some
shockumentary footage first.
Oh, man! Don't tell me you're still
trying to scam on Tamara?
How long have we known each other?
Don't be a dweeb, Wayne.
She's only interested in
what you can do for her.
She is a user.
She's sexy.
So what? So's this guitar.
I'll talk to you later, all right?
There's a big storm
predicted for tonight.
You're making a big mistake.
It's not too late
to put you back on shore.
If Miss Van Deusen
knew how afraid...
She didn't push me into this.
Why are you doing this to yourself?
I don't even know what I'm afraid of.
I can't even remember
when it started.
Don't you think it's time I found out
and got over it?
Facing your fear
doesn't always conquer it.
I'm staying.
OK.
Man, this place
is aching for a video!
Wayne, you're an asshole.
So what do you think?
Time for some personal experiences
to fuel our minds?
I agree.
Mommy?
Help! Help me!
Toby!
Is that a muscular bod or what?
He's undefeated, you know that?
Julius is the only senior
I'd even consider doing it with.
He is so good-Iooking.
Gorgeous guy at 10 o'clock.
Look sensual.
I think it's time
for some recreational activity.
Have you seen my niece?
She's motorvating downstairs,
what's the problem?
Senior predictions has started
and she hasn't shown up.
Maybe some of us
don't want our futures predicted.
In your case, I'm sure that's true.
Night-time is the right time.
- No thanks.
- Don't be a lightweight.
If we get caught,
I could lose my science scholarship.
You're talking to the prom queen.
Would I risk getting caught?
- Jesus!
- Have you guys seen my dog?
No, we haven't.
Would you care for a hit?
No thanks.
Real space cadet.
Wonder if she'll nark on us?
Here, boy!
GAMES ROOM LAZARUS.
Ready to party and then some.
- What are you doing in here?
- Nothing.
Are you girls using drugs?
Do you think I would use drugs,
Mr McCulloch?
We were just exploring the ship.
I'll be coming to your room
in exactly 15 minutes, Miss Mason.
Have your biology project ready
or I'll be phoning your parents.
They're out of town.
I'll make sure that you remain
on board
while your classmates
are out seeing the sights.
- Now what?
- Relax.
I've got McCulloch covered.
That narking bitch niece of his
is a different matter.
Rumour has it she's a teensy bit
afraid of the water.
Nice fight, Julius. I need to work
on my left-right-left combo.
Listen, no hard feelings, OK?
What do you say we track down
those babes?
- So, are you having fun yet?
- Yeah, a lot.
Come on, level with me.
If you can't trust me,
who can you trust?
It was an accident, I swear.
Stay calm
and grab the life preserver!
I've got you. Come on.
That was truly excellent.
- Let's check out the waiters.
- I think I'll pass.
- What?
- See you later.
Some friend you are.
Come on, grab her hand!
It's OK. Sit down.
Grab her some towels.
She's fine,
just go back to what you were doing.
Care to talk about it?
I can't swim.
No kidding.
Have you thought about
taking lessons?
It's not that simple.
Good God!
Take it easy, she's all right.
You've done wonderful job
supervising the kids. What happened?
- It wasn't her fault.
- Give me those towels.
You stay away from her. Both of you!
He's come back
and you're all gonna die.
Just leave me alone!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Help!
The door's open.
I'm in no mood for any more
of your stall tactics.
Where is your final project?
Wouldn't you like
a glass of champagne first, Charles?
Where did you get this?
I packed it just for us.
That's it.
You're not stepping off this ship
until we return home.
I haven't even shown you
my biology project.
What do you think you're doing?
You stop that!
I mean, really.
Take a closer look, Charles.
I want to make sure I've labelled
all my organs correctly.
Get off of me! I don't believe this.
What do you think you're doing?
I'm your teacher.
Not only are you going home
but I will see to it that you spend
next year back in high school.
What is going on?
- Get anything good?
- Very kinky.
- Give me that tape!
- Come and get it.
You're going to be very, very sorry,
young lady.
And as for you, you can forget about
attending any film school.
Ever!
Relax, he's not going to risk
trying a thing.
I guess you're right.
Listen, this is going to sound
supremely lame and I know it
but I've had the major hots for you
since our sophomore year.
That's so sweet, Wayne.
And I really would love
to stay and chat
but I really am pressed for time.
- Let's get together later.
- I just thought...
Maybe we could...
Wayne, you're an asshole.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Let's kick in the stabilizers,
keep the seas off the quarter.
Yes, sir.
These kids are in for
one hell of a storm.
- How old's your boy now?
- 19 months.
Tremendous age.
Take some advice.
Don't push him too hard.
- Take the helm, Jim.
- Certainly, sir.
I'd double-check
those lifeboat stations, too.
My God!
- Can you take us home?
- I'll the Coast Guard for you.
What about you? Are you staying
here?
I'm never going to be
what he wants me to be,
so I guess I'm going with you.
Jesus!
Dad?
Attention everybody.
This is Sean Robertson.
Have you seen JJ? She was supposed
to be down in the power room.
This is an emergency.
Everybody come to the bridge.
What the fuck is this?
Mayday.
Shit.
This is the motor vessel Lazarus.
What's going on?
- Jesus Christ.
- Can anybody out there hear me?
Thank God.
Hello?
Are you there?
I demand to know what is going on!
Christ.
Where's the radio?
It's dead.
You're all gonna die.
You're the last ones.
He's come back for you.
- What are you talking about?
- Jason Voorhees.
You're insane!
He's been dead for years.
He came down the river
and he got on board.
He walks this ship here and now.
Yes, a killer walks this ship.
And it's certainly none of us!
- Bastard!
- What are you doing?
You're the one who's insane.
That lunatic has been talking about
Jason ever since he came aboard.
- It's no coincidence.
- It doesn't prove he's the one.
Walking corpses are not real.
These dead bodies are real enough.
I say we regroup
and go find this motherfucker
before he finds us!
- Are you with me?
- Watch your mouth!
You'll do no such thing.
I'm in charge here!
School is out, McCulloch. OK?
Let's go.
You come back here!
Christ. Where's Rennie?
She's dropping the anchors.
- You had me worried to death!
- Sean said to drop the anchors.
I'm the one
you should be listening to.
Do you think dropping an anchor
in the middle of a storm makes sense?
Come on.
Tamara?
Did you hear the announcement?
We managed to scrounge this up
in game rooms and hallways.
All right, grab what you want.
- What are you taking, Julius?
- Nothing...
...but this gun.
JJ?
Are you down here?
You got a major problem, Wayne.
Shit, I can't see a damn thing.
Did you find Rennie?
She's safe in her room,
no thanks to you.
Have you brought her
back on course yet?
He's doing the best he can.
He's the son of a captain.
He ought to be able to operate
this thing. Do something!
It worked.
- We're back on course.
- Good!
- What's that?
- The fire alarm.
We thought about that. Nobody could
see a flare gun in this storm.
Only one person needs to see it.
I'm gonna find that deck hand.
But what about the fire?
- How do we know there really is one?
- What?
Use some common sense.
Setting off
a fire alarm causes panic,
the same panic caused by suggesting
Jason is alive and on this ship.
Enough is enough.
Help me!
I don't understand
what's happening to me.
- What is that?
- The power room.
Listen. I want you to stay here
until I get back with the others.
Understand?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Water's got into the engine circuit.
ENGINE ROOM.
We have to get everybody
off the ship!
Quick! Dive!
What the hell? Let go of her!
She shouldn't be on this ship!
It's all your fault!
- It's Jason's fault.
- Not another word, you hear?
No, I don't!
You listen to me
if you want off this ship alive.
Thank God.
I just lowered the lifeboat.
We have to go.
Wait! I left the others
in the restaurant.
There is no more restaurant.
Come on.
Get back!
Son of a bitch!
Come on.
Hurry up!
Start rowing!
Come on!
Keep rowing!
I hope you can find shore soon,
Captain.
We don't want to drown out here.
Do you have any idea where we are,
Sean?
Come on, man. I made it, so can you.
All right, man.
Hey, man. Wake up!
Shit! Check it out!
Damn! We're in New York! You did it!
We are in New York! New York City!
I don't believe it, we made it!
There must be a phone around here.
Wonderful choice of places
to dock a boat, Mr Robertson.
Wonderful.
- I can't believe we made it.
- Or that we're alive.
We are all very lucky.
- Give me your money.
- Give him the money. Now!
Here.
Got some good shit here.
You got that right.
Give me your wallet.
- Ain't that sweet.
- Bastard!
Go ahead Superman, be a hero.
- Come on, now.
- Got a problem, Dad?
- Please don't hurt her.
- Miss Princess?
Would I do that?
You look like a real party girl.
Want to go on a date
with me and my friend?
If you're free, that is.
Follow us,
we'll blow her fucking head off.
Are we just going to stand here?
Let's go.
Julius! Calm down, will you?
You heard him, they'll kill her!
We have to find the police!
I think it'll be more productive
if we split up.
No discussions now, please!
Help! Stop it! Somebody help me!
Shut the fuck up!
Welcome to the Casbah, princess.
Please, don't hurt me.
Loosen up, baby. You'll feel
way better if you're stoned.
Better sling her some more caine.
We only got a half load here.
We're in for a long night.
It's your parade, princess.
It can be smooth, it can be rough.
It's your choice.
Come on, baby. Lay back and enjoy it.
I think I'm in love.
Forgot my money, homes.
Who the fuck are you?
You're dead, fuckhead.
Come on. Operator, this is
an emergency, get me the police.
Use the combos, keep the feet light.
This is it.
Take your best shot.
Motherfucker.
- What did they do to you?
- He's here.
Jason is here.
We have to find the others now.
- Freeze!
- It's OK, she's with me.
My apologies, miss.
Are you all right?
Thank God.
Are you OK?
Mr McCulloch,
Jason is here in New York.
- Rennie saw him.
- Just shut up about Jason.
Is it true?
I find it a tall tale indeed
but you seem honest
so I kind of believe
some of what you say.
First we need to find Julius.
I'm sure he'll pop up.
I'll call for back-up.
Dispatch!
Hold it! What are you doing?
For God's sake, Rennie, slow down!
Quickly! Let's move!
Miss Van Deusen!
It's so pretty today.
Perfect day for swimming.
You've been coming out here
every summer for three years
and you still haven't learned
how to swim.
I'll take some lessons this time.
I promise.
That's what you said last year.
I think the time has come
for your first swimming lesson.
You don't want to end up drowning
like that Voorhees boy, do you?
He never learned how to swim, either.
He's still in the bottom
of this lake.
- He is not.
- He is.
And he's ready to pull down
anybody who falls in and can't swim.
You're telling a lie.
Am I? Let's find out.
Better swim, Rennie,
before Jason pulls you down.
- I can't!
- You can and you will!
Come on! Swim!
You pushed me into the lake.
I was only trying to teach you.
You almost killed me.
I was drowning!
I pulled you out, I saved your life!
You son of a bitch!
He was down there.
Just keep away from her!
You! It's not possible!
Please!
I'm begging you! Please!
I was at school when they told me.
Rennie, your parents died
in a car accident.
It seems like
everybody I care about I lose.
That won't happen this time.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Help!
EMERGENCY BRAKE
$100 FINE FOR UNLAWFUL USE
Is this my stop?
Get it moving!
DANGER 6000 VOLTS.
SUBWAY.
It's over.
- Somebody please...
- Let's go!
You are dead meat, slimebag!
Yo, man. It's cool.
Di's Diner.
- We're open till 3am like always.
- We've got to call the police.
There's a payphone in back
but it's broke.
Look, you don't understand,
a maniac is trying to kill us.
Welcome to New York.
Son of a bitch.
Come on!
What are you kids doing down here?
- Can you help us get out?
- We haven't got a man to spare.
- What do you mean?
- Toxic waste.
The sewer floods with the stuff
at midnight, ten minutes from now.
Follow me.
You didn't get me in the lake
and you're not gonna get me now!
DANGER
TOXIC
CHEMICALS.
Get up!
Go!
Run!
Mommy! Don't let me drown!
Help!
I hear there's a statue here
that's 22 storeys tall.
Toby!