I believe that each of us
has a role in life.
We all have something
unique to offer.
And there's a place where we can
maximize our abilities.
A place where we can maximize
our abilities...
"Be Ready for that Job Interview!"
I'm convinced that your company
is the right place for me.
Isn't that Kato?
Hey, watch out!
The express service
will not stop at this station.
The train's coming!
Get the station master!
Get someone!
Here I go.
The train is coming!
Sir, are you OK?
Hey! Can you move?
Somebody, give me a hand here!
He's drunk!
Come on, wake up!
Somebody! Anybody!
Kei...
Is that you, Kei?
Help me!
Damn it.
Come on, on your feet!
Pull him up!
Kato!
Thanks...
What the...?
Two more came.
Come on...
That's Tokyo Tower.
It won't open.
There's no way out.
What is this place? A hospital?
I don't know.
Listen, back at the platform...
- We got run over!
- You ignored me.
I didn't... I...didn't see you.
I knew you wouldn't!
- Was it at primary school?
- We met three times after that.
Anyway...
Weren't we run over by that train?
We were.
But we're alive.
Just like us.
I got run over by a car.
Where are we?
Heaven! The apartment version!
That's one possibility, but...
It has to be! I know I died.
What's this?
That's how you appeared.
Why is she naked?
- Take that off.
- Hey.
Are you OK?
Rise and shine,
it's a new morning for us
A morning of new hope
Breathe in, a chest full of joy
Look up at the clear, blue sky!
Listen to the radio
The summer breeze
is so wholesome
Breathe in and exercise now
To the count of one, two and three!
"All of your old lives are gone."
"I will decide how to
use your new lives."
"That's the way the cookie crumbles."
What...?
"You will all please go now
to finish off this guy."
What do you mean, "guy"?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
"Onion Alien"
"He stinks and he likes onions."
What are these?
He's breathing.
He's warm.
Does that mean he's alive?
"Kurono"
It has my name on it.
You're right.
"Yamada..."
- How come...?
- Dunno.
I'm Inamori.
Get all of them.
Cosplay...?
Is this for me?
I guess so.
- Do I put it on?
- Dunno.
"Kishimoto"
Are you Kishimoto...?
You can put this on.
But...
Um...
Am I dead?
I don't really know.
But you're naked, so...
Will it fit?
Were they expecting me?
Is this some kind of a toy?
It's heavy for a toy.
There are no holes on the muzzle.
Oh, yeah...
- Don't point it this way!
- It has no holes, look!
- Point it away!
- Sorry.
Everyone!
Uh... sorry, it's nothing.
You can't stop there.
Tell us.
I remember being taken
to a hospital.
Then I vaguely remember
being sedated.
Sedated?
Yes. I was also hit by a car.
I remember being taken to hospital,
all bloody.
And I was drugged there.
That's when I started
to get drowsy...
But wait a minute.
What's suspicious about that?
Sorry, you're right.
I'm beginning to see
the whole picture.
It's like I thought.
We're not dead.
We were taken to the hospital
in a coma and drugged.
The drug is making us hallucinate.
Really?
It's like group hypnosis.
See? We're all
seeing the same thing.
That must be it!
We're being forced to take part
in some kind of strange experiment.
What is this thing?
I don't know.
It's a hallucination.
Kei!
"go now, please."
Wow.
We're outside.
We're out now.
I guess we can go home.
I've had enough.
Wait a minute.
You deserve an explanation.
This is for TV.
You're under hypnosis on TV.
See? I knew I wasn't dead!
My father is the producer
of the show.
It's a project by American cable TV
and Yale University.
It's a virtual reality show.
Don't you know American Try Out?
If you complete the mission,
you win $100,000.
I begged Dad to put me on the show.
$100,000?
That's 10 million yen!
Kato, look over there.
Take a good look.
He's our target on the mission.
Is he, really?
We have 20 minutes.
First one to get him grabs the money!
I'll be damned!
I got laid off last month, so...
10 million...!
Wasn't that a child?
Go and see for yourself
if you want to know.
Stop running!
Stop, you brat!
Come on, wait!
Go, spread out!
What's this thing?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
You can have my onion.
You can have it.
That's some mask.
You little prick!
Get him!
How come there's nobody around?
Are we walking in circles?
"lchinomiya, Tama City"
We're in Tama City.
What's going on?
I'll take a look.
Now there's only us left...
Where do you live?
I'll walk you home.
I'm going, too.
Surround him!
Where is he?
There!
Where did he go?
There he is!
He's fast!
Turn on the light.
So...can I shoot this gun now?
Take my onion.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Is that all?
This is real.
God damn!
Ouch!
Damn it!
10 million yen...
It's so realistic.
That's enough!
What are you looking at, punk?!
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, so let go!
Fire! Shoot the fucker!
Call the police... The police.
I know we are going back
to that apartment now...
When's the drug wear off?
Kato?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh, God.
I'm OK?
Why?
This is crazy.
Shit.
I knew it.
I'm sorry.
Using the attaché case was creative.
It was close.
Now you know what the suit's for.
Shoot him, you deserve the points.
It's on me.
Come on.
He killed everybody.
I like the look in your eye.
You disappoint me.
You won't survive the next round.
It's happening again.
We have so many survivors tonight!
Explain! This isn't TV, is it?
Ask Gantz.
That's Gantz. When I came along,
people had already called it that.
Hey, I thought you were dead!
Even if you're bleeding to death,
you're OK as long as you're alive.
"It is time for the scores."
"0 points for Kishimoto,
your tits are too big."
What?
"0 Points for Kato,
your too much of a chicken."
"0 points for Suzuki,
you are so invisible."
Invisible.
"0 points for Kurono,
you stare at Kishimoto too much."
"5 points for Nishi,
getting 79 in total."
Just 5 points?
What's this about?
Gantz evaluated our
mission performances.
Our mission is to kill
the space invaders.
Who are you?
I'm one, too.
An alien.
Don't get serious.
I'm just kidding!
You arsehole!
What happened to the others?
They got killed. You saw it.
See?
They're the ones who've died
in the Gantz missions.
Did you see the way the yakuza
was blown up?
And how Mr. Hypnotism
was trampled on!
He died before he knew it!
It was even more awesome
the other day...
You could have helped those guys!
I know, you're one of
those hypocrites.
And you're clueless.
You're taking it out on the wrong guy.
Leave Kato alone!
Will you shoot this time?
Yes, I will.
Tell us what you know.
What is this place?
Talk.
Sorry.
Maybe next time.
Was it a dream?
"Witnesses please report"
Is this about the accident
we saw yesterday?
Oh, please don't remind me.
Sorry! There was no toilet paper.
Oh, gross.
"..passengers were hit
by the train..."
I believe that
each of us has a role in life.
We all have something unique to offer.
And there's a place where we can
maximize our abilities.
What is it that
you want to do here?
Pardon?
What position?
You don't say that
at a job interview, man.
I'm doing better than Kurono.
- Nobody wants to hire him?
- No.
He's kind of invisible, isn't he?
He's the unemployable type.
He boasts about being
a football star.
At primary school. Come on!
He'll vanish in the real world.
That concludes the lecture today.
Don't let them bother you.
I'm kind of invisible too.
What's the best way to get noticed?
When I met my old friend
at the train station...
Kei?
Was it primary school?
Kato!
I'm Kojima.
My name's Tae Kojima.
"Students' addresses"
"2, Yaguchi, Ota"
"Kei Kurono, Masaru Kato"
"Your friend forever, Kato"
Kei, you're my hero!
Don't forget I saved your butt!
I won't! We're friends forever!
You're home early, Akira.
It's me, Dad.
Kei, I didn't know you were here.
How are you?
I'm going now.
Did you find yourself a good job?
I'm working on it.
Don't be a slacker. Akira already
has his sights on a college.
There's no house here.
"2, Yaguchi, Ota"
"lchinomiya, Tama City"
Hello.
You know who I am?
Hey!
That's the...
I had it on when I woke up.
I visited Kato at his house.
Kato...
I wanted to...
confirm with him
what happened two days ago.
But...
it looks like he's moved.
I only had an address
from ten years ago.
I see...
Should we go to the police?
They won't believe us.
I guess not.
I can walk you to the station.
I have a favour to ask you.
- Sure.
- Can I stay over?
Uh-huh.
Huh?
Is it OK if I sleep on the bed?
Of course.
Thank you.
I hope I won't have a backache
in the morning...
I'll sleep on the floor.
No, sleep on the bed. I'm OK.
Are you sure you don't have to
go back home?
My boyfriend's things are there.
Oh, you live with him?
We broke up recently.
He just moved out.
Oh, really.
Then on impulse
when I was in the bath...
I slit my wrist.
I didn't really mean to do it.
You committed suicide?
When I woke up,
I was back at my place...
I was too scared
to look in the bathroom.
I didn't want to see my body
in a pool of blood.
What's that?
I borrowed it from Kato.
I have to see him.
I want to thank him for being kind.
It's his diary.
Maybe his address is in here.
Parole officer?
"Masaru Kato, on parole."
Was he in juvie?
- Let's stop.
- I saw his address.
Now I remember.
I heard that he never went
to high school.
That's nothing to do with us.
There was lots going on in his life.
His dad was a violent alcoholic.
Maybe Kato is too.
He's not the type.
How do you know?
He's the kindest person I know.
If only I'd met him earlier...
Would you have lived?
Whatever.
I'm sorry.
I'll turn off the light.
"Masaru Kato, caretaker"
Brother!
Hey, bro.
Aren't you going to bed?
I will, soon.
Trouble sleeping again?
Bad dreams?
Off to bed, Ayumu.
Wake up on time
if you want to eat.
Not again.
Rise and shine,
it's a new morning for us
A morning of new hope
Breathe in, a chest full of joy
Look up at the clear, blue sky!
Listen to the radio
Is this everyone?
The summer breeze
is so wholesome
Breathe in and exercise now
To the count of one, two and three!
"All of your old lives are gone."
"I will decide how to
use your new lives."
"That's the way the cookie crumbles."
"You will all please go now
to finish off this guy."
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
"Tanaka Alien,
he's as bright as sunshine."
"He loves boom boxes."
You understand now?
Gantz scanned us.
It knows everything about us.
There's no escape.
You'll be called back every time.
Every time...
To get ourselves almost killed?
Right.
Gantz was recruiting people
long before me.
They fought the aliens
and were replaced when they died.
Many of them died.
And I survived.
You could have told us that!
If we knew, those others
might still be alive!
You understand nothing, hypocrite!
You used them as bait.
Correct answer!
I knew you and I were alike.
What?
Aliens lose focus
when they are killing humans.
Isn't that funny?
Tell us what you know!
Tell us what we should do
to survive.
Don't depend on me.
How about using your brain?
This suit...
Put it on.
It should be of some help.
Off I go.
Good luck!
Grandma!
Do I have to do this again?
How many times?
I don't know.
Put the suit on!
The attaché case.
Here.
"go now, please."
Where are you, Grandma?
Grandma!
Ryo!
Grandma, where are you?
Grandma!
Ryo!
Ryo, don't worry.
Grandma's with you.
You'll be all right.
Grandma will protect you.
Is that it?
Kurono...?
He's in trouble!
The suit's dead!
Help, now!
Kato?
Kato!
Oh, my God...
Can you hear me?
You'll be OK.
Get 100 points.
What will happen
when I get 100 points?
With 100 points...
you can resurrect me.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Kato!
You're in the way!
I can't move!
Go away!
Me?
Hold it!
That hurts, damn it!
Kei.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Sorry, I was quicker.
Kei.
Kei!
Kei?
Where's Kei?
What's happened to Kei?
What's going on?
You made it.
Am I alive?
"It's time for the score."
"0 points for Kishimoto,
stop staring at Kato."
"0 Points for Kato,
stop being stared at."
What is it evaluating anyway?
"0 points for Suzuki,
where were you?"
"0 points for Shiraishi,
I saw you."
"7 points for Kurono,
making it 7 in total."
7 points.
Wow.
“93 points to go."
Get 100 points.
Gantz...
what happens when I get 100 points?
"Choose from the 100-point menu"
"100-point menu"
"1.Wipe your memory and be released.
2.Resurrect any player you like."
Released...
Dead ones can be brought back to life?
Huh?
It's real.
Hello.
Oh, you answered!
It's me Tae Kojima, from college.
I've never called you before!
Where are you now?
Uh...you know...
Do you read comic books, Kurono?
Sure.
Do you like reading them?
I guess so.
Don't laugh when I tell you this...
but...I draw comics.
What kind?
So? What do you think?
Awesome.
I know girls' comics don't usually
have male heroes!
I chose an ordinary guy like you
to fight evil.
It's like me when I was a kid.
Oh?
It reminds me of my childhood.
I used to protect my friend
from bullies.
Oh, did you?
Yes.
I bumped into him the other day.
I bet he doesn't remember me
protecting him.
You know...
it's a hero's duty to fight evil.
Anybody who's scared can run.
I'll protect them all.
Here's your coat.
You met my brother?
Yes, but I didn't talk to him.
I didn't know how to explain
our situation.
Kato...
what's going on in that room?
Are we dead?
Or are we alive?
When I woke up in the room
I thought I'd finally died.
For a while...
death seemed a good option.
But now I want to live.
Because I met you, Kato.
So you saved me.
- That's why...
- I...
I was in juvenile detention.
I killed my own father.
My father...
He was drunk every day
and beat my brother.
I wanted to save him...
but I failed.
I couldn't be there for him.
I always want to be around
to protect my brother.
Sorry, I got carried away.
Let me walk you home.
There was a fire early this morning
at a Shinagawa parking complex.
It's thought that leaking petrol
caught fire,
but the details are still
under investigation.
Similar cases of destruction
have been reported in Tama City
and other suburbs.
The police suspect a connection...
You look tired.
Why don't you take a day off?
Maybe I should get a job, too.
Don't be silly,
you should be studying.
Something's bothering you.
There's nothing.
OK, I've been having
nightmares recently...
with lots of people dying.
They all get killed,
but I can't do anything to help them.
I can't save any of them.
Lucky it's just a dream.
You're right.
Speaking of dreams,
I had a dream recently
that you disappeared.
But I'd be OK. You're the one
who'd be in trouble.
You can't cook.
Ayumu.
I won't go anywhere.
I won't disappear.
I know you won't.
Give it here.
I believe
that each of us has a role in life.
We all have something
unique to offer.
And there's a place where
we can maximize our abilities.
Here it comes!
Here I go!
Ayumu.
I will come back for you.
Is it happening again?
Yes.
Listen to me carefully.
This is where the selection is made.
Will you go to heaven?
Or will you burn in hell
for infinity?
Merciful Buddha watches us
and decides our destiny.
"Ill-tempered Alien. He's enormous
and likes peace and quiet."
You aren't dead yet.
Join our fight so we all survive.
I'll tell you what I know.
First put on the suit
that's in the case.
We've already experienced this.
You're going to have to fight,
like it or not.
Shut up!
Don't be tempted by his words!
The Lord says this man
is the devil's advocate.
You have to trust me
in order to survive!
Put the suit on now!
Kato.
Don't waste your time!
Newcomers won't get it.
Don't you want to help them?
Yes, so I'll go alone.
You'll die like the kid!
I'm different from him.
Don't worry. I'll protect you, too.
I just don't want
to see any more deaths!
Kato.
Are you serious?
Maybe you just want
to get out of here.
No!
I know you.
You're a hypocrite.
That's not true!
This isn't something
for a guy from juvie.
Come on.
Let me go.
Kato.
There's no time for this.
No way...
Where is Hitomi?
She was with me a minute ago.
You want to put the suit on?
You can trust that guy.
This is cool.
We're in Ueno Park.
It's so realistic.
That's it.
That's the one we saw on the orb.
It's our target?
Listen very carefully.
Something unbelievable and horrifying
is about to happen.
If we cooperate, we can all survive.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What the hell?
Run!
Come on!
Surround him and shoot!
Kei, out of the way!
This sucker is mine.
Damn!
Kei, step aside!
Help everyone evacuate!
- But Kei...!
- I'll finish him off!
You can't!
I've got him!
Out of my way!
I nailed it, didn't I?
That was not good.
- We lost our guy.
- That one's your fault.
Next time make sure
everyone evacuates.
I'll take care of the bad guy.
How come we're not returning?
It hurts.
Is she dead?
There's another one.
Kurono, behind you!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Thousand-Armed Buddha...
Shit!
I'll go.
You'll get killed!
- You're hurt.
- I can do it.
It's just like when we were kids.
You were my hero.
I always wanted to be like you.
But...
..you're right, Kei.
Maybe I do just want
to get out of this place.
I'm just a hypocrite.
Look after Kei for me.
Kato!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
You attacked us first.
You killed my friends.
I will avenge their deaths.
Go, Kato, now!
Kato.
You have Ayumu.
Go back to him.
Kato!
Kato...
I will avenge their deaths.
You will die.
Your people will die.
I will destroy everything.
Kei!
Kato!
I can do this.
I know I can.
Kei...
Oh, my God.
Kato.
Kato, it's finished.
I knew you'd be the hero.
Kato.
Pull yourself together.
We're going back now.
Thank you, Kei.
I can go back to Ayumu...
I can...
Kato...
Hey, Gantz, hurry up!
Kato, don't die on me!
I'll be waiting for you!
"It is time for the scores."
Hold on a minute...
Kato's not here yet.
"13 points for Kurono,
getting a total of 20."
"80 points to go."
Gantz...
Show me the casualties.
Give him back!
Give Kato back to me!
"100-point menu"
"1.Wipe your memory and be released.
2.Resurrect any player you like."
I have to keep fighting
to resurrect him?
You want me to fight
until I get 100 points?
That's insane.
Hi.
I drew the next part of the story.
Sorry, not today.
I'm not in the mood to read it.
Well...um...
Did something happen?
I showed you my comic artwork
the other day,
and...
Kurono.
You said you liked it.
But you were acting strangely.
You scared me a little.
I know when you're not yourself
because I watch you.
I guess it sounds creepy
if I watch you...
I'm sorry.
You must think I'm weird.
Hey, watch out!
My cap!
No, the train is coming soon.
Honey, the train's coming.
Oh, no...
I want my cap!
The train's coming.
Thank you.
Thank the nice man, darling.
The express service will not stop
at platform 2.
Please stand back
as the train approaches.
Kurono?
Come on, get up from there!
Kurono!
Don't die!
Sorry.
I like you.
I like you. I care about you.
So please...
Please don't die.
Brother?
Ayumu?
Yes?
I believe
that each of us
has a role in life.
We all have something unique
to offer. And...
there's a place where
we can maximize our abilities.
Those with talents and gifts
have to make an effort.
They're obliged to fulfil
their potential.
I want to come back alive...
to my girlfriend.
If someone's waiting for you...
We'll go home alive.
Mind if I follow you?
You make me believe
that I can do it.
We are not dead.
Get 100 points...
and the dead ones...
will come back to life.
"100-point menu"
"1.Wipe your memory and be released.
2.Resurrect any player you like."
So please trust me.
Let's fight together.
Rise and shine,
it's a new morning for us
A morning of new hope
Breathe in, a chest full of joy
Look up at the clear, blue sky!
Listen to the radio
The summer breeze
is so wholesome
Breathe in and exercise now
To the count of one, two and three!
Let's go.
There's a rumour
of a black orb
in a mysterious room.
Not everybody can go.
Gantz is acting up.
Out of battery?
He's the one who killed me!
Long time.
Kei.
Now
Mystery
Unveils
Transport me now.
Gantz!
The Last Alien
The Last Target
The Last Mission
The Last Choice
The Only Choice
An Ultimate Choice to be Made
There must be a better choice...
Witness the Perfect Answer!