Do you believe in the afterlife?
Do you believe ghosts are real?
Have you ever proven that your beliefs
aren't just nonsense
or just superstitions?
I'd like you all
to meet two important people
who will change your beliefs forever.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Damn!
Damn it!
I-- Oh.
Hey, Dr. "I'm not afraid
of ghosts," you screamed so loud.
I didn't say I wasn't afraid.
I said I don't believe in them.
Shouldn't you be sleeping
before your shift tonight?
-Yeah, yeah.
-Dr. Gla. Dr. Wee.
-Heard about the ER case the other day?
-No.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Well, there was a third-degree burn case.
He felt slighted by his wife
so he tried to commit suicide by arson.
He was burnt to a crisp when he arrived
and the whole room stank like burnt flesh.
That's right,
plus, something fell on him
and split his head half open.
I heard he wailed and twisted
and turned until he died in his bed.
Damn!
-Update me if you hear more news, Joon.
-Sure.
What news could there be? He died.
Dude, I didn't mean that
sort of news. I meant news
of the paranormal.
You're a surgeon, not a shaman.
That was very funny, Dr. Wee.
Nice clapback.
I have to go now.
Madam's physio should be done.
Dr. Ar-Jong to Room 237. Stat.
"Ar-Jong" again!
Dr. Ar-Jong to Room 237.
It's "Arj-Ong."
They keep calling me "Ar-Jong."
Shitheads.
They do it in meetings too.
Just embrace your first-year nickname.
I've had it since preschool, actually.
OK.
Are you ready, Dr.--
"Ar-Jong"?
Very funny.
RATANARAJ HOSPITAL
Hi.
Did the physio see you today?
Hmm?
Do you feel better?
-Are you tired?
-Hey, Gla.
Oh, hey, Mai.
What's up?
Hey, how long
has Wee's mom been at the hospital?
Seven years? Eight?
He studied medicine
because of his mom's illness.
His paycheck
goes back to her hospital bills.
This is like his home now.
So,
need a doctor, cutie?
Of course I do.
I feel a sharp pain in my heart
as if my partner's got no time for me.
Want to get food?
Let's go.
Mom, do you want me to read
you something before bedtime?
Or are you too tired?
I see. You want to sleep right now? OK.
MORGUE
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
-Hey!
-What?
Do you think there are
any ghosts here in the dark?
How can they exist?
Just think.
CERN's machines can detect
particles from outer space,
but they've never detected any ghosts.
But are ghosts particles?
The things you see are just photons
that strike your eyes, isn't that right?
Basic science.
Maybe ghosts aren't photons.
Maybe they're energy or matter
that CERN scientists don't know about yet.
Like the platypus.
Before the discovery
of the platypus,
no one thought mammals could lay eggs.
You even believe
that aliens are real, duh!
Hey.
There are good reasons to support that.
Life-forms can live on planets
with water, heavy elements, etc.
What other energy is there
besides the law of physics?
The power of love.
Hey, dude.
Are you really gonna ignore Joon?
Our hospital doesn't have
many beautiful nurses.
When you were giving orders back there,
I saw her looking at you, smitten.
I have to look after Madam.
I have no time for anyone else.
Whoa. Get some real food
if you're that hungry.
You want snacks or you want me
to kick your ass? Help me carry these.
Wow. You're so mean these days.
Gla.
Damn you, Gla. Hey.
Wow, you're really committing to the bit.
Excuse you. Save these pranks
for the ladies. They won't work on me.
Hey.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
A ghost!
Damn it. Wee!
Shit! Did you see what I saw?
Wee, you saw that, right?
An actual ghost, damn it!
A real ghost!
Oh my God!
Damn it!
Wee, you saw it too?
An actual ghost, damn it. A real ghost!
Maybe we were hallucinating.
Identical hallucinations?
That's impossible.
I don't get it.
There's no way to explain this.
Want to find a way?
MEDICAL OFFICE BUILDING,
RATANARAJ HOSPITAL
Why are we at this old place?
It's an employee housing building.
This is all storage.
-Ouch!
-Whoa.
It's a damn birdhouse.
Does no one clean up here?
I asked Namo to let me
use this room for my research.
I like this place.
No cameras here.
It's convenient.
You need a camera-free zone
for pediatric intestine research?
NORTHERN LIGHTS QUEST
What did you want to show me?
I'm researching ghosts.
I'm sure these videos and photos online…
are all fake.
I understand
that in the past,
images of ghosts were rare. Makes sense.
But now, cameras are everywhere.
Even security cameras.
So why can't they record
any clear videos of ghosts?
The conclusion is
cameras can't record ghosts, damn it.
That movie Shutter is bullshit.
GHOSTS = ?
DESERTED CEMETERIES
DESERTED WAREHOUSES
Hey. What is this shit?
Ghost research?
Are you insane?
In second grade, my dad died.
One night, after the wake,
I came downstairs.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Though I only saw him for a split second,
I'm confident
that it was him.
Since I saw Dad's ghost
over 20 years ago,
I've always wondered about ghosts.
It's my life now.
Last night,
we both saw a ghost.
I'm really sure
Dad came to me back then.
It's like the questions
I've asked my whole life
are now answered.
Just think.
If I found a way
for others to see ghosts like we did…
what would happen?
I believe I was born to prove
ghosts are real.
I'm in.
Experiment log number 38,
16th May, 2019.
We have big news
about the Northern Lights Quest.
"Northern Lights Quest"?
It's inspired by ancient Inuit people.
They believed
the Northern Lights were departed souls
communicating with the living.
Well, say something, Dr. Specs.
Right. Well…
-Just talk.
-What's so funny? OK--
Hello, I'm Cheewee.
N-- Next,
the two of us
will try to prove the existence of
and find answers about ghosts--
It will be one of
the most important discoveries. Like--
Sir Isaac Newton's laws of gravity--
Franklin's electricity or--
Einstein's Theory of Relativity.
Our work
must be published in The Experiment,
the world's most famous research journal.
What research did you do
in the past four or five years?
I did field research.
So tell me what you saw.
I interviewed everyone…
You mean ghosts?
I saw it over there and I got goosebumps.
…who saw ghosts.
Here?
I performed every superstitious ritual
to try and see ghosts.
I went to famous haunted places like
a cemetery in Kanchanaburi,
the House of Four Corpses in Chonburi,
an abandoned prison in Vietnam,
a haunted house in Korea,
the Suicide Forest in Japan.
I went to all the famous spots.
But I never saw ghosts anywhere.
Patients die here every day.
I've looked at all
the reported ghost sighting sites.
But I never saw any ghosts. Not until…
We both saw one by the vending machine.
How do you find time for this?
What do you think I do
while you look after Madam?
And if I'd told you,
you'd have said I was mad.
If cameras can't record ghosts,
there's only one way to prove
ghosts are real. All we can do…
is make people see them like we did.
First, we'll have to find
some mechanisms or scenarios
to control the ghosts' appearance.
APPEARANCE TRIGGER, PROOF, PUBLIC
To date, I've seen ghosts
just twice and you've seen one just once.
We need to see more
to find out what makes them appear.
OK.
So first, we need to…
FIND GHOSTS AS PARTICIPANTS
Alright. Good night, babe.
Why not tell Mai about this?
There's no point.
Hey, it's past 3 a.m. already.
Is her condo near here?
If you're sleepy,
go get some sleep. I'll stay here.
We've been here over a week now.
We've seen nothing.
It's not working.
Let's try something else.
A new method.
It's the wind.
Shit.
Damn! Wee!
We were so focused on visible ghosts,
but there are other kinds.
For example, poltergeists are invisible.
What are poltergeists?
Some of my interviewees
said they saw
objects moving, heard strange noises,
and often felt
the temperature suddenly drop.
This past week,
I looked at the hospital's CCTV
and found these images.
Hold on. It's crashed.
Come on.
You go first.
-Are you scared?
-I told you to go first.
It's so dark. Turn on the light.
Will it scare the ghosts away?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
-Damn it.
-Hey!
-Sorry.
-Dumbass!
-What?
-Watch your step, jackass!
You made me hold
all this. You're holding one thing.
Which way now?
-Left.
-Sure. You go first.
Hey.
Why's the wheelchair here?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Shit.
Hey!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Shit!
-Hey!
-It--
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What's the temperature?
Unnatural, don't you think?
This time,
we're one step closer to ghosts.
We witnessed energy
and temperature fluctuation.
But our videos are no better than
those that have been shared online.
Our evidence isn't solid yet.
I need to review my interviews.
I may learn more.
Gla, you can do it later, man.
Dr. Gla.
Are you alright?
-Stop the bleeding.
-Apply pressure.
Someone get Dr. Namo in here stat.
Immediately, please!
You messed up
the tracheotomy. You nicked the thyroid.
Do better, top student.
Your late-night research is your business.
But you should know
that doctors' stupid mistakes
cost patients' lives.
Yes.
Certainly. Thank you so much.
Gla.
-Hmm?
-I have bad news.
Listen,
in December,
I have to oversee
a condo project in Pattaya.
Can we postpone
our Northern Lights trip to, like,
around next February?
-Oh.
-Hmm?
If that's convenient.
Hey! Wait a minute.
Are you being smooth?
You forgot about our trip?
I can tell. I know you.
Sorry, babe.
I hardly see you now.
It's fine.
When you're obsessed with work,
it's so terribly sexy.
I have to go.
Sure.
I'm going now.
-Bye-bye.
-Bye-bye, babe.
FIND GHOSTS AS PARTICIPANTS,
APPEARANCE TRIGGER, PROOF
Your platypus story gave me an idea.
-Tell me, how do we classify animals?
-What? Why?
How do we group them?
We use criteria.
Some are vertebrates.
Some lay eggs. Some don't.
-The number of legs varies.
-How might we classify ghosts?
Have you noticed that when we saw ghosts,
we knew some of them,
but some of them were strangers?
-We knew some.
-Uh-huh.
-Like my dad.
-That's right.
The burn victim was a stranger to us.
KNOWN VS UNKNOWN
Just think.
Unknown ghosts.
Why do they appear to us?
-I don't know, man.
-Exactly. We don't know. It's dumb luck.
Consider the known ghosts.
Why did your dad's ghost come to you?
Maybe he missed me or wanted to see me.
If we focus on ghosts we know,
we'll know where
and with whom to go find them.
We could try
observing someone
whose relative or lover has recently died.
The only problem is…
who'd let us do that all night?
Especially if they know
we're researching ghosts!
We can't do that.
Here's another way.
Don't be afraid.
Alright?
I know this girl,
a first-year student who's
in the final stage of cancer.
I heard she's single.
Imagine that.
She's never dated and she's dying.
But if you or I
become her first and only boyfriend,
when she's gone,
she'll surely come back to us.
Are we going too far?
Fooling a dying person for our experiment?
I think we'd be crossing the line.
So what?
She gets some love
before she dies. We get a participant. So,
win-win, right? Wee?
That feeling when we saw the ghost…
The universe opened
its door of secrets to us.
My curiosity's unstoppable now.
Hello?
What?
The brain can survive
without oxygen for three minutes.
without oxygen for three minutes…
I resuscitated her.
She's still unresponsive.
Mucus blocked
her airway awhile before we arrived.
No oxygen reached her brain
for seven minutes. You have to choose.
-Hey!
-Hey, Wee!
Mom…
do you remember…
the robot you bought me when I was a kid?
One day, I threw it a bit too hard,
and after that, it couldn't walk anymore.
Back then, you said
that it couldn't walk…
because it was broken inside…
and we'd be able to fix it.
But…
I know what's wrong with you,
so why can't I help you at all?
So you're sure
the afterlife's real?
Do you want to go now, Mom?
Am I torturing you here?
I believe
that it's real.
I'll let you go, Mom.
Please come back to see me.
There's no new patient here yet,
so I installed a camera
to capture any weird movements.
And tonight,
I think I should be by Wee's side.
Mom?
Mom!
Mom seemed to be saying
something, but I couldn't tell what.
I saw her crying.
Did I make the wrong choice?
Maybe the truth is
she didn't want me to let her go.
After that day,
Mom never let me see her again.
I have so many questions in my head,
I feel like I'm drowning.
So I decided to do PHQ-9, fMRI,
as well as blood and urine lab tests
for chemical imbalances.
We found nothing.
That means
I'm not depressed
because of what happened.
Therefore, my decision
isn't influenced by anything else.
I will cross over.
"Cross over"? To where?
I'll die and go to the other side,
and I'll come back
to do the experiment with you.
Dude. Chill, man.
It's what we need
for our experiment to continue.
Even if the cancer patient fell for you,
even if she came to you,
how much could you experiment with her?
She could disappear
in an instant like your dad.
She doesn't know our experiment
like us or understand what we're doing.
Only I can come back for our experiment.
Snap out of it.
You're upset about your mom.
You're just depressed, so you're suicidal.
Wee, listen to me, damn it.
You lost your mom,
but you didn't lose everything.
-You still have so much to do.
-Like what?
Huh?
What's left to do?
Why care if I die?
You're my friend!
And you're my friend too.
I'm doing your experiment.
Since we saw that ghost together,
and my mom came back to see me,
I'm not afraid of the afterlife anymore.
In this world,
there's no one left for me to worry about.
I just want to see my mom.
I wanna know what she said.
You're the one who told me
"the universe has opened
its door of secrets to us"
and you expect me to do nothing?
It's not unusual, Gla.
Lots of scientists trade
their lives for discoveries.
Didn't you say so yourself?
That you were born to do this?
This is it! This is how you prove it!
You don't understand shit!
I got you into this!
How can I let you die?
Think it through.
I can't let you die for this!
Don't stop me!
You'll get a participant.
I'll get to see my mom.
Win-win, yeah?
Just admit it.
This is the only way
our experiment can continue.
If someone must die,
it will be me.
What the hell?
Fine, I admit it.
Yeah, you're right.
This is the only way we can continue.
But I started this project.
-This crucial task should be mine!
-You're talking shit. I volunteer!
I volunteer too!
I will die
for the research I started.
I have that right too!
So let's make it fair.
If it's heads,
I'll go.
If it's tails,
you'll go.
Whatever the result is,
you'll accept it.
I thought it through.
I'll write a suicide note.
I'll say I got depressed
after my mom died.
You'll just pretend you found my body.
Forensics will say
that I killed myself for sure.
Just keep our experiment secret
so the cops won't bother us.
I'll wait on the other side to see
our names on that front cover.
A free solo mountain climber,
or a climber who uses
bare hands and no cables or safety gear,
has fatally fallen off a cliff
attempting to set a new record
by climbing at Yosemite National Park
in the US state of California.
Why do people do this stuff?
What do they get from it?
Is it worth dying for?
Experiment log number 65,
23rd August, 2019.
Every life has an ending.
But what
are we going to use that ending for?
True science
is the journey from ignorance
to knowledge,
from stupidity to wisdom,
from mystery to enlightenment.
My journey today
will bring us closer to
the truth of the universe.
This video clip will record
my entire journey to the other side.
Dr. Arjong Soonyata
will conduct the research on this side.
If I don't return soon,
Dr. Ar-Jong may have to work harder.
I think
it's time
for us to begin our journey.
I don't know what it'll be like there.
But I will do everything
to make contact with you.
And you have to do
everything you can to contact me too.
I swear I will, man.
I won't stop until you get back,
until we succeed.
Shit!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I was born to prove ghosts are real.
I'm in.
Our work must be published
in the most famous research journal.
I'll wait on the other side to see
our names on that front cover.
Come back to me, Mom.
What are you two doing, honey?
Mom!
I can't do it.
I really can't. My mom, she…
I'm sorry.
It's OK, man.
I'll come back.
-Doctor, it's your cue.
-Alright.
Have you ever proven
that your beliefs aren't just nonsense
or just superstitions?
Ready?
I'd like you all to meet
two important people
who will change your beliefs forever.
Do you believe in the afterlife?
And spirits? What do you think they are?
I, Dr. Cheewee Prometheus,
and Dr. Arjong Soonyata,
our key research participant,
are standing side by side right now.
We'll now present our results
as seen in the world-class journal,
The Experiment.
You are the first group to witness this.
Are you ready,
Dr. Ar-Jong?
It doesn't work!
Dr. Cheewee,
I'm happy for… your success.
But for this discovery,
which you say is so amazing,
were you really willing
to sacrifice a person's life?
Do you even have a heart?
You let your friend kill himself
for an experiment
you don't know will succeed or not.
You're not the researcher
or scientist you think you are.
You're a murderer.
Mai.
Hey. No!
NO CONTACT
ON-CALL ROOM SUICIDE!
WHY DID DOC SHOOT SELF?
DOC KILLS SELF IN HAUNTED HOSPITAL!
TRAGIC DOC'S MOTIVE UNKNOWN
I tried everything I could
to stop Wee's thoughts.
I never thought of this method.
But once he said it,
my heart started beating hard.
I felt…
Damn!
Is this the solution we seek?
I'll come back.
I'm sorry.
Come back now.
Gla donated his body
to the hospital for educational purposes…
DR. ARJONG
…to benefit others.
But the monk said
that suicide is a grave sin.
I'm doing everything
to make him pure like anyone else.
Wee, do you think
what I'm doing
will help Gla find peace, sweetheart?
Thank you, Wee.
I'll bring it all to his mom.
Could you think it over again?
Why would Gla do this?
I really don't know.
I'm sorry.
Not knowing anything
really freaking hurts.
It's like I meant nothing to him.
Shit!
Whoa! Shit!
Jackass!
You're back, asshole?
It's you, right?
Gla!
Gla?
You're here?
You're back? Why can't I see you?
Why don't you show yourself to me?
Maybe… you can't show yourself yet.
Communicate.
Make sounds. Or--
Or do whatever you can.
Do your poltergeist shit.
Hey… you're communicating with me, right?
Why can't you communicate more?
I was falling and you pulled me back!
Hold on.
You saved me when I was falling?
Let me guess.
What boosts your power
is me being in danger, right?
If I put myself at risk again,
will it boost your energy again?
I'm a surgeon.
Save my finger, OK?
Dr. Wee?
Shit.
Please sign the schedule.
I called but you didn't pick up.
Alright.
Shit!
Is my hypothesis correct?
Is my idea right?
Ghost participant
found. You're back.
Next, we need to find
a way for you to appear.
So do you know what ghosts are now?
Gla's return doesn't answer
all the questions we're asking,
but we've learned a lot.
First of all, Gla can't see other ghosts.
How about there? Can you see anything?
Secondly,
he only sees what's around me.
He says that before this, he saw nothing,
until I jumped.
Suddenly, he saw me and saved me.
It's like something connects
me to Gla, who's in the afterlife.
That means the soul's power increases
when triggered by something.
In our case,
Gla was worried about me being in danger.
Let's say ghosts are natural phenomena.
If ghosts are like wind…
Wind, initially, can't be seen, right?
But add air pressure
to wind and you get a storm,
which can increase in both speed and size.
And then,
when that mixes with water vapor,
it creates an electric charge. Finally,
we will see…
the shape of an actual storm. I believe
that if I can boost your power like this,
you'll be able to appear for sure, man.
"Weird"? How are my thoughts weird?
"Beach"?
No beach pictures in here.
Where do you see a beach?
Gone already?
W-- What stupid beach
are you talking about?
Aunt Koy?
This picture…
Where was this?
Oh, that was taken in Ranong.
It's Gla's hometown.
When his dad passed away,
I moved back to Bangkok.
You said you wanted to talk to me
about Gla.
What is it?
Well…
I saw Gla in a dream.
He told me to tell you something.
He said…
he's still around.
He can't be reborn yet.
What do I need to do?
Did he tell you?
I guess suicide is a very serious sin.
I'm afraid that he's going to
carry on as a wandering ghost.
I got goosebumps.
Wee, do you feel it too?
-I do.
-Maybe Gla is here somewhere.
Mom.
Excuse me, Wee.
What you're saying is upsetting my mom.
Plus, you're a doctor. You aren't
supposed to believe in this stuff?
I'm just worried for Gla.
What you said…
don't you think it hurts Gla?
He might be here with us now.
That's nonsense.
You're only hurting my mom more.
You should leave.
Please go.
-Gift.
-Hush, Mom.
"Kha Kai."
I just remembered.
In my dream, Gla said, "Kha Kai."
"Chicken legs"?
I don't get it either,
but he really said, "Kha Kai."
Wee.
Do stay for dinner.
Gla loved my Kha Kai curry.
Oh.
He meant curry.
He must want me to offer alms for him,
so he told you.
Whoa.
Wow. Your cooking is amazing, Aunt Koy.
You could open your own restaurant.
That's what Gla said too.
Gla complimented me.
He said my curry was so good
that I could run a restaurant.
I didn't buy that.
So he dared me. He said
he'd have you come to taste it.
He said you'd say the same thing.
Gla said that I'm not confident…
that I think I'm not good at anything.
He said, "But
if that's true,
how did you raise your kids alone?"
He said, "You raised a doctor, right?"
"Compared to that, Kha Kai is so easy."
"Why won't you believe
you're a great cook?"
Thank you, Wee.
Now I understand
what Gla wanted to tell me.
The curry brought your mom peace.
Did you derail my experiment on purpose?
You know the plan.
I'm trying to make you worry
as much as I can. It worked, see?
I understand
if you don't like me doing this.
But it's for the experiment.
Right now?
So is this the beach
in Ranong, your hometown?
Hey, Gla!
Gla! Hey!
Damn it, Gla!
Gla has been missing for three days.
Is this normal?
Does every spirit have this phase?
Or maybe he left
because he's consoled his mom.
WORLD OF THE LIVING
GLA
Or is the beach another world
the dead have to
cross to, like how some folks say
"the dead go to find peace."
Come back.
Three…
two…
one!
Wee. If you have any problems
or stress, you can tell me.
Or the hospital
has professionals who can help--
Meaning what?
A nurse says you tried
this once before. Is it true?
Who maims themselves?
-So is it true?
-I can handle it. I don't need help.
Shit.
Oh, hi, Mai.
Why are you here?
I came to see you
to ask you this.
The day I returned Gla's stuff,
his laptop was missing.
The one with the red cover.
It's not at his mom's place
and the cops didn't take it.
Have you seen it?
I haven't.
I'll look for it and let you know ASAP.
OK. I understand.
I have to go.
Mai.
Gla chose to do what he did.
Looking for answers
is putting you through pain.
So can you stand it?
Wondering and never knowing?
Shit.
How'd you get in?
-Let me explain--
-About hiding Gla's laptop?
-Mai--
-Explain to the cops.
Mai, no! Hey! Mai, wait.
Mai, listen to me first.
I found his laptop
two days ago, in the trunk of my car.
Earlier, I had to lie about not finding it
because you made it sound like
the laptop was evidence. That scared me.
I swear I knew nothing about it.
I want to know Gla's story too.
But his laptop is locked.
I can't get in.
Hey. We've tried for almost an hour.
We've gotten nowhere.
It'll be easier to hire an expert.
I know this friend
with IT qualifications.
Should I ask them?
Sure.
Alright. I'll take it to my friend ASAP.
You think I'm that stupid?
You're lying.
People like Gla
never just suddenly kill themselves.
I was his girlfriend.
I knew him the best.
I've been his friend for longer.
So what now?
Do I have to just accept it?
That all this time
I didn't know Gla at all?
I should have known
what Gla was thinking.
The night
before he killed himself, I was with him.
I was with him in this room.
I should have known what he was thinking.
Why didn't he tell me
that something was wrong?
Or maybe
he tried to tell me,
but I didn't listen.
Didn't I pay attention or…
What was wrong?
Was I such an awful girlfriend?
Was I so shitty that I didn't know
what was wrong with my boyfriend?
What was wrong?
Breathe, Mai.
I mean, look.
Even my boyfriend's password.
-I don't even know it, shit!
-Mai.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
It's alright.
I'll take this to my friend.
We might unlock it tonight.
What the fuck, man?
Didn't we agree
that no one could know about the research?
If Mai finds out,
she'll tell someone for sure.
What happens to it then? Do you care?
You were MIA so long.
You came back to tell your girl the truth?
I called for you, remember?
Why didn't you come?
Do you still care about what we're doing?
Huh?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Forget her!
Let her feel guilty. It won't kill her.
Whoa!
Shit!
Hello? Can anyone hear me?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
The elevator's stuck
on the 13th floor. Please help me.
Hello? Can anyone hear me?
Shit.
It's hot.
So you'll tell me the truth about Gla?
You found out more?
Yep.
I asked you to meet me here
so you could see for yourself.
You'll understand it all.
I have to go and prepare something.
I'll be back.
At Mai's condo yesterday,
I learned of another way
to boost the spirit's power.
ENERGY = WORRIES
ENERGY = WORRIES / VENGEANCE
Oh! Wow! I thought
that you weren't coming back anymore!
How's the beach?
Huh?
Experiment log number 103.
I decided to redesign
the experiment again.
This time, I'm sure that it will succeed.
So close now.
I'm this close to making the ghost appear.
Hey!
You said it yourself.
You want Mai to know
about the experiment. Look!
I got her to participate.
Isn't this good?
You want this, right?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hey!
Deep down, you know, right?
The truth is
I like Mai too.
Oh, right.
I forgot that you're dead.
Shit. Sorry, man.
You mind if I take Mai
for myself?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Where are you?
Tell me.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Where are you?
So close. We're this close.
GHOSTS = ?
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Hey!
Gla!
You can show yourself now.
Can you hear me?
We succeeded, damn it!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hell yeah, we're on the right track!
Shit.
Experiment log
number 104.
The results show that…
using his girlfriend
to trigger negative emotions…
made the spirit of Dr. Arjong…
show his true form for the first time.
This is our first time
seeing his "Northern Lights."
Fuck you, Gla!
Not so hard!
Now I know what to do.
Now, if you wanna expose the truth
or deal with someone,
I'll set it up. Maybe next time,
I'll get your sis--
Hey!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hey--
You can get back in your body?
Damn, this is
even more than we expected.
If I can keep you
in this form for everyone to see…
Our experiment is coming together!
I must film this.
Let me record this.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Wasn't it you who told me…
"If we really want the truth,
we must cross the line"?
When you shot yourself…
you didn't even think
of your mom, or Gift,
or even Mai at all!
You really want to go
to your beloved  beach?
I won't let you.
We've come this far already.
I have to finish it.
Whatever shit I must do,
I will do it!
Whoa!
How did we get to this point?
Gla.
I've become a monster.
And I'm turning you into one too.
Wee.
Thanks, man.
You kept your word.
Now you must stop.
No way, Gla.
If you don't stop,
what other evil things
will you do for the experiment?
But we've come this far already.
We're almost there.
To reach this point,
what did you have to sacrifice?
I've hurt enough people around me.
Everything must stop here.
Are you telling me
to let you die for free?
Wee…
you did your best for me…
for your mom,
and for this experiment.
You don't have to feel guilty anymore.
I have to go now.
My journey goes on.
Damn you, Gla!
Gla!
Sir, everything that happened
was caused by his severe emotional trauma.
after the loss of his mother
and his friend's suicide.
I know you want to protect your resident.
But the Council must investigate.
He may never practice again.
In my first year, I once asked Gla
why he was so fascinated with science.
He told me
that every day we live
is like a science experiment.
We set hypotheses
and our expectations.
We try to control the variables.
Some are controllable. Some aren't.
Sometimes what's been done
is almost completely ruined.
Whatever the result is…
we still learn something from it,
more or less.
NORTHERN LIGHTS QUEST
I got the laptop unlocked.
Mai, listen…
That night--
Wee. You don't have to say anything.
I talked to Namo.
I know. Back then,
you weren't really emotionally stable.
And maybe…
I wasn't in my right mind yet either.
You know what?
The night I fell asleep in your office,
I think…
Gla came to see me.
In my dream,
we were at the seaside.
But I don't know where exactly.
In my dream, I didn't say anything to him.
Just seeing him happy
was enough to make me so happy.
Hey, Wee.
In my dream,
Gla was holding this magazine.
On the cover was a photo of you two.
Wee.
I'm jealous of you.
You still have a chance.
Live your life for the both of us.
I think he's right.
We just have to learn from it.
As long as we live,
we must continue
our experiments until the end.
Subtitle translation by: Karina Suvapataya