Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Wait! Don't!
Hey, I told you
to stop doing that!
Oh, yeah, cos I listen to you.
What do we think
of this place?
Yeah, I like this place.
Yeah? You reckon
we could stay here?
Maybe.
Tide's on the move.
We'd better head back.
Good one for the blog.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh, my God.
There was something there.
There was something
right there!
- Nothing there.
- Something right there!
I don't see anything.
There's nothing here.
- There was something right there!
- Baby, there's nothing there.
I literally just saw something!
Tracy! Trace!
- Calm down. I believe you, OK?
- OK.
- I believe you.
- Let's just get back, alright?
- OK. OK.
Nice and calm, OK? Come on.
Come on, baby.
Luke, hurry up!
Oh, fuck.
Luke?
Luke!
No, no, no!
No!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Fuckin' awesome!
Ugh.
If you wanted a rollercoaster
we could've gone
to Dreamworld.
Charlie.
Was just a couple of turns.
- And a chandelle.
- Ah, shit.
You gotta
be kidding me. Why?
You know what,
your mess, you clean it.
Alright?
Well, technically,
it wasn't my mess.
Hey, I thought
you were the nurse.
Triage nurse, Charlie. Triage.
Piss bottles and puke bags
are not on my radar.
He threw up on the microphone.
Well, don't put it there!
Bathroom. Come on.
Gonna have to
change the plugs soon.
She's starting
to run a bit rough on idle.
OK. And?
I think that's
enough work for today.
Y'know, there's a couple
of beers in there
with our names on 'em.
You know I'm mad at you, right?
Doesn't look like it.
So...
the bank called again today.
Mm.
I told them
that you would call them back
when you landed.
Come on.
You want me to charm them
into an extra few weeks' grace?
Yeah, well, I would love that
but we can't
keep doing that forever.
I can.
We can't.
If we do, they're gonna
cut off our line of credit
and then
we can't run our business.
You can be so damn
practical sometimes.
Fine, you win.
I'll call them.
Thank you.
What?
Nothing.
You ever think maybe
we should get married?
Hold that thought.
Pearl Air Charter Service.
Yeah. Yeah, we do that.
I'll just have
to check my... my bookings
but when were you thinking?
OK, great.
I can... I can make that work.
Have you been on the website?
Great.
Great. OK.
If you could just give me
your email address.
Yep.
Perfect. Well, I'll flick you
a note to confirm
and we'll see you tomorrow.
- Tomorrow?
- Yeah!
Hell's Reef. Lunch on the reef.
The whole enchilada!
- Tomorrow?
- Yeah, midday.
Hey.
It's OK. This is good.
Hey. They're here.
- That's a nice car.
- Fancy.
Alright, let's go.
"Minase."
I thought he was Italian.
Hi, there.
Kaz Fellows.
Welcome to the Pearl Coast,
Mr Minase.
Joji,
but everyone calls me "Jo."
Thank you.
My wife, Michelle.
- Hi.
- Hi. This is Charlie.
You two spoke
on the phone yesterday.
Ah, yes, of course.
Captain Charlie.
"CC." Like the chips.
- Yeah.
- Nice to meet you.
- You too.
- Uh, so we ready?
We're all set.
Ready when you are.
- Very good.
- Great.
I told you we'd make it
for the 12th.
There's wonderful snorkelling
out there, if you're interested.
Oh, I love it.
Runs in the family.
But we don't get
to the water much.
No. I'll just sit on the beach
and if there's a cold beer
in my hand, I'll be happy.
Now, that I can guarantee.
Alright. Well, come on.
I'll show you round.
Oh, wonderful.
We're just
loading everything up.
- Watch your step right here.
- Oh, thank you.
- Oh.
You first.
- Here we go, eh?
- Yeah.
Um, how long?
90 minutes cruising.
Arrive in time for a late lunch.
Excellent.
I hope you're not expecting
anything too rough?
I'm not a great flyer.
I make sure all my passengers
have a good flight.
Is he coming?
Benny's our cook.
As long as that's all he does.
You guys good back there?
Yes, we are.
Keep your eyes open,
you might see a whale.
Or a shark.
- Shark?
- Great white.
You don't wanna go swimming
with one of them, eh, Jo?
Benny.
Unlikely.
It's the wrong time of year.
- You sure?
- Oh, yeah.
He's sure.
Charlie here trained
as a marine biologist.
He was a good one.
I thought so too
until the shark
took a bite out of me.
Here we go.
- Really? What happened?
- Darling, please.
He may not want
to talk about it, y'know.
Bring back bad memories.
No. No, no, it's fine.
Doesn't worry me.
I was researching
black-tipped reef sharks
and their pack-hunting skills.
They're damn good at it.
One day, I was out on my own,
first mistake
and one grabbed me
from behind, spat me out.
Never saw it coming.
Second mistake,
not paying attention.
Luckily, it was more of
a love bite than a real chomp.
A love bite that put him
in the hospital for two weeks.
Ooh, you'll love this, Joji.
Hey, few years back,
a group of tourists
went on one
of them shark tours...
...when a three-metre shark,
great white
jumped into the back
of the boat...
Scared the hell out of them.
Benny.
It's OK.
Welcome to Hell's Reef.
We made it.
Officially, it's called
"Imperious Reef"
but local divers renamed it
after a pearl lugger
was shipwrecked here on the reef
out there during a storm.
It's actually a crazy story.
Eight crew members
were stranded here for 15 days
with no food and no water.
Only one of them survived, an...
An 18-year-old Japanese diver.
Saeki Morita.
Yeah.
My grandfather.
12th of October, 1951.
You know the story?
Every pearler knows the story.
Saeki's a bit
of a legend around here.
His dying wish was
to be here with his shipmates.
Shall we take a look around?
- Uh...
- Yeah, yeah.
- Go, go. Here.
- Oh. Thanks.
You gonna tell 'em
it's a national park
and they shouldn't
be doing that?
No, I'm not.
Just go help Benny, alright?
Come on, big boy.
Stunning.
I love it out here.
Me too.
Hey, you know how we were, um
talking crazy yesterday
about the idea
of maybe getting married?
I think you should make
an honest man out of me.
Well, I don't know
if that's possible
- but if you were being seri...
- Look!
God, they're beautiful.
Charlie?
Mm?
I'm pregnant.
Wow.
Yeah.
Wow!
Are you gonna say
anything else?
Wow! Are you... are you OK?
I'm fine.
Is that it?
So what now?
I think that we, um...
finish this trip and then...
get married, yeah?
Are you sure?
About being pregnant
or getting married?
No, about me being the father.
You're such a jerk.
I know this...
wasn't planned at all
but are you OK?
I am.
I really am.
It's a surprise,
but an awesome one.
I just don't really know
what we're gonna do, y'know?
With the business and money
and us and a baby...
We'll be fine.
More than fine.
We'll crush it.
Like we always do.
Hey!
- Charlie!
- What's he carrying on about?
Kaz!
What's up, mate?
Yous two need to come with me.
Hey, Michelle.
Are you OK?
No, she's not fucking OK.
Whoa. What is it?
There.
Charlie.
Charlie!
Fuck.
Ah, shit.
We need to get them
outta here, OK?
A shark attacked him?
Yeah.
- Should we tell someone?
- I already did.
The coastguard
are gonna handle it.
It's gotta be
out there somewhere.
What?
Their boat.
She could still be alive.
And out there,
she won't last very long.
She? How do you know
there's anyone else?
We should leave this
to the authorities.
You've got no idea where to look
and the chance of finding
anything is almost zero.
- Yeah, we have to try.
- I wanna get outta here.
- My charter, my call!
- It's not happening, mate.
We've got
45 minutes fuel reserve
so we're gonna put
our eyes on this place.
We'll be at 1,000 feet.
Anyone sees anything,
we'll check it out.
I'm guessing all this shit
went down yesterday
so with the tides and currents
best we can do
is cover the eastern side.
There! Down there!
OK, we're going down.
Gotta take a look.
Yeah.
No.
You can't.
If you get hurt down there,
who flies this plane?
Benny?
Sure.
If anything goes wrong,
bang on the hull.
Loudly.
Come on, Benny.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Benny!
You OK?
Was she attacked?
Shit.
Come on, guys.
Let's get outta here.
You alright?
What's next?
Home.
Come on, Benny, move it.
Yeah. Sweet as.
What the hell was that?
Michelle. Hey. Hey, hey, hey.
- Are you OK?
- Uh...
- Get her out of here!
- C'mon!
Benny! Where's Benny?
- Benny!
- I can't get if off!
- Ow!
- Benny, get the life-raft.
OK, OK. Move. We're done.
This thing'll be on the
bottom in a couple minutes.
- The seatbelt, get it.
- I can't...
OK. Are you OK?
- Are you sure?
- Now, Jo!
I warned you. I told you.
- Get out!
- C'mon, Jo.
Mayday, mayday, mayday!
- Cessna 206 Seaplane...
- Charlie!
We gotta get outta here!
Just grab whatever you can.
Lifejackets, flares, wetsuits
water, whatever.
Mayday! Mayday! Mayday!
Cessna 206 Seaplane, 31417.
15 nautical miles
northeast of Hell's Reef.
Do you read me? Please respond.
Charlie,
we gotta get out now!
Five POBs,
starboard pontoon destroyed.
We're sinking fast.
If you read me,
please respond! Over!
- Get in the raft, Jo!
- I'm not getting in that!
Suit yourself,
but this plane's
gonna be on the bottom
in a minute.
I'm not floating around
with that thing out there!
Jo, please!
Like I said, your choice.
- Put the life jacket on!
- Jo!
Jo, come on!
Hurry up!
Jo!
Come on, Jo!
Yes! Quick!
Come on!
Quick! Grab him!
You're gonna need
a couple of stitches
but it's actually
not that deep.
Sorry.
Thanks, Kaz.
You get a mayday out?
Maybe, I'm not sure.
You're kidding me.
He's not sure.
That shitbox
have a safety beacon?
It's gone with the plane.
We've been attacked.
We're floating around
in this piece of plastic junk
and you're not sure if anyone
knows how fucked we are
or even where we are?
What about the rescue boat?
It's on its way, isn't it?
Shouldn't we wait for them?
They know we're out here.
We're in the current.
By morning,
we'll be 75 Ks from here.
It'll take them days to find us.
And a search plane?
It'll be dark soon.
They won't send a plane
until first light.
We're way off course
and I figure 150K from shore...
150 kilometres?
Our best chance
is to use the current.
It's running for us,
and if we paddle with it
we could make land
by tomorrow afternoon.
If we're not picked up
before then.
Could we go back? To the reef?
Not an option.
Says you.
Yeah.
And what do you gotta say,
mate?
Because all I've seen so far
is a bunch of
pissing and moaning.
What, you got a better idea?
The current is running
at five knots.
Running east, towards the coast.
Hell's Reef is over there,
to the southwest.
We can't paddle against it,
we won't get anywhere.
So we use it get to the coast.
They're the facts,
you're the analyst.
you fucking figure it out.
What about...
it?
Maybe it'll go away.
Maybe the rising temperatures
messed with its season.
Maybe the lack of fish.
So far, so good.
You saw it?
And?
About five metres.
I've seen bigger
back home, though.
How's the arm?
I can paddle.
- You OK?
- Yeah.
You're gonna have
a little bump there
but it's actually not so bad.
Thanks.
I'll live.
Jo hates the water.
Always has.
He almost drowned
when he was a kid.
I had to work on him
just to get him
to come on this trip.
And this happens.
Yeah.
How'd you meet Charlie?
Uh, I was, um...
I was working at the hospital
when he was brought in
after his attack.
It really just amazed me
how calm he was.
Even though
he had almost lost his leg.
That's Charlie for you.
Do you have kids?
No way.
I mean, I'm...
I'm just not ready yet.
I get that.
Kinda feel the same way.
Are you...
Yeah.
When are you due?
In about seven months.
How far do you think we've come?
Maybe 15 Ks.
That's good.
Yeah. Yeah, we're doing OK.
Speak up, Captain.
What are you saying?
I said we've still got
over 130 Ks to go.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What was that?
There.
- There.
- Shark!
Jo!
Sit down, ya numbnut!
Fuck off! Leave us alone.
It's a dolphin.
Jo! Sit down.
Oh, my God.
Fuck, Jo. You scared
the hell out of me!
What?
What if you'd fallen overboard?
Yeah.
Yeah. You're right.
How many more
of these do we have?
That's the last one.
You know sharks, right?
I thought I did.
And like you pointed out,
I'm the investment analyst.
You know what that means?
What it is I do?
I study situations.
Weigh up the odds, and then,
based on the facts
I predict the outcomes.
You say you're
a good marine biologist.
Well, I'm a good,
very good analyst.
A clinical assessment
of our situation, as I see it
is if the shark
is still out there
I'd rate our chances
of all surviving at...
less than 5%.
And that would be
fucking optimistic.
So do you think it's gone?
- I really don't know.
- Bullshit!
You said they're
not normally out here
and that thing is
and it's killing people!
It's not gone.
He knows it, and so does she.
- What do you want from me?
- The fucking truth.
OK.
It's still out there.
And it's close.
Hey.
That's enough.
I can go a while longer.
Give me your hands.
Thank you.
Oh, shit.
Michelle?
I think I dropped the paddle.
What do you mean,
you dropped it?
I-I was paddling
and it just seemed
to come out of my hand.
I'm so sorry.
I got it!
There!
I'm sorry. I'm...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Charlie!
Kaz! Kaz!
- No, no, no, no!
- I'll be fine. I'm fine.
Come on, Kaz.
She's almost there,
she's almost there.
Just there...
Come on, Kaz, come on.
Come on, Kaz.
Son of a bitch.
Kaz! Kaz! Come on, Kaz, move it!
Come on, Kaz! Move it!
Move, Kaz!
Quickly!
Up, up, up!
Here, put these on.
They'll keep you warm.
Thanks.
Here, let me help you
with that...
Take your hands off my wife!
- Back off.
- What'd you say?
Hey, Benny.
I said take that rod
out of your arse
and use it to paddle.
Benny!
What the fuck
is wrong with you?
Benny! Benny!
- Benny...
- Where is he? Benny!
- Benny, come on!
- Come on.
Benny, Benny, come on!
- Steady. Nice.
- Ow, my arm!
- Come on!
- Hey, look at me.
- Come on, Benny.
- Come on, right here.
Right here.
Look at me, Benny. Come on.
- Almost there.
- Got you.
Come on!
Come on, almost there.
Gimme your hand.
Come on, mate.
Let's get you in.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Benny! No!
- Fucking idiot!
- Don't, don't, don't.
- You fucking...
- Don't, don't!
He's not worth it.
Benny.
I had him.
I had his hand.
If I could've just held onto him
a little bit longer
- I think I could have...
- Stop. Stop.
It wasn't your fault.
Hey, Michelle.
Just one mouthful.
Thanks.
If could get close enough...
Its brain's small,
set between the eyes
in the middle of the skull
which is pretty much
unprotected.
If got this in the right place
it might work.
You'd have to be really close.
That's the tricky bit.
That's a terrible idea, Charlie.
I didn't say it was a good plan.
Please.
Jo.
Here.
Have a rest.
Thank you.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Charlie!
Get back to the raft, everyone
get the fuck outta the water!
Jo!
Move, Jo. Move!
- Move!
- Hurry up!
Jo, no!
- Move, Jo. Move!
- Move it!
Jo! Jo!
Jo! Swim!
Just swim! Swim to us now.
Jo!
Come on, let's go!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Jo! No!
No! No!
Easy. Easy.
Easy, Michelle. Easy.
He's gone.
Kaz? Hey, Kaz?
Kaz, look at me.
Hey, look at me.
I'm OK!
Jo... Jo! He...
He's alive, he's... he's alive.
He's... come on, Jo!
Jo! Quickly!
Jo, Jo! Quickly, quickly...
Jo, it's OK.
We're gonna get him.
Please...
Jo!
Help me.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Please.
Jo! No!
No...
Please take care of him, Grandpa.
Michelle?
Michelle.
We can't give up.
We have to keep trying.
We can still survive, OK?
Like my grandfather did.
Yeah.
OK.
It punctured the raft.
We're losing air.
If we do nothing, we die.
But if we keep
this bloody thing moving
there's still a chance
that we can make it home.
Why don't you both
just rest a while?
No, it's OK. We can keep going.
Kaz, just rest a while
the current's taking us
the right way.
I'm fine.
Just take a breather,
sweetheart.
We're doing OK.
Oh, shit.
- Charlie?
- It's alright, keep still.
If it comes close enough,
I might have half a chance.
It's alright. Keep still.
Where is it?
I...
I can't see it.
Goddammit!
- Charlie, what? What?
- Oh, fuck!
They're hunting in packs!
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
I love you.
Where is it?
In the middle, in the middle.
It's alright,
it's alright, it's alright.
The shore.
I can see the shore.
Oh, my God. We're gonna make it!
Charlie!
We did it, Charlie.
We did it!
Alright, c'mon, let's go.
Oh, fuck.
What do we do?
We're sinking.
Charlie, this raft
is not gonna make it to shore.
Charlie!
What are you doing? Charlie!
You girls are gonna
make a run for it.
Whatever happens,
just don't look back.
Just get to shore.
Just get yourselves out of here.
Charlie, no. No!
Together.
We do this together, OK?
I was supposed
to look after you.
Together.
Always together.
OK.
Right, here.
You get one in its mouth
or in its eye
and I'll go for the brain.
Take one out,
then we'll go for the other, OK?
OK, you swim.
Just get to the land.
You ready?
Yeah.
Come on, you fucking pricks,
come on!
Michelle! Swim!
Now! Swim!
Come on!
Now!
Charlie!
No!
Kaz!
Oh, my God.
Come here, come here!
Kaz!
Where's Charlie?
Michelle!
Kaz!
Shit.
Michelle!
When I tell you to
swim to the shore
as fast as you can.
You?
I'll be right behind you.
Now! Go now!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull