(BELL TOLLING)
(SAXOPHONE PLAYING
OUT OF TUNE)
(GROANS SOFTLY)
BOY: Shut up!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh, hey,
you're up.
I wasn't sure if you,
you know, wanted to sleep in or not so...
(COUGHING IN DISTANCE)
Am I in a dorm room?
Uh,
yeah.
(MOUTHING)
(CELL PHONE RINGTONE PLAYING)
(SINGING ON CELL PHONE)
♪ Yeah, it's my birthday ♪
♪ And now you gotta ♪
♪ pick up the phone ♪
(SIGHS)
Where are my clothes?
On the dresser.
I folded your pants,
last night.
You know, I wasn't sure, if that,
material gets wrinkled.
Great.
Uh...
Don't know if you remember my name or not.
- Pretty wasted last night.
- Tylenol?
What?
My head is killing me.
Do you have any Tylenol?
Yes.
Yes, I do.
Sorry.
Thanks.
I'm Carter,
by the way.
Not a word of this to anyone,
got it?
Yeah.
Sure.
Dude! Did you hit that fine,
vagine or what?
Nice one, dickhead.
(BOYS CHEERING)
Hey! (CHUCKLES)
Stop global warming?
GIRL AND BOY: Oh. (LAUGHING)
GIRL: Run!
FRAT PLEDGES: (SINGING)
♪ 63 bottles of beer on the wall ♪
(CAR ALARM BLARING)
FRAT BROTHER: (ON MEGAPHONE)
26 hours, that's all you got?
FRAT PLEDGES:
♪ Bottles of beer on the wall ♪
FRAT BROTHER: I can't hear you!
♪ 62 bottles of beer ♪
♪ You take one down ♪
♪ Pass it around ♪
FRAT BROTHER: Keep going!
Hey!
Hi.
You haven't,
returned any of my texts.
Yeah, sorry,
I've been busy.
Yeah,
I can see that.
Okay, Tim, we went on a date.
One.
I don't have to text you back.
We're not, like, a thing.
Okay.
I just...
You know, I figured we had a nice time.
You had a nice time.
I was miserable.
I mean, who takes their
first date to Subway?
It's not like you have a footlong.
(VIETNAMESE MUSIC PLAYING
ON HEADPHONES)
SORORITY GIRL: Hey, does
this look infected to you?
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
SORORITY GIRL 2:
Someone drank my kombucha!
SORORITY GIRL 3:
Is this gluten-free?
SORORITY GIRL 4: Yes. Of course.
(SIGHS)
Oh, my God!
You sneaky little beeyotch!
Who was it?
Nobody.
Sisters don't keep secrets.
Seriously, it was nobody.
Well, I hope "nobody",
used a condom.
We don't want somebody,
looking like a whore.
Thanks, Danielle.
Super helpful.
What are sisters for?
Oh, and don't forget,
house meeting at lunch.
Living for it.
Hmm.
She finally rolls in.
(GROANS)
Did I totally embarrass myself last night?
(CHUCKLES) Not at all!
Unless you consider...
...dancing on a table,
starting two fights...
...and barfing pretzel chunks
all over the bar embarrassing.
Please tell me you're kidding.
Oh, and you also rammed your
tongue down Nick Sims' throat...
...right in front of Danielle.
(SNICKERS)
Oh, God! But she was so
nice to me this morning.
Yeah, I think she was
as drunk as you last night.
So consider it collective amnesia.
- (SIGHS) Thank God for that!
- (LORI LAUGHS)
Oh, crap!
I'm so late for class.
I can't find my,
damn book!
Ha!
(LORI CLEARS THROAT)
Did you really think you could
keep it a secret from me?
How did you find out?
Driver's license.
Not the best picture, I might add.
I assume you changed my ringer, too?
Who, me?
Never.
(LAUGHS)
What'd you wish for?
A new roommate.
Wench. (CHUCKLES)
I made that from scratch!
Sorry, too many carbs.
Toodles!
(SIGHS)
Locomotive response in the
subject shows an acceleration...
...across the quantum plane.
This creates,
great orbital overlap...
...between the partially positive base of carbon...
...and the partially negative hydrogen,
alkali group.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Thanks.
(SLURS) Get your school spirit
on before the big game.
10% off with your student ID.
DANIELLE: We really need to step up
our game at the Sigma parties, okay?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
And we still need to pick this year's charity.
I can say right now,
...there's no way,
we're doing the Special Needs Art Fair again.
Totally freaked my shit out.
Thoughts?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What's wrong?
Oh, I don't know.
What's wrong, Tree?
Nothing.
Except for that cat lady buffet
you just dumped at our table.
And is that chocolate milk I see?
I missed breakfast.
What is breakfast,
Becky?
(SCOFFS)
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
- Oh! Asshole!
- I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry, Tree.
- (SIGHS)
Wait,
you two know each other?
- Yeah.
- No!
We had a,
class together last year.
Look, I was,
bringing you this back.
Sorry, I didn't know where you lived.
You know, I...
Yeah.
I'm sorry again about the mess.
(SIGHS)
What a douchebag!
MAN: (ON PA) Dr. Lawrence
to outpatient services.
Dr. Lawrence to outpatient services.
(CELL PHONE RINGTONE PLAYING)
♪ Yeah, it's my birthday ♪
♪ And now you gotta ♪
♪ pick up the phone ♪
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
- Lori!
- Hi.
Hi.
Um...
So, I thought you only work nights.
Doing a double for Jen.
She has the flu.
That's nice of you.
So, I guess I don't need to
ask what you're doing here?
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
Got to go!
Look, Tree.
It's none of my business,
...but,
I think something like this...
...is bound to have some
pretty serious consequences.
You're right.
It is none of your business.
WOMAN: (ON PA) Dr. Surd
and Dr. Margolan, 2476.
Dr. Surd and Dr. Margolan, 2476.
(GREGORY SIGHS)
We can't do this today.
There's too much going on in the building.
I have patients.
And I'm losing mine.
(TREE MOANING)
(DOOR HANDLE RATTLES)
(KNOCKS ON DOOR)
STEPHANIE: Gregory.
- Hi.
- Hey, sweetie.
What's with the door?
Stupid thing got jammed.
Oh. Just wrapping up here.
Have you met my student, Theresa?
No, I haven't.
Hi, it's nice to meet you.
Thank you so much
for helping me out.
This is a nice surprise.
JENELLE: (ON TV) Nathan's been
acting really strange since our big fight.
And this morning,
...he drove to Atlanta for
a last-minute business meeting...
...about opening a new gym.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Enter.
JENELLE: Which is weird because I've
never heard anything about it before.
But I'm trying not to
let that bring me down.
Is that my top?
How,
cute is it on me?
Whatever.
Just don't get anything on it, please.
You mean like Nick's nutter butter?
Wow.
Classy, Danielle.
What time are you going to the party tonight?
I don't know.
Later.
- (ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
- DANIELLE: Ugh.
Our tuition dollars at work.
Anyhoo, don't be too late,
or all the cute Sigma boys will be taken.
Okay.
Bye.
Bye!
- GIRL: Who took my hair dryer?
- (SCOFFS)
Crazy bitch!
DAVID: (ON PHONE) Theresa, it's Dad.
I sat in that restaurant waiting
for you for over an hour.
I can't believe you would do
this to me, today of all days!
(CHEERING)
- Bayfield, baby!
- Ooh!
Babies for life!
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(HAPPY BIRTHDAY TUNE
PLAYING ON MUSIC BOX)
(SCOFFS)
Okay, you guys are hilarious.
You can come out now.
Losers.
(CLATTERS)
(SIGHS)
Yo, I think your friends went the other way.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Can I help you?
Look, weirdo,
I'm not scared.
Why don't you go try this with one
of the heifers at Delta Gamma?
They're into cosplay.
Okay, I'm calling the cops.
(FOOTSTEPS RECEDING)
(HAPPY BIRTHDAY PLAYING)
(GASPS)
(SCREAMS)
(GROANS)
(PANTING)
(SCREAMING)
(BELL TOLLING)
(SAXOPHONE PLAYING
OUT OF TUNE)
BOY: Shut up!
Oh, hey,
you're up.
(SIGHS)
I wasn't sure if you,
you know, wanted to sleep in or not.
(RINGTONE PLAYING)
♪ And now you gotta pick up the phone ♪
Oh...
Right, yeah.
I folded your pants,
for you, last night.
You know, I wasn't sure,
if that material gets wrinkled.
Uh...
I don't know if you
remember my name or not,
...you know, you were,
pretty wasted last night.
But, uh...
- I'm...
- Carter.
You remember.
- Tylenol?
- What?
Uh my head is killing me.
Do you have any Tylenol?
Oh, uh...
Yes.
Um...
It's over there.
Right.
It's under your clothes on,
on the thing.
Right. Right.
(SIGHS) Thanks.
And...
(CHUCKLES) It's like
you've been here before.
Are you okay?
Tree.
Dude! Did you hit that
fine vagine or what?
I'm...
I'm sorry.
(SIGHS)
Nice one, dickhead.
(BOYS CHEERING)
GIRL: Hey!
Stop global warming?
Sorry, no thanks.
GIRL AND BOY: Oh. (LAUGHING)
GIRL: Run!
FRAT PLEDGES: (SINGING)
♪ 64 bottles of beer on the wall ♪
♪ 64 bottles of beer ♪
BOY: I'm soaked!
FRAT PLEDGES: ♪ You take one down ♪
♪ Pass it around ♪
♪ 63 bottles of beer on the wall ♪
(CAR ALARM BLARING)
FRAT BROTHER: (ON MEGAPHONE)
26 hours, that's all you got?
Keep going! Faster!
FRAT PLEDGES:
♪ 62 bottles of beer on the wall ♪
♪ 62 bottles of beer ♪
FRAT BROTHER:
Keep going! I can't hear you!
Hey!
You,
haven't returned any of my texts.
Tim, what day is it?
Uh, Monday the 18th.
You're sure?
I'm pretty sure.
I, um...
I gotta go.
(SIGHS)
Call me!
(VIETNAMESE MUSIC PLAYING
ON HEADPHONES)
Oh, my God!
You sneaky little beeyotch!
Who was it?
Sisters don't keep secrets.
(CHUCKLES)
I'm totally having déjà vu right now.
Oh!
I have it all the time.
It's supposed to mean like
someone's thinking about you...
...while they're masturbating.
I have it at least five times a day.
Seriously, I've been having
it all day. It's so weird.
Maybe you should switch
to water next time, hon.
I... Yeah, thanks.
I'll keep that in mind.
What are sisters for?
Oh, and don't forget,
house meeting at lunch.
Hello?
It's been on the board
since last Thursday, Tree.
Yeah.
I remember it.
Um... (CHUCKLES)
She finally rolls in.
That's so weird.
LORI: You okay?
You were kind of a mess last night.
Oh, shit.
I'm so late for class.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Did you really think you could
keep it a secret from me?
Don't you wanna
know howl found out?
Driver's license?
Clever girl.
That picture, though. (CHUCKLES)
I gotta go.
But,
you didn't even blow out the...
Candle.
DANIELLE: We really need to step up
our game at these frat parties, okay?
And we still need to
pick this year's charity.
I can say right now,
...there's no way we are doing
the Special Needs Art Fair again.
BOY: Get your school spirit
on before the big game.
10% off with your student ID.
DANIELLE: What's wrong, Tree?
Um, I'm just a little tired, I guess.
No, dumbass.
What's wrong with that?
So not Kappa cuisine.
And is that chocolate milk I see?
I missed breakfast.
We all miss breakfast, Becky.
Becky, look out!
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry, Tree.
Wait,
you two know each other?
- Yeah. I mean...
- No!
We had a...
a class together last year. That's all.
I'm sorry about all this.
Hey.
What?
My bracelet.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh.
You know, I'm sorry again about,
the mess.
DANIELLE: What a douchebag!
We can't do this today.
There's too much going on in the building.
I need to talk to you.
(SIGHS)
Tree,
I...
I know what you're gonna say.
You do?
Look.
It's normal for a young girl to
have feelings for an older man,
...but you can't fall in love.
I'm not falling in love with you.
You're not?
No.
I've been having the weirdest day...
(MOANING)
Your wife.
Uh, that's,
kind of a buzzkill.
(DOOR HANDLE RATTLES)
STEPHANIE: Gregory.
Are you in there?
Thank God you looked the door.
(CHUCKLES) Hey, sweetie.
Uh, I didn't realize
I'd locked the door. Um...
Just wrapping up here.
Have you met my student, Theresa?
No...
I haven't.
Nice to meet you.
TREE AND TREE'S MOTHER: (SINGING)
♪ Happy birthday to us ♪
DAVID: My favorite girls.
Blow it out.
(LAUGHS) There you go.
TREE: That! What's that?
TREE'S MOM: You guys,
I think I just found a bug.
- Where?
- Right in there.
DAVID: Take a look.
- And Mom goes in for the kill.
- (LAUGHS)
DAVID: Oh, no. Oh, no.
Hey, don't look at me.
Oh, I guess...
- I'm not having leftovers.
- (KNOCK ON DOOR)
JENELLE: (ON TV) ...for a last-minute
business meeting about opening a new gym.
I know!
I'm just borrowing it for tonight.
What time you going to the party?
But I'm trying not to
let that bring me down.
Hello? (SNAPS FINGERS)
Earth to space bitch.
What?
(MIMICKING DEAF PERSON)
What time are you going to the party?
Uh...
I don't know. Later.
- (ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
- DANIELLE: Ugh.
Our tuition dollars at work.
(GASPING)
Okay, whoa!
Chill out. It's just another
rolling blackout, sweetie.
- It happened before?
- Yeah.
Like two weeks ago.
Anyhoo, don't be too late,
or all the cute Sigma boys will be taken.
GIRL: Who took my hair dryer?
DAVID: (ON PHONE)
Theresa, it's Dad.
I sat in that restaurant
waiting for you for over an...
(GROUP CHEERING)
BOY: Bayfield, baby!
Babies for life!
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
STUDENT: Yo, Mike.
Come on. Hurry up, man.
MIKE: Hold up. I'm coming.
STUDENT: Here we come.
(HAPPY BIRTHDAY TUNE
PLAYING ON MUSIC BOX)
(GASPS)
No way.
(SHRIEKS)
Surprise?
What the hell, Tree?
Oh, my God. I'm so sorry.
I thought that you...
I am so, so sorry.
Don't mess with a Kappa bitch.
(ALL CHEERING)
(UPBEAT MUSICPLAYING
ON SPEAKERS)
(LIVELY CHATTER)
- Yes.
- Are you serious?
Yes.
- That slut.
- Who?
Lori.
She said she'd be here.
She's so,
out of the house next year.
I think she said she had,
like, a double shift.
- Whatevs. She's been boning some mystery guy.
- (SNICKERS)
There's your stalker.
He's so hot.
- Danielle!
- What?
- That's so gross.
- Oh, okay.
Truce?
Hi.
Why were you wearing that,
stupid mask anyway?
Big game's on Friday.
I just thought I'd show
a little school spirit.
Never thought I'd get clocked for it.
(LAUGHING)
I really am sorry.
Did you ice it?
It's fine.
You can make it up to me later.
What?
Don't "what" me.
You know exactly what you are doing, Tree.
What am I doing, Danielle?
Danielle!
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING
ON SPEAKERS)
(KNOCKS ON DOOR)
Nick?
(CHUCKLES)
Wow.
(EXHALES)
Oh, shit.
Oh, shit, Nick. You scared me.
You want me to,
punch you in the face again?
(CHUCKLES)
Welcome,
to the pleasure-dome.
(LOUD UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(CHUCKLES)
It's a little loud, don't you think?
- (CHUCKLES)
- (CELL PHONE CHIMES)
(MUFFLED SCREAMS)
Okay!
I'm officially over this.
Have fun in the Sahara Tent.
Come on. Nick, seriously!
Danielle's, like, freaking out.
- (SCREAMS)
- (GRUNTS)
(SCREAMING)
TREE: No!
Help me!
(VOCALIZING)
You asshole!
(TREE GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
- (BELL TOLLING)
- (GASPING)
Is everything okay?
(CELL PHONE RINGTONE PLAYING)
♪ Yeah, it's my birthday ♪
♪ And now you gotta ♪
♪ pick up the phone ♪
What...
I don't know if you remember my name or not.
- You were...
- Pretty wasted.
Yeah.
- And your name is Carter?
- Yeah.
And we've never met before?
I mean, no, not until last night.
Oh, my God. This is a nightmare.
I'm sorry.
You were the one that wanted
to come home with me.
(GASPING)
Dude! Did you hit that fine vagine...
(SHRIEKS)
Nice one, dickhead.
Stop global warming?
Oh!
A simple "no thanks" would do.
(GASPS)
Oh. (LAUGHS)
(CAR ALARM BLARING)
(GASPS)
FRAT BROTHER: (ON MEGAPHONE)
26 hours, that's all you got?
Keep going!
FRAT PLEDGES: (SINGING)
♪ 62 bottles of beer ♪
♪ You take one down ♪
FRAT BROTHER: I can't hear you!
- (SHRIEKS)
- Hey!
You okay?
You haven't returned any of my texts.
LORI: She finally rolls in.
Hey, you okay?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Tree?
Tree, what's wrong?
Say something.
Lori...
I feel like I'm losing my mind.
I don't know what's happening to me.
Okay.
Just calm down.
Tell me what's going on.
Look, I know this isn't gonna make,
any sense,
...but,
I have already lived through this day.
Twice.
Tree.
No, no, no. Believe me.
I know it sounds totally crazy,
...but this is happening to me,
I swear to God.
Tree. I'm sure it feels,
like you're living through...
Okay, you made me a cupcake.
For my birthday, right?
You're about to give it to me...
...and then later on tonight
there's a surprise party.
Ugh.
Who told you?
Was it Becky?
No, no. Nobody told me.
That's what I mean.
Don't you see? I know
what is going to happen...
...before it happens.
Lori...
Lori, somebody is gonna kill me tonight.
Oh. (CHUCKLES)
Okay.
Okay, I get it.
Who put you up to this?
- Was it Danielle?
- No, no, no.
This isn't some stupid joke!
This is actually happening to me.
I don't know who is going to kill me,
but someone is.
I just don't know who it is yet.
Tree, you're starting to freak me out.
How do you think I feel?
Tree, look at me.
Nobody is trying to kill you.
Yes, they are, Lori.
Tree, look at me!
I know that today is hard
with your mom and all.
Why don't you skip class?
Just,
take the day off and get some rest.
I promise you,
you'll feel better tomorrow.
Okay?
Let's see you get in here now, asshole.
(GRUNTS)
(DOOR HANDLE RATTLING)
(KNOCKS ON DOOR)
DANIELLE: Tree,
why is the door locked?
Um...
I just need,
some, alone time.
What time are you going to the party tonight?
I don't know.
- (ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
- DANIELLE: Ugh.
Our tuition dollars at work.
Anyhoo, don't be too late,
or all the cute Sigma boys will be taken.
Okay. See you soon.
GIRL: Who took my hair dryer?
JENELLE: (ON TV)
...opening a new gym.
Which is weird because I've never
heard anything about it before.
But I'm trying not to
let that bring me down.
Because I'm on my
way to pick up Jace.
(SCOFFS)
BARBARA: I'm just happy
you're gonna see Jace.
JENELLE: I know.
BARBARA: 'Cause it's been,
like, almost a month.
He's gonna be so
excited to see you.
Where'd Lori put the freaking remote?
(SIGHS)
BARBARA: Hi, Jace!
JENELLE: Hey, Jace.
Hey.
(JENELLE EXCLAIMING)
- BARBARA: Hi.
- WOMAN: Hi.
I'm Barbara.
I am Crystal.
- BARBARA: Hi.
- CRYSTAL: Nice to meet you.
JENELLE: Can you
say bye to Mamey?
JACE: Bye.
JENELLE: Stay buckled
and have a good time.
MALE BINGO ANNOUNCER: G-48.
It's that great. G-48.
G-48!
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
BARBARA: I don't know what's going
on with you and that other guy, okay?
REPORTER: ...is being treated
for a gunshot wound...
...following a deadly shoot-out this
morning that left one officer dead.
Tombs was the subject of...
(GASPING)
(RUSTLING)
- (WOMAN SCREAMS ON TV)
- WOMAN: ...boring hairstyles?
Do you go through
a can of hair spray...
...trying to get that full,
volumized look?
Then bump it up with Bumpits
and get that salon-style look.
Flat to fabulous, instantly.
Imagine being able
to create today's...
(SHRIEKS) No!
(SCREAMING)
(BELL TOLLING)
What's wrong?
- (HYPERVENTILATING)
- What's going on?
(CELL PHONE RINGTONE PLAYING)
♪ Yeah, it's my birthday ♪
♪ And now you gotta ♪
♪ pick up the phone ♪
- Ow!
- Tree, are you okay? Are you sick?
Shut up! Shut up!
Oh, my God. Make it stop.
Make it stop.
- Are you okay?
- Get away from me.
All right.
- (PANTING)
- Come on, just...
(PANTING)
(DISTORTED) Stop global warming?
(GASPING)
GIRL AND BOY:
Oh. (LAUGHING)
- (HYPERVENTILATING)
- (CAR ALARM BLARING)
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
FRAT PLEDGES: (SINGING)
♪ Bottles of beer ♪
♪ You take one down ♪
♪ 61 bottles of beer on the wall ♪
Louder!
FRAT PLEDGES:
♪ 61 bottles of beer on the wall ♪
♪ You take one down ♪
♪ Pass it around ♪
FRAT BROTHER:
I can't hear you!
- (GASPS)
- I'm sorry.
You forgot your stuff.
FRAT BROTHER: Keep going!
Help me. (SOBBING)
(SLURPING)
Will you please stop staring at me...
...like I took a dump on your mom's head?
I'm sorry.
I'm just trying to,
wrap my brain around this.
How's that going for you?
Assuming that I believe any of
this is even remotely possible,
...there has to be a reason
you're stuck in this day.
Okay? Out of all the days of your life,
what makes this day special?
- What gives this day meaning?
- (RINGTONE PLAYS)
Nothing.
♪ Yeah, it's my birthday, ♪
♪ And now you gotta pick up the phone ♪
It's your birthday?
- Yeah.
- Hello?
So? Birthdays are just excuses to, like,
eat cake and open presents and shit.
There's no real meaning behind a birthday.
No, it's symbolic.
Okay? Whoever's killing you
knows it's your birthday.
All right, look.
Give me a list of names,
of everybody who knows it's your birthday...
...and,
whoever is trying to kill you.
Well, thanks to my sorority,
...pretty much the entire school
knows it's my birthday.
God, they're throwing me this
stupid surprise party tonight.
I mean, it literally could be anyone.
I mean, who has motive?
Okay, maybe it's Danielle.
All right.
Apparently, I made out
with some guy she liked...
...right in front of her last night.
Huh.
Must have been before we met.
Busy night?
Okay, Mr. "I'm gonna take
this drunk girl home..."
"...and take advantage of her."
Don't judge.
For the record,
I didn't take advantage of you last night, okay?
I slept on Ryan's bed.
So,
we didn't have...
No!
You were wasted last night.
You know, I was afraid you were gonna fall...
...or choke on your own
vomit like Janis Joplin.
Uh,
what were we...
- Suspects.
- Right. Suspects.
Um, okay, so Danielle.
(SIGHS)
Gregory. Um,
his wife.
Creepy Tim.
Ooh! Um, that tiny girl from
T.J. Maxx that I got fired.
And maybe the Uber driver
that I spit on last week.
I think his name was...
What?
Nobody's perfect.
Okay.
This isn't helping.
(SIGHS)
- This is pointless, isn't it?
- All right, look.
The way I see it is...is,
you have unlimited amount of lives.
So you have unlimited opportunities
to solve your own murder.
So I'm, just supposed to keep dying...
...until I figure out who my killer is?
That's your genius plan?
Do you have a better idea?
(UPBEAT POP MUSIC PLAYING)
BOY: Yo Tim!
(MOUTHING) Oh! He's gay!
- (STABS)
- (GASPS)
(BELL TOLLING)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(SIGHS)
(SHRIEKS)
(GRUNTING)
It's so exhausting. (GRUNTS)
Asshole!
- You bitch!
- (SCREAMS)
I knew it was you!
- (CONTINUES SCREAMING)
- Come here!
- Get off of me!
- I'm gonna kill you.
(HORN BLARING)
(BELL TOLLS)
(GRUNTS, YELLS)
(MUFFLED SCREAM)
(INAUDIBLE)
- (GRUNTS)
- (GROANS)
(BODY THUDS)
Oh, my God.
Becky?
Becky!
(BELL TOLLING)
(SAXOPHONE PLAYING
OUT OF TUNE)
- BOY: Shut up!
- Ow!
(CELL PHONE RINGTONE PLAYING)
♪ Yeah, it's my birthday ♪
♪ And now you gotta pick up ♪
Oh, hey,
you're up.
I wasn't sure if you wanted to a,
sleep in...
Your plan totally sucks.
What?
(MOANS)
(SIGHS)
I don't know if you remember my name or not.
You know, you were,
pretty wasted last night.
- Um... But I'm Carter.
- (GROANS)
Are you okay?
Never better.
(STAMMERS)
(GROANS)
Are you sure you're okay?
I'm fine.
Dude! Did you hit that fine vagine or...
What's up?
Hey.
Um, I'm sorry to bother you guys, uh...
(ECHOING) How did it go?
I had to sleep in my car,
so he could finally get laid.
(GRUNTING)
Carter, please,
a little help. Carter!
(EKG BEEPING)
(HYPERVENTILATING)
Tree.
Hey, hey, hey, calm down.
It's just me.
How you doing?
What happened?
You,
collapsed this morning.
What day is it?
It's Monday.
What's the date?
Uh,
it's the 18th.
Oh, we've been trying to, get in,
contact with your parents,
...but,
for some reason there's...
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
- Jeez!
- Can I help you?
Uh,
I'm just checking on her.
It's okay.
He's a friend.
Sorry.
Visiting hours are over.
Got it.
Thanks, Carter.
Feel better.
When can I get out of here?
(CLEARS THROAT)
I'm having a hard time
pulling your medical records.
Why?
We just got these back from imaging.
And these are signs of,
major trauma.
Given the,
severity of the scar tissue and the size of the lesions...
This is gonna sound crazy but,,
technically,
...you should be dead.
Hey. Hey, hey!
What are you doing?
I need to get out of here.
No way. No, you need to
stay here for observation.
If I don't get out of here, I'm gonna die.
Tree, Tree. (SHUSHES)
Listen to me.
You are absolutely safe here.
Okay.
I won't let anything happen to you.
I'm really thirsty.
Could you get me a soda?
Sure.
Thank you.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Special delivery.
(PANTING)
Keys, keys, keys.
Oh, Greg. Where are the car keys?
Come on!
(GASPS)
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- (DOOR OPENS)
- (GASPS)
Tree. Tree. It's okay.
It's okay. It's just me.
Gregory, look out!
(GRUNTS)
(GASPING)
(SCREAMS)
- (GRUNTS)
- (YELPS)
Come on. Come on,
come on, come on.
(CAR ALARM CHIRPS)
(PANTING)
(YELPING)
(GASPING)
(SHRIEKS)
(CHOKING)
I did it.
I did it!
Whoo!
Yeah!
Catch me now,
bitch!
(LAUGHS)
Whoo!
(POLICE SIREN BLARING)
What?
Oh, no, no, no!
Come on!
No!
Oh, shit!
Shit, shit, shit.
I know I was speeding, officer.
I just...
Turn off the engine, please.
Yes, officer.
License and registration.
I, um...
I don't have it.
- Pardon me?
- He's trying to kill me again.
- Again?
- Yes!
I mean, no.
He was trying before, but this time I got away.
But I, I didn't have time to grab my clothes,
...and my driver's license is in my pocket.
Ma'am,
are you under the influence of alcohol...
...or any other controlled substance?
No!
That is what I'm trying to...
Wait.
If I am, does that mean that
you're going to arrest me...
...and lock me in a jail cell?
That's how it usually works.
I'm drunk.
You are?
Wasted.
And I'm high.
You know, pills, weed.
You name it, man, I'm on it.
Uh...
Well...
Then I'm, gonna,
put you under arrest.
That's a good idea.
Let me help you.
Uh,
all right.
- Never been arrested before.
- Uh-huh.
Thank you.
DISPATCHER: (ON RADIO) All units,
...we got a 1-8-7 at University
Hospital. Suspect is...
(SCREAMS)
(GASPING)
Shit.
Oh, God, get me out. (GRUNTS)
Get me out, get me out!
(GASPING)
(SHOUTING) What do you want?
Why are you doing this to me?
Who are you?
Show your face, you pussy!
Where are you going?
Oh, shit!
Oh, fuck.
(BELL TOLLING)
(GROANS)
Oh, hey,
you're up.
Silence!
(CHUCKLES)
(CELL PHONE RINGTONE PLAYING)
♪ Yeah, it's my birthday ♪
♪ And now you gotta ♪
♪ pick up the phone ♪
What, you've been here before?
Hey uh, you know,
I don't think you should be taking that many.
I mean, you could...
You could die.
If only it were that easy.
(MUFFLED) Water, por favor.
Come on.
There you go.
(EXHALES)
Dude!,
Did you hit that...
Hi.
I'm the so-called fine vagine.
And if that's the way that you refer to girls,
...you and your hand are going to have a very,
lasting relationship.
Have a nice day.
What?
Are you...
You're always this charming in the morning?
Mmm.
Just this one.
So were you,
having a bad dream or something?
Sorry?
You were just,
screaming before you woke up.
(SIGHS) Well,
I was dying.
Again.
What?
Um,
it's a long story.
(STAMMERING) Well, I've got time.
I'm not doing anything today,
if you wanna...
Seriously,
I hate this sticker.
Hey, wait.
Why are you following me?
I wanna hear your story.
Look,
no offense,
...but the last time I explained it to you,
it got me nowhere. So...
The last time?
Hey.
So you're,
you're having bad dreams.
I took an elective course on
neurocognition and dream content.
Hooray for you.
- I'm just saying I... (STAMMERS)
- (EXHALES SHARPLY)
(BOY SCOFFS)
I might be able to help,
you know?
Can you help me stop reliving
the same day over and over...
...only to be murdered bysomeone
I may or may not know?
Yep,
thought so.
- Stop global warming?
- Mmm.
(CHUCKLES) Wait, you literally
think you're reliving the same day?
Yep.
And somebody kills you.
Yep, again.
All right, come on.
You're just messing with me, right?
Sprinklers.
(SNAPS FINGERS)
GIRL AND BOY:
Oh. (LAUGHING)
Car alarm.
(CAR ALARM BLARING)
Now, see that pledge over there?
The one in the baseball hat?
He's going to fall right now.
FRAT BROTHER: Keep going!
Any questions?
TREE: How are your fries? Mmm.
CARTER: Yeah, they're good.
(BURPS)
- That's, impressive.
- Mmm.
That was nothing.
(FARTING)
(GRUNTS)
Did you get it all out?
Whatever.
You won't remember it anyway.
(CELL PHONE RINGTONE PLAYING)
♪ Yeah, it's my birthday ♪
♪ And now you gotta ♪
♪ pick up the phone ♪
It's your birthday?
(RINGTONE STOPS)
It's your dad. You wanna...
You wanna get that?
I was never close with my dad.
Can't even remember the last
time he called me on my birthday.
Kinda,
always forgets.
Yeah.
I'm supposed to be with mine.
I don't know.
I couldn't bear the thought of sitting
through another uncomfortable celebration...
...while we both pretend that everything is awesome.
Are you closer with your mom?
Was.
What happened?
Oh,
she...
Yeah.
Three years ago.
I'm sorry.
That...
That...That sucks.
Yeah.
We actually shared the same birthday, though.
Seriously?
That's crazy.
Yeah, when I was,
a kid,
I always got to skip school.
We'd go to the beach.
My dad would buy us this, like,
huge birthday cake...
...and put just one candle on it.
We'd blow it out together.
I bet you miss her.
Yeah.
You know, it's funny.
You relive the same day over and over again,
...you kind of start to see
who you really are.
If my mom saw me now,
knew who I've become...
I don't think she'd be very proud.
Don't say that.
It's true.
I'm not a good person, Carter.
Maybe this is karma.
Maybe I deserve it.
Look, I don't,
know you all that well,
...but it's never too late to change.
I mean, especially if what you're saying is true.
Each new day is,
it's a chance to be somebody better.
See, that's just it.
I don't think I have that many chances left.
I keep on getting weaker every time I come back.
Maybe I'm like that cat with nine lives.
Eventually, I'm gonna run out.
REPORTER: (ON TV) Let's go live
now to Bayfield University Hospital...
...where Jennifer Tran has the
latest on this developing situation.
I'm standing outside the
Bayfield University Hospital...
...where suspected murderer,
John Tombs,
...is being treated
for a gunshot wound...
Can you turn that up, please?
...that left one officer dead.
Tombs was the subject
of a nationwide manhunt...
...that ended after
a five-month pursuit...
- ...across four state lines...
- What's going on? Tree?
...that left
six female victims.
Authorities are still not sure if
Tombs is responsible for the murders...
Oh, my God.
...of more than
a dozen other victims...
...he's claimed to have buried
across the vast desert of Arizona.
He's been here the whole time.
CARTER: What? Tree!
Hey...
Tree!
He's going to escape. Call the police.
- Who?
- John Tombs.
- Just call the police.
- What?
Wait! Don't go in there!
Shit.
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
(GUN COCKING)
(SCREAMS)
He has a gun!
He has a gun, run!
(PANTING)
Come on.
CARTER: Hey!
TREE: Carter!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Stop!
Stop it right now. Hey!
(GRUNTS)
(GUN CLICKS)
(LAUGHING)
- (GUN CLICKING)
- No.
No.
- (NECK SNAPS)
- Carter!
(HYPERVENTILATING)
(TREE SHRIEKS)
(GRUNTS)
There's nowhere to hide, little girl!
(DOOR CREAKING)
(TREE GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
Carter.
(NECK SNAPS)
If I don't reset this day, he's gone forever.
(GROANING)
TOMBS: You should've killed me
when you had the chance.
(TOMBS LAUGHING)
Come on. Olly, olly, oxen free.
TREE: Hey!
See you soon,
asshole.
(INHALES)
(NECK SNAPS)
(BELL TOLLING)
(CELL PHONE RINGTONE PLAYING)
♪ Yeah, it's my birthday ♪
♪ And now you gotta ♪
♪ pick up the phone ♪
- (GROANS)
- Oh. Hey, you're up.
(GASPS)
I wasn't sure if you wanted...
I can't believe you tried to save my life.
Thank you so much.
Yeah.
Yeah, no biggie. I just,
you know, brought you home.
Uh, I don't know if you,
remember my name.
Carter.
Yeah.
- You... I...
- Oh!
Do you mind if I borrow this?
Uh...
Yeah, yeah.
Sure.
See you at lunch.
Dude! Did you hit that fine, vagine or what?
TREE: You naughty, naughty boy!
Fine vagine out!
What just happened?
Hey! Stop global warming?
Sure.
You save that planet, girl.
Yo!
Sprinklers about to go on.
You're welcome.
- (CAR ALARM BLARING)
- FRAT BROTHER: (ON MEGAPHONE) 26 hours, that's all you got?
I can't hear you!
FRAT PLEDGES: (SINGING) ♪ You take one down ♪
♪ Pass it around ♪
♪ 62 bottles of beer on the wall ♪
Oh, Tim.
I know you're back there.
Hi, Tim.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Um, you haven't,
returned any of my texts.
Look, Tim. Let's get real.
I know you don't like girls.
Stop trying, to be someone you're not.
Love is love, right?
Now you go out there and get
yourself a fine piece of man ass.
Good morning.
Oh, my God!
You sneaky little beeyotch!
His name's Carter.
No,
we did not have sex.
But,
if I finally make it through this day somehow...
I'm gonna have his babies.
Lots to do,
got to go.
She finally rolls in.
What's wrong?
Ugh.
Um, nothing. (CHUCKLES) I was...
Look, Lori...
I have been,
the worst roommate.
You've always been there for me,
...but I've been way too selfish
to even appreciate it.
Can we start over?
I promise not to be such a loser.
Are you high?
On life.
(CHUCKLES)
Oh! By the way,
I wanna hear about this mystery guy.
When extreme agitation occurs,
locomotive response in the subject...
...shows an acceleration across...
Dr. Butler.
Can I have a word, please?
What the hell do...
What the hell do you think you're doing?
I'm ending this.
Wait.
What?
I never should have started seeing you.
It was wrong.
And I...
(SIGHS)
Anyway, I can't change what I've done,
...but I can start trying to
be a better person today.
(SCOFFS)
What lame little self-help
book did you get that from?
(SCOFFS)
You know what? You have a wife,
who loves you so much.
So if you can't be faithful to her,
...at least have the balls to leave.
Don't expect me to let you
coast by my class now.
Already dropped it.
I just have to say, how, totally sad,
and disappointing it is...
...when certain people,
can't be bothered...
...to make it to a mandatory house meeting.
We were supposed to be picking this year's charity.
Becky,
...is that chocolate milk I see?
- I skipped breakfast.
- Ah!
TREE: Mmm. Mmm!
Oh, my God.
That is so good.
What's up with the fat fest?
We're Kappas.
Come on, hon.
Live a little.
Few calories won't kill ya.
No.
It'll just turn me into a chunker.
Like Becky here.
Okay.
(GASPS)
(GIRLS EXCLAIMING)
(LAUGHING)
Oh, my God.
(GASPING)
(DANIELLE SCREAMS)
GIRL: You'll be okay.
Hey, Tree.
Hey.
Just, uh,
coming by to uh...
What was,
that for?
I have to run,
but what are you doing later tonight?
Nothing.
Do you wanna take me out for my birthday?
What's the punch line?
Look, I know it's really random,
...but I promise I'll explain everything tomorrow.
Assuming there is one.
Just say yes.
All right.
Yeah.
Great.
(CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS)
Excuse me.
Can I pay for my coffee, please?
- You're not gonna eat?
- No, just the check. Please.
I'll be right back.
Hi, Daddy.
Sorry I'm late.
I like your tie.
Thanks.
How's school?
Fine.
You like your classes?
(STAMMERS) They're fine, Dad.
I don't wanna do that anymore.
Do what?
Small talk.
It's just that,
this day...
This day is really,
hard for me.
And, um...
I miss Mom.
You know, I miss her so much.
I miss the way that she smells.
I miss that crazy (LAUGHS)
horse laugh she had.
(CHUCKLES)
Yeah.
Me, too.
I...
I, I guess I thought that if,
I avoided all of it,
...if I avoided you,
that somehow it would be easier,
...but it's not.
It's been so much worse.
All of this running and hiding
has made me so miserable.
(SIGHS)
And I think I finally figured it out.
I mean, it took something like totally crazy...
...but I'm here.
And I love you.
And I'm so,
so sorry that I hurt you.
- Happy birthday, baby.
- (CHUCKLES)
(SNIFFLING)
(BEEPS)
(TICKING)
(SIGHS)
TREE: Stay calm.
I need you to stand up,
slowly.
Slowly.
Okay, good.
Okay, this is a really bad idea.
So is dying for the 16th time.
Okay.
Now, turn around.
I need you to listen to me.
He's going to escape.
We can talk about this.
Just put the gun down.
He's going to escape.
Go get help.
Go!
Okay.
I know you're not asleep.
Open your eyes.
(GUN CLICKING)
(GASPING)
Safety's on, little girl.
(GROANS)
- (GRUNTS)
- (GASPING)
TOMBS: Ah-ah.
(LAUGHS) Look what we have here.
Hmm?
(WHIMPERS)
You know...
A real nice surprise,
you coming to visit me like this.
- (GRUNTS)
- (GROANS)
- (SHOUTING)
- (SHRIEKING)
(PANTING)
(SIGHS)
I like you.
Damn shame.
But you're a feisty little shit, ain't you?
- (LAUGHS)
- (GROANING)
That's right. Crawl, little girl, crawl.
Don't worry.
I'll just make this one
real quick for you, okay?
(BEEPING)
(GUN SAFETY SWITCHES)
Hey!
Safety's off.
Thanks for the tip.
(GROANS)
- (PANTING)
- (POLICE SIRENS BLARING)
(CHUCKLES)
GIRL: Who took my hair dryer?
So this has got to be, like, the strangest
birthday you've ever had, huh?
You have no idea.
Did you ever,
figure out how Tombs got free?
No.
No one knows.
It's kinda like Houdini.
Yeah.
I guess.
What are you gonna wish for?
Tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
But isn't that kind of a given?
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Wanna aim for anything higher?
No.
Tomorrow is good enough for me.
(BELL TOLLING)
(SAXOPHONE PLAYING
OUT OF TUNE)
(MOANS)
BOY: Shut up!
(CELL PHONE RINGTONE PLAYING)
♪ Yeah, it's my birthday ♪
♪ And now you gotta ♪
♪ pick up the phone ♪
Oh. Hey,
you're up.
Carter?
Yeah. I'm surprised you remember my name.
You were pretty wasted last night.
This can't be happening.
- What?
- I killed him!
I solved it!
Who?
What are you talking about?
(SOBBING)
What's going on?
I mean, look, you were probably...
...just having a bad dream or something.
That happens to me all the time...
...when I'm drinking,
you know, I...
Nice one.
Dickhead.
LORI: She finally rolls in.
- Going somewhere?
- Yes. (PANTING)
As far away as possible.
Tree, what's wrong?
Me.
I was wrong.
I thought that if I stopped
running that I could beat it.
But it's never gonna stop.
Tree, you're freaking me out.
Oh well,
that's me, a freak.
Tree.
Tree, look.
Happy birthday.
Thanks,
but I already ate it last night.
Oh, my God.
I died in my sleep.
LORI: What?
You killed me.
What?
You poisoned it.
But I never ate it before.
(INAUDIBLE)
So you had to find another way.
Then Tombs fell right into your lap.
The perfect scapegoat.
You had access to him.
Did you drug him first?
You knew that if he escaped everyone
would assume that he killed me.
(SCREAMING)
But it was always you.
(CHUCKLES)
(STAMMERS) Tree,
is this a joke?
You think I would actually try to
poison you with a freaking cupcake?
Eh... (SCOFFS)
Okay, then.
Prove it.
Go on, Lori.
Take a bite.
(CHUCKLES) You really are crazy.
Okay, then...
I'll take it down to the police.
I'm sure they can tell us what your
little birthday treat is made of.
(SCREAMING)
You stupid little whore.
I know I've been a bad roommate, but,
isn't this a bit much?
What the hell?
Oh, I don't know,
...maybe because you wouldn't
stop sleeping with him.
But...
Gregory?
But he just kept choosing you,
over me.
Guess all he wanted was
a cheap slut like you.
Wait.
You've been killing me
over some stupid guy?
(SIGHS) Oh, that's not
the only reason.
You're a dumb bitch, too!
But what I really wanna know is...
(SHUDDERING) ...how did you figure it out?
Because you've killed me before.
(INHALES)
Then I guess I'm just gonna have to do it again.
(GROANS)
(SHRIEKS)
(GRUNTING)
Stop!
Bitch!
(DOOR HANDLE RATTLING)
- TREE: No!
- (KNOCKS ON DOOR)
What the hell's going on in there?
Nothing. Tree just fell.
Everything's fine.
Whatever,
clumsy hoes.
I better see you at the meeting today.
We'll be there.
(WHEEZING)
Eat it, bitch!
(SCREAMING)
(GASPING)
(GASPS)
(SHRIEKING)
(SPLATTERS)
(PANTING)
(KNOCKS ON DOOR)
DANIELLE: What are you losers
doing in there?
Lori, ate,
my cupcake.
DANIELLE: I just knew,
there was something wrong with Lori.
She never wore makeup,
never posted any cute selfies...
...and she literally,
owned a pair of Crocs.
All the signs of
a psycho killer with...
(EMILY SOBBING)
Hello!
I'm trying to get interviewed here.
- (CARTER SNICKERS)
- Okay.
Oh, my God. She is such a tool.
Anyhoo...
Lori's little plot was super lame.
Poisoning a cupcake, really?
We're Kappas.
We don't eat cupcakes.
- Is this local or national?
- (CELL PHONE RINGTONE PLAYING)
REPORTER: Local.
- Hey, Dad.
- DAVID: Are you okay?
- Are you hurt?
- Dad, no. Dad, I'm fine.
I promise.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
- (DAVID SIGHS)
- Just a little scratched up.
- All right.
- Okay. I'll see you soon.
- I Love you.
- I love you, too. Bye.
So uh, now that your,
bedroom is officially a crime scene and all,
...where do you plan on crashing tonight?
(LAUGHS) Is that an invitation?
You sure you want to wake up
in a dorm room again?
Only if it's yours.
I mean, of course you'll have to,
sleep in Ryan's bed.
- Of course.
- Yeah.
We can...
Yeah.
(LAUGHS)
Oh! Uh...
Almost forgot.
You left this little guy.
Thanks.
You know,
what your little scenario reminds me of?
What?
What's that?
Groundhog Day.
The movie, Groundhog Day?
I don't know.
With Bill Murray?
Who's Bill Murray?
Are you kidding me?
Ghostbusters.
Sorry.
I...
- How...
- I don't know.
How do you sleep at night?
You've never seen Groundhog Day?
TREE: No.
(BELL TOLLING)
(CELL PHONE RINGTONE PLAYING)
♪ Yeah, it's my birthday ♪
♪ And now you gotta ♪
♪ pick up the phone ♪
Oh. Hey,
you're up.
I wasn't sure if you uh, wanted to, uh,
you know, sleep in or not.
(PANTING)
I'm kidding.
It was... It was me.
I just called your phone.
What?
It's Tuesday, the 19th.
You made it.
Oh, my God.
You are such a jerk!
- I'm gonna kill you.
- Hey, that's enough.
What is wrong with you?
That was not funny.
You are such a punk.
- (LAUGHS)
- I hate you. (LAUGHS)
- (SIGHS) She's back?
- Out.
I'm not sleeping in my car again.
It smells like Hot Pockets and feet.
- Get out.
- I just want clean underwear.
(CHUCKLES)