[insects chirping]
- [footsteps]
- [sighing]
- [people shouting]
- [man 1] Hey, hey, hey!
[man 2] Come. Come. Come here.
[man 1] Hey, hey, hey, hey!
[dog barking]
[barrier slams]
[in Dinka] I'll protect you.
[truck door slams]
[engine starts]
[waves crashing]
[wind whistling]
[coughing]
[whispering]
[murmuring]
[whirring]
- [loud crash]
- [[exclaiming]
Nyagak!
[screams] Mama!
[sighs]
[traffic and voices outside]
[woman in English] You were dreaming.
What did you dream about?
Our wedding day.
[echoing shouts outside]
Explains the screams.
[tuts]
[voices outside continue]
[door opens]
You're wanted in the gym.
- [man shouts]
- [children playing]
Why?
[does zipper up]
[man] Don't get your hopes up.
They will send you back to die,
like the bastards always do.
[man shouting outside]
[shouting grows louder]
- [distressed shouting]
- [scuffling]
- [man crying]
- [shouting]
[door slamming echoes]
[slurping]
[knocking]
- [phone chiming]
- What about the child?
[man whispers] They lost her, last year.
[phone chimes]
[man] Congratulations.
You're being released from detention.
Today if you're lucky.
- Today?
- [man] Mm.
- [laughs]
- [sighs]
[laughs]
[laughing]
- [woman sighs]
- [man laughs]
This is bail, Mr. and Mrs. Majur.
You're being released on bail
as asylum seekers.
Not as citizens, not yet.
You both understand?
Until then, you'll be subject
to certain conditions.
If you fail to meet these,
even just the once,
you'll be returned to detention.
Your case may be disqualified
and you'll be sent back.
Do you understand?
Okie-dokie. All right, conditions.
You will be reviewed
and must report to us weekly.
You must not miss a single report.
A yes, if you understand, please.
- Yes.
- Yes. Yes.
You will be given financial weekly support
of 74 pounds in total.
You do not have permission to work
or to supplement your earnings
by any other means.
A yes, if you understand, please.
- Yes.
Final condition. You will be sent
to a home of our choosing.
You must reside at this address.
You must not move from this address.
This is your home now.
A yes, if you understand.
We are good people.
- Yes.
Whether or not you're good people,
it's not me that needs convincing.
Where are we going?
[man] All right.
Do you speak English?
[Bol] Yes.
All right. [sighs]
This is for you.
Here we are, then.
Home sweet home. Amazing, innit?
It's a palace.
Normally, it should be half the size
with twice as many of you in it, but...
[sniffs]...this is all yours.
This is... this is all for you.
Why are we so special?
You must've won the jackpot.
Shit.
All right, a few ground rules.
Uh... no candles, no smoking,
no animals.
- Uh...
- [clinks]
- [flipping switch]
- Oh...
We'll fix that. No pets,
no guests, no friends, no parties.
No ball games, no games, no balls.
Uh...
Get some screws for your door.
There's a shop round the corner.
Uh, say hello to your neighbors
and that, and...
Yeah, you'll be all right.
[clicking]
Didn't have time
to get the cleaners, but...
give it a wipe down.
[flies buzzing]
There's a doctor down the road.
I'll draw you a map.
I wouldn't worry about the smell.
Open a window, the place should air out.
Main thing is it's yours.
A new beginning starts
with a single step, innit?
[angry yelling]
Confident signature.
I work in a bank.
I worked in a bank.
[speaking Dinka]
[speaking in English] Rial...
- Eh?
- This entire house is just for us?
Yeah.
All of it.
Home.
Bigger than my house.
I think you two are gonna be all right.
As long as you can get along, fit in.
- We are not going back.
- That's the spirit.
Make it easy for people.
Be one of the good ones.
[children shouting outside]
[distant siren blaring]
[vehicle accelerating]
[gasps]
[groans]
[laughs]
[whimpers]
[sighs]
- [music plays from phone]
- [switch flipping]
[flips switch]
[grunts]
[sighs]
We will be new here.
We're born again.
Born again.
[Bol sighs]
[music playing]
[turns music off]
[shouts and laughter outside]
- [glass smashes]
- [laughter]
Hm.
[female voice hums] ♪ Hm, hm, hm ♪
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- [loud thump]
- [gasps]
- [laughter]
- [running footsteps]
- [panting]
- [whispering sounds]
[sounds of screaming]
Shh. Shh...
- [sounds of shouting]
- Sh, sh, sh...
[shouting and screaming grow louder]
[woman screaming]
[woman screams]
[sounds fading]
[exhales]
- [distant shouting outside]
- [female voice] ♪ Hm, hm ♪
[clicking sounds]
[rustling sounds]
[rustling and skittering sounds]
- [loud thump]
- [gasps]
Hello?
[rustling and skittering]
[garbled voice calls softly]
[clicking sounds]
[rustling]
[gasps]
[wooden clattering]
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
[rustling]
[soft thud]
[gasping scream]
[gasps]
- [screeches]
- [gasps]
[cawing]
[wings fluttering]
Strange country.
[crow caws]
[door opens]
[metal clicking]
[speaks Dinka]
[children playing outside]
[crows cawing]
[speaking in English] Look.
It's their queen.
[chuckles]
[Rial laughs] Mm.
Where is Charles?
[both laughing]
Aah...
[dog barking]
[whirring]
Where are we?
High Street, mate.
In London?
[chuckles] Why not?
[church bell ringing]
[man whistles]
You one of them refugees?
Got something for ya.
[crowd cheering]
[man 1] This is the cavalry
coming home for Stoke City.
Crouch began perfectly...
[man 2] Bad selection of players
to me going in.
[man yells] Come on, lino!
Hey!
[laughter]
♪ He's big, he's red ♪
♪ His feet stick out the bed ♪
♪ Peter Crouch ♪
♪ He's big, he's red ♪
[all] ♪ His feet stick out the bed ♪
♪ Peter Crouch ♪
You were singing songs
about this Peter Crouch?
Adult men.
It's just a funny song.
I think it is the worst song
I've ever heard.
[laughs]
[sighs]
Maybe I'll go out tomorrow.
Wonderful.
- [laughter outside]
- [music thumps from car radio]
[car accelerates]
- [sighs]
- [men talking outside]
[vehicle approaching]
[vehicle accelerates away]
[soft thumping sounds]
[footsteps climbing]
[footsteps continue]
- [dragging sounds]
- [footsteps continue]
[steps creaking]
[lightbulb buzzing softly]
[soft clattering sound]
[flips switch]
[flipping switch]
- [wind whistling]
- [water dripping]
[creaking]
[grunts]
[loud crash]
[water dripping]
[grunts]
[thumping sounds]
[creaking]
[echoing groaning]
[gasping]
[yelps]
[gasps]
[female voice humming] ♪ Hm-hm, hm-hm ♪
[sighs]
[dog barking]
[child's voice] Mama?
Bol?
[distant siren wailing]
[door creaks]
"Church Street."
[boy] Hello.
Hello? Oi. Hello?
[scoffs]
[music from car radio]
[baby crying]
[children playing]
[dog barking]
- [scrabbling at fence]
- [loud barking]
[barking continues]
[woman shouting]
[barking continuing]
[motorcycle engine roaring]
- [woman talking]
- [boy 1] All right, want some chips?
Want some chips?
- Mate, do you want takeaway?
- [boy 2] No, I...
[boy 3] Bruv, I want wings, bruv,
I don't want chips.
[whooping]
[boy 3]
I don't want what's in your box, bruv.
- [boy 1] All right, get another one.
- [boy 2] Hey.
- I don't want you to have one, anyway.
- Them chips are wet, bruv.
Um, these chips are nice.
- What the fuck are you doing?
- What's all this?
- [Rial speaks Dinka]
- [in English] What's your problem, bro?
- [chuckling]
- Go speak to your auntie, Sam.
- [Rial speaks Dinka]
- Owww!
- [in English] Watch it!
- Fam, your auntie.
- Chat to her, bro.
- Aw, you need to chat to her, bruv.
- [Rial] Can you help me?
- Mm.
- You all right?
- Can you...
- Stop...
- [Rial] Where is Church Street?
- Pardon?
- Sorry?
- Church Street.
- [mimics accent] Touch Street?
- Church?
- Church...
[mimicking] Touch Street?
Church Street, darlin', yeah?
But anyways, it's that side,
I think, on the left.
- Bruv, what are you talkin' about?
- What do you mean?
Take this left here,
walk all the way down to the end.
- It's just on the right hand side, yeah?
- Are you nuts?
- Nah, it's like, down there, by the bank.
- Yeah.
- You're chattin' shit.
- You know the bank?
- Oh! No, no, no, he's right still.
- Is he?
No, he's right still. Yeah, sorry, my bad.
No, it is. Head back that way.
- It's just by the bank, yeah.
- You sure?
- For real, 100 percent.
- Yeah.
- [speaks Dinka]
- [speaks in English] Apafa-what?
- Go back to fuckin' Africa, man.
- [all laughing loudly]
Is it... Stop foolin' about.
- [mimicking Rial's accent]
- [laughing]
- [whooping]
- You better upgrade them ankles!
Go back to Africa.
Only English around here, darlin'.
[chuckles]
[machine whirrs]
I love your necklace.
It was Nyagak's.
Oh, is that your daughter?
Mine's a real handful.
You registered her yet?
We should take a look at her, too.
- [machine bleeps]
- Perfectly normal.
[undoes cuff]
Those are pretty.
These I've had since I was a little girl.
Mm.
These I gave to myself with a knife.
When I found my family butchered.
There are two tribes where I'm from.
They're both killing each other.
Depending on which one you belong to,
you mark yourself.
I marked myself with both.
I survived by belonging nowhere.
We lost her.
When we crossed the sea.
[liquid splashing]
[splashing stops]
[girl] Hurry up!
I think there's someone living there.
Mm.
[male voice] Come.
- [rustling]
- [clattering]
Come.
[overlapping whispering voices]
[voices continuing]
- [door slams]
- [keys rattle]
[distant siren wailing]
- [drops coat]
- [dog barking outside]
[siren and barking continuing]
[sighs] I'm sorry. I lost track of time.
You went outside?
- Wonderful.
- [shoes fall]
Wonderful! [clears throat]
But maybe next time, we can use the table.
[sighs]
[vehicle pulls up outside]
[car door slams]
[clattering]
[Bol chuckles]
All I can taste is the metal.
You will get used to it.
Hm! Mm, mm!
Mm, mm, mm.
We will thrive.
I have seen jobs here.
They give you a chance here.
We can start a family.
I am restless.
My mother used to tell me a story.
In our village, there was once
an honorable but poor man
who wanted a home of his own.
He wanted it so badly,
he began to steal from others.
One day...
he stole from an old man
who lived by the river.
He didn't know that this man was an apeth.
A night witch.
And so the thief could not know
that when he built his home...
the apeth, too, would live there.
So, before long,
the walls would whisper
the spells of the apeth.
From the shadows...
the dead would come.
The apeth would not stop...
until he had consumed the man entirely.
An apeth has arisen from the ocean.
It has followed us here.
It spoke to me.
- [loud clattering sound]
- [heavy thump]
[sighs] What did it say?
We don't belong here.
If we leave...
and repay our debt...
[sobs]
...it would guide us back to her.
[gasps]
To Nyagak.
[sobs]
[breathing shakily]
She's gone.
My love, she's gone.
- The sea took her.
- You're not listening.
- We survived.
- [in Dinka] If we missed something...
English!
- I will speak my mother's language.
- Listen to what you are saying.
- [in Dinka] She lives!
- She's dead!
- [yells in Dinka]
- [crockery breaks]
[Bol yells in Dinka]
[in English]
We have grieved enough. Enough.
There is no witch.
I had assured myself it was a dream.
Perhaps I am...
[breathes shakily]...overwhelmed...
imagining things that aren't there.
But now I have looked into your eyes.
You're a liar.
[loud tearing]
[sighs]
[dog barking outside]
[scraping]
[sighs]
[door opens]
[door creaks]
Rial?
[dragging sound]
[running footsteps]
[female voice sighs]
[female voice hums] ♪ Hm, hm, hm ♪
[humming continues]
[humming grows louder]
[Bol sighs]
- [male voice joins in humming]
- [loud tapping]
[creaking]
[humming stops]
[loud crash]
[running footsteps]
[child's voice] Mama.
[gasping]
[gasps]
[child] Mama.
Mama.
[knife thuds]
- Mama.
- Nya?
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
- [knife thumps]
- Mama.
[knife thumps]
Mama.
- [screeches] Mama!
- [yelps]
[running footsteps]
- [screeching]
- [Bol grunts]
- [Nyagak yells]
- [gasping]
[Nyagak hums] ♪ Hm, hm ♪
- [running footsteps]
- [whispering and humming]
[overlapping voices]
[gasping]
[cat mews]
[purring]
Huh.
[whirring]
You saw it.
- [rumbling]
- [creaking]
[door creaking]
Bol.
What are you doing?
We have to destroy everything.
It's cursed.
- Everything we brought is cursed.
- Bol, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
Leave it! Stop!
No, that's my father's.
[Bol] We've been marked!
What do you mean marked?
What did you see?
[gasps] Wha...
Bol?
[flame whooshes]
- Oh... Why? Don't!
- Let...
[Rial gasps]
[sobs]
[in Dinka] Don't leave me with nothing.
[in English] Don't.
[gasps]
[drops necklace]
[flames hissing]
[radio chatter]
[thumping]
[grunting]
[panting]
- [thump]
- [yelps]
[bulb buzzing]
[Rial whispers]
He doesn't want to leave you.
Perhaps if you spoke to him...
[Rial sighs]
Perhaps you think we're going mad.
I think it's not healthy
for you to be alone all the time.
Dwelling with your thoughts.
Tomorrow, we will find you
something to do.
Something in the community.
Make friends, be good.
- We are not like them.
- We can be.
You don't wonder what it tells me?
You are right.
Maybe you are mad.
Frightening yourself
with imaginary things in the dark.
After all we've endured,
after what we have seen...
what men can do, you think it is
bumps in the night that frighten me?
You think I can be afraid of ghosts?
[scoffs]
It says I can get her back.
And it says I should be afraid of you.
This is our home.
- [bulb buzzing]
- [plate rattling]
[water sloshing]
[male voice speaks in Dinka]
[voice continues speaking]
- [splashing]
- [wind whistling]
[overlapping voices murmuring]
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
[splashing]
[gasps]
[yells]
[footsteps outside]
[murmur of voices]
[creaking]
- [loud creaking]
- [growls]
[gasping]
[moaning]
- Oh...
- [light bulb buzzing]
[Nyagak whispers in English] Help me.
[floorboards creaking]
[footsteps growing louder]
[Nyagak] I'm cold.
[footsteps crashing]
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
[footsteps stop]
[low screeching]
[screeching]
- [gasps]
- [Nyagak] Help me, I...
- [floorboards creaking]
[angry male voice muttering and growling]
- [male voice] Help me. Help me.
- [muttering and growling continue]
I can't breathe. Help me.
- Help me.
- [Nyagak sobs] I can't swim.
- [creaking]
- I can't swim.
- [whispering]
- [male voice] I can't breathe!
[loud thumping running footsteps]
- [light bulb buzzing]
- [Nyagak] Mama?
Mama?
[creaking]
[overlapping voices] Mama?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
[voices whispering]
[Nyagak whispers] Mama.
[growling]
[yelps]
[breathing heavily]
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Nyagak?
- [yelps]
- growling]
- [hissing]
- [screeching]
- [yells]
- [moaning]
[yells]
- [screeching]
- [yelps]
[yelling]
- [creatures growling]
- [Bol yelling]
[gasping]
[hyperventilating]
[light bulb buzzing]
[breathing slows]
[choking]
[sobs]
[gasps]
- [whispers]
- [Bol yelps]
- [skittering]
- [thumping]
[thumping footsteps]
[Bol whispers] This is my house.
[yells] This is my house!
Get out!
Get out! Get out!
[yelling]
[yells] This is my house!
- My house!
- [hammer thudding]
[yelling]
[car horn blares]
[radio playing softly]
Adam, uh...
do you wanna get him some juice?
So, Bol, what's goin' on?
The house.
[Mark] The house.
You havin' problems with the property?
- [liquid pouring]
- [sighs]
You wanna live somewhere else?
- [microwave pings]
- Mm.
Oh. Okay.
- [Bol] Yes?
- Uh...
Sure, yeah, we can look into that for you.
But first, you have to tell me why.
I mean, can you name me
one of the problems?
There are... vermin.
Rats and bugs.
They are making us sick.
Rial is very ill.
Has she seen a doctor?
- Yes.
- Good.
He says...
"Get out of the house."
We have to move.
Where?
[Adam] His house is bigger than mine.
[man] Bigger than mine, too.
Uh...
Look, mate, this is...
this is gonna raise
a lot of questions... Bol.
I... [swallows]
They're gonna ask you
why you're not adapting.
- Adapting?
- [Mark] Adapting.
We are adapting.
[photocopier whirring]
[sighs]
I used to work in a bank, too,
believe it not,
back in the day,
before they moved all the jobs...
abroad.
[chair creaking]
[sighs] The point is, many of us, we end
up in places we never thought we'd be.
But I think...
I think that's life trying to show you
what kind of man you are.
Do you know what I'm sayin'?
I'm tryin' to work out
what kind of man you are, Bol.
I just need a new house.
- And we'll get you one.
- [pen clicking]
Right after the inquiry.
- [Bol] Inquiry?
- Yeah.
Look at the state of you. You're a mess.
You don't look well, mate, you look ill.
You don't smell good. You smell bad.
You're not making any sense.
It would have to be reported. And then...
people, not me,
but people are then gonna ask,
"Why is he bitin'
the hand that's feedin' him?"
- We can live anywhere else.
- There's rats everywhere.
- Anywhere else.
- Oh, right. So it's not about the rats.
[sighs] There's something... very wrong
- in...
- What is that?
- What is it? Tell me.
- [laughs]
Can't be that bad, you're laughin'.
If you want me to make a fuss,
mate, I will make a fuss.
- Yes!
- If you want me to do it, then I will.
Yes! [laughs]
[glass crunches and snaps]
[Mark] Bol.
Hang on.
[Nyagak] Mama.
[running footsteps]
[men shouting in distance]
[woman] Why don't you just leave?
What?
Why don't you just leave?
We live here now.
They're gonna kick you out anyway.
I'm tryin' to help you.
I'll give it a week.
[brakes squealing]
[dog barking]
Must be big rats.
Telling me that rats...
did this?
Come on, man.
Well, I'm...
I'm gonna have to report it now.
Please. Please...
No, I'm gonna have to.
I'm gonna have to take photos.
- No, please. No.
- [shutter clicking]
No. No!
Let me fix it.
We are not going back.
Please.
We are one of the good ones. Remember?
We are not going back.
Yep. All right then, mist...
Mr. Majur, we will let you off
with a warning this time.
- Hang... hang on a minute.
- Let me deal with it.
[Rial] Have you told them about the witch?
[footsteps]
You haven't told them?
[scoffs]
There's a great beast in this house.
It followed us here.
My husband's been chasing it
all night with a hammer.
It knows great magic.
It's filling this house with ghosts.
It torments my husband
with visits from her.
Nyagak.
But my husband is a very stubborn man.
He still believes he can deny it.
You should put that into your report.
- [men shouting]
- [dog barking]
[Mark] We'd better write 'em up.
They can kiss England goodbye.
[man] Dude, she was wearing her bedsheets.
[Rial] This is what they want.
- They like to see us crazy.
- [van engine starts]
- Makes them feel like big men.
- [van drives off]
They don't want to be reminded
that it is them that are weak.
How poor...
and lazy...
and bored they are.
Rial.
Now, sorry.
- Sorry, sorry, sorry...
- Rial.
And you...
You still idolize them.
[laughing] You beg them.
And then you thank them
for the unseasoned scraps they throw us.
You eat them up.
Let them send us back.
But this is our home.
We're going back.
I'm leaving. With or without you.
How quickly you forget everything
we went through to get here.
How quickly you forget our daugh...
You are sick.
This is our home.
You are not going anywhere.
[thump]
This time, you talk to me.
[breathing slowly]
[creaking]
[breathing sounds]
[faint howling sounds]
[sighs]
[exhaling]
Where are you?
[male voice, echoing] Thief.
- [faint chattering sounds]
- [Bol] Show yourself.
[howling]
[creature whispers]
Your life is not yours.
[echoing] You stole it.
Repay what you owe.
[Bol] You are a beast.
[creature] You are the beast.
And I am the butcher.
No matter where you go, I follow.
You are mine now.
What do you want?
Your life for Nyagak.
What?
[knife swooshes]
Take this knife and open your flesh.
[echoing] Your body for hers.
Why don't you come for me yourself?
You can't touch me.
You can't touch me. You can't hurt me.
[laughs] You're just a bag of tricks.
Make yourself at home.
Pictures can't hurt me.
- [laughs]
- [creature hissing]
[echoing] Why don't you sleep?
[thunder crashing]
[wind howling]
No.
No, no, stop!
No, stop.
Stop! Stop! Stop!
Stop! Stop!
[thunder crashing]
Pictures can't hurt me.
[whispers] Pictures, pictures,
pictures can't hurt me.
[gasps] No!
[screaming]
[faint skittering]
[skittering]
[creaking and tapping]
Rial!
No. No, no.
- Get off.
- Come.
- Get off me.
- Come back.
- Don't touch me! Stop!
- Get back!
- Stay in the house!
- Get off me! [grunts]
- [grunts]
- [Bol yells]
[groans]
- [panting]
- [grunts]
Hey!
[thumping]
- Rial!
- [banging]
- [gasping]
[thumping]
[yells] Rial!
[gasping]
- [banging]
- [Bol] Rial!
Rial!
[birdsong]
[children playing]
[laughter]
Rial? [speaking Dinka]
Ohhhh! [speaking Dinka]
- [gasps]
- [sighs]
[both speaking Dinka]
Oh!
[choir singing in Dinka]
[ululating]
[singing and ululating continue]
[whooping]
[silence falls]
[woman whispering softly]
[in Dinka] I know what you are.
This is just a dream.
[woman starts singing in Dinka]
- [women join in song]
- [Rial] Where is she?
Who?
My daughter.
[singing continues]
[ululating]
[ululating grows louder]
[sounds fade]
[Bol] Rial?
Rial?
[fly buzzing]
Rial!
[distant machine-gun fire]
[gunfire]
[gunfire continues]
[footsteps]
Rial. Hey. Come.
Come. It's okay. I'm here.
I'm here. I'm here.
Rial?
Rial.
Look at me. Look. Look at me.
We have to leave now.
Now. We have to go. Come.
Rial. Rial!
Please, please, please, please.
Rial. Please. Rial.
Come. Come.
- [flies buzzing]
- Come.
Rial, come.
[flies buzzing]
Come, come, come.
[murmur of voices]
[laughter]
[explosions]
[distant gunfire]
[explosions continue]
[crickets chirping]
[people shouting]
[Bol] Come.
Hurry.
[woman] Come, come, come.
- Come, come forward.
- We are going to make space.
[woman] That's it. That's it now.
- You have space for two more?
- Too many. No.
Two more! Two more! Two more!
- Please!
- Children only!
Come, come, come. That's it.
- No. Get off.
- You have space!
- No, no, no! You wait!
- No, sir. No, sir.
- Please!
- Mama.
That's it. Too many now.
- We're full. We are full.
- Please.
- Wait. Wait!
- Mama.
- I'm sorry. Now come...
- [machine-gun fire]
[screaming]
We have to go, sir.
- I said children. You are not a child.
- Wait...
No! We have to go! We have to go!
- No!
- She... She's a child! She's a child!
- Please!
- [people clamoring]
[gunfire]
[thumping]
[Bol] Excuse me, excuse me, excuse me.
Thank you.
[thumping continues]
[woman] Nyagak!
- [Nyagak screams] Mama!
- Nyagak!
- Mama! Mama!
- Sh, sh, sh.
- Mama!
- [thumping on windows]
- [engine roars]
- Nyagak!
- Mama!
- Nyagak! Nyagak!
- [screams] Nyagak!
- Mama!
- [wails]
- Mama! Mama!
- Sh, sh. Sh, sh.
- It's fine. It's fine. It's fine.
- Mama!
Mama!
- [mother] Nyagak!
- Mama!
[crying] Nyagak!
- [gunfire]
- Nyagak! [screams]
[screams and sobs echoing]
[woman] You have no daughter.
[in Dinka] I'll protect you.
[sobbing]
[wind whistling]
- [crash]
- [gasping]
[whirring sound]
[echoing sound of waves crashing]
[shivering] Is she...
Is she dead?
Nyagak!
[screams] Nyagak!
[screaming and shouting]
Nyagak!
No, let me go!
Bol! Nyagak!
Nyagak!
[Nyagak screaming]
[sobs]
[gasping]
[sobbing]
[sniffling]
[gasps]
[creature] I can bring her back.
[sniffles]
[metal scraping]
Sever his flesh.
Give me his body...
and I will give you what you want.
[water dripping]
- [rainfall]
- [dog barking]
[barking continues]
[rattling]
[clattering]
[Bol sniffs]
[low creaking sound]
[groans]
[creaking]
[sighs]
[creaking continuing]
[Nyagak] Mama.
[creaking]
[turns tap on]
[water running]
[turns tap off]
[clattering and scraping]
- [knife swishes]
- [Bol groans]
[clattering]
[scraping]
[sighs]
- [sighs]
- Oh... [murmurs in Dinka]
[gasps]
This is what it wants.
- [gasps]
- It will come for me now.
[Rial sniffles]
- [gasps]
- Let me save her.
[creaking]
[sobbing]
- [sighs heavily]
- I should have tried harder.
I should have saved her.
I see them, too.
[gasps]
[whispers] What do you see?
I see her.
All of them.
[blood dripping]
From the boat, from home.
[sobs]
And what does that make us?
- [sniffles]
- [low voices chanting]
He's coming.
[sobs]
[rumbling]
[Bol] He's coming. You must go.
Go!
[creaking]
[stone scraping]
[rattling]
[rumbling]
- [rumbling intensifying]
- [cracking]
[thump]
[bulb buzzing and pinging]
[thumping]
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
[gasps]
- [hissing]
- [yelps and groans]
- [Bol yelling]
- [hissing]
[growling]
- [groaning]
You are mine.
- [clicking]
- [Rial gasps]
[growling]
[Bol yells]
- [hissing]
- [groaning]
[whimpering]
[screams]
- [screaming]
- [growling]
[Bol yelling]
Aaaaah!
[growling]
[birdsong]
[Rial] I have to say goodbye now.
I'm going home.
- [Bol screaming]
- [roaring]
[Bol yelling]
[screams]
- [yells]
- [roars]
- [grunts]
- [gasps]
- [groans]
- [thump]
[panting]
[knocking]
Hello, Rial. Sorry to bother you.
Uh, we work with Mark. May we come in?
Come in.
[shutter clicking]
[dog barking outside]
[crackling]
[shutter clicking]
You seem well.
[footsteps climbing stairs]
[Mark] Is there still a witch?
Rial killed it.
[chuckles]
I think I might paint this room red.
Hm.
Are you completely mad?
What about the rats?
- [shutter clicks]
- Perhaps I was being a little dramatic.
Do you still see her?
Nyagak?
Your ghosts follow you.
They never leave.
They live with you.
It's when I let them in,
I could start to face myself.
This is our home.
We are happy here.
[man] They shouldn't be using a barbecue.
[woman] And they shouldn't be
doing that to the walls.
All right, then.
That'd be all.
[man] Right.
Thank you, Mr. and Mrs. Majur.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[slow music plays]
[slow music continues]