You got to help me look for a new place.
My nosy neighbors are getting worse.
They are saying I come home late
because I'm a hooker.
Does that bother you?
Nope. But I'm not a hooker.
Maybe it's easier being a hooker.
You sleep with them then they pay you.
Wouldn't be that easy.
You have to put make-up on every night.
And your client may be rough or too big.
You have to know how to pick them.
And how would you do that?
How would I know if a client
is rough or too big beforehand?
I'd check before
I'd agree to sleep with them.
If his dick was limp, how would you know
it would be too big?
I would know.
You wouldn't
because you're a clueless virgin.
Hang on, a car is coming.
You didn't put me on speaker?
If the boss finds out,
you'll be in trouble.
Done.
Aren't you using up all your phone data?
I don't care.
Tonight's so quiet, it's creepy.
Who's on your shift with you?
Mr. Chondro was here. But he left
for the office. I don't know why.
They're closing this toll booth soon.
Not many cars come through this gate.
Soon no one will be assigned
to any gate.
It's ridiculous that they are replacing
everybody with machines.
Nobody will have a job.
That's why we need to start
our clothing store soon.
I won't miss this. I won't have to deal
with so many weird people.
Like the guy in the old sedan
that has been stalking me for weeks.
I told you. Maybe he's just coming home
from work every day.
Dini, he drove by here twice
or three times in one night.
Isn't that strange?
And he looks at me as if
he's going to eat me alive.
What are you, a newbie?
I already told you.
Don't ever look the drivers
in their eyes.
Just look at their hands.
His hands were gross.
Dirty fingernails and all.
Maybe he's a gravedigger.
You're not helping. It's easy for you,
you're not alone there.
Who is stationed there with you?
I got that dude Wahyu.
He's always looking my way.
He's been driving me home
these past three days.
Is Wahyu really into second-hand items?
Can't you listen to other songs?
It's so last century it sounds creepy.
No. My radio's stuck in AM.
The FM mode is not working.
Shit.
What's wrong?
That creepy car is here again.
Hello?
Maya?
He's still here.
Oh, no. What is he doing?
He's staring at me.
I'm calling the office.
He's finally gone. Thank you, Sir!
Shit, my heart almost stopped.
Din! It's still here!
He's walking towards my post!
What should I do?
Din!
Stay calm. I'm calling the office.
Can someone come
to Bukit Selatan 1 gate now?
Someone is harassing an officer.
Now, please!
Okay, okay. Just stay calm.
Lock the door! Close the window!
Find something near you!
What do you mean?
A metal stick, a rock,
anything you can use as a weapon?
There's nothing here. I'm so dead!
Security guards are coming!
Are you Rahayu?
No, my name's Maya. Can't you read?
- Is that your real name?
- Yes.
Hey! Don't mess with her! Go away!
Are you from Harjosari Village
in Mandiraja?
What do you want?
Is your father's name Ki Donowongso?
Maya!
He's going away. He's going.
If help doesn't come in a minute,
just get out of there. Leave the booth!
Is anyone coming
to the Bukit Selatan 1 booth?
Dini, he's coming back with a weapon!
What weapon?
Maya!
Help!
Hey!
Drop your weapon!
We...
We just don't want
what your family left behind.
Please take it away.
Hey, you wanna check my new collection?
Not now.
Pay for the shirt
you bought last week then.
I can't pay you right now.
But you got lots of customers!
Exactly. I'm busy now.
Come on. Just get your purse
and give me my money.
You need a new bra?
We should've checked first...
...whether this market
was good for business.
Relax.
We got duped because the rent is cheap.
We'll sell these online.
These crappy fakes?
That's why we'll sell them online.
Even I wouldn't wear one of these.
I'd rather wear a plastic bag
or a rice sack.
Sorry I dragged you into this.
We used up all your money.
It's not like you put a gun to my head.
I wanted to join this business.
I'm going away for a week or so.
Where to?
Who are they?
After the attack,
I dug into my late aunt's stuff.
I found this photo.
I think they're my parents.
You "think"?
I never saw photos of them before.
And I was too young
to really remember them.
Rahayu?
So the psycho dude was right?
I do remember my aunt
called me Rahayu when I was young.
Then she started calling me Maya.
I don't know why.
So what?
Look at the photo again.
What do you notice?
You were really short
for a five-year-old?
The house?
The big house.
It's the key to solving our problems.
My family's house.
But you don't even know where it is.
The psycho mentioned
the name of the village.
Harjosari, Mandiraja. I looked it up.
This could be our chance
to start a new life.
I'm going with you.
No.
You are my best friend.
No way I let you go alone.
And if you turn out to be rich,
you can't leave me behind.
What about our kiosk?
Nobody comes to buy our stuff anyway.
Hey! You can't smoke in there!
You can't be in here, pervert!
This is the ladies room.
Shut up! Get the hell out of here!
What happened?
It's the wound.
How come it still looks fresh?
I don't know.
I just need some disinfectant.
Because I know it's not that time
of the month for you.
Stay here.
I'll get you some disinfectant.
Dini?
You haven't gone home?
We will soon.
Dini?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
People are getting lazier these days.
They turn the lights off early
and lock the doors.
The pharmacy is closed.
No medicine for you, then.
HAVE A PLEASANT TRIP
What are you reading?
Business planning.
What business?
Any business. So I know my way around
if we're to start another.
Besides, if I don't read,
I'll just go to the toilet all the time.
Turn off your light.
The guy behind us is annoyed.
Goddamn hillbilly.
How long until we get there?
The driver said six hours.
See, now I have to pee.
Use this, Love.
You're not going to need it?
It's okay. I'm not cold. Go to sleep.
I'll wake you up
when we reach your parents' village.
I wasn't bothered by you or your friend.
I cough sometimes so the spirits
on this bus won't bother the passengers.
Spirits?
There are spirits on this bus.
They don't know where to go.
Don't think I'm weird.
I am a university lecturer.
A lecturer? What do you teach?
Russian literature.
I know
it's not much use in this country.
But I love Russian.
Well, I love all languages.
You know Javanese?
Why would I study foreign languages
if I don't know my own?
Do you know what this says?
This is very ancient Javanese.
It's a spell so that the carrier
won't be bothered by evil spirits.
So this is like an amulet?
Yes. But this was made
by an evil person.
Where did you get this picture?
From the internet.
What's on your mind?
Nothing.
You're thinking about your parents?
Do you know anything about them at all?
No. My aunt raised me.
And she wasn't much of a talker.
If I asked her about my parents,
she wouldn't say much.
Parents are overrated.
I've known my parents all my life.
It didn't do me any good.
Didn't make me happier.
But at least you know them.
That's true. Especially if your parents
may have left you with a fortune.
But we really have to be careful.
That's why we're going there
just to check things out.
If I do have some sort
of inheritance there,...
...we'll come back with a lawyer.
Lawyer? How fancy.
Thank you for coming with me.
Don't mention it.
Just pray we won't have to stay
in a place with roaches.
- Holy shit!
- What's wrong?
I swear I saw
those three little girls...
...standing by the side
of the road earlier.
It's 1 a.m. All children are sleeping.
I swear to God!
How long did you say
before we get there?
Five hours.
Have you heard of Harjosari?
Harjosari? Never heard of it, Miss.
Where did you look the place up? Google?
I tried but couldn't find it.
So I called the Provincial government.
It's there under their territory.
Well nobody ever heard of it.
We've only asked one person.
Have you heard of Harjosari Village?
Yes.
Can you take us there?
No.
Why?
It's too far.
How much?
A hundred thousand Rupiah.
Okay.
For each of you.
Where are you from?
"Bloodsuckers Village"?
No, I'm from "Handsome
and Rich Village".
Wait until my horse finishes his lunch.
When did you last feed him?
Last month?
Last year.
Why do you want to go to Harjosari?
We're university students
and we're doing research.
In Harjosari?
Research on what?
Why are you laughing?
There's nothing in Harjosari.
It's a secluded village.
That's right. We're doing research
on secluded villages.
I see.
What do you know about the village?
Not much.
I know about the village...
...because I recently took
their village elder home.
The village elder is a puppet master.
He was in my town for a performance.
What's his name?
Ki Saptadi.
He's quite well-known.
Why don't they build
a proper road to the village?
I heard they didn't want to.
Why?
I don't know.
Dini, please take off those sunglasses.
But it's so sunny. I'm dizzy.
What's your plan?
Miss, where do you want me
to drop you off?
Just drop us off at Ki Saptadi's,
the village elder's house.
- Okay.
- Are you sure?
Well, I don't think
we can find a hotel here.
Are we staying the night
in this village?
I don't know.
What do you mean you don't know?
Depends on the situation.
We don't even know
if my house still exists.
I didn't ask you to come with me.
Don't be fussy.
Holy shit, it's huge.
Do you know whose house that is?
I don't know.
I asked Ki Saptadi
when we passed the house,...
...but he didn't say anything.
What a waste, right?
A house that big sitting empty.
Do you want me to wait for you?
No, but thanks a lot.
Here's my business card just in case.
Thank you.
Let's go, Gorgeous.
We need to come up with a new story.
We can't say
that we're university students.
Why not?
What should we say
if he starts to ask about our research?
I don't know anything about it. Do you?
Just don't say that we're students.
What then?
Let me think.
Who are you looking for?
We are university students, Ma'am.
We are hoping to see Ki Saptadi.
What for?
We are writing a book on puppet masters.
We heard Ki Saptadi
is a famous puppet master.
He isn't home.
He'll be back in the evening.
You can come back here tomorrow morning.
Ok, we'll come back tomorrow.
Should we call the horse driver
to take us back?
And return here tomorrow?
What a hassle.
There's a pathway.
I think someone must come here often.
We'll have to make a huge sign
saying, "Do Not Enter!"
It's huge.
Yes, it's really huge.
How long has it been
since the house was abandoned?
Not sure.
How old were you
when you moved to the city?
According to my aunt,
when I was five years old.
And you're 25 now?
So this house has been empty
for 20 years.
Who is that?
I don't know. I'm new here.
It seems that this house
was abandoned in a hurry.
What do you mean?
All the furniture is still here.
Yeah. This still works.
Where are you going?
To check the most important place
in a house.
We'll have to do
lots of pumping tonight.
This is crazy, Maya!
This house and the land
may be as big as 900 square meters!
Imagine how much money you'd get
if you sell it.
What are you doing?
I found it in the drawer,
still wrapped in a plastic bag.
Does your aunt keep
any of your parents' documents?
Not that I know of.
I bet your dad also owned
properties in other places.
We have to reclaim that property too.
My God. You may be stinking rich!
Don't you forget about me, okay?
They made a cute couple.
Are you sad?
No, I'm just puzzled.
Puzzled? Why?
I'm not in any of these photos.
I'm only in the photo
that I've shown you.
Maybe they didn't get the chance
to take your photo.
There are piles of pictures here.
None of me.
Maybe you were an ugly kid?
Don't think about it.
Maybe they just preferred to kiss you
rather than to take photos of you.
Isn't that better?
I think someone just died
and was buried.
Are you sure your parents
were buried here?
Where else would they be?
But you said you think
your folks left in a hurry.
You meant they had to leave
the village right?
You might be right.
Let's just finish this row
then we go back to the house.
Can we go back to the house now?
Dead people are just dead people.
Why are you afraid of the graveyard?
I'm not scared.
I just don't see the point.
Dead people should just be cremated.
So they won't take up space like this.
It's better to turn the land
into housing for the living.
You have to promise me.
When I die, please cremate my body.
And spread my ashes in the sea.
I might get reincarnated as a fish.
It's better than being a human.
You'll get caught by fishermen
and turned into sushi.
I'll be a shark. And eat humans.
Sharks don't eat humans.
Unless they're really hungry.
They're here.
Okay, you've seen their graves.
Now let's go.
Hold on.
Do you know the prayer for dead people?
You're asking me?
Just say it in Indonesian.
You think God only speaks Arabic?
What did you pray for anyway?
So that they rest in peace.
Did you pray
so you can get their fortune?
That too.
Good.
Maya, why are there
so many children's graves?
Maybe they're not children,
just really tiny graves.
Just look at the dates.
They didn't even have names.
What is up with your village, Maya?
HARJOSARI CEMETERY
COURTESY OF THE DONOWONGSO
It seems that the villagers
don't really like your family.
Dini!
What?
Did you hear something?
Yes.
I heard your annoying voice.
I'm serious.
I'm so tired.
How can you sleep
in a dusty bed like this?
Shut up.
Shit.
Dear Almighty.
Give me pain that I can bear.
What are you doing?
I think someone just died.
Again?
Maya, where are you going?
Within two days, two people have died.
No wonder this village seems empty.
Wait!
What are we going to say?
Just be cool.
I heard that you came
to my house to see me.
Yes, Sir.
You are writing a book
about Wayang (Javanese shadow puppetry)?
For our university, Sir.
We are university students.
Why do you choose this village?
We've visited other villages
that are still performing Wayang.
Then we heard about you.
So we came here.
How old are the both of you?
We're 20 years old, Sir.
We are very sorry to come
during an inconvenient time.
Don't worry about it.
Come to my house if you want to talk.
Thank you so much, Sir.
We need to leave this village now.
What?
This place creeps me out.
They look like
they're going to eat us alive,...
...and someone dies here
on a daily basis.
Probably just a coincidence.
No way.
If you're desperate
about your inheritance,...
...we can send someone to come here
and take care of it.
You think we can afford that?
We're broke.
We can't even pay rent this month.
We'll figure something out.
We always do.
Look, we're here now.
We just have to stay a little longer.
We may not have to spend another night.
We'll ask Ki Saptadi if the house
actually belongs to my family.
Then, we go.
We have to ask him in a gentle manner.
Yes, a very gentle way.
I'm not sure of this idea.
Come on, Din. We can do this.
How are you going to ask him
about the house...
...without revealing that you're Rahayu?
It's risky.
Someone tried to kill you, remember?
And most likely
it was because of the house.
Understood. So let's just play along
as students.
Nobody kills students.
I'm gonna go back to the house.
I stink like a dead racoon.
I should take a shower.
Fine. I'll find us something to eat.
Hi, can I buy some food?
To eat here or to go?
Two to go, please.
Rice with egg and vegetables.
Do you know anything
about that big abandoned house?
Do you know who it belongs to?
A family used to live there
when I was still a child.
Who?
(speaking in Javanese)
What did she say?
My grandma said it's a house of disease.
What does she mean?
She said devils used to live there
and left a horrendous disease.
We heard that you two
spent a night here.
It's not allowed, Miss.
So sorry.
We couldn't find another place.
This old house
has been abandoned for a long time.
It's not safe. The roof might fall off.
I know. Thank you for your concern.
We're leaving soon.
I know it's a pity
a house this big is unoccupied.
But it doesn't belong to us.
So we can't use it.
Who does it belong to?
The heir of this family. A girl.
Ki Saptadi has all of the documents.
He has been waiting
for the girl to claim it...
...so he can give back
all of the documents.
So this house will no longer
be his responsibility.
Is the girl's name Rahayu?
Yes. How do you know?
Because...
...I am Rahayu.
Well, Ki Saptadi is about to go
to another village.
If you can meet him now,
he can give you the documents.
Where's your friend?
She's getting us something to eat.
She really is a college student.
I'm accompanying her.
Well, it's up to you.
If you want to wait until Ki Saptadi
is back from his trip,...
...he'll return in three days.
Three days?
But earlier today he told us
to come to his house tonight...
...so my friend could ask him
some questions for her thesis.
Yes, that was before.
But he got a sudden invitation
to perform in another village.
And it's quite far from here.
Okay, then. I'll go meet him now.
We can take you to him.
I know where he lives.
No, he is at a villager's house.
Not far from here.
Come, we'll take you there.
Are we still far?
Just a little bit more.
Why are we not talking the main road?
It's closer through here.
I think I'd better get back.
My friend is waiting for me.
What the hell?
Listen.
You don't have to rape me.
I'm no virgin.
All you have to do is ask.
Don't cut her skin.
Dini?
I brought food. Aren't you hungry?
The number you're calling
is not active or out of coverage area.
Please try again in a few minutes.
Please...
What do you want?
Please let me go.
What can I do for you
to let me go? Please...
Sir! Please help me, Sir!
I don't know what I did wrong.
If I ever wronged you,
please forgive me, Sir. I beg you...
Rahayu...
We're ready, Sir.
Mother…
Please help me, Ma'am!
What are you up to?
There are two women
who are headed into labor soon.
If we hurry, we might be able
to save their babies.
I assumed you weren't coming.
Are you here for the interview?
Actually, I'm looking for my friend.
The one who was with me earlier
when we met.
Why is she not with you?
I don't know. I left to buy some food...
...and when I returned
she wasn't at the house.
I will ask someone to look for her.
You can wait for her here if you want.
That's okay. Thank you for your help.
But I want to keep looking for her.
Very well.
I hope you're able to find her soon.
Thank you, Sir.
You're welcome.
Our baby is going to be alright.
Excuse me, Miss.
You can watch from the other side, Miss.
I want to ask Ki Saptadi
if he has any information...
...on my missing friend.
We've looked for her everywhere,
but we weren't able to find her.
We'll look again
after this show finishes.
All right. Thank you.
The number you are calling
is not active.
Where are you, Dini?
A woman is going into labour.
Come and see.
Push.
A little bit more. Come on.
Just one more push. You can do it.
You said my baby
was going to be healthy!
You're a liar!
A liar!
I'm doing all I can to help you
and everybody in this village.
Damn you!
Will my baby still be cursed?
What are you doing here?
I'm just wandering around.
Go home.
I want to see the baby.
Go home!
Come with me.
Don't worry.
I'm not like the others.
Come.
What's going on in this village?
What's wrong with the babies?
I will tell you. Come.
I have to find my friend.
I will help you look for her.
But for now you have to hide.
It's not safe.
Come. I live by myself.
Please come in. Don't worry.
My name is Ratih.
I'm not a bad person.
The baby I saw…
It's cursed.
What?
This whole village is cursed.
A cursed village? In this day and age?
Didn't you notice
anything peculiar about this village?
Haven't you noticed
there are no children here?
I saw three girls last night.
That's impossible.
There hasn't been children
in this village in 20 years.
What do you mean?
There was once a very rich man
in this village.
He was our village elder.
He and his family lived
in that big abandoned house.
They had many servants.
One of them was Nyi Misni,
Ki Saptadi's mother.
The village elder had a son.
His name was Ki Donowongso.
When his father died,
Ki Donowongso inherited all the wealth.
He was not only rich,
but also a brilliant puppet master.
He was so good
at making the puppets, too.
He was also famous
among the neighbouring villages.
Then there was Nyai Shinta,
the most beautiful woman in the village.
All the men wished to be her husband.
But Ki Donowongso
succeeded in marrying Nyai Shinta.
It was a huge wedding.
The party lasted for seven days.
Unfortunately,
after three years of marriage,...
...they could not bear a child.
Nyai Shinta was depressed and ashamed.
Finally, after five years of trying,
Nyai Shinta got pregnant.
Ki Donowongso
really took care of his wife.
They held a party every Saturday night.
He would perform
with his puppets all night long.
The weird thing is,...
...no one knew about
the baby's condition after it was born.
And no one ever saw the baby.
What do you mean?
The baby was born without skin.
Since then, Ki Donowongso refused
to mingle with the villagers.
Not long after that,...
...a five-year-old girl
in the village went missing.
She was never found.
Soon after that,
two more girls went missing.
One day, the villagers saw
Ki Donowongso's baby for the first time.
She looked so healthy, so beautiful.
It was only then that the village
learned the baby was named Rahayu.
A rumor started to spread
among the villagers.
Saying that Rahayu's father
had something to do...
...with the three missing girls.
But no one dared to confront him.
Until one night…
Ki Saptadi said Ki Donowongso
had been practicing black magic,...
...making a pact with the devil
to protect his daughter.
But then he went mad.
It was said that a loyal servant
took his daughter away to the city.
And ever since that day,
the village has been cursed.
Every baby has been born without skin.
Why do they have to kill the babies?
Because if they were allowed to live,
they would be living in misery.
You don't know that.
Perhaps there is a cure.
No. There's one baby
who was allowed to live.
He now lives in the forest.
Uncured and in constant pain.
Ki Saptadi said
in order to lift the curse,...
...the first girl who got the disease,
Rahayu, has to be skinned...
...and her skin has to be made
into leather puppets.
Why do the villagers
believe in Ki Saptadi's words?
Who else do we have to look up to here?
Is there anything else we should do?
Did we miss something?
We got the wrong girl!
You must be hungry.
I'll get you some food.
No, I'm okay. Thank you.
I'll get you some rice.
Who's that in the picture?
My husband.
Listen up!
The woman we've been looking for
is here in this village.
Yes!
You know what she looks like.
Get her!
Look for the girl!
Block all the village's exits.
The curse will be lifted soon!
Where is your husband now?
He went to the city three months ago.
He was looking for a cure.
Cure for what?
Can you feel that?
My great grandmother, whom you met
at the kiosk, is a good shaman.
She said if someone made a pact
with the devil,...
...and a curse is born,
it can never be reversed.
It will only transform
into another curse.
That's why I don't believe
in killing you, Rahayu.
It will not lift the curse.
And that's why I asked my husband
to search for a cure in the city.
I believe he will be able to find it.
Did you see the city girl?
City girl?
Yes, two city girls came to our village.
One of them is Ki Donowongso's daughter.
Ki Saptadi killed the other one.
The wrong one.
They skinned her, turned her skin
into leather puppets. What a waste.
What do you think you're doing?
You won't share some food
with your neighbors now?
No. Please go.
Why are you so hostile?
Are you lonely because your husband
has been away long?
Do you want me to stay with you tonight?
How long since you've seen
a man's erection?
Get out.
Just stab me.
Or I'll kill myself.
Then my ghost will haunt you
for the rest of your life.
Pigs!
Come on, Miss.
I'm so sorry about your friend.
I need to get out of this village
as soon as possible.
Stay here for a while.
It's not safe out there.
They won't come again.
We don't know that.
At least if I run now, I might be able
to escape from the villagers.
Dini...
Dini. My best friend.
This is all my fault.
No, it's not.
It's the work of the devil
and weak humans.
Do you have a mobile phone?
Hello?
Miss? I'm with a police officer.
We're on our way.
We're taking a motorbike so it's faster.
We're almost there.
Thank you. I'll be there.
They're almost there.
She said to meet her
at the North Entrance.
I know where it is.
Then, can we drive faster?
This the fastest I can go.
I've met your husband.
He tried to kill me.
I was working and he came to me.
He was shot by the policeman, and died.
Please forgive me, Ratih.
Is this it?
Yes, this is the North Entrance.
Brother Suryo.
Evening, Brother.
Bambang?
I told you to stay put.
I can handle this by myself.
We just want to help.
Who are you, people?
We're from this village.
You know them?
I'm from here, too. Me and my wife.
Didn't I tell you?
No, you didn't.
- Listen, Mister?
- I'm Nano.
Don't worry, Mr. Nano.
Our village is safe
and the villagers are friendly.
Give me your phone.
No.
- Just for a minute.
- No!
Are you testing my patience?
Fuck you!
Over there!
Where is she?
Find her!
Sir, help me. People are chasing me.
They want to rape me.
Get in!
I'll just ride at the back.
I don't want them to see me.
Okay, hurry!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Help.
Hurry!
Find her!
Don't let her get away!
You will forget.
The unborn shall perish.
Good morning, Miss.
She must be here!
Find her! Now!
Come on! She must be here! Get her!
Hurry, find her!
Don't let her get away!
Get her!
Blood for blood.
Hurry!
She has nowhere to run!
Bury our skin with our bones,
and the curse will be gone.
Maya! Wake up!
We have to get out of here.
What is that place?
It's where Tole lives,
the cursed child who was kept alive.
I want to see him.
You have to go now.
Who's there?
It's me. Ratih.
I'm hungry. I want food.
Who is that, Ratih?
I will be back with food.
It's all my fault.
It is not.
But I can make things right.
Why are you still helping me?
Hating you will not change anything.
They will hurt you
if they know you're helping me.
They've hurt me all my life.
Let's just do whatever you plan to do.
What is that?
The skin of the missing girls.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Your work here is done.
You must go before it's too late.
I'm not going anywhere
until I know that the curse is gone.
A woman is going into labor tonight.
We'll wait and see.
I used to live in this house.
This is where Donowongso's father
used to fuck me.
This is also where I gave birth
to Saptadi.
Go to the woman who is in labor.
Please go now!
Of course I didn't tell him
that Saptadi was his illegitimate son.
I never asked him
to take any responsibility for Saptadi.
I knew my place.
This is all your fault.
Even before I was born,
you tried to destroy me.
You started this curse.
You...
...are a mistake
that I need to erase.
Don't come near me!
Stay away!
Sir, please, let me go.
Sir, please, let me go home.
We have to do this.
Please understand.
Sir, everything is alright now.
There will be no more curse.
No more babies
will be born without skin.
What?
The three little girls,
the ones that were never found...
My father buried them inside the house.
In the basement.
Their spirits came to me.
They asked me to bury the puppets
that were made from their skin...
...in the same location
where their bones were buried.
So they can rest in peace.
I've done everything
that they asked me to do.
Go look. The puppets are gone
from your house.
Please, Sir.
Please, Sir. I'm not lying.
Please, Sir. I'm actually your daughter.
What did you say?
I'm your daughter.
I know everything.
I am your child, Father.
Yours and Nyai Shinta's.
Grandma put a spell on you to forget.
Don't listen to her!
Grandmother! What have I done
to deserve this?
I've been living in misery all my life.
You brought me into this world.
Now you want to kill me.
Shut up!
Is this true, Mother?
This is all your fault.
You dare to talk that way
to your mother?
Enough!
I've had enough with you
controlling my life.
It's her, or your mother.
My wife's in labor, Sir.
It's me or her!
Father...
The baby's healthy!
Please...
Oh Dear...
Give me back my baby!
Please.
You have to die!
Our child.
You have to go now.
Come with me.
It doesn't matter where I go.
My life will be the same.
Go!
Go! Go now!
Hurry!
The baby is healthy.
Of course he is.
He keeps kicking me, honey.
Maybe he hates me.
Of course he hates you.
He knows that you've knocked me up.
And are putting me through a hard time.
This is what happens to pregnant women.
We pee a lot. The joy.
Be careful, Love.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What happened?
What happened to the baby?
Where's the baby?