Did you just say you
can't feed yourself
with white-sand brain death?
What?
You said you can't feed yourself
with white-sand brain death.
What does that mean?
I didn't say that.
You did. Maybe you
were still asleep.
You know what, I asked
if you wanted breakfast.
If we should get up
and get some breakfast.
But I heard you...
Why are we here?
It isn't helping. You're
so frozen these days
I can't even tell if
you're sleeping or awake.
Hey, come here.
No. Let's get breakfast.
No, forget breakfast.
No, no, I don't want
to miss the buffet.
Oh.
Come on. Maybe we can
catch the omelet chef.
Ladies and gentlemen,
ladies and gentlemen.
May I have your attention
for a moment, please?
As some of you may know,
we are approaching
the rainy season
here in Li Tolqa.
For the locals, this period
before the storms come
is known as "Umbramaq,"
or "The Summoning."
It is celebrated with
traditional music,
and feasting, and of
course, good company.
So, this morning, I would
like to welcome you all
to Umbramaq and to anoint you
with the "fet yegga" pigment
in the colors of the
coast, because it signifies
that we are all
bound by friendship
and we are closing out
the season together.
Oh, and if any of you would
like to purchase "ekki" masks,
they are still available
at the gift shop.
Thank you! Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Where are we?
This was your idea, remember?
Feeling inspired yet?
Oh, thank you. You didn't
say you were hungry.
There's a boat tour
of the Tra-kla Island
formations this afternoon.
I was thinking we
could go on that,
and make reservations
in town for dinner.
We could try the Chinese place.
I don't think I'd survive
another dinner in town.
Even the idea of it.
Does anyone think
it's a real town?
Why would they have
a Chinese place?
Is it okay if I go? I'll
meet you on the beach.
Yeah, sure.
Okay.
Oh, shit.
What's going on?
Someone's making a statement.
One of the locals, I'd guess.
What do you think
he's trying to say?
He's saying that he
wants to put a long knife
right through here.
And after you die,
he'll hang your body
at the airport to scare
off the other tourists.
Seems a bit extreme.
The Li Tolqans are a
melodramatic people.
I loved your book.
Sorry?
You're James Foster.
I loved your book.
Sorry, is that gauche?
I don't mean to put
you on the spot.
Oh, no.
No... Thank you. Thank you.
It's just, um, not a lot
of people read my book.
I'm Gabi Bauer.
Um, I'm James Foster.
James Foster.
Alban.
This is James Foster.
Hi, nice to meet
you. Alban Bauer.
Alban. Pleasure.
He wrote a book that I love.
The Variable Sheath.
Oh. Oh, yeah, I remember.
I thought it was brilliant.
Yes.
James, do you think
I could convince you
to join us for
dinner this evening?
I've been seeing you
around the resort
for a few days now and I
would love to get to know you.
We have a reservation
tonight at Yangs.
Yeah, it was a good, kind of...
learning experience,
I would say.
All right.
Is there anything
else I can get you?
Um, that's all, I think.
All right, everyone,
please have a great meal.
- Thank you.
- And let me know anytime
if I can make your experience
even more enjoyable.
Interesting guy.
Yes.
This is what is labeled
in the resort guide
as a multicultural
dining experience.
Well, it certainly
is an experience.
So, Alban, what is it
you do for a living?
Oh, architecture, but
I've mostly retired.
Now I run a journal out of
Los Angeles called Glass Pane.
You're French?
Mm, oh, no. Swiss
first, from Geneva.
Then Paris, then LA.
I'm from London
first, then Paris.
- We met there.
- That's how we met.
Oh.
But I couldn't get work there,
so I made Alban move with me.
And what do you do?
Well, I'm an actress, of course.
- Oh, really?
- She's great.
- For commercials.
- Okay.
I have a contract
with an LA company.
They've been grooming me.
I specialize in
failing naturally.
What does that mean?
"Failing naturally"?
Finding a natural-seeming way
to fail at any given task.
In each of the
commercials that I'm in,
I'm the one who simply can't
go on without the product.
It's ridiculous for me
to not have the product.
Okay.
- Show them.
- No.
- No, you should.
- Yeah.
Please.
You wanna...? Do
you wanna see it?
I wanna see. I wanna see.
Here.
She's amazing.
I just... I...
I can't.
How... how can I...
It's impossible.
No one can cut
bread with a knife.
- No one.
- No.
No one. I need the BunChop.
Yeah.
James, don't you
need the BunChop?
Yeah, you need it.
Clearly.
And see, each act of failure
is a sort of mental
and physical puzzle.
You know, I've been waiting
six years for your second book.
That's true.
Is it coming out soon?
We'll... We'll see.
Did I say something wrong?
Oh, no, no. It's just he...
He hasn't been writing.
No, no.
No. I'm... I'm working on it.
Hm, writer's block?
Well, I'm starting to think it
might be the lack of talent.
- No. No.
- No.
Don't say that. Please.
I actually came here
looking for inspiration.
To a... To a resort.
It's quite pathetic.
So, what do you
do for money then?
Do you teach, or?
He married rich.
That's a good one.
Well, it's good for an artist
to have a patron, isn't it?
- Yes... Yeah.
- Oh, sure.
I'm in danger of becoming
a charitable organization
at this point.
What's wrong?
No, I just...
I don't understand
why we're doing this.
We barely know these people.
We spent last night with them.
You know what I mean.
We're not supposed to
leave the resort strip.
It's a poor country. I
know it's not their fault,
but they have a high crime rate,
and the guide says
they target foreigners.
Well, maybe a little
therapeutic mugging
could fix my back.
Come on.
I'm sure it's safe if
the Bauers are going.
They come here every year.
You're just happy you
found your fan club.
Well, Em, you knew it
had to be somewhere.
All right? It's one day.
Let's mix things up
a bit. It'll be fun.
And then now you have to
be especially careful...
Hi!
- Hi.
You made it.
- Yeah.
- How are you?
- Good.
- Good. Good.
Are you well? You slept well?
- Yeah.
- Nice to see you.
This is Mr. Thresh.
He's been kind enough to
rent us his car for the day.
Down there.
Can I help you?
- Oh, thank you.
- Yeah.
Isn't it beautiful?
Yes. Fuck off. It's
very, very beautiful.
Baby, you need your umbrella?
Thanks, darling.
- Come on.
- Take the wine.
- Take this?
- Yeah, yeah. Sure.
Thank you.
James...
do you want a buffalo sausage?
No, if I ate another
sausage, I would vomit.
Can you vomit first
and then eat one?
They're coming out perfectly.
Are you trying to kill me?
I'm just fattening
you for dinner.
You will be our final course.
Once the oil starts
coming out of your eyes,
I'll fry you with rosemary,
and Em can eat your balls
like a real marriage.
How do you know I
haven't already?
Look at him, he's
too disobedient.
- Gab?
- Hm?
Do you want a buffalo
sausage, baby?
No.
Also disobedient,
and she doesn't even
have balls for us.
So why this guy,
if you don't mind?
He has no money. Why him?
I don't know.
Mm, I suppose it has
to be daddy issues.
Daddy issues?
Well, my father hates him.
Oh, come on, be serious.
She is serious.
My... My father runs
a publishing house,
and the one thing
that he told me
was to never marry a writer.
Of course.
But my father was
also a monster,
so I married the
first broke writer
to spill coffee on me.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Almost done.
I'm sleeping in
the back with Em.
Fuck, I'm still drunk.
I can drive.
You sure?
Yeah, I'm good.
All right, thank you.
Okay.
Come on.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
No!
What the fuck was that?
James?
Stay in the car.
What did you do?
Oh, my God!
Fuck, James. Fuck!
I didn't see him.
- I couldn't see!
- We have to call someone.
Call who?
Call the resort, they'll
call our consulate.
Nobody will find us.
How do you call the police?
No police. Get
back in the car.
We're not calling the police.
W... Wait.
Do you know anything
about jail in Li Tolqa?
This isn't a civilized country.
It's brutal and it's filthy.
We're not getting
picked up for this.
Get back in the car now!
It was an accident.
She's right. It's very
dangerous for us now.
Oh, my God. James, we can't.
What do you think's
gonna happen to you?
You'll be raped
by police tonight
and tomorrow they'll
find your body.
That's how it works
with these animals.
I'm not doing that.
You get back in the car,
we drive, you go to bed.
Alban and I will
deal with Mr. Thresh
directly in the morning. Now!
Now! Alban, drive!
Hello?
- Hey.
- Hi, there.
Guys, we seem to be locked out.
And who are you?
Well, we're guests
at the Pa Qlqa.
We're staying here
but we got lost.
How did you get
through the gate?
Excuse me, sir.
But we were just coming
back from the disco,
and we seem to have found
ourselves outside somehow.
We... We must have gone around.
Here, look. My key card.
I'm sorry, I'm not
sure what happened.
Maybe the fence
is drunk tonight.
James, you have your key card?
Guests are not allowed
beyond the border
of the compound.
Yeah, we know.
We're extremely sorry.
It won't happen again.
Thank you.
You're okay, yeah?
You're gonna be okay.
We'll see you at breakfast.
Yeah. I'm coming.
I'm coming!
Mr. James Foster?
Yeah?
You'll have to come with us.
Excuse me. Excuse me,
where are we going?
No, no, no!
James!
We're together.
We're together!
James!
I'll go... I'll go with her.
Em, I'll find you!
I'll find you!
Hello?
Hello? Can you let me
out of here, please?
Hello?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Where's my wife?
Mrs. Foster is fine.
I was speaking with
her in the other room,
just down the hall from here.
A lovely woman.
You must feel very lucky.
Smoke?
No, thank you.
My name is Detective
Iral Thresh.
That surname will
sound familiar,
as you met my uncle Dro Thresh,
who works at the Pa Qlqa
Pearl Princess resort.
I'm told he rented you
his car yesterday morning.
James, I'm going to
ask if that's true,
but before you answer, I
should explain that my uncle
will be in a great
deal of trouble
if he rented you the car,
so, for his benefits,
would you agree to answer that
he did not rent it to you?
What would that change for me?
Nothing. It's just something
I would appreciate,
given the situation.
Okay.
Thank you.
Mr. Foster, did a resort
worker named Dro Thresh
rent you his car
yesterday morning
at the Pa Qlqa Pearl Princess?
No.
Good.
The Bauer couple,
Gabi and Alban,
have already explained
that after stealing a car
from a man named Dro Thresh
at the Pa Qlqa Pearl Princess,
you went on a joyride with
your wife up the coast.
There you became
intoxicated and hit a farmer
named Myro Myron,
killing him instantly.
You fled the accident without
contacting the police,
and Mr. Myron's body
was found by his family
yesterday morning.
Your wife has
confirmed this account.
Em... Em did?
Mm-hm.
She was quite forthcoming.
Under our federal
law in Li Tolqa,
if you are responsible
for the death of a man,
including in the case of
an avoidable accident,
his eldest son should kill you
to preserve the family's honor.
We do it here in the
station, on Level B.
Wha...?
What... What'd you say?
In the case that
there is no son,
the state will
take on that role.
But luckily, Mr. Myron
has two sons,
ages nine and 13.
But... But... But... But
it's not... I'm sorry.
Please. Please. It... it...
James, it is unlikely
that we will kill you.
Are you aware of the Revised
Process of Doubles Act
for International
Visitors and Diplomats?
Physical doubles.
This is the deal my
government offers
to foreign visitors
in your situation
as part of our longstanding
tourism initiative.
For a significant sum, the
state will build a double
to stand in for your execution.
Importantly, and this is key
to our diplomatic agreement,
it will also maintain
your memories,
and so will believe itself
to be guilty of your crimes
at the time of death.
Do you, James William Foster,
consent to be doubled,
and to the associated fee,
for the purposes of satisfying
our legal proceedings?
I'm sorry. I... I... I
don't quite understand.
Would you prefer to be executed?
Please sign.
No, no, no.
Gown, please.
Inside.
This, please.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Are you all right?
Em? Where am I?
We're still at the
station. You're recovering.
Does it hurt?
My head is killing me.
They told me the double
turned out correctly.
It's already finished.
The double?
The surrogate.
They're waiting
for us downstairs.
Often, it takes a few attempts.
Even the smallest imperfection
is unacceptable to the
language of the law.
But this one...
has turned out the first time.
But how...?
It's horrible.
It looks just like me.
You will both be present
for the execution.
Oh, no. I don't
want to see it.
This is non-negotiable.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Oh.
Oh, my god. Oh, my god.
Please... James.
No. No, no, no.
Please. Don't. I... I...
Please don't. I didn't...
Em, please. Em, please!
Em! Em!
Em, help me! Em!
Please help! Em!
Help me! Help, Em! Help!
No! Em, please!
This is the ashes
for you to take.
Consider this a souvenir.
A car is waiting to bring
you back to the resort.
Can you fucking help?
All right, there's a shuttle
to the airport in 15 minutes.
James? James!
Yeah? Yeah.
What the fuck.
Where the...?
What?
My passport. I can't
find my passport.
What do you mean?
I don't know. I always
put it in my carry-on.
It's not here.
What do you mean
you can't find it?
I... I don't know where it is.
- It... It's all...
- James, we have to leave.
Well, I know, I'm
looking but it's not,
- I can't... I don't know...
- We have to leave!
We have to leave!
Fuck!
If you want to go without
me, I'll understand.
I'll come home as soon
as I can get on a flight.
Em?
It's really so disgusting.
What?
It's really so disgusting
that you could just...
sit there
and watch it happen.
Like a robot.
What's wrong with you?
I'm gonna go down
to the front desk,
see if they can help.
Okay?
I'll be right back.
Yes, I understand.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you for your
patience, Mr. Foster.
Would you like us to
extend your room booking?
Mr. Foster?
Sorry. Um, is our
room still available?
Yes, Mr. Foster.
Your room is still available
until we close down at
the end of the month.
We have a number
of free rooms now
with the rainy season coming up.
Okay. Well, let's say extend it
by another week, to start with.
Uh, will this still
be under Em Foster?
Yes.
Wonderful.
Is there anything else I
can help you with today?
No. Thank you.
Are you leaving us?
As soon as I can.
That's a shame.
James, I'm sorry.
Come have a drink with
me and let me explain.
Please.
The first year we came,
Alban was working as
a consultant on the
construction of a new resort.
The Bot Vre 2. Do you know it?
No.
It's just a few
compounds over from here,
north up the beach.
They were installing
an infinity pool,
one of Alban's designs.
A little pervy,
with a glass bottom
that you could look
up into from the bar.
But the plate split
and fell off the crane,
and two workers were killed.
The owner of the Bot Vre
put the blame on Alban
and so we were arrested.
Penalty of death.
And we made a discovery then
that you have now discovered.
A discovery.
Are you upset? Maybe
think of it as a gift.
You said you were
looking for inspiration.
There's something to the
experience, isn't there?
You come out of it feeling...
it's hard to explain but
I can see it in your eyes,
if you know what I mean.
Will you come to
our villa tonight?
There are a few others we've
encountered over the years
who share our little secret.
Oh, James.
James, you made it.
You're completely transformed.
You look so beautiful now.
I can see the beauty just
pouring right out of you.
Here, quickly.
- Yes.
- Quickly.
Yes, that's correct.
A little bit more.
Here. Here. Come.
- Thank you.
- Come, come, come, come.
Everyone, everyone.
This is the new friend
I was telling you about.
James, this is Charles,
Jennifer, Dr. Modan,
and the beautiful Bex.
Nice to meet you.
Do you know that Bex's
father is a film producer?
Wow.
Maybe he'll turn your
book into a movie.
So, you're a writer?
Sort of.
Sort of?
What does that mean?
James wrote a very
brilliant book that I love.
Mm.
Okay.
So then, what is
this book about?
Don't harass the man. He's
just had a very bad day.
It's quite all right.
I'm just curious
about our new zombie.
You don't have to
be afraid, James.
We are all zombies here.
Well, you're certainly
a flesh-eater.
- Oh, please.
- Ladies.
Everyone here is
a brother, James.
You don't understand
Li Tolqa yet,
but they are very
generous with discipline,
especially if they
know you can pay.
Very conservative
outside the resorts.
Very religious.
They will kill you for
drugs, blasphemy, sodomy.
Can you guess which
one of us was sodomy?
Honestly, it's
amazing that anyone
is still alive in this country.
You know, James, I'm glad
you could come tonight.
It's a great time
to have you with us.
Dr. Modan is writing a paper
on the Li Tolqan
doubling tradition.
It's Bob, please.
I was wondering if I
could ask you a question
while you're still
fresh, as they say.
Sure.
Do you worry they
got the wrong man?
Oh, God.
Do... Do you think, I
mean, looking back on it,
that they killed the real James?
That was my biggest fear
after my own experience.
Because you wake up
in that little room,
and for all you know, they
could've just swapped you out.
Hard to say what happened
while you were asleep.
So, what does it matter?
You have to let it
go. I've let it go.
How can I?
I'll never know if
I'm really myself,
for as long as I live.
Exactly, so who cares?
What do you think, James?
Do you fear you may have just
witnessed your own demise?
I can only hope.
Are you feeling all right?
Ah, yeah, yeah.
Just, um...
Maybe I had too much to drink.
I don't think that's it.
The first day is
always difficult.
It's like a new skin
working itself into place.
And in your case, I can see
something special happening.
I have this...
pressure... in my head...
It will pass.
James...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Will you trust me tonight?
He got it from one of
the cleaning staff.
It's fine. Come.
That was a great shot.
James. James, why don't you
come over here for a moment.
I have a proposition for you.
Don't worry about this gun.
I hear you have a
passport problem.
Is that right?
That can be a lot of trouble
in a place like this.
I tell you what,
I will talk to my
connections in immigration
and see if I can help
if you play a little
game with us tonight.
Ooh.
We just have a little
plan tonight, James.
Just a bit of fun.
Yes, tell him about the mission.
- The mission?
- Yes.
Early this week, the
owner of Bot Vre 2 resort,
he was awarded a medal for
promoting Li Tolqan prosperity.
And there was a
ceremony on the beach.
We found out the
owner lives in a house
just up the hill.
So, we decided tonight we will
go get the medal for ourselves.
Just a little game
to play, for fun.
It's actually rather
important to us, James.
I mean, after all, he
did have us executed.
At a certain point, if you don't
respond to an insult like that,
you're such a coward that
you'll just fall to the ground
and never get up again.
What do you say?
Or maybe we just off you now
so you don't give us away.
A perfect likeness.
We found it!
Have you ever
fired a gun before?
It would be so easy.
Not everybody gets this chance.
Hey, what are you
kids up to in here?
Just playing chicken.
Oh. Have you seen what
he has in this place?
James, you're going
to want a drink,
and you're going
to want a cigar.
You have beautiful taste, sir.
I'm really starting to like you.
We need to get him
inside, right now.
Yes.
My building is just
around the corner.
To the right.
It's okay, honey!
- I need some towels.
- James, what's going on?
No, no, no, no!
They really should
have water in here.
Charles, do you have
any water on you?
They took my bag, sweetheart.
Why don't you be a gentleman
and give Gabi your seat?
Because I'm old.
I went for a
colonoscopy last month,
and it was like looking at
a painting by Jackson Polyp.
James, do you know why
the doubling tradition
is unique to Li Tolqa?
I'm starting to think it's
just their poetic flair.
We've spent years trying to
reproduce the process in the lab
but we're far too literal.
We just never taken
into account...
Uh, finally.
The transcend connection...
Hi.
We've been waiting
in here for hours.
Do you feel you've
been inconvenienced?
Well...
Our country is not a playground
for foreign children.
It sometimes seems we
have forgotten this.
But maybe not today.
You've tested the limits
of our hospitality.
And today I'm feeling
inspired to make a statement.
What do you say?
Yes, please.
- Hey, hey, hey!
- Hey!
I can walk.
What's going on?
- Go now!
- Okay.
Okay.
Come on.
Where are we?
Detective, where are we going?
We're ready to pay now.
Alban!
Leave her alone!
No!
Get away from me!
- Get away from me!
- James!
No! Go! Aah!
James!
Bravo! Bravo!
Well done, James!
I didn't think
you had it in you!
Beautiful.
Em?
What's wrong with you?
With me?
I'm leaving.
I don't have a passport.
Well then, I guess
you get to stay.
They told me I've already paid.
Is this a dream?
It would make more sense.
You've gone wrong
around the eyes,
like one of those
crabs at the dump.
Go on, then.
Run back to Daddy.
Wait...
Em left today.
That may be for the best.
We've been together ten years.
It's none of my business
but I don't really
think she suits you.
Men are trained by women like Em
to see themselves as weak.
It can take some work to undo.
It can take some blood.
I don't know about that.
The rainy season is coming.
Will you walk with me?
What's that?
It's called the ekki gate.
It's a traditional
Li Tolqan root drug.
I got it from one of the guards.
What does it do?
It's a hallucinogen.
Also an aphrodisiac.
Drug use is heavily restricted
in the modern state,
but this is considered
to be religious.
I want you to show me
how strong you are.
It's horrible.
You'll come to like it.
How long does it
take for it to work?
Come on.
Pathetic.
Ooh.
Not so loud.
You know, James,
I spoke to my son-in-law
about your passport.
About what?
Your new... Your new passport.
He said it's Thresh who is
the problem, the detective.
Thresh is holding you
back from leaving.
Probably hoping to
bring you in again
and fill up his pretty
police piggy bank.
The Li Tolqans only
understand one thing.
You need to show him that you're
the dominant in this conflict.
Yeah.
They're like baboons.
Like baboons, but
we think we know
just the thing to help.
Oh, yeah?
Trigeminal neuralgia, James.
It seems the
detective is due for
a glycerol injection tonight
at Li Tolqa Brain and Spine.
Hey, James. James.
Why don't you stand down?
We're gonna be fast.
Any trouble?
There was a police van...
Almost ran me down.
Oh. They just sold
out their boss.
Probably had to get drunk first.
Oh.
Show him your strength, James.
Yeah, I like that. I like that.
Attaboy, James.
Come on. Come on.
Oh!
Aaaaahhh!
Whooh!
James.
James, come on. You aren't
really upset, are you?
It's just a little joke.
We paid the detective
to make another double
just to have a
little fun with you.
James, open up.
Maybe I'll bring the double
here and you can both fuck me.
Have you ever tried that?
Don't be pathetic
tonight, James.
It's so unattractive.
Hi.
James!
Come out, James!
What are you doing
in there, James? Huh?
Where do you think you're
going, you little baby?
James!
Members of the bus!
Give us the coward James Foster,
or I will come in shooting!
He is a spineless
worm and a bedwetter
and he'd sell his own mother
for horse meat to save himself!
Yeah. Jamesy!
Come on. Come on, little baby.
Come on, James. Come on. Come.
You're so pathetic, James.
A real sucky baby.
I can always pick out
a sucky baby for us.
What a joke.
This whole time, we've
been laughing at you.
You're just a bit of fun
for us on our vacation.
And such a terrible driver!
I can't believe you ran
that guy over, James.
Do you remember that?
We thought we'd have to
get you into trouble,
turns out you're such an
idiot you did it yourself.
Faster!
I never read your book.
Did you believe that?
I'm a good actress.
It was hard to look you up.
One shitty book six years
ago that nobody read.
Bad reviews.
You're so vain, James,
to actually believe
that we read it.
It's sort of funny,
but really more than
anything, it's depressing.
Mm.
I do have a review
with me, Jamesy.
Have you read this one?
"The Variable Sheath:
As Bad as Its Title.
Seeming to recognize
his own lack of talent,
newcomer James W. Foster
overcompensates with pretension,
failed posturing that
only serves to emphasize
how truly terrible
this debut really is.
Sheath is a book that
has nothing to say
and lacks the words to say it.
One can't help but wonder
whether its very existence
is owed to Foster's
powerful father-in-law,
media mogul Edward Servek.
Maurice Tate is an
overwritten urologist
whose unconvincing marital
struggles therein..."
Ah. Oh, no. Alban, my wine.
-Oh, Jamesy! Oh, no. Oh, no.
James. What are you doing?
James!
No! No!
No! No! No!
Oh, no! James!
Come on.
James.
Ah!
James!
Help...
No, don't...
Help me, Em.
Em, please help me.
Hello?
He emerges! Back
from the dead!
Hey. James, here.
Come. It's okay.
It's okay. Come forward.
Today we're going
to fix you, James.
I know it's been hard,
but believe me when I say
that we are on a
mission of mercy.
It's time for you to shed that
disgusting larval mind of yours
and find out what kind of
a creature you really are.
Bring the dog.
Come on.
The dog is here for you to
complete your transformation.
Only through blood can
you release your past.
Sacrifice the dog, James.
Kill the dog.
Fuck you. Fuck all of you.
Pick up the knife, James.
It's for your own good.
You pick it up.
Go on.
Go fetch!
Come here. It's okay.
Yeah.
Mm-hm.
Mm.
Well, I'll land at ten,
so I'll be home
around 11, 11:30.
I'm so sorry, baby.
Really am.
Yeah.
I miss you.
Okay.
Okay, but, I should
probably get going
so I don't miss the shuttle.
But I'll see you very soon.
All right?
I love you. Bye.
Thank you.
Thanks.
There you go.
Oh, Charles, did
you remind Stacy
I have a spare key
under the planter?
I spoke to her yesterday.
I swear it's in one ear
and out the other
with that girl.
Gabi, what are you two doing
when you go back to LA?
Oh, well, Alban is going
straight back to work,
aren't you?
Oh, yes, unfortunately.
The spring issue of the
journal is coming up fast,
and I'm behind.
Which means I'll be eating alone
and rearranging the house again.
Please don't.
Whenever I'm bored,
I rearrange the house
and it drives Alban crazy.
You don't.
You and Bex must be related.
I like to repaint
the walls as well.
Don't give her any idea.
Alban, that actually reminds me
that we need to pay Jonas for
the work he did on the garage.
I paid him last month.
You did? He just sent me
an invoice before we left.
This is a pre-boarding call
for passengers traveling on
flight LT 907 to Los Angeles.
Those passengers requiring
assistance boarding,
those with small children,
and passengers flying with us
in business class today,
please proceed to Gate C.
That's us.
James, great to meet you.
Hopefully we'll see
you again next year.
Have a good flight.
You too.
This is the final boarding call
for flight LT 606 to Melbourne.
All remaining passengers
proceed to Gate One.
I repeat, this is the
final boarding call
for flight LT 606.