Who is it?
Hi, my name is Quinn,
I was looking for Elise?
It's okay, Warren.
Go upstairs.
I'm Elise.
Hi.
I'm sorry to bother
you like this.
I got your name from
Claire Ortirski's mom.
Mrs. Ostirski -- Emily,
sorry. Emily Ostirski.
Yeah, she told me you worked as a psychic and
that you were really amazing. And she saw you.
I remember her...Emily.
Yeah. She's awesome.
She's like, really nice.
And she told me
how great you were.
She gave me a phone number
for you, but it wasn't working.
So...
I'm really sorry to have...
just shown up like this.
It's okay.
But if you're looking
for a reading...
Unfortunately I don't
do those anymore.
I have money.
I brought, like, $50.
No, no. It's
not that, honey.
I just can't. And I'm
pretty busy, so...
It's okay.
Where did you come from?
Leland Park.
That's a long way.
Yeah, it's no big deal though. I mean,
I'm the one who just showed up.
I'm really sorry I've
wasted your time.
Why don't you
come in for a minute.
A good chat is never
time wasted, right?
I love the style
of your house. It's...
Thank you.
- Have a seat.
- Thanks.
You're a very smart
girl, Quinn.
Depends on who asks.
No, you are.
You read a lot.
You have a lot of books
in that bag of yours.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah. I love reading.
What made you come
all the way here today?
I, I wanna talk to someone...
Who's not around anymore...
Who?
My mom.
She died a year
and a half ago.
She had cancer.
I mean, well first, she had breast cancer.
And then, she had a mastectomy, but...
It decided to hang around
and travel to her lungs.
So...
Guess you could say it went and appeared to
her just as much as everyone else did.
Tell me about her.
She was great.
Like, I mean, she could always
hang out, with all of my friends...
She loved old music...
Like vinyl records
and stuff. And...
She always wanted
to talk to me.
Like...
I'm sorry.
No, no. It's okay.
It's like...
It's like sometimes I
can feel her around me.
Like at night, I'll
be in my room, or...
I'll be asleep, and, and
something will wake me up.
Or, you know, I find
things in weird places.
Like, I find my diary
somewhere strange.
I mean I guess
it's kinda crazy.
Not to me, it isn't.
You've tried to contact your
mother on your own, haven't you?
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, I've...
I've asked her to talk
to me but, she never does.
That's why I came here.
You know...?
I really need to ask
her some questions.
I know what that's like.
All right.
You have to give
me a moment.
And I can't promise anything.
Here, please take a
little bit of money.
No...
I got out of this business. If I
accept that from you, I'm back in it.
Normally, we do this
downstairs in my reading room.
What's your mom's name?
Lily.
Lily Brenner.
I'm calling out...
and trying to make
contact with Lily Brenner.
Lily, if you can hear
me, please talk to me.
Lily, are you out there?
- I can hear someone.
- Is it my mom?
No. It isn't your mother.
Go.
Go away, go.
I'm sorry.
Sorry. There's a reason I
had to stop doing this.
There's other people that do this.
You have to find one of them.
You're going to
be okay, Quinn.
But take my advice...
And do not try to contact your
mother on your own anymore.
You have to be very careful.
If you call out to
one of the dead...
All of them can hear you.
Are you there?
Mom?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
You and I both
know it's a design....
No, today? No I
don't think so, no.
Hey, you know what?
What I mean is that I can't be
in two places at the same time.
Yeah. The whole building
needs to be rewired.
The original guys
really screwed it.
You know that's an entire
extra day of work for me.
You got that, right?
Hang on, Bill.
There's no food.
- Didn't you go to the grocery?
- Yeah. I did.
Well, what did you get,
I mean what's this? Quinoa?
Quinoa?
I have to go.
Yeah, of course I'm gonna call
the guy. I got to get the part.
Hang on, Bill.
- What are you doing?
- I'm taking a photo.
- Why?
- It's for my blog.
None of what you just said
to me makes any sense.
It's not supposed to.
Okay, well how about
don't blog it. Just eat it.
- That's a great T-shirt.
- You weird...
You're such a weird person. Nobody
cares what you're having for breakfast.
Will you just go get your
brother ready for school, please?
Alex.
Alex!
Come on. Get up.
Get ready for school.
I am.
God, it stinks in here.
Come on. Get up.
OK, fine. I'll tell dad.
Can you hold on a second?
- I was getting-- get out!
- Don't touch me!
I'll never forget this.
You'll go to the end of the world. And
you'll find me waiting there.
Your servant.
You'll always find me
waiting there, your servant.
Okay.
I'll never forget this.
Alright. I am. I'm
hurrying. Right, bye.
Why is it quiet?
Quiet's not good.
Alex. You see this face?
This is my whoop ass face. When you see
this face, it means I'm about to whoop ass.
Get ready.
Come on.
You gave me life
when I was dying.
When I was leaving this world...
- Quinn.
- You scared me!
I need to rely on you to
get him up and going.
He's lying around
like a corpse.
I did.
No, I need you to get
him ready for school.
Dad, I have to
learn my lines.
- When am I gonna do that?
- I need your help here.
I'm drowning.
He's running late. You
could've done this anytime.
You're being selfish.
Yeah, I'm being really selfish
for worrying about my future?
Just help me out.
Come on.
Oh. Good timing, Hector.
Now you got
to see Quinn.
- Were you waiting there?
- Shut up!
I wasn't, like, waiting.
I just came out.
I know.
So, what have you got first?
I'm not going to school today.
I have an audition for a
theater school on New York.
You serious?
That's awesome.
New York.
It's far away.
Quinn? You gotta
see these birds.
There's a flock of 'em at city hall.
But these ones are nicer.
But you can't eat them.
Sorry, kids...
Sometimes, she's not sure
about what she's saying.
I know her.
That's what you have to look
forward to when you get old.
- Yeah, so do you.
- Yeah, but you'll get old first.
I can't wait for this thing.
We're taking the stairs.
No.
See you, Hector.
See ya. Later.
Mom. Help me get
through this.
Quinn Brenner.
- Hi there, Quinn.
- Yeah, hi.
- Thank you for coming in.
- Thank you...
I'm so excited. I'm a huge
fan of your school. I've...
You know. It's always been a
dream of mine to go there.
- I've always---
- Great.
Have you prepared
something for us?
Yeah, I have.
Whenever you're ready.
I won't ever forget this.
You will go to the
end of the world,
and you will find
me waiting there.
Your servant.
It's okay.
You can stop
the scene again.
Yeah, sorry.
I know...
I..
Do you wanna take a break
and come back in a little bit?
I hate him!
And I don't, I don't
mean I pretend hate him,
like, "really, I love you I'm just mad at
you". I actually, literally, hate him.
Save the word 'literally' for
when you're being literal.
Shut up!
I don't want this.
Look, we have a few months of parental guidance left
and then this reality we're currently living in is done.
That's what's so great about it.
You pick a college
on the opposite coast,
he becomes a
weekly phone call,
that turns into a monthly
phone call when you need money.
It's like he's not your dad anymore. He's
just a bank you visit on Thanksgiving.
But I'm not going
anywhere, Maggie!
I botched the audition, to
the one school I wanted to go to.
I don't have a backup
plan. It's over.
Lord, you are so born
to be an actress, Brenner.
"It's over".
No, I'm serious.
That school is all
that I wanted.
And my dad
wants me here,
raising my brother.
You're gonna be gone.
You're gonna be okay.
Everybody always says that.
Hey. Come on.
Oooh. Lesbi-friends.
Oh no, you're right.
Where's the nearest
Jesus Camp?
Have fun with
your little boys.
Goodbye. Goodbye.
Let's get out of here.
Come on, Lesbo.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh, no!
Someone help us, please!
On my count. 1, 2, 3.
Monitors showing kneecap...
Okay, we got multiple compound
fractures on the right leg...
163, dropping.
Rates degrading.
Okay, give me 1 amp of
Paddles at 360.
Charging, 360.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
OK, we've got her.
We got her back.
Let's keep her stable, folks.
Mom?
Hey. It's dad.
Honey, I'm here.
Do you remember anything?
I was with Maggie.
Then there was this
man waving at me.
He was at the theater too.
Then everything went dark.
One second, hon.
Oh, Mr. Sean.
How you doing?
Hey, Harry.
Really sorry to hear about
what happened to your daughter.
Thanks, Harry.
She's here.
That's what counts.
The man who can't breathe.
The man who lives
in the vents.
I heard him, saying
your name last night.
I heard him
in your room.
While you were gone.
He's up there right now.
Standing in your room.
You will see him.
Surprise!
Welcome home, badass.
- Yay.
- Oh, my gosh. Quinn.
Yeah. A little busted.
Wheelchair's just until
the bones in her legs heal.
Thank God, huh.
Thank God.
I'm just happy that
you're gonna get better.
These people are crazy.
The way they drive around
this neighborhood, you know?
I'm so sorry this
happened to you.
Yeah, its... It's
pretty embarrassing.
- I sent some flowers.
- We got 'em.
Hey, can I sign this thing,
or what, is that cliche?
- No, knock yourself out.
- Okay.
Wow, you've been
saving that one.
Just had to wait for
Quinn to get hit by a car.
I think, she's done
being shown off now.
Listen, we just wanted
to see you, Quinn.
- Okay.
- Listen, anything you need...
Thanks, Ernesto.
I mean it...
See you later.
Home again, huh.
Alright, ready?
One, two, three...
Great neighbors we have, huh?
Crazy cat lady
on one side,
the boy who's clearly in
love with you on the other.
He's not in
love with me.
You know, everyone that looks
at me isn't in love with me, dad.
Especially since
I'm crippled now.
Hey...
No sarcasm.
Not since I got you such
an awesome gift basket.
Everything you like.
Books...
Bell, in case you
want me to wait on you.
Some French food.
The French onion dip, oui?
Snacks.
What?
I'm vegetarian.
Really?
Yeah.
- When did that happen?
- Doesn't matter.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
So...
Did any letters come
from my school?
No, I don't want you to
worry about that right now.
The only thing I want you to think
about right now is getting better.
Understand?
Think of it as a gift-wrapped excuse to
do your favorite thing in the world:
Sleep.
Hey, you need me, I'll
totally hear the bell.
No, I'm fine.
Good night, Warren.
Goodnight, Jack.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What the hell was that?
I'm not making
this up, Mel.
It cracked my ceiling.
I'm not saying you are.
I'm just showing you that there's
nobody living above you right now.
See?
Yeah, well, I heard it.
And it came
from that room.
Mel, come look at this.
What the hell do you see now?
No one up here, huh?
I don't know
what to tell you.
Tell me who's gonna pay
for the crack in my ceiling.
Why can't I ever...
Quinn, where's the
frying pan, please?
Right drawer
on the far left.
Yeah, I looked there already.
You know what, I can't take
this right now. I'm too busy.
Alex, no eggs this morning.
Just find what you can in
the fridge for breakfast, okay?
Whatever.
Come on, Quinn,
eat your breakfast.
I don't want to.
You have to.
Can't taste it.
Can't taste anything anymore.
- Alex, are you dressed?
- Yes!
I went to see a psychic.
I wanted to talk to mom.
You what?
I went and saw a psychic
woman named Elise.
Claire's mom gave
me her address.
- When was that?
- Like a month or so back.
Strange things have
been happening.
Like that knocking
I heard last night.
I think that was mom
trying to reach me.
Quinn...
I don't want you to
get any funny ideas.
You know, these nutcases, are...
they're paid to give you hope.
That's what they do.
They make stuff up.
Why couldn't that
have been her though?
What if she's trying
to tell me something?
Why don't you ever wanna talk
about her or acknowledge her?
I do talk about her.
No you don't. You
just fight with me.
You keep all this chaos so you can
pretend that she never existed.
No, Quinn.
I see her every single day.
When I look at you.
Fine...
I'll help her.
But you're staying here.
I'm reaching out
to Lillith Brenner.
If you can hear me,
please answer me.
Your daughter may
be in danger.
She needs your help.
Please, Lily.
Answer me.
I need to speak with you.
Lily, please.
Show yourself.
What do you
want from her?
I know you're
not her mother.
She thinks you are.
But you aren't.
And I'm not
afraid of you.
I know you're there.
I've fought many like
you in my time, demon.
Show yourself.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
I can't...
I can't do
this anymore.
Kate Witter is
still a bitch.
Mr.Paul is still hot.
Hector is still asking about
you in a really unsubtle way, like...
Oh, he just needs to stop..
And everyone at school is pretending
that they care about prom,
and that they're gonna
wear ironic costumes.
That sounds so fun.
No, it's not.
It's the worst, believe me.
Oh, I wish someone would run
over my legs with a truck.
Wait, so how's your
college application going?
No, we're gonna
talk about you.
How's it going
with your dad?
He's taking all
this time off work.
He's out talking to his boss
about it right now. It's like this...
It's like this whole
big situation.
That sucks.
Well...
What do you do when you
need to go to the bathroom?
No.
No way. You
kidding me?
Hey, is that Alex?
What?
Standing right
next to you?
What? What are
you talking about?
Alex.
Just right...
Maggie.
Maggie?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Quinn.
What's happened?
Are you hurt?
Are you okay?
Someone's in here.
Someone in here?
I'm here now, it's okay.
This will prevent her from moving in
a way that could injure her neck further.
Easy, honey.
Just hold still.
Thank you.
Quinn.
What happened?
I was thrown out of bed.
There was no one in your
room. I would have seen them.
It wasn't a person.
It was a...
Before, I thought that it was
mom trying to contact me.
But it's not.
It's something else.
Are you sure it wasn't
just a bad dream?
No.
I saw him.
He had on a mask.
He had on a
breathing mask.
I believe you.
I do...
You're gonna be okay now.
Get some rest out here.
I think we've done everything.
Come on.
Thank you very much.
Harry.
She's gone.
She just wouldn't wake up.
Oh, Harry.
I'm sorry.
People called
her the cat lady...
Crazy lady, but...
She wasn't any of that.
She was somebody. She meant
something. She was my wife.
We were together fifty-two years.
She had her whole life,
before she got sick.
She was beautiful.
So, so beautiful.
The most beautiful
girl in the whole town.
I knew she didn't have long...
I tried my best to tell her
what she meant to me.
And the sad part is...
I don't think she understood
a word I was trying to say.
She knew what you said.
She knows how
much you love her.
Harry...
If you ever need anything,
anything...
Just tell me, okay?
Thanks.
No.
Help, help!
Help!
Daddy! Help!
Dad, help!
Dad!
Help me.
- Dad!
- Quinn!
What are you doing up here?
Dad, I told you.
Jesus, he jumped.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Quinn!
Dad! Help!
Help!
Quinn.
- Who's there?
- It's Sean Brenner.
I'm Quinn's father.
I told her I don't really
give readings anymore.
Believe me, I wanna help.
But this ability I have, to contact
the other side, I promised myself
I wouldn't do it anymore.
Look, I don't know
anything about this stuff.
I don't know what's
real, what's not.
I only know her.
She's real.
She's my daughter and
something's trying to kill her.
And I don't know
what to do to stop it.
I can't let that happen
again, not after my wife.
She told me that
you lost your wife.
I'm so sorry.
Loving someone is just,
delaying pain, isn't it?
Eventually you're gonna lose
them one way or the other.
I lost my husband.
A year ago.
He took his own life.
So, I couldn't even blame fate.
He'd suffered depression
before, but I...
I never thought...
There's so many things
I needed to say to him.
'Goodbye' would have been nice.
So I tried to contact him.
I just couldn't help it.
There are two worlds...
That exist, beyond
ours, Mr. Brenner.
Think of them as
light and dark.
I visited the dark
looking for him.
Something I've
never done before.
Something we, living people,
are not supposed to do.
But someone followed me back.
A woman.
An entity driven by evil.
Ever since then,
whenever I use my ability...
This woman...
I can hear her in my head.
Screaming over and over,
that she's going to kill me.
I think...
No. I know...
If I continue
with this work...
She's going to kill me.
Then just, visit Quinn.
That's all I ask. You won't
have to do anything else.
Just talk to her.
Thank you.
We're gonna be okay.
Quinn.
Elise.
You came.
Lucky you look
good in white.
What's happening to me?
One night after
you came to see me...
I had a vision of you.
You were standing
in the dark.
A man was walking toward you.
A man who couldn't breathe.
I've been to that
dark place, too.
It's not a place
for pure souls.
It's very dangerous.
When you go there...
Things come back with you.
I don't wanna die, Elise.
You have a long
life ahead of you.
I cross my heart.
I am here, with
Quinn Brenner.
I want to speak to the entity
that has attached itself to her.
Can you hear me?
Are you there?
Where is the man
who can't breathe?
I wasn't trying
to upset him.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Get away from me!
Get away!
I'm not going any further.
I always wanted to know,
how I was gonna go.
Tell me, friend.
How I meet my end.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Elise?
Elise.
Elise, Elise.
Elise, wake up.
Elise.
Wake up... Elise!
The woman...
That wants to kill me...
Was waiting for me...
I'm sorry. I can't...
I can't help you.
I'm sorry.
Elise...
It's pretty great.
Some of these rooms still
having equipment in them.
I'm telling you, Dad.
These guys can help.
Throughout this hospital over the
years, a lot of paranormal experts
have come in here.
I don't know. They
look like fools.
They found a house that was
being haunted, and they cleaned it.
Trust me.
I don't.
Dad, we have to do something.
I'm Sean, Quinn's dad.
- Hi. Specs.
- Tucker.
This is Alex.
Yeah, he's a big
fan of your website.
Web series.
I showed him that one where you
guys get the ghost at that hotel,
- The boiler room ghost?
- Oh, yeah.
- That was a good one.
- Thanks, little man.
Some of my best
editing on that one.
Definitely some of
our best editing.
So, do you guys do
this kind of thing often?
Ghost hunting?
All the time.
Yeah. It's actually, all
we do. We literally,
don't do anything
else. Just this.
So what happens now?
Probably five, maybe four.
Excuse me?
And I'll have to call you back.
Text me some peeps.
Roger that.
Come on, she's in here.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Thanks.
Excuse me.
Now this custom-made camera of
mine is outfitted with a small lens.
Basically, a hidden camera.
It's not basic.
And it's not hidden.
'Cause we're keeping it right out in the open
to capture whatever may occur tonight.
We do hide it though sometimes.
Thanks.
This, is our sound backup.
Any noises, we'll
record it right here.
What do I do?
Nothing. You just go to
sleep like you normally would.
We're the ones who'll stay awake.
Hello, Elise?
It's been too long.
I save here for special occasions.
That's her.
She says, one day, eventually,
I'm going to die by her hand.
And I believe her.
That's why I had to
stop using my gift.
But now, I'm realizing...
My gift is all I have.
It's all I am.
First of all...
Okay, you're more
than one thing.
And second, you've been helping
people get rid of these spirits for so long.
Eventually, one of them
was gonna come after you.
You can't be afraid of her.
Alright? You're stronger than her.
- You're alive.
- Yes, I'm alive.
But I have spent more time on this
earth among the dead than the living.
Do you really think
we help people, Carl?
We do what we can.
If someone gets attacked by a person
on the street, they can go to the police.
If they're attacked by
something they can't see,
something they
can't comprehend...
Then we have people
like us to go to.
Here.
Look at what you
did for that family.
You saved them.
That boy is a grown man
now, with a son of his own.
I don't want you to stop
helping families like them.
They need you too much.
- What's that?
- I don't know.
She's up.
- What?
- No.
She can't be doing
that, that's impossible.
Well, she's doing it.
Go, go.
She's gone. Come on.
Look.
I gotta go get her.
Yeah.
Good idea, you should.
Quinn?
Quinn.
Where are you, honey?
Wait.
Here, keep the flashlight on the closet.
Yeah...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
She took it off.
Quinn.
Quinn...
You're a useless
fucking father.
Your wife had to die
to get away from you.
No.
And now, I'd rather be dead, too.
But I'm gonna
keep you alive,
to watch you suffer.
I'll be waiting
in the dark.
When the pain
finally kills you.
No! No!
No!
Quinn.
What do we do now?
I don't know.
We are not qualified for this.
This thing, and dark empty
rooms is way out of our league.
What do you mean?
Are you telling me you have
no idea how to help us?
No.
Are you saying, that you're a couple
of goddamn internet pranksters?
I let you in my
house, you bas---
Stop it, Dad! Stop it!
- This isn't going to help Quinn!
- Get out! Get out of my house!
Let them stay.
We may need them.
What? What for?
To help me get rid of the foul parasite
that's attached itself to your daughter.
I need you to stay at
Ernesto's tonight, buddy.
- But I wanna be here.
- I know.
I'm not leaving, Dad.
Alex...
We know you love her.
But you do not want to see the
things that tonight may show you.
She's gonna feel your love.
Goodnight, buddy.
Now, what?
This entity, is very powerful.
It's a spirit who used to live
in this building a long time ago.
It's been alone
for a long time.
But she's making it stronger.
It's feeding on
her life force.
It wants to possess her?
Usually, entities
of this type...
Living in the dark...
They wanna possess
the bodies of the living.
So that they can
leave the dark...
and return to life.
But there's another kind of spirit.
It's an even worse kind.
One that does not
wanna leave the dark.
That wants the
souls of the living...
to join it in
the shadows.
She's only half a
person right now.
After the accident,
it got half her soul.
It needs all of it..
And if we don't hurry,
it's going to get it.
Okay, what do we do now?
To bring all of your
daughter back...
I'm going to have to
go to where it lives.
You can record everything?
Even in the dark?
Yeah. Of course.
Whatever you need, I'm
the technical part of the team.
Then you better get set up.
What's your contribution?
This should be good.
It's not good. It's great.
It's our blog.
I'm the writer of it.
Okay then, you write down everything
I describe when I'm under.
If you can keep up, that is.
Now, I'm going
into another plane.
...into another plane...
Stay strong.
No matter what happens...
No matter what you see...
...no matter what...
Okay, could you just, maybe,
write it down and try not to talk?
Oh. Yeah...
Sorry, does this other
plane have a name?
Let's call it, "The Further".
Cool name.
Now, we're going
to be quiet.
Into the Further...
we go.
I'm here. It's dark.
I'm entering the hallway.
You lived in this
building too.
He made you kill
yourself, didn't you?
Where is he?
We're going upstairs.
His voice was always so mad.
I was his pet.
He's got a new pet.
The girl.
Quinn, is his new pet.
There's no way to it.
You can't even kill yourself
to get away from him.
It's okay. You're free now.
I hear...
Breathing.
I hear it.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Turn around.
You're stronger than her.
You're alive.
This is how you die.
Not today, it isn't.
Come on, bitch.
Let her go.
Do you hear me?
Release the girl.
Jack.
Hi, Eli.
Come.
Sit here with me.
What are you
doing here?
I could feel
you were here.
I had to find you.
I've missed you so much!
I know.
How? How am I
supposed to move on?
I never even got
to say goodbye.
Well maybe you
can move on.
I can't exist anywhere
without you.
So, I wanted to ask
you to join me here.
You'd have to leave
your other world behind.
Stop breathing, like I did.
Stay with me here.
You'll have to
do it yourself.
I can't help you.
Don't you want
to be with me?
Want.
Want is not a
strong enough word.
I know my...
turn to cross over will come.
But I know...
That my Jack would
never ask me to do this.
Demon.
Give me the girl now or
I'll do a whole lot worse.
Give her back.
You may have half of her.
But I am whole.
And I am very strong.
Elise, wake up.
Elise.
Elise...
This way.
Quinn.
- Honey?
- Quinn.
Honey, please.
What's happening to her?
It's got her.
Wake up.
Don't let it take you.
Grab her hands.
Quinn, don't leave.
Don't leave.
Stay with us.
This world is your
home. Not that one.
This one.
What's happening,
is she dying?
- Just hold on to her.
- Is she?
Yes.
No, bring her back.
Bring her back! You said
you can bring her back.
You need to help me.
Quinn.
Quinn. Quinn, hear us.
Come back to us.
Quinn.
What are you doing?
There's another woman
here who died.
In this building,
a few days ago.
Yeah, Grace.
Grace, the neighbor's wife.
She's saying
something to me.
I can't hear her. Exactly
what is she saying?
- Honey, please.
- What book?
Grace, what book?
Hurry.
Elise, hurry.
Quinn's diary.
This is it.
"Quinn, I wanted you to read
this the day you graduated."
This is the letter that
Lily hid from Quinn.
She wanted her to find
it on her graduation day.
She tried to get
her to read it early.
She was trying to
reach Quinn.
Quinn.
Lily, I know you were
trying to reach her.
We know that you wanted
her to read this letter.
Lily, we need you now.
Help us.
Dad.
Thank you.
We had some help.
Who?
Someone else is
here with us.
Someone who really
wants to talk to you.
Mom.
I need to know
that this is real.
I know.
She's saying something
about a stage.
An audition.
She says that when you were on stage
you wanted to know if she was there.
She was there.
And she was
so proud of you.
She wants you,
and you, Sean...
To know that you don't
need to look for her anymore.
Because she'll
always be with you.
No matter what...
She's gonna be
standing right beside you.
Even though you can't
see her, she's there.
And anytime you're feeling...
Confused, or alone...
She's gonna be
whispering in your ear.
She's never coming
back again, is she?
Not to this world.
I love you.
Good job, boys.
Careful.
Thanks.
Was that the first time
you've seen a ghost?
- Yeah.
- Yes.
You never
get used to it.
Spectral Sightings.
- I like that.
- That one's mine.
- Is it?
- Stop.
You boys
fight too much.
It's unnecessary. It's clear
you both need each other.
Maybe we should go
into business together.
Thought you said this business
was too dangerous for you...
And you said,
it could kill you.
Yeah. Well, everybody's
gonna die one day.
I think it is high
time for me...
to get out of my house
while I'm still alive.
What do you think?
- Yes?
- Sure.
Well then, take
me to my car.
That's great.
I also think, that you guys should
think about wearing something
a little better if we're
gonna be working together.
I'll have you know this
Tee's extremely rare.
Oh, I'm sure it is.
So you should apologize.
I apologize.
What would you
have us wear instead?
Shirt and tie
might be nice.
Ain't gonna happen.
Warren, you old dog.
Thank you for
looking after me.
Where is the...?
I love you too, Jack.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)