My child.
My baby.
Finally inside me.
No one will take him from me.
No one can hurt him now.
No one.
Matthieu.
She's doing just fine.
So, Sarah...
have you got a name
picked out for the baby?
All right. We'll admit you
tomorrow morning at 7.
Nothing happens by evening,
then we can always provoke labor.
Don't worry, Sarah.
It'll go just fine.
You have someone to bring you
here tomorrow morning?
Usually, we'd have an ambulance,
but on Christmas morning,
I'm sure you can...
Yes, someone's gonna take me here.
Good.
Thank you, Doctor.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Right.
And enjoy your last night
of peace and quiet.
It won't be long now, huh?
Hmm?
Well, I had four kids.
Your first one, I bet.
It's horrible, the first kid.
In my own case,
it took 13 hours to deliver it,
my first baby.
Oh, murder.
I mean murder.
I was in such fucking pain.
He put me through all that,
but... he was born dead.
You know very well
that smoking's forbidden here.
Everyone here is so full of shit.
Twat.
I must say,
with what's happening right now,
I'm glad you don't have to work.
It's really nothing
to be freaked out about.
A couple of cars burned.
Well, personally,
I feel better with you home
rather than photographing riots.
It freaks me out less.
So, Jean-Pierre seems like a nice man.
Have you and he gotten to be...
He's my employer.
That's too bad.
I was hoping to be introduced
one of these days, you know?
Well, so...
what do you wanna do?
Christmas dinner at your house or at mine?
I'm not hungry, Louise.
I'm sick of eating.
We're going to be all right now.
Look, I need to be alone, Louise.
Go home now, would you, please?
Hello?
Yeah?
What?
I don't give a shit
that he needs headlines.
I don't give a shit.
Go ahead and tell him.
Exactly.
Then you get on it
and figure something out.
Explain it to the guy.
It's burning cars and the whole
fucking mess on page one.
That's the headline.
Nothing else. Thank you.
Right. No. Nothing.
All right. So long.
Merry Christmas.
That fucker makes...
gets me fucking irritable.
Bloody mess in the burbs
and not one competent man
to cover it.
So, sweetheart,
how have you been?
It's been rough without you out there.
It's just kids having a blast,
'cause they're bored.
Yeah.
Meanwhile, cars are burning,
the cops are on edge,
my reporters are all duds.
Shitty Christmas, you know?
So, my place,
6 in the morning?
- That so?
- Mmm.
I guess that means I better
cut my Christmas Eve short
so I don't keep
the pretty lady waiting.
What about you?
Will you be with your mother tonight?
I don't give a shit about Christmas.
I'd rather be alone.
You won't say that next year.
I can guarantee that.
No, Louise.
No, don't bother coming tomorrow.
I told you, I'll be fine alone.
We've already been through all that.
So you'll come by on Monday.
No, Jean-Pierre's coming to get me.
We just spoke about that, Louise.
I mean, I gave him the keys, yeah.
No. I had enough of this.
I'm gonna turn in.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Horseshit.
I can't see.
Yeah, who is it?
Hi. Excuse me for disturbing you
on Christmas Eve,
but I got this problem.
Could I come in to make
a quick phone call, please?
Don't you have a cell phone?
My battery's dead.
What exactly happened?
My car broke down on the corner.
No. Sorry, but, uh,
my husband works.
He's already gone to bed.
I won't make any noise.
It'll just be a minute.
I promise.
Please?
No. I'm really sorry.
Yeah, look, try, uh...
try another house.
There's lots of dinners tonight.
Please, it'll only take a second.
I don't want to be alone
with all this violence.
My husband's sleeping, I told you!
Your husband's not sleeping, Sarah.
He's dead.
What?
Open the door, Sarah.
Who are you?
You know my name. How?
Open the door and you'll know.
I'm calling the police, all right?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Fine. Go fuck yourself.
Hello?
Look, there's some strange lady
outside my house.
You gotta come really quick.
I can't imagine what she wants.
She knows my name.
She knows all about me. She...
I'm pregnant!
The cops are gonna
be here in five minutes.
Get the hell out of here!
Good evening, ma'am.
Did you call Emergency
about an attempted break-in?
Yeah, that was me.
Come on in.
You live alone?
Yes.
Another guy scared of becoming a dad?
Not that simple.
And who is this woman?
I don't know,
but she knows my name.
Which is on the letterbox right outside.
All about who I am.
You're sure it was a woman?
You get a look at the face, or...
No. She stuck to the shadows.
I mean, I tried to get a picture,
but this is all I could get.
Yeah, right.
Not much we can do with that.
Nobody around.
Don't worry.
I'm sure she left.
Look, I'm gonna lock you in for the night.
We'll notify the unit on patrol tonight.
We've got everyone
on duty already, but...
we're gonna post a bulletin.
They'll call around
in the course of the night
to make sure you're okay.
Thanks.
Pretty empty around here
for Christmas Eve.
That's how this neighborhood is.
- Good night, ma'am.
- Bye.
- So long.
- Don't worry. She won't be back.
Have a good night.
Which has been going on
since last November 27th
and the accidental death
of two French citizens
from immigrant families.
Rioting has since spread
throughout underprivileged areas
of the Paris suburbs
as well as other major cities.
Mass transit passengers
as well as police
and firefighters have been injured.
Over 300 communities have been affected.
4,900 vehicles set ablaze
while scores of businesses,
homes and places of worship...
More than 2,000 immigrants
involved in the riots...
What do you want,
you pain in my ass?
The interior secretary's
inflammatory comments,
much quoted in the press
this morning,
exasperated an alre...
Hello. It's me again, Jean-Pierre.
Well, look, you're feeding
your face, I guess.
Something pretty weird
happened tonight,
so I was hoping that tomorrow
you could enhance
a couple of shots of mine.
Right.
See you in the morning.
No!
Sarah?
Oh, excuse me.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Jean-Pierre Montevant,
Sarah's chief editor.
Sarah's on the way to...
to my Christmas dinner.
I stopped here
to see if she was a bit,
you know, worried with
this suburban violence.
I'm supposed to pick her up...
so she left me her keys...
tomorrow morning.
Anyway, I see her mom
got here... before me.
When a daughter needs,
her mother knows.
Right.
Well, so everything's okay?
She went to bed an hour ago.
I better get going.
See you later.
Oh, please don't run off.
Will you have a drink?
I've been looking forward to meeting you.
Do say yes.
So, Mrs. Scarangelo,
looking forward to being a grandmother?
It took her hours to fall asleep.
Don't wake her.
Oh, of course.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
I'm glad she's holding up well.
She went through hell
after the accident.
Of course, so did I.
These past few months
have been awful.
But I know the birth will save us.
Another drink?
What the hell?
My little photographer.
Always taking her pictures
and leaving them around.
When did she take this one?
Have any idea?
Because I'm pretty sure it's
one of these Sarah called me about.
Really?
What did she have to say?
Something was bothering her.
There was a picture
she wanted to try...
to enhance.
Enhance?
I'm not sure what it's about.
She might have wanted...
to just enlarge it
or to try and clean it up.
Like this face, for example.
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
Where's Sarah?
Maybe you should tell us who you are.
You just barge into somebody's house?
Keep your voice down.
Sarah's sleep...
Where's my daughter?
Well, then, who are you?
Pictures of you.
Sarah?
Everything all right up there?
Mom...
Mommy!
Mommy.
Sarah?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Help me.
Help me. Help me.
Shit!
Who the fuck are you?
Open your door.
Open it!
Open the door.
Why me?
I want one.
What kind of a man would fuck
a maniac like you?
Open it, Sarah!
Don't be afraid.
You don't want that child.
I'll take good care of him.
What are you talking about?
We just stop off to see
if the nice lady is all tucked in, okay?
Then we'll take our nightly jackpot winner
to the station,
Mr. Abdel Shani Asadi.
Abdel Hanusian.
You got the wrong guy, man.
I swear.
I mean, I'm not into Molotov cocktails.
Anyway, if I'm gonna go torch some cars,
I'm not so crazy,
I'm gonna have my I.D. In my wallet.
Fuck.
- I wasn't doing anything.
- Quit trying to confuse the issue.
First, we'll see
if Mrs. Scarangelo's head is on her pillow,
then we bring
this misunderstood child to get booked,
then we go get his homeys
back in the hood.
Can't let him spend Christmas
all alone in the lockup
with nobody else around.
Your friends are out there.
We're gonna go get them,
and you guys can party down.
- I don't observe it, so fuck Christmas.
- Whoa.
Well, hey, right.
Doesn't observe Christmas.
Excuse me. Hello?
How are you, babe?
Think his girlfriend
is such a pain in the balls?
Maybe. Meantime, he's
in the car with the heat on.
I mean, no.
We're going off duty.
We just gotta check out this woman.
We'll be back right after, you know?
Yes, I love you.
Come on. Quit it.
Busting your chops, right?
Wait. Hold on.
Shut your face, all right?
Yeah.
No, I'm talking to a perp in the car,
not to you.
Joy to the world
Mrs. Scarangelo, it's the police.
- Hi. Merry Christmas.
- Merry Christmas.
Just stopped by to see if you're okay.
Our duty log says
a woman was harassing you.
No, it's been hours.
I'm okay.
Don't hesitate to call us
if she comes back.
Yeah, sure.
Excuse me.
What's that noise?
It's the spin cycle
on my ancient washing machine.
- All right.
- Cheaper to run at night, huh?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Well, you have a good one.
- Right.
- Thanks.
- Merry Christmas. So long.
Bye, Officer.
God, a cup of coffee about now.
Hey.
No, I hear you, I hear you.
Did you forget something?
One stupid detail.
Just wondering what
you were gonna name him.
Who?
Your child.
Watch her.
Holy fuck!
Arrest her!
Hands behind you!
On the ground! Fast!
It's a fucking war zone.
It's the police.
Don't move!
All right.
I'm gonna remove the scissors.
Don't move.
Open the door!
No! No!
All right. All right.
You can make it.
Open the door.
Open it!
Open the fucking door!
Oh, my fucking God!
Sorry. Gotta go.
You're gonna have to come along.
- What?
- Something went bad.
That's police brutality, man.
You're putting me on a leash like a mutt?
Put a sock in it and come on.
- Hey, chill out a second.
- Move it.
- Officer, let me out of here, please!
- Here, take this.
Let me go!
We gotta get out of this fucking place!
Get the hell in here!
You all right?
All right. Just calm down.
All right?
Lt'll be all right.
It'll be all right.
You, get it together!
It's fine.
I'll be back in a second.
Just stay there.
You. You!
- You know how to use that?
- No.
You arm it here, okay?
And fire.
Yo! Just point
and pull the trigger, okay?
- Please let me out of this awful place!
- You're coming with me.
I'll be right back.
Stay here.
- What happened? Huh?
- Is she gone?
Yeah, she's gone.
She went out the window
of your bedroom.
She's still here! She's still here!
No, calm down.
Calm down. Christ.
You got a circuit breaker?
Know where it is?
Look at me, now.
Downstairs?
All right. Let's go.
One second.
I'm gonna give you a gun.
Take this. Take it!
Careful. Oh, shit!
Got any bandages?
You got any bandages?
- There...
- Yes?
There? In the drawer?
Here. Hold this.
Take the flashlight.
Hold it up!
I can't see. Here.
Hold the light up, for Christ sake.
It's all right. Relax.
- Take off the handcuffs!
- Shut your face!
Hold this, okay?
Hold the light steady.
I have to put the breaker back on, okay?
Wait for me here.
Hold still.
I killed my mother.
- I killed my mother.
- It's all right. Calm down now.
Man, we gotta get out of this place!
Shit!
I'm gonna call for an ambulance
and backup from my car, okay?
You'll be all right.
All right.
Put this on.
Can you walk? Yeah?
Okay, so you'll wait in the bedroom.
Give me your hand.
Give me your hand!
Help her up.
Okay. Can you walk?
Okay?
You all right?
Be right back.
Let's go. Walk.
Hold the light.
All right.
Once I get the lights on, I'll let you go.
Once you're outside,
find every cop you can.
Hold the fucking light!
There's nobody here!
Don't shine it in my eyes!
- Oh, fuck!
- The flashbulb!
- What?
What kind of crap is this?
Back up.
Back up!
Hey, lady!
She's still here!
Come on! Get up!
Fuck!
Where the fuck are your keys?
Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
Sarah.
Where are you hiding, bitch?
You can kill me again, Sarah.
You already did once.
My child.
My baby.
Finally inside me.
No one will take him from me.
No one can hurt him now.
No one.
They told me that
there were no survivors.
Officer?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
The baby's coming.
The baby!
Shh!
Mommy!
Calm down.
I'm right here.
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
I think it's stuck.
- Mommy!
- Shh!
Mommy!
Subtitled By J.R. Media Services, Inc.
Burbank, CA