Warning: Jump scare in 5 seconds
Beverly walks into her husband as she packs her belongings.
Henry Bowers' face appears out of the water.
Warning: Jump scare in 5 seconds
Balloon pops, revealing Patrick Hockstetter’s corpse.
Sudden cut to a gong being hit.
Warning: Jump scare in 5 seconds
Pennywise devours the girl under the bleachers.
Naked monstrous woman runs at Beverly.
Warning: Jump scare in 5 seconds
Giant statue appears beside Richie.
Pennywise suddenly runs at Richie.
Warning: Jump scare in 5 seconds
Corpse-like hand grabs Bill.
Beverley’s head is suddenly on fire.
Warning: Jump scare in 5 seconds
Pennywise is suddenly behind Ben in the locker.
Eddie is attacked by the rotting corpse.
Warning: Jump scare in 5 seconds
Henry Bowers appears behind Eddie in the mirror.
Inflatable clown collides with Bill.
Warning: Jump scare in 5 seconds
Henry Bowers attacks Mike.
Stanley-spider runs at Richie.
Warning: Jump scare in 5 seconds
Corpse pops up out of the water.
Giant balloon bursts loudly.
Warning: Jump scare in 5 seconds
Torch reveals Pennywise.
Pomeranian transforms into a monster.
Warning: Jump scare in 5 seconds
Georgie reveals a corpse-like face.
Mike runs into Pennywise.
Warning: Jump scare in 5 seconds
Eddie is impaled.
Shriveled Pennywise lunges at Mike.