Help!
Hey!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Every 23rd year, for 23 days,
it gets to eat.
And the things it leaves behind,
like the thing it left in
Poho County that night,
the nightmare on four wheels,
was a horror all its own.
Oh.
Go get the sergeant.
Sergeant!
We got the truck open.
God.
God-damn slaughterhouse
on wheels.
Police scanner.
It's been listening to us.
Whatever it is.
Some of this stuff,
I don't wanna know what it's made of.
Where the hell is that tow truck?
100.
Coroner's still down in the jail.
Should I get him up here?
Those are for sawing.
I don't wanna know for what.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Get that god-damn
thing in the impound!
Oh my god.
I don't believe it.
Jesus Christ, where
the hell have you been?
How many did you lose tonight?
You hold it together
and you answer me.
Three officers, an
inmate down in the jail.
And then the kid.
The one he flew off with.
Name of Jerry.
His name was Jerry Jenner,
his sister's a train-wreck.
She's inside waiting
for her folks that are
driving in from Stillwater.
Where is the last place you saw it?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Don't touch that, and stay back!
Show me.
We threw everything
we had at it, Danny.
All the fire and manpower
this building had to offer.
And it just made a whole lot of noise
and flew off with
exactly what it wanted.
Sheriff, don't you want
us towing that truck?
They just towed it out of here.
Oh, no, no, no!
Can't raise them, they're
not answering any frequency.
- Where are they taking it?
- To impound, where else?
Jesus Christ, we couldn't
leave it sitting there!
You saw what it did.
We gotta get an
armada round that thing.
You make it happen, now!
Anybody, everybody, get
on out there, move fast!
Just a god-damn minute, Danny.
You tell me how the hell
you know about any of this.
Because what happened
here happened before!
You think that thing
torched that church tonight
because it wanted a camp fire?
It was destroying information,
trying to get rid of what
it doesn't want us to know.
And that truck?
That truck is that
thing's rolling history.
Which is why we get it in
the impound and tear it apart.
It ain't gonna make
it to the impound!
Looks like rig up, old Chevy Cabo.
Cabo engine, I'd say 1940s.
That cow-catcher's
gotta be custom.
You wanna tell me what
the hell a truck like that
needs a cow-catcher for?
If you knew what was inside that thing,
that wouldn't be your only question.
Code three, you read me?
- Code three!
- Come again, sergeant?
Just tell
that driver to put his foot
on the gas, we're trying like hell...
What the hell?
- What is that?
- Jesus Christ!
Holy shit!
Fear has a scent.
You can't have seen
that thing and hate it.
Like it could sample fear
right out of the air.
Dispatch, this is Lang
with the impound vehicle.
Please respond.
That's how it picks
what parts of us to eat.
Captain, are you in range?
- And it eats...
- This is Dana.
We have a situation with
the impound vehicle.
To rebuild itself.
You hear that?
It's coming back.
What the...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Stop!
Frank!
It never hunts in the same place,
for more than a day.
It's done with Poho County.
All we can do now is head north,
and follow the birds.
It's not much, but it's all we know.
Ravens and crows, they
travel when it does.
Davis, I've looked that
ugly thing eye to eye.
23 years ago.
I know it.
And it knows me.
Why do you do this?
It hurts too much seeing you like this.
Mom, just listen, okay?
Time's up, it's coming
back just like I said.
Why?
Stop asking, it doesn't matter.
You.
Tell me why it's coming here.
Pieces of it left behind.
They're full of secrets about it.
That's what's buried up here?
- A piece of it?
- There's no more time.
It's coming here and you
can't be here when it does.
- How do you know it's coming?
- I'm a part of it now!
How many times do I
have to tell you that?
It knows what's buried here,
and it will come and take it back.
Oh, killing you wasn't enough?
Why didn't it take it 23 years ago?
It ran out of time!
It always runs out of time,
I can't keep telling you this.
If you won't leave to save yourself,
then do it to save Addison.
Addison?
Addison!
You think that we have any money?
Kenny, are you listening to yourself?
Are you list.
Just pack up and go?
Pack up everything,
just leave for where?
He knows it's here, Mom,
'cause I'm a part of it,
and it's a part of me.
Today, tomorrow or sometime soon,
it is gonna walk up this
hill and it is gonna
dig this thing up right
where I'm standing.
And when it comes, it'll kill
anyone that's still here.
Go away, Mom.
Now.
Good morning, handsome.
Hey, you hungry, buddy?
Damn.
Come on.
Gotta go talk to Grandma, and
I don't wanna do it alone.
Grandma?
Are you okay?
I'm taking the truck into town.
We need hay.
Who is gonna pay for it?
I was thinking maybe we
still had some credit at Hooks?
He called again.
We owe them more than we can pay.
- Cal did say that he...
- Grandma, no.
- Addie.
- I already told you.
I'm not selling Rocket, Grandma.
Selling him would be like
giving away my own child.
What a good mother
might have to do
so that child wouldn't go hungry.
I want you to go
away for a few days.
Maybe stay with Gracie.
Why?
Can you?
Is there something that
you don't want me here for?
Yes.
I'm expecting company.
You've got your team.
You've got experienced
men who know this thing.
Boss.
Michael.
This his old man's truck?
It's an old Vulcan cannon.
She's amped up to shoot 20mm
rounds, 6,000 rounds a minute.
You test this thing?
Mikey.
Is this thing tested?
This thing throws up a wall of fire.
A wall of fire that
nothing from this world
or the next can get through!
Not without being torn
into a million pieces.
She may not fly, but this
is our killing machine.
Davis!
He watched that thing fly down,
and punch a hole in his old man.
He stood there and
watched it pull the heart
right out of his daddy's chest,
and swallowed it
right before his eyes.
Miller was only 10 years old.
You're not losing your mind, Davis.
You just got bloodied last night.
Now do you wanna guess how
much blood I got on my hands?
You've seen that thing now.
So you got blood
on your hands, too.
And no matter what you
do, it's gonna stay there.
Whether you walk away,
or not.
Rendezvous on station one!
North!
Can I beg some hay off you?
Sure, stranger.
Our horses are up in Bolander.
You're not up there with
Rocket winning trophies?
I can't even afford the gas
to drive up there right now.
What's the matter?
Your grandma?
Yeah, she was up on the
hill again this morning.
Screaming at the wind?
Calling it Kenny?
Didn't he die like 20 years ago?
Mom!
You know you got a
rabbit in that trap?
That's what it's there for.
So it's suffering, are you
just gonna leave it in there?
Mom!
Mom, he's got a rabbit in the trap.
Hey, Addie, long time no see.
Mom said they were
eating up her garden.
I didn't say you should trap them.
- You didn't say I shouldn't.
- How's your grandma doin'?
He doesn't care
about the garden.
He traps them because he
likes killing them, he's sick.
I mean, who likes to trap
and kill things for fun, huh?
Psychos, maybe?
He's too stupid to
even know he is one.
Alright, stop, and you take
care of this before you leave,
by which I mean let it go.
It's not in any pain.
Don't leave it in the
trap, it's cruel, honey.
Stop!
It's a rabbit, Mom.
Do you know how small
their brains are?
- 10 times bigger than yours?
- Well, then you let it out.
And I hope it bites you.
It's a wild animal, idiot,
it's kill or be killed.
Just let it go
and stop trapping them, okay?
You're all a bunch of women.
Kirk.
Get back here.
Tell them about the law of
the jungle, will ya, Addie?
Kirk, get out of the car and let it go.
- What's out in the hay barn?
- Dad took what we had.
That's okay, I'm on
my way to Hooks anyway.
Oh, are you?
Yes, and shut up.
Buddy Hooks has a huge
crush on Addie, Mom.
But neither one of
them are brave enough
to do anything about it.
You wouldn't wanna come
with me to Hooks, would you?
And get in the way?
Do you like him or not?
He does have a really cute butt.
And from that springs love!
Idiot.
What the hell is that?
Somebody just ditched it out here?
Hell, I would.
What do you think's in it?
Other than cow shit,
what do you think's in it?
- No way.
- Oh, hell no.
- No way what?
- Look at that license plate.
Beating you?
Be eating you, and no way.
Right.
No way, that story's bullshit.
No, no, I
heard it really happened.
Yeah, I did, too.
- Real people disappeared.
- 20 years ago.
23 and it's just a story.
What story?
The guy who drove
around and ate people.
In a scary-ass old truck
with that license plate.
Jeepers Creepers.
What?
Wasn't that the song the
guy sang or somethin'?
Look, it's homemade.
At least one idiot
every Halloween
makes a license
plate that says that.
You think it just drove in?
The tracks look fresh.
Do you think somebody
could be in there?
Man.
It's warm.
Of course it's warm, you dip-shit.
It's been sitting out in the sun.
Who'd dump it out here?
Who wouldn't?
Hello!
I can't see shit.
What say we beat it
in case they come back?
Anybody in there?
Hey, hello in there!
What the is wrong with you, man?
What?
- I was just knockin'!
- Well, don't.
Idiot.
Man, I say we get the hell outta here.
Wait.
Break the windows first?
Hell yes, we do!
We gotta kill Frankenstein's truck, right?
Dibs on the windshield.
Kiss my ass, you ugly old bitch!
Did you see that?
That thing tried to kill
me, nicked my ear.
Maybe it tries to kill things
more stupid than it.
What the hell?
Those can't be real.
Those flies are real.
That smell is real.
You gonna be driving
up to see us?
Go Wheaton Valley.
Right?
So, 10 bales of Alfalfa?
Right.
No grandma today, huh?
How's she doin'?
Um...
You're not on the load list.
Oh-oh.
Do you wanna talk to my dad?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Do you want me to?
I should put her on my load list.
You know why she lives
with her grandma, right?
Addie couldn't get
along with her stepdad,
so instead of kicking him
out, her mom ships her ass
out here to live with
her crazy grandma.
Can you really blame me
though, I mean, look at her.
I'm just gonna go
to Carlan's and see if we have
some credit on there.
Hey, just wait a minute.
What happened?
Bernardy's, load it up
and get it out there now.
He' waiting for it.
What are you doing?
She loves that horse more
than anything in the world,
and right now it's
got nothing to eat.
'Cause they're broke!
You think we're ever gonna see
the money that they owe us?
The state's not even
sending them checks anymore.
And how do you know that?
Biggs down at the post
office, how do you think?
Make your point, Dad.
You can do better.
That's my point.
Got some hay for you!
Turn that thing around!
Let's get your horse some breakfast!
What's the problem?
I thought you said you
had a hungry horse!
Get it out!
We gotta call someone!
Just get it the hell out!
What do you want us to do?
Alright look, it's long
enough, I can pull it out.
Do you want me to pull it out?
Just call someone!
There's no service out here!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
So shut up about the
god-damn phone, alright?
- Kirk, look at me.
- Just do something!
Like what?
What the f... do you want us to do?
You want us to try and pull it out?
Alright, hold him up!
Oh, shit.
Okay, on three, are you ready?
Hold him steady, come on!
On three I'm gonna pull
like a son of a bitch.
You guys ready?
One!
Two!
Oh, shit.
No!
What the f...?
No, help, help!
Oh, shit.
Help!
No!
Help, help!
Red!
Help!
Come on, come on!
No!
Help, no!
Help!
- Don't leave me.
- I'm not!
I don't know what to do.
Maybe we could cut the cable.
With what?
Try the phone again!
Come on!
So this is the famous Rocket, huh?
He's a beauty.
You understand what
I'm saying, don't you?
Every word you say.
Yeah?
Well in that case,
do you think Addie here
would ever be interested in
say, a guy like me?
In the city, my mother and I had a cat.
Addie.
I liked the cat.
It crapped in her boyfriend's shoes,
every chance it got.
What happened to the boyfriend?
She married him.
Then got rid of the cat.
Look, I'm not great at this.
And when I get nervous,
I start talking too much.
I, uh...
Is that your grandmother?
Thank you for the
hay, but please just go.
Okay.
You wouldn't wanna come?
I mean, I gotta get the rest
of this stuff up to Bernardy's.
Have you ever been up there?
It's really something.
I mean, only if you want to.
I'd love to.
Okay.
What are you doing?
I need to know what you found.
Mom, what are you doing?
And why it killed you for it!
No you don't, you don't
wanna see what it'll show you.
Go!
Away!
Hey!
Stop!
Hey, stop!
No!
Come on, Gaylen, are you out there?
I got a lot of units
headed out to station one.
What is that, a roll bar?
Did you reinforce this thing?
First time I met Gaylen was 23 years ago.
On the worst night of her life.
Her son Kenny and his
date, Darla Cleeway,
disappeared on their
way to the prom.
All they found was a wrecked
pickup and no bodies.
When Gaylen finally believed
what happened to Kenny,
she asked if she
could join the team.
That was the beginning for me.
Like last night,
was the beginning for you.
Where is everybody?
Buddy.
Hurry.
Go tell the sheriff to
get up here and fast,
and bring everything he's got.
Get out of here.
And keep your eyes on the sky.
Do it.
- Lock your door.
- What's going on?
I don't know.
There's men under that trailer.
- Roll your window up.
- What's happening?
Come on!
Stop making noise.
- Who's that with you?
- Addison Brandon.
What's going on?
- I've got guns in the barn.
- Guns?
For what?
Do you think you
could make a run for it?
I'd do it myself if not for
my leg and this god-damn cane.
What about those
guys under the truck?
They won't move.
They think they know this
thing, they got a name for it.
Mr. Bernardy, what,
who are you hiding from?
I don't know, I've seen
it and I still don't know.
Something came
down and got Apple.
Came down?
Spooked the horses so bad,
they jumped both the fences.
It tried to come
down at get Matheo.
What did?
Matheo put up a fight.
What are we talking about?
It dropped him out there somewhere.
No, no, no.
Come on.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Gaylen!
Gaylen Brandon!
Mrs. Brandon?
Gaylen?
I've been calling you.
What the hell is the matter?
It's here.
Is that what you came here to say?
If it's not, it will be.
What happened?
Just tell me one thing.
Did you bring something that can kill it?
He found it 23 years ago.
Kenny.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
The night before he died.
It fell from the sky.
He didn't tell me he took it home,
or that he hid it in the hay stool.
The horses wouldn't stay
in the barn with it.
Mom, get the horses.
He wouldn't
say what was happening.
Mom, just get the horses!
He must have touched that thing,
and that was why he was
so angry and frightened.
He wanted to kill it, whatever it was.
Maybe he thought he did.
I trapped it.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
It's under there.
Be careful.
If you touch that thing,
if you put your hand on it,
you see.
You see how it came to be.
And,
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
what it is.
Buddy.
Bud?
Seen a suspicious person.
Stay down.
Quick, can you see anything?
Like what?
There's knives
and stuff on both sides.
Can you reach one that
will cut your rope?
I tried, but it's hard for me to move.
You think her dead kid came
over the hill this morning
to tell her to vacate the premises?
What if she's right?
What if we can learn
that thing's secrets,
just by touching that
piece of its own flesh?
You're gonna go over there
and hold hands with it, aren't ya?
Just like she did.
What do you think this
is if it isn't a war?
War that absolutely won't stop,
until that damn thing
doesn't exist anymore!
If this thing gets away again,
I'm either gonna be dead,
or too damn old next time.
What if the secret to
what this thing is,
is the secret of how to kill it?
Hurry.
Sometimes he comes back fast,
it's usually with another body
and you don't wanna
be here for that.
Kirk?
- No way, Addie?
- Oh my god.
My leg, I can't walk on it.
But I could drag myself,
just get me out of this.
I checked.
They're dead.
He thinks I'm dead,
too, and probably you.
Why aren't we?
I was passed out when he
wrapped me and threw me in here.
But from what I could tell,
I think he's in too big
of a hurry to care if we are or not.
Yeah, well let's get out of here.
No!
Only he opens those, you
try, it'll split you in two.
This whole truck's a death-trap.
Maybe the front.
Try the driver's door.
What do you see?
It just looks like a door handle.
There's a chain, should I try that?
Try what?
I don't know, maybe
it does something.
Like maybe the horn.
Try that door handle.
Say a little prayer that
one of these doors opens.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Get behind him.
Put your hands on him.
Danny.
I know where you're going.
You will come back.
Danny!
Look at me, boss!
Sheriff!
- Boss!
- Danny?
Danny?
Danny!
Danny.
Look at me.
I'm next.
Boss?
Are you out of
your god-damn mind?
With all due respect,
sergeant, you stand down.
You don't tell me to stand down.
You don't know!
Not like us.
You got no takeaway in this.
Alright.
No!
Stop, stop, stop!
Get him off!
Anybody out there read me?
Repeat, Team Deputy...
Get off me!
Any team members
out there at all, copy me.
Repeat, Deputy Mike McGrail...
Hello!
I got a flipped vehicle
in a field up Turvy Road.
And I mean upside-down
and still smokin'.
It's headed to the nine.
Who is this, is that the sheriff?
This is team leader Miller.
We copy and are putting
rubber to the road.
Maybe 15 minutes away.
No lights, no sirens.
This thing hits the nine, we're
gonna take it by surprise.
You and Brady, you
come in from the east.
Miller, you and Jenkins,
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
see if you can find a road
that gets you in front of it.
The point is to stay alive.
It's what your old
man would have wanted.
You find Addie and the two of
you get the hell outta here
and don't come back until
I tell you different.
So you're just okay now?
I just saw you rollin'
around on the ground
like you were having
your brain scrambled.
I can drive, Danny.
Danny!
Danny, god-damn it, move
over and let me in there!
I got no idea, sheriff
up in Kissle says
they can't even get
a man down here.
Bud is really scarin' me.
He's in some kind of
shock or something,
and he's not snapping out of it.
- I'm getting ready to run him...
- I let her go.
I let her go.
I couldn't hold on, Dad.
I let her go and now she's out there
with that thing somewhere.
Sit.
- I left her out there.
- Sit down.
- I left her, Dad!
- Sit down and stop.
Stop talking.
All I know is that the truck
looks like it's been rolled.
It's missing a god...
Jesus Christ.
Bud!
Holy Mary Mother of God.
You son of a bitch.
Straight with me, can we kill this thing?
Are you still a sharpshooter?
Bet your sweet ass I am.
Get me up closer to
that son of a bitch!
Take his tire out.
Hit him again!
What the hell are they made of?
Again!
Son of a bitch!
What the hell?
Mikey?
Oh, come here, you big ugly bastard!
- Oh, my sweet...
- Christ.
Everything ricochets off that truck.
Mikey, come in, Mikey, listen to me.
That truck...
Straight at it, Jenky, go!
Mikey, come in!
Michael!
Don't shoot at the god-damn truck!
Mikey!
Do you read me?
Mikey, come in.
Michael, pick up!
Mikey, do you read me?
Don't shoot at that god-damn truck!
For my old man and 1,000 others, you ugly.
Hold on!
Danny?
Danny!
Take this!
Son of a...
Cover me.
Davis!
Get down!
Don't give him what he wants.
Swallow your fear.
Don't give it to him.
You cover me as best you can.
Then you haul your ass outta here.
It can't get both of us if we split up.
Split up?
We both gotta take him, Danny.
We need the firepower!
Hey!
Hey, you!
Davis, get the hell
out of here, move!
Whatever you think
you can do, you can't.
You're not gonna stop me.
So go away.
It took her, Mom, it's got Addison now.
What?
Where's Addie?
You have reached
the tri-county Sheriff's
department, servicing Baniff,
Trotula and Poho Counties.
This line is for emergency calls only.
If this is an emergency,
please hold the line.
Addie?
Every 23rd spring
for 23 days, it gets to eat.
That's what we know.
And the terrible things
it leaves in its wake,
missing fathers and mothers,
brothers, sisters,
daughters and sons.
We know that, too.
The creature reshapes our minds,
and changes the course of our lives.
What are you doing here?
They're picking me up here,
I didn't miss 'em, did I?
- They're picking you up here?
- So I could say goodbye.
They don't care,
it's on the way.
Really, are you doing okay?
I'm out of the house, out in the sunshine.
And back with your
old boyfriend, huh?
They say it's gone, you know.
You really believe it?
Gone for another 23 years?
You think we'll still be
around here to find out?
I'm gonna worry about you.
I can't believe they're letting you go.
The last time we made it to state.
I don't think Armageddon
will keep us from goin'.
Is that your dad talking?
I got a family who live in Bolander.
I might stay an extra day.
I'm gonna miss you.
Well, I'll miss you more, I'll bet.
Keep an eye on my truck for me.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
At the end of those 23 days,
in an open field by a
broken down school bus,
it once again ran out of time,
at the rusty tip of a homemade harpoon.
But most of you know this already.
I record these words as a testament.
This 23rd spring is a call to arms.
We will not fail and we will not fear.
My name is Trisha Jenner,
and this time when it comes,
I will destroy the thing
that killed by brother.
So...
Come and get me,
you son of a bitch.
MkvCage.com
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)