"JU-ON"
"A curse created by someone
who died with strong hatred in their heart."
"it remains in the places they dwelled"
"before their death, and grows.“
“Those who it touches die,
and a new curse is born.“
We're visiting a house where we've received
a report of child abuse.
We're going to check it out.
I'm here with...
...Yoshizaki from the Child Welfare Center
and a police officer.
-My name is Yamamoto,
-Hello?
and I'm with the prefeclural
child services department.
This is the police. Please open the door.
ls anyone home?
I'll check the back.
This is the police. I'm coming inside.
- It smells terrible.
-This is the police.
ls anyone home?
There's clothing
and partially eaten food everywhere.
Mom? Dad? I'm with the Child Welfare Center!
This does not appear
to be a good environment for a child.
This is the police. ls anyone home?
Toshio?
We're going upstairs.
This is the police. ls anyone home?
ls anyone home?
Mom? Dad?
Toshio?
What's wrong?
Please don't touch anything. I'll call HQ.
Did you find something?
The body of a child.
Was it Toshio?
I don't know. It's been several days
since he died.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
"Yui"
You want me to teach the class?
Yes. I'd like you
to take a class of the 3rd graders.
But the new quarter has already started.
One of the teachers has quit suddenly
for personal reasons.
But I only have my substitute
teacher's license,
and I've never been a homeroom teacher.
I'm aware. We've chosen you anyway.
First quarter has only just begun.
You've got a lot of time
to get to know your students.
You can learn on the job, Miss Shouno
"Yui"
Okay, I'll come to you again
once I've revised the script.
Alright. Contact me when it's ready.
Yes.
Thank you.
How'd it go?
I've got a job.
I'm an elementary school teacher!
That's great. Congratulations, Yui.
Listen to this, Naoto!
I'm a homeroom teacher, too!
That's great. It's a lot better
than just being a substitute.
I'll buy us some wine this evening,
and we can celebrate.
Okay, thanks. Talk to you later.
JU-ON: The Beginning of the End
I was so sure I wouldn't get a job
since the school year's already started.
"Class 3-3 Documentation"
They said the last teacher quit suddenly.
Did they get married?
I don't think so. It was a male teacher.
“Class 3-3“
But that's good luck for you.
Hmm...l wonder if I'm really going
to be able to do this.
I'm not really ready for it.
You'll be fine.
Just be happy you got the job,
and enjoy yourself.
This is what you wanted.
Yeah.
You're right.
I'll have to work hard to catch up to you.
What about you?
ls your movie script going well?
Well, they're interested.
I see. I can't wait to go with you
to see the movie you wrote.
‘Yui Shouno"
My name is Yui Shouno.
If there's something
you're not sure about, just ask me.
Okay!
Be seated.
Toshio Saeki.
"Toshio Saeki"
This is the seventh day in a row
he's been absent.
I'll take attendance.
Yuuya Aida.
Present.
Katsuki Asanaga.
Hello, you've reached the Saeki household.
We're not currently available...
Please leave a message.
Toshio Saeki. He's been absent
with no word from his parents.
I phoned his home several times
during lunch but no one answered.
I've asked someone else
to handle my classes for the day.
I'm going to his house.
I've read the records Mr. Konishi left.
This is the seventh day in a row
he's been absent.
ls Toshio sick?
I don't know the details.
Has no one gone to check on him
after Mr. Konishi?
Mr. Konishi met with his parents
and spoke with them.
We haven't simply been ignoring them.
That's true, but...
From now on, you're Toshio Saeki's teacher.
Goodbye, teacher!
Goodbye.
"Nanami"
Look at Nanami‘s face.
Hey, where are you going?
You'll see!
There's really a ghost, right Aoi?
A ghost?
It's true!
I heard it!
Seriously?
What did you hear?
Nanami!
You don't have to be scared.
It won't attack you.
Stop it.
Nanami gets scared easily.
They say nobody lives there
but you can hear a child's voice.
It's haunted by a ghost!
Rina! Aoi! Stop it!
Who told you that?
I don't know!
It's a secret!
You know, right Aoi?
I don't know!
It's fine, Nanami.
Hurry!
Here we are! This is the place.
This?
It's just a normal house.
Let's go.
“For Rent"
We're really going inside?
Of course we are!
Why else would we come here?
Aoi‘s sister is a real estate
agent who's in charge of this house.
Come on, guys!
But are we really allowed inside?
We're looking at a house
we might want to rent. It's fine!
I'll wait out here.
We can't leave you alone with the ghost!
Yayoi!
Come on.
Hello?
This isn't what I was expecting.
Of course. She's trying to rent
this place out.
Did you think it was going to be like
a haunted house at an amusement park?
It's really clean.
I bet there's not even a single cockroach.
This is so boring.
Aoi!
What was your sister saying about this house?
That nobody wants to rent it.
Liar! You were saying the house was cursed.
- I'm not lying!
-You're lying!
There's just these creepy stories, she said!
That's not what you said!
His!
ls not!
Hey, you two. Stop messing around.
Fine, fine.
She said you hear laughter
and footsteps and stuff.
Yayoi?
What are you doing?
This was on the floor.
What is it?
What's up?
It's kind of creepy.
That's weird.
What is this picture?
The face is all red!
He's on fire.
What? That's hilarious.
Yeah!
Look, his jaw's all screwed up.
Somebody's a worse artist than Aoi!
This is the worst one, I think.
- Yeah.
-it's a mess!
Who's there?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What?
What's going on?
Rina? Aoi? Who's there?
Stop screwing around
and open the door! Please!
Who's there? Who's there?
What's wrong, Nanami?
You look so pale. What happened?
Are you okay?
Did you see something scary?
Terrifying isn't it?
Did you see a ghost?
Did you see a ghost, Nanami?
"Kayako"
Toshio?
Mrs. Saeki?
Are you there, Mrs. Saeki?
Excuse me.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I'm coming inside.
My name is Shouno, I'm Toshio's new teacher.
I'm Kayako, Toshio's mother.
So...how is Toshio?
His father took him.
To the hospital?
Please, come inside.
ls he sick?
He'll be home soon.
Toshio?
ls that you, Toshio?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
ls something wrong?
I'm sorry. I wanted to see Toshio‘s room.
This isn't Toshio's room.
I'm sorry, I should've asked...
I've made some tea.
Please have some.
Ma'am?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
"Yayoi"
Aizawa!
She's open! Aizawa!
What's wrong, Yayoi? Are you okay?
Rest a bit. Switch out!
You can rest.
-Okay, remember to yell nice and loud!
-Are you okay?
Okay, remember to yell!
ls someone there?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Excuse me.
Nurse?
What is this?
What the hell is this?
Ma'am?
This is the 10th day Toshio‘s been absent
without permission.
Without permission?
His mom spoke to you,
right? When you went there?
But I didn't get to see Toshio.
What is it that you want to do?
If you're that worried, go see his mom again.
But...
There was something not right about that woman.
You mustn't say things like that!
If one of the parents heard that...
I'm sorry.
Be more careful.
Um...
ls it possible for me to meet Mr. Konishi,
the last teacher?
Alright.
He's dead.
Mr. Konishi is dead.
I received word from his family this morning.
I visited Toshio Saeki's house yesterday.
His mother was there.
I asked about Toshio,
but she just stood in the front hall
and said he was resting, over and over again.
I never was able to see him.
I'm going back there after school today.
I'm back.
Huh?
Why are you sitting in the dark?
There's a kid in class who isn't coming
to school.
It must be hard to be a teacher.
Which kid?
The one on the far left in the front row.
His name's Toshio Saeki.
Bullying?
I don't think so.
He doesn't look that weird.
I'll make dinner.
It's fine, you're hungry right?
Let's go somewhere.
Yeah, okay. I'll get changed.
Stand up!
Attention!
Good morning!
Be seated.
Anyway, my wife is waiting.
The young man found himself walking
a narrow road, deep in the mountains.
The damp fog...
Toshio?
Stop that.
Stop it, Toshio.
"Rina"
I'm sorry. Rina can't see anyone right now.
Please!
Rina is our friend!
Rina?
This room doesn't have a lock.
Rina!
Rina...
Rina?
Rina!
Where are you?
Aoi...over there.
They're coming.
They're coming!
What?
They're coming! They're coming!
T-the white child...
What are you talking about?
Aoi! Help me! Aoi!
Calm down!
Please, save me!
Save me!
What's going on?
AoimAoi, let's go.
Let's go! Come with me!
Wait!
This is a charm. You can have it.
Aoi! Hurry!
Rina...
I know!
Rina, we'll come back.
Aoi, we can't stay here!
The white child...
the while child's curse will kill me.
The while child!
The while child! The white child!
Stop it!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Teacher...
"Teacher's Office"
Mrs. Saeki?
What's this? A diary?
You're back.
Yui?
Yui!
Toshio...
"Class 3-3 Documentation"
"Toshio Saeki"
I moved to the house on the hill today.
This is exactly the kind of place
I'd always wanted to raise a kid.
I'm sure you'll find this house
beautiful too, my child.
I went to look for clothes for you, my child.
Just looking at the tiny clothes and shoes
was enough to make me short of breath...
I bought a picture book
I think you'd want to read.
Whenever I read it, it's strange...
I feel like you're right beside me...
I can't wait to play with you
in this huge living room.
I tried changing the way I walk,
like there was a soft ball in my tummy, but...
The last few days I was sure
I'd finally become a mother.
But I was wrong.
God, is it my fault you won't give me a child?
Did I do something wrong?
This house is hell.
I stood under the waterfall at a nearby shrine.
I was unclean.
My body is so clean now.
The temperature of my body
is perfect for your arrival.
I purified myself.
A single thread will connect you to my belly.
It's so mysterious.
I'm disappointed.
Takeo's always away on business.
That's why it's taking so long for you
to get here.
It's Takeo‘s fault.
Please, god.
Pour a soul into my body.
I can't take this anymore. I want a child.
I don't care whose child it is!
Let me give birth to it!
I want a child!
A child...a child...a child...
A child! A child! A child! A child!
It's been so long since I've written here,
but something wonderful has happened.
Takeo was away, as always,
and I was alone in my bed on the second floor.
And then a boy came to me.
He called me mother.
I know I must be pregnant.
I'm sure of it.
Takeo knows nothing.
He won't know until the day he dies.
It's a secret between me and my child.
Takeo will play the role of his father.
I came up with the name Toshio.
Toshio...Toshio...Toshio...
It's such a lovely name.
"Aoi"
Why are you spacing out? Romance problems?
No!
Hey...
Remember when we were talking about
that haunted house?
Yeah...maybe.
Sis, wait...is that true?
You said you couldn't find anyone
to rent it because of a ghost.
It has nothing to do with you.
Tell me!
I want to know the details.
Aoi.
You didn't go there, did you?
Of course not! Not if you're telling me
there's a ghost there.
I hope so...
That place...
Stop it, Kyosuke.
We've finally almost found a renter.
Somebody's going to rent that place?
You went, didn't you?
You didn't go inside though, right?
No way!
Stop it, seriously.
Aoi, go take a bath.
It's your fault
for talking about that stuff at home.
Rina...
What happened to you?
Yayoi?
Where did you go?
I'm sorry...
Aoi?
I'm sorry.
Rina?
Aoi?
Aoi!
Nanami.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What?
Let me go!
I'm sorry.
I'm sor-
No one's living here now
so you can move in immediately.
It's nice and bright!
You told her about this place, didn't you?
Yes. Kayako...
My wife, she knows about it.
Normally it's the wife
who's against these things.
I'm sure. It would be weird if she wasn't.
If it's a problem, Mr. Saeki...
Takeo!
Let's move here. It's wonderful.
" Naoto"
So you're with the school.
Yes. The child who lives there
isn't coming to school,
so I came to you.
I see. Alright.
Mr. Saeki‘s not picking up.
What is his family like?
A normal family.
Husband and wife and one child.
The front door was left open.
I see. Then I'll go pay a visit tomorrow.
ls there anything...
...going on with that family?
Anything?
If you know anything...
I can't share any information
about our renters.
Toshio Saeki‘s teacher
is someone I'm very close to.
And she's...
She's been acting weird ever since
she went there.
Tell me, please. I want to save her!
It's not the family.
Huh?
It's the house that's strange.
The house?
I told Mr. Saeki about it.
We're required by law
to notify them about that stuff.
What happened?
A child died.
A child?
19 years ago,
a child was left alone inside
that house during a heat wave.
I see.
Thank you.
It's not just a rumor!
If your friend...
has gone inside that house,
you should be careful.
10 years ago...
My wife and her little sister went inside
that house.
They just went inside, that's all.
That was all, but...
"Child Starves in House,“
“Locked inside in a room for 7 days
in hot weather"
This is it...
Child welfare received a report
from a neighbor about possible child abuse.
"Locked in room in hot weather for 7 days,"
"Hands and feet bound"
A child's body was found
in a second floor bedroom
with its hands and feet tied.
It was later learned that
the child was Toshio Yamaga,
the eldest son of the house.
Toshio...
"Toshio Yamaga"
10 years ago...
My wife and her little sister went inside
that house.
They just went inside, that's all.
That was all, but...
Yui!
Yui! Yui!
"Scanning.
I knew it.
It's the same face.
What's going on?
Naoto?
"Toshio"
July 28th, 2005.
Toshio has come to our home!
Look at the camera again.
Okay, baah!
Baah!
Our baby.
What's going on?
‘Saeki Takeo Kayako Toshio"
You made it already?
Okay, there's our name plate.
Thank you so much! This is Toshio Saeki!
Okay, look over here, Toshio! With your dad!
Toshio, hold your dad's hand.
What's wrong?
It's your dad!
'7th Birthday Party"
He's not scary!
Okay, Toshio. Your mom made lunch!
Put it down for a second and look over here.
Toshio! Look over here! Toshio!
Toshio! Call me daddy!
Why are you looking at me like that?
Stop it! He doesn't like that!
Huh?
Mom?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Who is it?
Whose child is that?
Tell me whose child it is! Tell me! Tell me!
It's my child.
And only my child.
Toshio is only my child.
You didn't have anything to do with his birth.
You don't have a child.
Mom...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Teacher...
Save me...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Mom.
Yui!
It's time! You need to get ready!
Naoto?
Upcoming jump scare (Major)