Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
The police is still looking
after twenty-one years
College student Heather Price.
She has been missing for three days,
after last
a friend had visited in "Mills Falls"
At the time of her disappearance
she wore a striped sweater,
a dark blue jeans and sneakers,
The police are looking for anyone who notes
on their current
Can give whereabouts ...
Photo will be uploaded
The time has come.
Kill Kristy,
Kristy: Female first name
Latin origin.
Kristy means follower of Christ.
Kill Kristy, then you kill God.
Kristy is pretty,
innocent and sheltered
Find them,
Follow her,
Recognize your fear,
mobile phone jammer
Photo will be uploaded
Let all partake of your work
Together we are strong.
They are weak.
You are Kristy.
To see the world in a grain of sand
and heaven in a wild flower,
hall infinity in your hand
and the hour is for eternity.
A robin in a cage
calls the wrath of heaven ...
Can not you even be serious?
I have to laugh.
because you sound so bored.
No, I think it's not boring.
I just do not know how to unravel it.
This is poetry, you nerd
No dry physics.
Did you just "nerd"
said to me? - Yes.
This is not an equation
or a formula, but interpretation.
As for poetry,
can hold a candle Hardly Blake.
Therefore, the best way is perhaps
mentally to slip into his skin.
Not in all of us
slumbers a writer
A dormant writer
Sounds interesting. - Okay,
a two in the course can I forget.
I focus
on the other subjects,
I save at least my
Scholarship. - I'll help you.
You wanted to start driving time
remember?
Sulking because someone?
You did not come.
Everything good, Aaron. You got me
? achgelegt, now you can go.
Take with Nicole, if you want
Is it idiotic,
Thanksgiving hang out here alone?
A long weekend, two girls
innocent and alone, you can find idiotic?
Actually, this sounds hot. - That's right!
Too bad that you can not be there.
Down there! - Just you wait. you!
Heisenberg dealt with the limits
the Predictable. When light for example.
We know exactly what happened,
when sodium nitrate meets water. Boom!
But no, the turbulence
Qualms of the previously calculated.
I know, Mom., We have already
discussed. The flights are really expensive.
Every time for the holidays
explode prices.
No, I just said, explode prices
Yes, I'll see you at Christmas.
And you've got to happiness
Tammy and the baby.
Should I leave the lights on, Justine?
No, you can make it quiet
I'm also almost finished.
Come on, come with me.
I swear to you, she lets you in peace
I will never forget the 4th of July
where they asked me
as for my career
as a dishwasher so runs.
Since she has misunderstood what.
- But she already understands that some people
for their livelihood
have to work. - Now is time well.
My goodness,
sometimes you're something of stubborn.
What should I do
so are you satisfied?
I want you to stay here.
With me. Just this once.
You know my family
I must go there.
Einstein's universe
is a universe of order,
in principle, everything is predictable
Whereas Heisenberg theorized,
the world is chaotic by nature
and ultimately not predictable.
Your missing me terribly.
Hey, Justine!
That was Scott the caretaker
You're also soon end, yes?
So then I wish you a nice
Thanksgiving. - I wish you well, Greg.
A famous quote that Einstein at least
is attributed, is: God does not play dice.
In contrast, according to Heisenberg's approach
dices God continually,
Say it. - What can I say?
You know.
Your high-tech weapons
not work for me unfortunately.
Say it. - Come on, Aaron.
I love you.
I raise you, Justine,
Have a good trip,
Come on.
Until then.
Hi, Wayne, how are you?
- Hey! Well, you alone at heart?
I console myself with wash laundering and
Then I stick my nose in the books.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh shit!
- Oh my God, I'm sorry.
Are you okay? - Yes, all right.
But this light makes me really ready.
Say. is this the whole weekend
remain so? - Well, as I know my luck.
God
There you go, who says's it.
Do you still have space in the machine?
You're the best.
And do not forget the sweets.
No, never.
as I could. - See you soon!
The windows were smashed and the
Tire was found dried sludge residues.
The investigators gave further known
that her body
in a nearby
Has found dumpster.
They assume,
that a connection
to the recently reported disappearance
of two other women there.
Hello, Anna. And?
You fly to London today?
No, only to friends in the north.
Nicole and you, will you really stay here?
Yes. the turkey pie
sizzles already in the oven. - Doswidanje.
Happy Thanksgiving.
Yes, all good.
I know, Dad
If it breaks up
I can do that too.
Okay. then we long afterwards,
I love you too.
You're not serious? - Please do not be angry,
my dad has suddenly appeared.
As a surprise, he has
the whole family invited to Aspen.
Okay.
- I'm about to pick up.
Come with me also.
A plane ticket I'll get you yet.
No, thank you.
- You can not stay here all alone.
Hi, Jus! - All good.
I get by, honest
I'm really sorry. I swear
I wanted to hang out with you.
But my dad has an extra
interrupted the campaign
and the whole family will be there.
And it's Aspen. - All good, Nicole.
I understand that but everything
Family is family.
But promise me. that you do not
all the time on campus hang around.
Driving times and get some fresh air,
somewhere into the green.
You can take my baby,
- Better not, because if something goes wrong.
Please, take it now already.
I know you're very keen on it.
Thank you.
You're the best. - Take care.
Take good care of yourself, okay?
- I Mach.
Thank you for your understanding. okay
Hey, last chance. - All right.
Stop!
Thank you.
Until then.
See you after Thanksgiving.
- I take care good care of the car.
Good morning and a happy Thanksgiving
from all of us here at 106 5th
Yes, and we wish
that everyone in the party circles
seiner.Lieben can spend. Jimbo?
- Man, what a beautiful morning.
Perfect Thanksgiving weather,
Unfortunately, we have evening
expect again with rain.
Just then. if all cozy
gathered around the holiday table.
What are you talking about. Spoilsport?
- I can not help it.
And what the heck, let it rain.
- Yes, let it rain: Let it rain.
Hey! Yes, we have a lot of fun.
Nicole is once again set off
for us to get some snacks,
How was your food?
With us, there's turkey pie and as a side dish
Sweets, a real festive food.
And later, we still have
a bottle of wine.
I have no idea.
Somehow my poems are not easy.
It is very quiet here
Quiet and peaceful.
Why not?
You, Wayne, with the lights
is wrong again something.
Yes, the guys at the Electrical
care, are only on Monday back.
And wo come because not ran.
Nicole gave you their luxury coach
borrowed for a joyride? - Yes.
I drive fast get what
Somehow I is for ice cream.
All right, then to the same. - Can I get you
what to bring? - No, I do not need anything.
I want my Thanksgiving buddy
really bring anything?
Mountain-Dew "and pumpkin pie.
Lemonade and pumpkin pie, it's ok.
Oh, Dave tell the target communication,
you're here over the holidays.
Alright.
Thank you Wayne, to the same.
Hi, I'm Justine Wills.
I stay here over the holidays.
Your admission card do you have? - Yes
Because I in an hour
will make the goal.
I'll be back in twenty minutes. Thank you.
As far as the latest developments
in the case of "Heather Price
And here are the little
encouraging weather forecast:
Early risers. the most is "Black Friday
want to do in front of stores,
must be based on some
to brace. Awaits us.
Thank you.
You have a nice car.
You are totally cute.
Student, yes? - Yes.
Listen, Rock Star: If you have anything here
want to buy, make a departure, okay?
The sunglasses, how much does it cost to?
What does it say on the price tag?
I would like a discount.
- Student card?
I want a discount.
All right, I'll pay that.
Do I like.
But I want nothing from you.
Since you liked something nice for someone to do
and then you get it from a shit.
You've still never
stuck in the shit, Kristy.
Now it's your turn.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What is this ?!
Hey!
Are you okay?
- Some people I understand not easy.
On holidays
so turn some people on the wheel.
Probably. - Was there trouble?
If you followed someone? - No, I do not think so.
The situation was just kind of weird
as someone wanted to make me afraid.
Alright. But I pass on to you
you know that. I'm here.
Yes. I know.
And I take care of yourself.
Then nothing can happen yes.
- Good night, Wayne. - Good night, little one.
Hi there.
- Hey. how are you?
Hey, all right with you? - Yes.
I just wanted to ...
No idea, just to hear your voice.
Me is there something funny happened.
- What was that?
Are you alone?
Yes, Nicole is still driven away.
Why is that?
- Any family affair.
Why you gave me
not members know?
I wanted to give you no
make bad conscience
Then I come to you now.
- Must you not. Really is not necessary.
Yes, of course. I'll be there in two hours
- No, please do not. Here's all good.
Justine, I will not let you
all night alone.
Hey 'Dave. - Yes?
If you found out what comic
let me know, yes? - I Mach.
Do me a favor,
enjoy the time with your family.
We'll see you again soon.
Oh well.
If that's really okay with you.
I'm a grown-up girl.
Everything is fine.
Wayne?
Wayne ?!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hi there!
Come on. come on
Wayne!
Error: Server not found
Why not does that?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
A beautiful room.
A handsome boy.
You really have everything. Kristy.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Wayne ...
Wayne! - Carry you to safety.
Wayne!
- Come on, get out! Quick, Justine!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Kristy!
No, my name is Justine
- You are Kristy.
The hunt has begun.
Running rid of God, Kristy.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Scott e
Hey, Scott! Help!
Scott ..
Scott!
Scott, Help!
Scott! Open up the door!
- Who's there?
Help!
- Moment. I'm already there. Second.
Oh. my God. - Quick, go inside
- What happened?
What's the matter, Justine? - Closing the
Door, quickly. You should lock the door!
Off, Titus!
- They killed him. - What?
Who killed who?
Who are you talking about?
The line is also dead.
Nothing works.
We can call the help no more. - Okay.
Now please stop me sometimes too well.
So, you tell me now
again very slowly, what happened
because I'm just stoned namely total.
Okay.
There are people. - Yes, dwell
And these people have
Dave and Wayne killed.
This is a crazy killer gang
Where did you get your phone?
Where is your cell phone, Scott?
Where is your damn phone!
Now not rotating through
- They're still there.
Scott
I have a motion detector.
The light goes on,
when someone approaches the house.
You sit down at best.
Sit quietly go there.
I'll be right back
Titus, you stay here.
The phone is lying around here somewhere
Where I've's the Matter?
Scott?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I'm here.
- Where did you get the phone?
We can not wait until the police
is here. - Damn, Scott, the phone!
You are here
Titus, good dog.
How many are there of those?
- Four. Four at least.
You stay here with Titus, okay.
Now you know
I have a gun!
Disappears from my campus!
No, stay here, Titus!
- Titus, no! Titus, come here!
Titus!
Let my dog ??at rest
her cursed Mietkerle!
Shit, where are you?
You have caught him.
Shit, man ... Titus.
This fucking assholes.
- We must get away from here. And do it now.
Take the building key.
You lie there on the table. - What?
Where is your phone? - I have no idea!
Maybe over there, look after!
Damn it.
where is this Mietding '?!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Emergency.
I grab you,
you son of a bitch.
Scott ?!
Scott!
No, please
Here is the PSAP.
have you just tried to reach us?
My name is Justin Wills.
I'm here in the "Birch-College '.
Here are people,
who want to kill me!
Three victims have been around!
I need help!
Roger that. We immediately send someone
Where are they? - I'm on campus.
The library. I walk to the library
I have the key.
I lock my door
and hide myself there!
Okay. make the. Go there
and you leave it on the phone.
Hello there?
I'm there. I'm there now.
Well, you remain on the phone.
We have a unit nearby.
It will be the same for you.
Thank you.
Oh God, thank you
- My pleasure.
Kristy ...
Your bad luck,
that the mobile phone number of the caretaker
is found everywhere on campus.
Select 9-5-5-0
for the concierge service,
receive video
good hunting
You're a good motive
Time to Die
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Give me a smile, Kristy.
But I'm not Kristy.
Why do you do such a thing?
Beautiful hair you have
And a nice car.
Aaron ...
Aaron!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What the hell ...
Justine!
Jus!
Are you okay?
Aaron!
Justine?
Hey, who are you ?!
Aaron!
Aaron, come here!
Come here! We have to go, Aaron!
Right now, you understand ?!
We need to get away. Aaron!
Now come on! Fast!
- Can you tell me what's going on here?
Are you okay?
Now tell me, will you ...
No!
No! No ...
Go to hell!
Go to hell,
you lousy piece of shit!
Come on.
Come on, Aaron
I love you.
I love you. Justine,
You can do it.
nails
Did you Kristy killed?
Yes,
I wait in the car.
I'm coming.
Think of the photos for the album.
Connect
the album
Kill Kristy,
Kristy is pretty,
innocent and sheltered
loading video
Six die in Austin.
Eight in Portland.
Tucson wants to see blood.
Hell opens up.
Slaughter the innocent.
Neither God nor the law
can they protect.
I would not do.
What is this?
The boundary of the Predictable.
Ever heard of Heisenberg heard?
Your people are dead.
You're in the shit
The hunt is over.
They have lost,
She was not the only one
Out there are many more.
the statement
the only survivors person
the events on the college campus.
the authorities has prompted ...
in connection
with a number of murder cases
the police 'in Colorado three young men
arrested and is searching for a fourth
reached us ... from Portland. Oregon
the message that ...
We are talking about real killer gangs,
in several states
a series of ritual murders
have committed.
Includes the statewide network
several independent groups,
for the deeds
be held responsible.
The authorities confirmed
that they are in possession of a mobile phone,
that insightful
Information on the methods
and staging
contains the criminal network,
Justine does not exist anymore,
My name is Kristy.