A Kindai Eiga-Nihon
Eiga Shinsha Production
KURONEKO
Executive Producers: Nobuyo Horiba,
Setsuo Noto, Kazuo Kuwabara
Screenplay: Kaneto Shindo
Photography: Kiyomi Kuroda
Music: Hikaru Hayashi
Film Editor: Hisao Enoki
Cast:
Kichiemon Nakamura
Nobuko Otowa
Kei Sato, Rokko Toura,
Kiwako Taichi
Taiji Tonoyama, Takao Kanze,
Hieaki Ezumi, Masashi Oki
Director: Kaneto Shindo
RAJOMON GATE
Who are you?
A wandering spectre
out so late at night?
No, no, I am no such thing
I am returning from Nobleman
Fujiwara's mansion...
...but I am afraid...
...of the bamboo grove ahead
It is dangerous at night with
highwaymen and robbers
Please help me
Will you see me to
the end of the grove?
What if I were a robber?
A fine samurai could
not be a robber
Are you one of
the distinguished Raiko's...
...renowned warriors?
Please help me
Very well
It's out of my way and late already,
but a little delay won't matter
Thank you
Woman
You're very fast
It is a familiar road
A cat?
What is it?
There you are. I wondered
where you'd gone
I heard a cat
Nothing to be afraid of
My heart is pounding
They are starving too
At the Kamo River bed...
...crows peck at the bodies
of those who starved to death
Thank you
It's a secluded place
We have nothing to offer you...
...but I would be happy
if you came inside
Well , let me see...
Mother and I live alone
Shall I accept
your kindness, then?
Please do
This way, please
A fine residence
Much better than my home
Like a nobleman's abode
Is anything wrong?
It seems cold
We only use it...
...when we have guests
I think your being here...
...will soon fill the room
with warmth
Strange things happen
in a war-torn land
Hail fell in Summer
Then it became so hot,
birds fell from the sky
My mother
Thank you for being
so kind to my daughter
Not at all , I enjoyed the night breeze
while I saw her home
I have a feeling we've
met somewhere
You're joking!
Isn't he, Mother?
I believe we have but
I cannot recall where
Serve him sake
A cat?
A homeless stray cat
Please have some more
Excuse me, but
how old are you?
What?
I also have a son
He is about your age
I am twenty-two
My husband is twenty-one
Where is he?
Serving the Emperor?
He went to war
To war?
Yes, three years ago.
He has not returned
Who is his leader?
We do not know
We had planted
Spring seeds
Seeds?
Yes
We must plant seeds in an age
of war to keep from starving
Suddenly , soldiers passed by
My son was taken,
plough still in his hands
Do not worry
He'll be a successful samurai
somewhere by now
Somewhere?
Far away to the north in Ezo
or south in Tsukushi
The whole land is up in arms
He must be so great
he has no time to come home
Don't worry. He was
lucky to be taken to war
It's a samurai's world now!
Noblemen cannot fight
So the samurai will
rule the land
The time will come when even
the Mikado must yield to our leader
I used to be a farmer, too
But since the war,
I've risen to this
Do not worry
Wars keep us in food
and everything else
Everything is ours
for the taking
Your mother?
She is being tactful
I am drunk. It is
very good sake
Please make yourself
at home
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I am glad you came
It's good sake
Please feel at home
Excuse me
RAJOMON GATE
An official is coming!
You are Raito Minamoto,
the leader of the samurai
It is not like you at all
Are you doing nothing about the spectre
that appears at Rajomon Gate?
Samurai
means men who are
proud of being strong warriors
The spectre may well appear
at any time in the Palace
I cannot sleep
peacefully at night
He told me in
his august voice:
I cannot sleep
peacefully at night"
Who's running all
over the land fighting?
It's me, Raiko Minamoto!
In the Palace, they kick
balls, play games
They write songs
and love women
Don't say I said this
It's frustrating
The monster's not
a supernatural being
Just an animal or
night-prowler!
Call Kintoki!
He went west
with his troops
Call Tsuna Watanabe!
He took his troops east
Fool! I know that!
I'm just trying to
stiffen your morale !
Is there anyone who will
kill the monster?
EZO, NORTHERN JAPAN
You cut off
Kumasunehiko's head?
Let me see it
Is it really his head?
He told me so himself !
He wore fine armour
and had an iron club
Good! It's really Kumasunehiko's
head. It's a great prize
General Takemaro Fujiwara?
He died in battle !
My army of two
thousand men?
They all died.
The enemy too!
Give me a detailed
account of it!
It was all muddy.
Rushes grew there
The enemy lured us
into the rushes!
The battle began at dawn
and ended at night!
He and I were alone by then
He was hairy all over like
a bear! I was frightened!
Kumasunehiko, I thought!
I was right! He told me so!
He asked my name.
I was going to say "Gintoki"...
Too simple , so I tacked on Yabu
and said I was Yabu-no-Gintoki
He said my name
sounded strong
Asking me if I were a general
he challenged me to a fight
Was he strong! Like Atlas
given an iron club!
I thought his club
would kill me!
I didn't want to die,
so I fought!
I finally cut off his head!
I will call you
Yabu-no-Gintoki
I will add you to my big "Four".
My big "Five" now
Jimbei, it's me!
I'm Hachi, Yone's son
You're...
What happened? My home's burned!
My home's gone!
Yes, you're Hachi all right
Your clothes?
Never mind that!
What about my home?
My mother and wife?
It was last Summer.
Kyoto burned for three days and nights
Conquerors and conquered
alike burned things
Fires everywhere in war
Sparks fell even here
We fled into the mountains
When we came back your home
had burned. It was just ashes
Did your mother and wife
burn to death or run away...?
We haven't seen them since
We don't know how
the house burned down
Mother! Oshigi!
Where did you go?
You've won great distinction
Your valour is known
all over the capital
Even beggars say
you're a strong samurai
Yes, young girls especially
make much of him
They hope for
a glimpse of him
The bravest man in the capital
must act accordingly
My orders:
Get rid of the monster that
kills samurai by biting necks
Do not fail since it will
affect my prestige
I offer you my cup
Pour for him
How about women, Gintoki?
Do you think
they're beautiful
Yes, I do
Very well
When you have killed the monster,
I will give you a woman
Any you want...so don't fail
What is the matter?
Afraid to walk
alone at night?
Are you passing through
the dark grove beyond here?
So am I.
I will see you home
Thank you
This is your home?
Yes
I live with my mother
My home's far away yet.
May I rest a bit?
Will you let me rest?
Welcome
It was nice of you to come
Please
Are your names Yone and
Shige, by any chance?
Excuse me if I were rude
You look exactly like my mother
and wife but are dressed differently
Where are they?
Three years ago, I was taken
east by the army to fight
I was working in the fields
I left my mother and wife
I wanted to return to my mother
and wife, so I fought as hard as I could
I could not die
I made a name for
myself instead
Leader Raiko named me
Yabu-no-Gintoki
But when I went home,
my house was gone
My mother and wife
were gone too
It's very strange
You two look exactly like
my mother and wife
I do not know where they are
But just as you fought day and night
in order to see them...
...your mother and wife must have
waited for you too, day and night
You have returned a fine man
I wonder what has
happened to them
My home was at the edge
of a bamboo grove
About here
How long have you lived here?
For three years
After I left for war?
Yes, I think so.
Is there a reason you are living
in such a lonely place?
A poor mother and daughter,
we live quietly and inconspicuously
If you came three years ago,
did you see my house?
If not, the charred ruins?
Who are you?
Reveal your true selves!
Monsters!
Why have you taken the image
of my mother and wife?
RAJOMON GATE
Woman!
Are you here?
Woman! Come out
if you are here!
Where are you, woman?
I did not come to kill you!
I came to see you!
Woman!
Are you here?
You must want to see him
I want to see my son too
Our vow is to kill samurai
and suck their blood
So we invoked
the evil gods
If only he were
not a samurai...
I beg you...
Bear it
Endure it
Be content to
see him...secretly
It's him!
Are you here?
Where are you?
What has happened to you?
You're here?
It is nice of you to come
We have nothing
to offer you
But permit us to celebrate
your safe return home
Serve him
I will not ask you
who you are
I just wanted to see you,
so I came
You look like my mother
You look like my wife
This is enough for me
I am glad to see you again.
I missed you
We also wished to see you
It will not be dawn
for a long time
Please relax and
be comfortable
I missed you
You have a cat?
No, it is a stray cat
without an owner
That reminds me. When I was taken
to war we had a black kitten at home
Never mind. I will forget
about my home
Excuse me
It will be dawn soon
Please leave before then
I will come again
Will you wait?
Returning empty-handed every
night...seen the monster?
Yes, I saw it but...
Why didn't you kill it?
It's...
You couldn't?
No...
You look bad
You look like
a monster yourself
Have you been bewitched
by the monster?
Your breast, your legs
are like Shige's
You are Shige
You are my wife
Shige, you are
good enough to eat
I'll chew you up and
make you part of me!
Hold me tighter!
More! More!
There you are
Where is she?
She is not here anymore
What? Not here?
Why? What happened to her?
She was permitted to see you
and love you for seven days
Please count and see
Last night was the seventh
She shortened her life
to seven days...
...to pledge her love to you
Are you not living
human beings?
So how could she shorten
her life for seven days?
I know not what you are!
Evil gods or ghosts- supernatural
powers can make you look human?
So you could not die!
She could not die!
I want to see her once more
Bound by a vow, I cannot
tell you who we are
We promised the evil gods
Gods of hate who wander
between this and the netherworld
Promising revenge by sucking blood,
we took human forms
She broke her promise
Our love?
Yes
You are my mother!
She's my wife!
Tell me who killed you!
We promised
So we cannot reveal what we
are or why we became like this
What did you promise?
To suck the blood
of samurai
of all samurai
You too, are one
Instead of killing you...
...she gave herself to you
So she fell headlong
into hell
She was glad to
Can I not see her anymore?
Is she gone?
Instead of sucking
hateful samurai blood...
...she preferred to love
you and go to hell
Hateful...?
Tell me why!
If only I could...
Bound by a vow,
I cannot tell you
Forgive me
Mother!
What happened to you?
You saw the monster?
If you saw it, I should
think you'd destroy it
I'll take that up later
Tell me what
the monster was like
Vengeful ghosts
murdered by samurai
So they hate samurai
and suck their blood
The ghost told you that?
Fool
We fight so nobles and the masses
can live without worry!
So how can anyone hate us?
Nobles may benefit from it...
...but the fleeing farmers
starve to death!
They are weak!
The weak always starve!
We risk our lives to
fight -it needs courage!
Isn't that why everyone
respects us?
Take yourself !
A farmers son once,
but Gintoki now!
Who'd respect or think
a farmer to be a human being?
A samurai, so women
make much of you!
No ghost is going
to hate us!
No ghosts can
make fools of us!
With a samurai's authority
I order you...
...destroy it!
One has been destroyed
What? One has
been destroyed?
How many were there?
Two
You destroyed one?
The proof?
Well ?
It will never appear again
Tell me why
It disappeared!
There was nothing I could do!
It disappeared from my sight!
One more left?
Yes!
Destroy it
- Let someone else...!
- Fool
If this one gets away...
...I will kill you
It is to uphold
my samurai honour!
RAJOMON GATE
Why did you
not go away?
You sucked blood
every night? Why?
Why can't you
rest in peace?
I wished to see you
just once more
I have lost my honour
and will be killed!
I have been driven to the point
where I must destroy you or die!
After seeing you, I was
ready to follow her to hell
Satisfied now that
you have seen me?
Please come
to my abode
Will you read the sutra
to me there?
Then I can rest in peace
Please. I have an
edifying sutra
If you read it, my deep-rooted
grudges will fade away
A puddle . Please be careful
What is it?
It's nothing
Something...?
It was a black cat?
I think so
Didn't you just pick it up?
Cat's legs aren't
just lying around!
Don't be angry.
Just a thought
Why would a cat
hate samurai?
They said demons appeared on
Mount Oe so I went for the Mikado
There are no demons
It was Shutendoji,
a bandit
No glory in killing a bandit,
so I said a demon
Now, you've destroyed a cat as big
as a cow and one thousand years old
To purify yourself,
pray for seven days
It's important to make
it the talk of the capital
Do it grandiosely .
Purification. Prayers
Mother
Are you a cat?
Are you my mother?
Return it to me
Mother! Are you a cat
or a ghost?
My mother couldn't be
Mother! Please come out!
If you are my mother,
please come out!
The sword that protects you...
...is in the way
Mother, please rest in peace!
I cut off your arm, thinking an
apparition had taken your form!
Take the sword away
Return my arm to me
What will you do then?
My arm is my weapon
Without it, I cannot suck
the blood of samurai
Will you wander forever
as a vengeful ghost, Mother?
Yes, I will
For the hate I bear
the samurai
For warring samurai
Excuse me...
Who is it?
Please open the door
Tonight ends the seventh
day of solitary purification
I cannot open
it until dawn
I know that very well
I am a medium in charge of
divination at the Imperial Palace
I cannot break the
rules for anyone
The Mikado is very
troubled about you
Tonight is the last night
So evil spirits may appear
to thwart your plans
The Mikado sent me here...
I am to seal them in so that you
may complete your seven day duty
Inform the Mikado...
...that I am a match for
any evil spirit!
You do not understand at all
Disobey him...
...and not only you
but your leader...
...will be punished too
It will only take a little while
Please open the door
Just a little while then
Excuse me for calling
so late at night
Is that the arm you
cut off the ghost?
Please divine or
purify the room
No, no, I cannot
go near it
You offered it to
your god there
I divine by the positive...
...and negative principles
Please show me
the arm more closely
Please be so good as to
bring the arm to me
Very troublesome
May I take it in my hand?
Please do
Your left arm?
I have it back!
Mother!
Spectre!
THE END