Okay, now make a wish.
Blow 'em out.
- Yay!
-All right!
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
All right.
Drayton,
where are your manners?
Give the first piece
to the thief.
I didn't steal
your fuckin' pigs!
You callin' my son a liar?
He saw your grubby hands
steal our property.
Why would I go anywhere near
your dirty pigs?
Or your filthy family?
I swear, the whole world
gonna find out
what kind of brood
you raising here, verna!
Shut him up. I've had enough.
-Ohh!
-Listen to me.
No hillbilly's gonna ruin
my son's special night.
You ready
for your present?
You know
you're my special boy.
Come on, jed.
Here you go.
Jed.
Yeah, this is it, jed.
Now, remember,
bad people like him,
they're trying to
break our family apart.
But we're not gonna
let that happen, right?
Now go on now, pick it up.
Jed, pick it up.
Jed.
Jed. Jed.
- Jed. Jed. Jed.
- Pick it up, jed.
Jed. Jed. Jed. Jed.
- Come on now.
- -You know what you have to do.
- That's right, jed!
- -Get him, boy!
--Come on now, jed.
Jed. Jed. Jed. Jed. Jed...
No! No!
- Here you go.
- -Get him, son!
No!
Ohh. Ohh. Ohh. Ohh...
- No!
-You can do it!
- Whoo!
No!!!
No, please! No!
- No!!!
-Jed. Jed.
- Jed. Jed. Jed...
Jed, go. Go.
That's right, do it!
Jed. Jed. Jed!
No!!!
Aaaah!
Stop! Stop now!
Hey. You let us down, jed.
--It's okay.
Your family's
always here for you.
Remember that.
Okay.
-You tryin' to make us crash?
-You want me to stop?
Nah, didn't say that.
Look out!
What the hell was that thing?
Hey, Betty.
What is it?
I don't know.
Well, let's go.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What?
It's just a kid.
Let's go!
We're gonna be late!
Hey, there.
You okay?
You shouldn't play in the road.
Help me! Please!
Hey, Betty, where you goin'?
I didn't hit him!
-There's something wrong!
-Betty!
He needs help!
Jesus Christ.
Hey, little guy, you hear me?
Let me help you!
Hello?
It's okay!
You can come out!
Betty!
Betty, where'd you get off to?
Hello?
Come on.
I won't touch you.
I just want to help.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Okay?
You done good, jed.
Looks like you can
learn a after all.
Nubbins, go ahead
and learn him some more.
Show him.
--Where is she?!
-Take 'er easy, hal.
-Let me through, goddamnit!
-Hold it! Hold it!
-Get the fuck off me!
-We need to figure out
what happened.
-Easy there, hal.
-That's my baby in there.
Is she in there?
Is my baby in there?
Answer me, goddamnit!
We got one of them.
Arggh!
I couldn't
get to her on time.
I'm real sorry, sir,
i swear to god.
Drayton Sawyer.
This time it ain't
the gorman house.
Nah. You're grown up now.
That means the gas chamber
for you.
For what?
You arrestin' me
for finding a body?
That ain't no crime I heard of.
How about I put a bullet
right in your fuckin' skull?
-Hold on.
-Put it away, hal.
He's right.
We ain't got nothin' on him.
Easy, hal.
Keep your head on.
Hal, he ain't worth it.
Come on, hal. Put the gun down.
Fuckin' trash.
You let those boys go
this instant.
Don't count on it, verna.
You see them do something wrong?
No, I didn't think so.
You uncuff him.
You let him out of the car.
No.
He's stayin' right there.
What for?
He's not under arrest.
He's under protection.
-From you.
-What are you talkin' about?
I can't count how many
crime scenes I've been to
where there just happened
to be Sawyers there already.
-Them kids ain't safe with you.
-Horseshit.
Send some units over
to the Sawyer house.
You round up all the minors.
I want all of them.
-You hear me?
-You can't do that.
Well, I'll have a warrant
that says I can
by the time we arrive.
It's called child endangerment.
You take one of mine...
And I'll take all yours, verna.
All of 'em.
In 1935, the state
of Texas instituted
an endangered childcare
program.
The first year nearly fifty
children were taken from homes
where criminal activity
was the norm.
Most of these children
were given new names
and entered into foster care.
Others, the product of
degenerate parentage,
were remitted here
to gorman house.
We take care of
their psychological
and physical needs.
Yes, sir.
I've been wanting to
come on here for a long time.
I think I can help them--
-Elizabeth.
Oh, please, sir,
lizzy's fine.
Elizabeth.
Most of these kids
will end up in prison
or mental institutions.
Keeping them here
is safer for everyone.
Keep your guard up.
Well, hello.
My name is lizzy.
I'm new here, and I want
to get to know y'all.
[Man[ Oh. That's bud.
You don't say all that much,
do you, big guy?
-Nuh-uh.
-Unh-unh.
-Uh...You're in my seat.
-Oh. Sorry.
I thank you kindly.
-Uh, I'm--
-lizzy.
Yeah, I heard. I heard.
S-sorry, I'm Jackson.
Jackson and bud.
And what meds
we have you on, Jackson?
Meds, huh?
They give 'em to us
and we take 'em, right?
We figured you'd know more about
all of that than us, lizzy.
You aren't gonna be trouble
for me, are you?
No, not me, lizzy.
Is there a reason
you keep saying my name
like that?
No, uh, I reckon I might like
how it sounds, is all.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Fuck you, asshole!
I'll pop your eyes right
the fuck out of your head!
-Let him go.
-Mind your own business!
Is it my business.
What is the problem?
He said some things
i didn't care for.
Something about a girl
in a nurse uniform,
what she might taste like.
Hey! Hey! Get off me! Let go!
Fuck you, Frankenstein!
Break it up, pinheads!
-Back to what you were doing.
-I didn't do nothin'.
Don't look at me.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What are you doing?
Come here.
What's the big deal?
It was just a stupid mouse.
Got a light?
You're not allowed
to smoke in here.
I got me special permission.
True story.
You can ask Dr. lang.
-I will.
-He'll tell you it helps me.
On account of my anxiety.
Truth is...
It's 'cause I'm his favorite.
He told me so.
-You just got yourself
a warnin'.
-For what?
-I was takin' a bath.
-Get out.
Bitch.
Everything all right?
Uh, yes, Dr. lang, I'm fine.
I'll have a word
with Isaac and bud.
Bud didn't do nothin'.
Lookin' forward to our session
tomorrow, Jackson?
Sir, he's right, actually,
bud didn't do anything.
He was just fighting?
-Well, he was protecting me.
-Remind me to tell you later
what he did to his last
foster family.
They took away his dog.
Yes.
That's a perfectly good reason
to bludgeon somebody
into a coma.
Yeah, well, I'm just sayin'.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
--I'm sorry,
I didn't mean to scare you.
You didn't.
Thanks for helping bud.
I know you don't even know him,
so that's, um, that's nice.
Well, I'm here to help you all.
You're the first nice one
we've had around here.
So I thought you should know.
Know what?
What goes on in the ect chamber.
Kids around here
got to callin' that
Dr. lang's chamber of horrors.
Piece of shit.
Why is that?
You drop by tonight,
you can find out for yourself.
I think maybe you could even
do something about it.
Yeah.
Jackson.
You're gonna get out of here
some day.
And just because you can't
trust certain people...
It doesn't mean
you shouldn't trust others.
Yeah, I'll think about that.
I'm sorry to
keep you waiting.
Barry Farnsworth.
We've been here an hour.
We?
- Miss Sawyer.
- [Farnsworth
it's Mrs. Carson now.
I want to see jed.
We've been through this before.
Year after year.
He's my son.
And I can afford me
a lawyer now.
Which changes nothin'.
He was taken from you
for a reason.
Show him.
It's an injunction.
The court says
Mrs. Carson has the right
to visit.
You have to let me see him.
You bring me jed.
Well, that's a problem.
Most of these kids
are given a new name
so they can hide
from their degenerate...
Criminal families.
Jed probably wouldn't be able
to recall you
or even his real name.
But you know who he is.
You and that sideways ranger.
You know 'em all.
I have a lot of patients.
We'll have to check the records
to be certain...
That's bullshit.
...And that requires
an entirely different
court order.
The records are very sensitive.
Get me the correct court order,
I'll be happy to help you.
That one took three months
to get!
Then I advise you
to get on it quick!
Jed is eighteen soon.
I'll recommend
he be transferred to prison.
You're a bastard.
Even though
you married into money
and hired yourself
a snot-nose shyster,
you are still hillbilly trash.
I have a friend,
a country clerk,
maybe he can push it through.
It don't matter!
It's all bullshit!
- Whoa!
-Lavatory.
That way.
I warned you, bud,
but you wouldn't listen.
Come on, man up, bud.
This is for your own good.
Go get her.
Office hours are over.
I can't go into
the ladies' room.
-Ma'am?
-It's Mrs. Carson.
Goddamnit, she's gone!
Get-- get...Off me!
Get out--
jed, I'm coming!
Jed! Jed!
- What in the hell is that?
I'm here for you!
-You hear me?
-What is it?
You're next, Isaac.
Are we ready?
--What the hell is that?
--Jed! Jed!
You can't be here!
Damn that woman.
I'll be back.
Jed!
--Jed!
Lizzy. Come quick.
The kids are loose
in the halls.
Help me.
Jed? Jed--
get your hands off me!
No way, she--
my client was acting
in self-defense.
-Get out. Get out.
She was--
that's it. Lock it down.
I can't believe you did that.
Want to give me a hand?
I saw you with him.
And you know
that ike is my soul mate.
There's an emergency exit
in the basement.
Come on, follow me!
I told you a thousand times
we're understaffed.
Just get here before they--
ah-- just hurry.
--Who's there?
Don't be stupid, bud.
Bud?
They'll never let you go.
Think about it, bud!
Let's get the fuck out of here,
y'all!
Ike, where you at?
Ike!
-Let's hide.
-Hide.
Right here.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Come on.
Jackson's got a hostage.
Hey what's up!
Hey, doc has a nice ride.
- Don't touch him!
- -Let go of me!
- Be quiet!
-Let go!
You fuck!
They'll think twice
about shooting us down
with her along.
They will!
Hey.
Hop in, stupid.
I owe you one.
Fuck you, gorman!
Well, don't you look nice.
You just had to bring the
prettiest nurse along with us,
didn't you?
Well, I didn't pick her.
No, Jackson did.
You got no reason
to be jealous.
Why'd I be jealous of someone
who's about to die?
Everything at the proper time.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Jackson!
Oh, here we go.
Hey, where do you think
you're going, bitch!
Unhh!
Put me down, put me down.
Fuck you!
Let go of me! Let go of me!
Do that again, I'll turn you
into strawberry pie.
I'm gonna kill him,
right before your eyes.
And that goes for you two,
as well.
Anyone bolts,
and everyone dies.
- You son of a bitch.
- Jackson, wait.
We're all gonna look out
for each other. It's okay.
Change.
No, you ain't makin' her
get undressed.
Oh, ain't I?
You got clothes underneath?
All right.
Cut it out, you bastard,
before I slit her throat.
That ain't no way
to talk about our new friend.
She's going with us all the way.
Where are you takin' us?
Mexico.
Perhaps you've heard of it?
Gonna find us some money,
find us some more wheels,
go past Austin, see my mom.
Y'all be welcome there,
my mama loves company.
And soon as we get
to the Mexican border,
we go our separate ways.
Jackson, you got someplace
you want to get to?
You got family somewhere?
No.
No, Mexico sounds like a plan.
-You sorells?
- Yes, sir.
Glad you could make it.
-We know which one did this?
-No.
We know who's missing.
They're pulling up the files
for us right now.
I bet I know who it was.
This ain't the work
of a confused child.
This is evil.
Needs puttin' down.
They all mine?
All but one were brought in
by you, yeah.
Roadblocks set?
Ten. Twenty miles out.
Push 'em out more.
I want every local cop
from here to new Mexico
on the lookout.
-Yes, sir.
Hello.
They're loose. Cops lookin'?
Yeah, of course we'll pay ya.
You just keep us updated.
We're gonna find jed.
-Lang's car was just spotted.
-Where?
South on 385.
I'll meet you there.
Sorells.
Yes, sir.
Knowing these kids the way I do,
they ain't givin' up easy.
-I understand.
-I don't think you do.
Just 'cause they're kids,
i don't want your men
going soft.
If they gotta shoot first,
then let god sort it out,
well, that's permissible.
Copy that?
Copy.
Fuck, I'm hungry.
I thought the plan
was not to be seen.
People are looking for a group
with a mongoloid.
We go in separate.
And you stays outside.
And you stays quiet.
-We have no money.
-Blah blah fuckin' blah.
We improvise.
There's food, there's money,
and there's cars to grab.
Get in there.
Want me to see if I can
throw it in your mouth?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
Oh, yeah.
You all right, darlin'?
Ma'am?
You haven't touched your food.
I'm just not hungry, I guess.
I'll bag it up for you.
Throw it in my mouth.
- Aah!
What the fuck you lookin' at?
Yeah, that's right, nothin'.
Everybody think
they can look down on us.
It's not funny.
You know,
why don't you check to see
if he's got a gun?
He's got a gun.
Let's start some shit up.
Okay.
I wish this was just normal.
I wish we were just
two people...
Here at a diner, you know.
I wish I was somebody else.
Sorry, y'all. That was my fault.
Think it's time y'all clear out.
Pay up and go.
Goddamn!
Holy shit!
Fuck, I love Texas.
Everybody go ahead
and put your keys and cash
on the edge of the table.
Clarice, get a bag.
Put your cash on the table, man!
-Clarice?
-Coming.
Put your money on the table.
Are you all deaf?
Get your fuckin' money out now!
-Get it on the table!
-Come on! We ain't got all day!
Fuck you!
-You!
-Let's go!
-Give it up!
-No, wait!
Thank you!
Let's go!
Fuck!
-Ow!
-No.
Where you go, bitch?
-Keep a hold of her!
-Stop it!
Let me go!
Go, go, go, go, go! Go!
Come on! Come on! Go!
Get in!
Yep, it were them.
No doubt about it.
What happened?
They went buck-shit crazy.
Cuttin' up with the waitress.
Then they started shootin'.
You see which way they went?
What car they took?
Maybe they left in a wagon.
-What color?
-Blue, I reckon.
Or gray.
A Ford.
Hey,
could have at least stolen a car
with a full tank of gas.
I don't look
at the gas Gauge
when someone's shooting me,
asshole.
Quiet, now.
Clarice, get over here.
Get the door.
Okay, on three, right? One,
two, three.
Smells like an old barn.
You first, lizzy.
Well, go on and get in there.
Get the fuck in.
Check it out, all right?
Well, it's as good a place
as any for the night.
We can rest up,
let the cops pass us up,
enjoy my mama's barbecue
by dinnertime.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Guess he died of loneliness.
- Sit down.
- -You're gonna be okay.
Okay.
I'm just gonna take a look,
okay?
You're gonna be okay,
but I gotta put some
pressure on it.
Moonshine.
That's good, that's good,
that's good.
--Now breathe slow.
-Come on, come on.
-Let's go. Let's go.
Squeeze. Make it better.
Big arms like that
and that's all you got?
That's good.
We just gotta put
some pressure on it. Okay?
Jesus.
Man, you're lucky I love you.
Want some of this?
All right.
Make you feel better.
Oh, god. Really?
Well, why not?
What else we gonna do?
-Yeah.
Easy.
--Yeah.
You're gonna aggravate
your condition.
My condition?
What do you know about me?
What now?
You know she's seen our files.
So?
So, she knows where
all those foster moms
who gave you shit live now.
No, I don't.
I only saw your medical charts,
i swear.
She's lying, Jackson.
She says she doesn't know.
Who cares if she saw anything?
You don't want to find your
family?
Bud's the only family I got.
No real family.
That's all I want.
I thought you said your family
were in Austin,
they'd be thrilled to see you.
They keep fuckin' movin'.
I swear, I don't know.
Come on, man,
let's leave her be.
You sweet on her now?
Fine...Lover boy.
Hey, good luck getting it up
with all the junk
they got you on.
Sleep tight, asshole.
Bud, you're on first watch.
Get your ass out of bed.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What'd I tell you
about running away?
Let go of me!
I guess I'm just too intense.
I think for the benefit
of folks sleeping
you best keep your mouth shut.
Run!
What in the holy hell
is going on here?!
This little piggy's
the worst goddamn lookout
in the lone star state.
And this little piggy
just tried to abandon us all.
Including his girlfriend here.
Well, then maybe it's time
we get rid of
all this dead weight.
Calm down. We got a plan
and we're stickin' to it.
Take these two back
to the trailer, okay?
Don't take your eyes off 'em.
Bud, you're an idiot and a fool
and I don't know why god
bothered to make you.
Now get away from me.
Shit.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Where's ike?
Hey!
Maybe you should
keep your voice down in case
somebody else is out there.
And maybe you should
kiss my texan ass.
Ike!
Where's bud?
Oh, shit.
Ike!
Okay, come on.
Ike?
Jackson! This is our chance.
Let's run.
If she finds bud
she's gonna kill him.
Bud can take care of himself.
Ike, where you at!
Whoa, stop!
What?
You don't want to see it.
Bud, you okay?
Hey.
What did you do, big guy?
Come on, let's get you up.
Come on.
I got ya.
Let me get a look at you.
Let's go.
Ike, where you at!
Ike?
Nope. Hands up, darlin'.
It's over.
I got one!
Drop the gun.
I said drop it.
All right, now turn around.
Where are the others at?
What do you mean the others?
It's just me and ike.
And I can't find him.
Just tell me
where the others are,
and you'll be safe and sound.
What do we got?
Fuckin' hartman.
He won't ask but once.
Just tell me where they are.
What'd she say?
That it's just her and Isaac.
She don't know where he is.
Nothin' but bullshit then, huh?
Good to see ya again, Clarice.
Aaah!
Jesus Christ, hartman!
You coulda killed her.
Get everybody to spread out.
They're close.
Dogs are on the way.
All right, fan out!
Wide circle.
They're somewhere close by,
okay?
Don't!
Yeah, you laugh it up, girl.
Let's see how funny this gets.
Feel that? Huh?
Hey.
This is your last chance, baby,
to tell me what I want to know.
--Huh?
Don't!
Where. They. At?
Cops! Cops!
Fuckin' cops!
Shit. Hide! Go, go. Go on.
Oh, fuck.
Who is he?
Rounds up kids like us.
Bad news.
He's a policeman.
Yeah, a policeman
that broke my nose once.
-He can help us.
-He's a corrupt son of a bitch
who has it out for kids
that get into trouble.
He filled gorman house
almost single-handedly.
--Get. Come on.
Get down there.
Come on out!
Y'all got nowhere to go!
You want to let me in
on the joke?
Fuck you, pig.
You're the fuckin' joke.
You ain't shit.
I said come out!
Your friends got guns in there?
You ain't law.
You're just a sad old man...
Cryin' over his stupid,
dead little girl.
If you go, me and bud
will be next.
Holy shit, hartman!
Jesus fuck, hartman!
You out of your mind?
You forget what
these fuckin' kids
did at the diner?
It's called justice, boy.
Let go of me!
Get in there.
What do you got?
We got a body.
It's not one of them.
It's been in there a while.
Let's move out.
They gotta be close.
Lizzy!
Hey!
Ohh.
-  -Fan out!
- Shit. Dogs.
We just got something
over here!
They been here.
It's nothin'.
Head over the Ridge.
Hey! Hey!
Stop! Please stop!
Stop!
Dispatch. I got three suspects
at the old bridge.
Copy that.
Backup is on the way.
Don't you fuckin' move!
Get back! Stay back!
No!!!
Stop! Stop it!
- Roaring]
They fucking killed bud! Fuck!
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck!
Fuck! Fuck!
Fuck! Why'd you run away?!
Why the fuck did you run away?!
You're insane.
You just killed that cop.
You got bud killed!
You got bud fucking killed!
Fuck! Fuck!
You're just like everybody else.
You fuckin' liar.
Why'd I think you'd be
any different?
Fuck!
It's hartman! Drive! Drive!
Hartman?
Come in, hartman, you there?
Hartman, come in.
It's sorells. Can you hear?
Hartman?
Hartman, come in.
Hello?
My name is Elizabeth white.
I was kidnapped
from gorman house
and held hostage.
Elizabeth?
This is trooper sorells,
Texas state police.
Where you at, girl?
I don't know.
I'm locked in the back
of a police car.
Why don't you go on
and tell me what you see?
An old barn.
Looks like it might collapse.
All right, you stay put,
darlin'.
Dispatch? I'm on it.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Get down there.
Jackson?
There is no Jackson, honey.
It's jed. Jedidiah Sawyer.
What are you doing to him?
I'm settin' things right.
You know where he started?
Killin' my little girl.
-Right here.
-Please let me go.
You ain't goin' nowhere.
This shit's about to get fun.
What do you want?
-Where's verna?
-Other side of town.
-Carson estate.
-She's not there.
Look, it's about jed.
Pig is here.
Says it's about jed.
What is it?
Hartman's got your boy.
Holed up in an old barn
somewhere.
-Sound familiar?
-Sounds right.
Hey. What about me?
What about you?
I thought we had an arrangement.
You know? Some kind
of understanding?
That we did.
Pig.
No.
No. No, no.
No. No! Aah!
Let's go get jed.
He's at the old barn.
You sure he's gonna remember us?
I got something
that'll jog his memory.
Don't do this.
-Well, who's gonna know?
-Me.
Hey! Hey!
Shut up, goddamnit!
Hey, verna!
We've been waitin' for ya.
No! No!
Jed!
Elizabeth, meet verna Sawyer.
Jed's aunt. Or is it mother?
Or maybe both.
You're too late, verna.
He's dead.
And I know you Sawyers
all travel in packs.
So where they at? Huh?
Y'all get in here! Now!
Hey!
Get on the ground!
Verna, get the fuck down.
Get in!
All right, well, maybe
I'll just get on a roll.
Kill every goddamn Sawyer
i see--
aaah!
Jed? Jed.
Jed.
You-- you all right
down there?
Jed? Come on now.
Pull him out!
Come on, we got ya!
We got ya, jed.
This'll hold it all together
till you're all healed up.
Okay, you're gonna feel it.
I'm gonna tug it real hard.
Almost at the end here.
Okay.
Oh, jed.
Elizabeth.
Untie me. Please.
Please.
Why?
What were you
gonna do with me?
I don't know.
But I'm sorry.
I am.
Jesus Christ.
Oh, god, let's go.
Nubbins, get over here.
-Make your brother
something to eat.
-Okay.
They're gone.
They're gone!
Unsheathes knife]
Go. Go!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
No! No!
All right.
Let's go.
You messed with
the wrong family.
Yeah, you're proud of
this goddamn family, huh?
Jed?
Jed.
Huh.
Ah, fuck.
What are you gonna do?
Huh?
This ain't over, boy.
Goddamnit!
This ain't fuckin' over,
ya hear me?
Jed? What did I tell you
about outsiders?
They fill your ears with lies.
You show 'em who you are, jed.
Look what that man
did to your face. Huh?
Jackson, don't do it!
You shut up over there.
You're next, do you hear me?
Fuck you!
Aaah!
Aaaaah!
Hartman screams in agony]
Goddamnit.
Go, go, go, go get her, now!
Go get her!
Whoo-hoo!
Jed, remember what I told you?
Go. Go get her.
Get her, jed.
Nobody messes
with our family.
Huh?
No!!!
Jackson, don't do this!
Please, don't do this.
I tried to help you.
That's all I ever tried to do.
You know that, right?
Listen to me.
It's not too late.
We can still
get out of here
together.
That bitch is a liar, jed.
She doesn't care about you.
Kill her. Kill her now.
Please don't
listen to her.
Please.
I know there's good in you.
I've seen it.
Please listen to me.
This isn't you, Jackson.
This isn't you.
It's your crazy mother!
It's your crazy--
that's my boy.
You done good, jed.
You made mama proud.
It's over