one three one
this is the dispacher go ahead
This is one three one! We have a male,
mid-fifties with burns over nine to nine
and a half percent of his body!
Prior to our arrival on scene,
patient apparently doused his head,
neck and face with some
sort of highly concentrated acid!
Patient’s airway is severely
compromised due to fume inhalation!
Vital signs unstable! Please
advise!
Patient is a criminal
suspect!
We’re coming in with a
police escort right now!
hi
Can I talk to him?
He can’t actually talk...
alright . Jesus...
can I  just
have a few minutes?
We wanna know who you are.
We’ll find out, you know. Sooner or
later.
You could save us some
legwork by communicating with us now.
Are you a Satanist? You in some
kind of cult?
Coz if there are  others involved,
we’ll find them too, believe me.
What’s the matter?
Is that it?
Is there someone you
wanna tell me about?
I’m sorry. The Nurse at reception
downstairs is on the phone.
She wants to talk to you.
Says it’s urgent.
i m coming
I’ll be right back.
yeah
His daughter? When was this -- is
she still here...?
did she leave any information,
a phone number...?
What do you mean a little girl?
How little...?
Jesus, Mary, and Joseph...
There is sin and evil in the world,
and we’re enjoined by scripture and
the Lord Jesus to oppose it with allour might.
Our nation, too, has a
legacy of evil with which it must deal.
The glory of this land has been its capacity
for transcending the moral evils of our past...
Eat some now, save some for later...
Now and Later...
the really tasty
treat...
Now and Later...
the
flavor can’t be beat..
Look at all those pieces
Owen...?
Flavors that are wow...
- Owwwwen...?
- What...?!
Dinner time honey...!
....and these Thy gifts,
for which we are about to receive,
..please guide and direct us for all our days.
And protect us from evil. Amen.
How was school today?
you didn’t go and spoil your dinner on me now,
did you? Owen?
...No...  I didn’t...
Eat. Please, honey.
Hello?
What?
Look, I’m not
gonna discuss this now?
We’re eating dinner
we had an agreement, John.
I think maybe you
better call my lawyer okay...?
Don’t talk to me like that
I will
not. Be spoken to. In that way!
Hey little girl...
Are you a little girl...?
are you scared?
I pledge allegiance... to the flag...
of the United States of America...
And to the Republic... for which it
stands...
One Nation... under God...
indivisible, with liberty and justice for all.
Mr. Zoric...?
Okay, Kenny! Ten laps! Now!
I didn’t do anything...!
Now! Or I make it twenty!
Hey little girl...
Ow! Don’t...!
Are you a little girl...?
That’s why he won’t go swimming
he doesn’t want everyone to see what
a little fucking girl he is
Hold him down! Get his arms! Get
his arms!
stop
Dude, shit! I think he pissed
himself!
Oh...! Shit...!
He fucking pissed himself!
Jesus! Fucking freak!
is that is for you?
Are you scared, little girl? Huh?
What are you doing?
Nothing
Nothing.
You guys just moved in, huh?
Upstairs.
How do you know?
I live next door to you.
Right there.
Just so you know, I can’t be your
friend.
...Why not?
That’s just the way it is.
who said I wanted to be your friend...?!
god!
what am i supposed to do?
to go out in there and do it myself? Huh?
what?
answer me
maybe i m getting slow
maybe i want to get caught...
maybe i m just tired
excuse me
can I get through here?
As some of you may have heard, there
was an incident last night
and one
of our recent graduates was killed...
i want assure you that everything possible is being
done to find those responsible for this tragedy,
but in
the mean time
we should all be on the
lookout for any suspicious activity...
Your safety is our number on concern.
it’s you again, huh?
You know, I really wanna be left
alone..
Me too.
So leave.
You leave.
I’ve lived here  longer than
you...
What is that?
...This?
It’s a Rubik’s Cube.
You don’t know Rubik’s Cube?
Is it a puzzle?
Yeah... Wanna try?
You can give it back
tomorrow.
...How do you do it?
You gotta make each side all one
color.
like that
...You smell kinda funny.
Aren’t you cold?
I don’t really get cold
I guess I'll see you tomorrow.
Help me...
...Hello?
Please... Help me...
Hey there... Are you okay?
What happened?
I fell...
Yeah...?
Can’t you get up...?
No...
How old are you, sweetheart?
Do you live around here...?
I live right here...
Can you carry
me...?
Okay, sweetheart... sure... Why
don’t you... here...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
You got it...?
you expect me to clean it up now...!
don't you?
...fucking bitch!
How did you do it?!
I just... twisted it.
Do I smell better now?
...What’s your name?
Abby. What’s yours...?
I’m Owen.
How old are you?
Twelve. More or less. What about
you?
Twelve years, eight months, and
nine days
what do you mean,
“more or less”...?
When’s your
birthday?
I don’t know.
You don’t know?
Don’t you
celebrate your birthday?
- Don’t you get birthday presents?
- No.
Well... you can... have this. If
you want.
That’s okay. It’s yours.
I really don’t get how you did
this...
...Want me to show you?
Yeah...
I must be gone and live, or stay
and die...
Yon light is not day-light,
I know it
It is some meteor that the sun exhales,
What were you writing back
there...?
...What do you mean?
In Cook’s class.
Let’s see it...
- ...No
- ...No?
Where is it...?
Show me!
- ...Jesus Christ, dude...!
- ...What...?
You explain that to his mom...
That’s okay...
She’s not going to tell her mom on
us, is she...?
She fell down on
the playground, that’s all...
Right?
Right...?
Say it, little girl... Say it...
come on, dude... Let’s go...
I fell down...
...On the playground.
Well you have to be more careful,
Okay honey?
I don’t like to
see my baby hurt...
Bless us o Lord and these thy gifts...
and protect us from evil
look , I made one for you,
and one for me
Are you reading this?
It’s for school, it’s boring
c’mon, look...! It’s so cool...!
We can talk to each other...!
Through the wall...!
Can you hear me through the wall?
...Only sometimes..
Did you hear anything the other
night...?
why was your dad so mad...?
Where’s your mom...?
Are you parents divorced?
My mom is dead
My mom and dad are getting a divorce.
What happened there...?
Just some kids. At school.
Where do you go to school anyway?
I never see you....
...Owen, listen.
...What...?
You have to hit back.
You have to hit back hard.
i can't
...There are three
Then you hit back even harder.
Hit them harder than you dare
And then they’ll stop.
...What if they hit me back?
You have a knife.
Yeah... But what if that didn't
stop them?
I’ll help you.
But.. You’re a girl...
I’m a lot stronger than you
think I am
...I have to get in there...!
...Move...
- Mr. Zoric...?
- Yes, Owen?
I was wondering. About the after
school strength training?
Can people still sign up?
...You like to get strong?
Okay. Four o’clock. You come. We
make you strong.
Cool...
you want some?! They’re really good!
They’re my favorite!
- They’re really really good!
- no thanks
What do you like...?
You can have anything you want...!
That's ok..
Okay...!
I guess that’s it...!
i guess i could have one
really!
here, try this
...Sorry
Owen... Do you like me?
Yeah...
A lot.
Would you still like me... even if
I wasn’t a girl...?
...What do you mean...?
I don't know... I guess...
...Why?
No reason...
So where are you guys from?
How come you moved here...?
We... move around a lot.
Yeah, but why would you move here?
Nobody moves here
I hate it here
Someday I’m gonna
get out...
And I’ll never come back...
People here ....
they're just stupid
Owwwwen...!
oh god
Hang on...
What...!
You promised me you wouldn’t
leave the courtyard!
mom I been here the whole time...!!!
Well, come up! It’s time for dinner...!
oh god
goodnight..
You going out...?
Is there a choice...?
Please don’t see that boy again...
Okay...?
Hey! Stop!
Hey!
- hey What's up?
- You know what?
- What are you doing?
- pushing back the seat
The handle is in the front.
- I hate this thing here
- Turn it
that will take me all night
- You need gas?
- Yes.
Fuck!
Help!
Thanks.
- Sup, Jenner!
- Hey, guys. what's going on?
what? What the fuck?
That's my car!
Stop!
Stop the car!
Stop, you bastard!
Stop!
Hey! Stop!
Help! Help!
Help!
Let me go!
Over there
he should be in the car
Hey!
There!
an unidentified man has been arrested
in connection with the recent ritual
murder of a local high school honor student...
...The suspect is hospitalized in
critical condition
with severe, self-inflicted acid
burns over his face and torso
making it impossible so far for
authorities to determine his identity...
Ladies and gentlemen, the President
of the United States: Ronald Reagan!
Excuse me!
I'm looking for my father.
Is he a patient here...?
Yeah... They... brought him in...
...The police did.
...Oh... I see...
Do you know where he is...?
He’s... he’s on the tenth floor,
sweetie... But it’s restricted...
- why don’t I call them, tell them you’re here..?
-  Oh, no -- that’s okay...
Oh my God -- you poor girl...
Sweetie!
...May I come in...?
...I’m sorry...
His daughter? When was this -- is
she still here...?
Well did she leave any information,
a phone number...?
What do you mean a little girl?
How little...?
Jesus, Mary and Joseph!
Help!
Owen!
Can I come in...?
No...wait
don’t look at me...
How’d you get up here...?
- I flew.
- Yeah, right...
Hey... you’re not wearing
anything...!
And you’re freezing...!
Is that gross...?
No.
Abby?
Yeah...?
Will you go steady with me?
- What do you mean?
- Will you be my girlfriend...?
Owen...
I am not a girl.
- You’re not a girl...?
- No.
What are you...?
Nothing.
Oh
You know, it’s okay if you don’t
wanna be my girlfriend.
You don’t
have to make stuff up...
- Can’t we just keep things the way they are...?
- Yeah.. sure...
Well...
Do you... have to... do anything special?
when you go steady...?
No.
-So everything’s the same?
- Yeah...
Okay.
-  We can go steady.
- Really?
Yes.
"I must be gone and live, or stay and die. "
ABBY + OWEN
If you play hockey, you play this
side! Free skate, this side!
Everyone careful for holes in ice!
Stay! Away! From holes!
I hope you been learning how to
swim...Coz today you’re goin’in...
go
You must be quick.
Faster, faster!
What you think you’re gonna do with
that...?
I’m gonna... hit you with it... If
you try anything...
Really? Wow!
You know what I think?
I don’t think you’re gonna do a
fucking thing...
I think you’re just gonna stand there,
like the  little girl you are...
And I’m gonna grab that stick...
and ram it right up your ass...
And then...?
You’re goin’ swimming.
hey hey
quickly
Dude....Zoric is over there
checking us out
let it go...
We’ll beat his little ass later...
Give me the stick...
Holy shit! Are you fucking crazy!?
Hey!
Okay.
Please, move back.
move back
Give me one reason I shouldn’t
suspend you, Owen...
Can you think of one?
Don’t you know what
could’ve happened...?
You seem like a smart kid.
I just don’t want to see you going down
the wrong path...
He’s a good boy... he really is...
Hello...? Is John there...?
Excuse me...? This is his wife
who’s this...?
hello, Cindy... Could you
please tell John that I called?
Hi there... Your mom or dad home?
Yes. Mom!
What?
- Sorry to bother you, Ma'am.
What’s this about...?
I’m afraid there’s been an incident
with one of your neighbors here in the complex...
So we’re just going around, talking to people...
see if anyone knows anything...
What kind of incident?
Owen, why don’t you go to your
room...?
- Sorry, guys!
- you wonder?
- what?
why do you need glasses?
so dangerous?
- Hey! Stop!
- How’s the cripple...!?
Stop! Hey!
Jesus Christ, dude... look out...!
Man, that kid wailed on your ass
Can you still hear me, bro  ?!
Stop!
- You going home?
-No, we’re going over to Mark’s...
Well can I borrow your keys...? I
forgot mine... Please...?
Give me the fucking keys!
Thanks!
- See you at home, little girl...
- Hey!
- Shut up!
- But I didn't say anything!
Shut up!
Abby, I did it!
You did what...?
They were gonna push me in a hole.
In the ice.
So I got a big stick
and I hit him in the head really hard.
He had to go to the hospital
I almost got suspended.
But I did it. What you said.
I stood up to them.
Owen...
...Yeah?
- Hey... You wanna go somewhere...?
- Where?
“ENTER UNDER PENALTY OF DEATH”
- It's pretty cool huh?
- Yes.
This this kid who used to live
in the building. Tommy.
He would come down here and drink and
smoke with his high school friends, and..
And when they weren't here,
He would play ping-pong with me.
He was really cool
Then he had to move away.
I kinda like it here...
It’s cool...
I don’t think any of the adults
know about it... just us.
So... what did you want to do down
here...?
I think I have an idea...
close your eyes...
keep them closed
Let's make a pact.
it only hurts for a second
Here.
Abby?
Go away...!
Goddammit ... Virginia...!
Phooey! Virginia!
Virginia!
What the FUCK ?!
Leave her alone!
Hey!
Somebody call 9-1-1...!!!
Mom!
Hello!
Dad?
Can I talk to you?
...Sure, pal... What is it...?
i don't know...
...Do you think...?
Is there such a thing As evil?
What?
What are you talking about, pal...?
-...Can people be evil??
- Where are you getting this...?
From your mother...?
-All her religious crap...?
- No.
You know what? Owen, listen put
your mother on the phone, I wanna talk to her...
she’s not here...
All right. please have her call me when
she gets back, alright...?
Well.
Dad!
Owen, I want you to get that crap
out of your head, okay?
You mother just... she has problems... and I’m
gonna talk to her.
So I don’t want to hear
any more about this, alright?
alright?
...Yeah...
You have a good
night, pal. I love you.
And I’m sorry about the last couple months,
but I’ll see you real soon, okay?
- I promise! Maybe next weekend.
- Okay...
I love you!
Can I come in...?
...You have to say it...
...You can... come in..
Are you a vampire...?
I... need blood. To live.
- How old are you? Really.
- twelve...
But...
I been twelve for a very
long time...
Where’s your dad...?
...He wasn’t... my dad...
What this stuff?
I like puzzles.
I’m wanna go home now...
I wanna go.
Are you gonna let me...?
What are you gonna do to me...?
...I told you we couldn’t be friends...
Hi... Are you Larry...?
can i talk to you for a
minute...?
Sure.
Sorry to bother you.
..How’s... she doing...?
It’s been... quite a night
They had to give her
almost six pints of blood...
We’re still waiting to
see if her body rejects it.
I won’t keep you too long.
I just want...
I need to ask you about the
description you gave. Of the little girl.
You said she had long blonde hair
was around twelve years old,
and wasn’t wearing shoes...
- Right?
- Right!
Have you ever seen this man?
He’s a suspect in a murder investigation.
Maybe... Looks like a guy
in our building
Did he have a daughter? Like the
girl you described?
I don’t know.
I’ve only seen him a few times...
Why?
You think this is related to the murder case?
Maybe. I began to believe that two of
victims were part of a Satanic cult.
What?
We found another body few days ago...
Same M.O. The victim was
completely drained of blood...
But there were bite marks on the
victim’s neck. Small ones. Like a child’s
Jesus Christ!
Virginia! God!
No!
“HI SWEETIE, MEETING WITH
THE LAWYER TONIGHT. BE HOME LATER.
THERE’S A POT PIE IN THE
FREEZER! I LOVE YOU! GOD BLESS! MOM.”
one patient who killed in a fire,
and one hospital nurse
the five alarm fire broke out on the
eight floor of the hospital..
The cause of the fire is
still under investigation, but....
...Hey.
You... have to invite me in.
It’s your home
What if I don’t...?
Why can’t you just come in...?
Is there something in your way...?
No! Stop! You can come in!
You can come in!
What was that?
I don't know.
I just know this is what happens
if you don't invite me in.
What if I didn’t say anything...?
Would you have just kept bleeding...?
You'd have died?
I knew you wouldn’t let me...
You can borrow one of my mom’s old
dresses if you want...!
Hello!
Owen?
I’m in here...! I'll be right there!
“Hi, Owen. Good morning. I am
in the bathroom. Please do not come in.
Want to hang out with me again tonight?
I really like you. Love, Abby.”
Hello...!
Police department! Open the door
Open the door!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Police officer!
No, no! Stop!
Jesus Christ, son !
No!
Owen... I have to go away...
Ah! Speak of devil! There he is!
Hi!
- today we start in pool, okay?
- Okay?
- Hi, Owen!
- Hi!
He’s here...
Come on, hurry up !
face into water:
one, two, three, breath.
One, two, three, breath.
One, two, three, breath. and again.
One, two, three, breath...
- Mr. Zoric there’s a fire!
- What?
- Outside! In back!
- Owen, I be right back!
- Where?
- In the basement!
Everybody go out of the pool!
What?
Move!
Let’s GO!
out! out!
get out of the pool!
out!
Out!
What are you gonna do with that...?
No! No! leave me alone!
No!
No! No!
No! stop!
No!
stop it!
No! stop!
Grab his arms! Get his arms!
No! No! stop!
We have a little contest.
Okay?
You stay under water...
three minutes.
If you can do it I’ll just give
you a little nick. On your cheek.
But if you can’t... I’ll poke out
one of your eyes... Got it?
An eye for an ear.
Three minutes.
Better take a deep breath ...
- Okay, Jimmy...
- Shut up!
- Dude, come on...
- I said shut up!
Go!
get me out of here!
Help!
Excuse me, can I see your ticket?
That trunk yours...?
TRAIN STARTS TO MOVE...
Eat some now, save some for later...