Are... you the... Are you the demon Lo?
Yeah.
Have... great power?
This... I know...
This I know.
Now clean the shit from your pants and tell me what you want.
A girl.
You summoned me for love?
Yes.
You would throw away my great power over such human trivialities?
You have to do what I say.
Look at you, pretending to be brave.
What's your name?
Justin.
That's a terrible name.
Doesn't fit your future. Allow me to baptize you...
"Dinner"
It's Justin.
Dinner!
You have to let go of the past.
I summoned you...
You have to obey my charge.
That might be loosely true, but I'm under no obligation to respect you.
And if given the opportunity, I will eat you.
I'm not afraid.
You are...
Where the fuck am I?
In my apartment.
Dramatic! You mind if I make a few... changes?
Now where would a stringy pork-chop like you get such an old goat?
It's not mine.
Really?
I would've pegged you as a "class A" warlock.
Belonged to her.
Pretty.
Not her best angle.
Do you know her?
No.
You're lying!
I warn you, Dinner.
Trying to read a demon is a thorny game.
You took her...
I took her?
Not you specifically, but your... people.
Oh.... I knew it!
You're racist.
She was taken by something.
A- A demon!
You sure it wasn't a bear?
I hear they're getting braver these days.
I'm not an idiot.
Okay? I might just be a bug to you, but I'm not a fool, okay?
She was taken by something, something like you.
I thought I was dying. It took April!
"It took April". Look!
Let me give you a nugget of advice.
Page 303. It's a closing spell.
Send me away before I get really hungry.
I'm not leaving here without her.
Look, Dinner.
If what you're telling me is true, and I'm sure it is.
The simple fact is: you're fucked.
You don't get out of Hell, that's it.
I want to see her.
Well, I don't know her.
Her name is Apr-
Yes! She's the rain that brings the flowers.
Look, I'm sure you two had a deeply emotional connection.
But the simple fact is: Hell is a big place.
Kinda gloomy,...
... endless amount of souls. Been around since, I don't know, the Dawn of Men.
We don't keep records.
Then I'll wait.
What? No.
What?
While you look for her.
No, no. I'm busy.
I'm yourMaster.
Demon, I'm yourMaster!
What you're asking is impossible!
But I'm still asking.
Frightened children shouldn't play with pentagrams.
If you so much as let a pinky outside of that circle, I will have you in my belly for 90 years.
That's how long it takes my acids to break down a little bitch like you.
Why me?
April!
April Oak.
Like the tree?
Yes.
Stupid name for a human.
Tell me about her.
Just find her for me!
That's what I'm trying to do!
But the better versed I am in your Juliet
the better chance I have of finding her out of the billions of dark matter
floating around in torment.
Oh.
Yes... "Oh".
What do you wanna know?
I want details. Emotional ones.
I want to feel your pain for her.
Well...
She's... She's 5'3...
Brown hair...
Stop!
Goddamn, Dinner. You are stupid.
I asked you for emotional details.
How you met, how you fought, how you fucked, how you kissed, how you ate,
date, hit, and shout at God!
Don't give me her stats, I'm not casting a movie.
So... you want... details...
Yes!
Like, how me first met?
"The Sound of Music" said it best.
Well, I was on lunch break at a restaurant I go.
What?
It's flashback time!
That's me?
No, that's me pulling the thoughts from your brain and projecting them on that wall over there.
I know, right?
Now hush. Let's just see what happens.
Hi!
Hi.
Is that good?
Yeah, it's okay.
Can I try it?
Your silence says "no"...
No! You can.
Do you... want a bite?
Yeah, I would!
Shit! It's good!
So good...
Would you like one?
Yes.
I thought you said you were eating alone.
Well, I am. I was! I didn't know she-
Is that a problem?
I guess.
Can I get another salad?
Should I put a rush on that?
Oh my shit.
I'm sorry!
Oh! No, really.
I wasn't very hungry. And there's another one on the way.
I just don't eat much.
I mean, at least I didn't use to, but...
I plan on eating tons now!
Are you...
... in some kind of trouble?
Well, I'm on the run. If that's what you mean.
What?
No, stupid!
I just liked the way you're holding yourself. It was kind of interesting.
And your salad looked ace.
How was I holding myself?
You see?! You're laughing at yourself!
That's so... weirdly... great.
I assure you there's nothing "weirdly great" about me.
I'm Justin.
Justin.
Justin!
And you are...
I'm what?
Your name is...
January, February, March, April, -
April!
Stop!
Dinner! I have a question.
Did your girlfriend just make up her name?
You're deceiving me...
You're deceiving me!
Oh, please...!
This would be deceiving you.
Justin.
I have been wandering the world searching for one mortal man
who can make my body quake with sex!
When I saw you eating your salad
I thought the planet was gonna blow the fuck up!
Do me like a lesbian, in front of all these jerk offs!
Stop! Stop!
What? That didn't happen?
Play the scene right.
That's your responsibility.
But be available to see things diversely...
Watching your life is a much different experience
than remembering it.
Really, I'm not hungry.
Have to go back to work.
Why?
"Why"?
Well, because I have to.
Sounds boring.
What's in there?
A book.
That's it?
That's it.
Keep a book locked up?
It's rare.
What is it?
Doesn't have a name.
Really?
Not that I've ever found.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Are you okay?
Weird girl...
She was different.
I know that.
It's what made me fall for her so quickly.
"Fall for her"?
"Fall for her".
You humans speak of love as if it were a 10 story drop!
What?
Oh... the face.
Right.
Have you read "The tragical history of the life and death of Doctor Faustus"?
It's hilarious!
Pleasure to meet you.
Oh...
You're one of the smart ones.
Oh, come on!
You know you wanna kiss me.
That's right.
It's me...
Oh my God! You're the de-
Demon Jeez.
Hero of Hell.
You gave me this.
Oh my.
That's good work.
Man, you are lucky to still be breathing!
Hmm... I can still taste your blood.
It's delicious!
You took her.
I know!
Got a medal for it too.
Now that's what I call pretty.
Bring her back.
No.
Please!
You summoned Lo...
Then I'll summon you!
You can't summon two demons at once!
It's like trying to... fuck two chicks at the same time with one dick.
A Shish Kebab.
Well, if I'm not yourMaster then why are you here?
Are you kidding?
You're the mortal that tamed the beast.
I had to get an exclusive with you.
I don't know what you mean.
Oh, you do...
You do know what I mean.
See, I've come into contact with an innumerable amount of humans in my day.
Ah, sure! I've felt a few things for them.
Disgust,...
embarrassment,...
sometimes a bit of humor,
and hunger!
But the one thing that I never did:
fall in love with any of them!
That's why it's so weird...
What's weird?
That it fell in love with you.
"It"?
Well...!
You call it "April".
Ew...
I'm gonna tell you a story.
Through song!
♪ Back in the day when you cretins thought the Earth was flat ♪
♪ The ground was a corpse from another of your combats. ♪
♪ A solitary demon went picking through the bones. ♪
♪ And found a battle soldier still alive under the stars. ♪
♪ The soldier looked up, still numb from the shock. ♪
♪ It ripped out his heart, put it into a rock. ♪
♪ (Yes, it did) ♪
♪ Demon girl ♪
♪ It ripped out his heart, put it into a rock. ♪
♪ You were born out of man's greed and war. ♪
♪ Demon girl ♪
♪ Doesn't know what her heart is good for. ♪
♪ You are different from the rest of your clan. ♪
♪ You abandoned your bloodlust for the love... ♪
♪ ... of a man. ♪
♪ "Death", you could say, was this maid's middle name. ♪
♪  Flick of its tongue sent the mighty to the flames.♪
♪ Had no use for mercy, just a hunger for your soul. ♪
♪ Somewhere lost inside it was a deep and gaping hole. ♪
♪ Centuries marched on and its heart felt distinct. ♪
♪ The mountains looked down every night, and they'd sing. ♪
♪ (Yes, they did) ♪
♪ Demon girl ♪
♪ The mountains looked down every night, and they'd sing. ♪
♪ You were born out of man's greed and war. ♪
♪ Demon girl ♪
♪ She doesn't know what that heart is good for. ♪
♪ You are different from the rest of your clan. ♪
♪ You abandoned your bloodlust for the love... ♪
♪ ... of a man. ♪
Can I get a little saxophone?
April.
You were Hell's golden reaper.
When I saw you kill...
I'd say to myself:
"Damn!"
You had it all going on.
And you played it off...
without a single trace...
of mercy.
♪ Something went wrong and your heart starts to swell. ♪
♪ Cleaned off your soul and escaped from your Hell. ♪
♪ (Yes, you did) ♪
♪ Demon girl ♪
♪ Cleaned off your soul and escaped from your Hell. ♪
♪  Goes fishing in the river Styx. ♪
♪  Demon girl ♪
♪  Like a combo is 6-double-6. ♪
♪ Demon girl ♪
♪ And she's horny but not in love! ♪
♪ You're a fool if you still wanna stay. ♪
♪ Demon girl ♪
♪ You were born out of man's greed and war. ♪
♪ Doesn't know what her heart... is good for. ♪
(Jeez! Best music goddamn ever!)
(Sexy!)
Bravo!
Bravo! What an exciting story told through song!
You're playing with me.
I don't play with my food, Dinner!
I'm- I'm done listening to you. You're only trying to confuse me.
I bring you the demon that took your love...
And you insult me!
I thought you didn't know her.
I lied.
I do that sometimes.
You're disgusting.
To call me disgusting is to call her disgusting.
We're the same ilk.
You don't seem to be a very intelligent lad.
Maybe the song went over your head.
So I'll explain it to you for the simple reality that it is.
Demons, all demons, ...
will eat, kill and rape anything.
Especially babies.
So I'll just reach down into the ass of Hell and get her for ya'.
And what about me?
If sh- she's everything you say she is, then what-
... Where do I fit in?
"What about you?"
That does amuse me to think about.
But you see, the thing about April is that pesky heart of hers.
You never knew what emotion it would settle into next.
She loved me.
Maybe.
But that doesn't change the facts.
You see, it happens all the time.
She gets restless, she doesn't understand why no one else does.
She calls in the middle of the night!
"I don't know why I feel this way!".
What am I supposed to tell her?!
I don't know why she feels this way!
One day she's a killer. A killer!
And then the next she's a fucking mess.
You were her friend.
No.
You can't bring her.
You don't have the strength it takes to do what I command.
"I don't have the strength"?
You can't even walk!
You're a cripple.
Can you feel that?
The essence of my hand, breaking through your barrier and squeezing your neck.
I may not be able to kill you from here, but I'm most certainly powerful enough to make you feel my desire!
Leave at once.
Lo?
Hello?
Lo?!
Goddammit.
Goddammit!
Goddammit, goddammit, goddammit, goddammit, goddammit, goddammit!
Goddammit, goddammit. Goddammit! Goddammit! God damn...!
Goddammit!
Goddammit...!
Who's that?
Who is that?
Wait.
It's saying what I'm thinking.
Just said that. And that!
I just said that, and I just said that, I just said that in my head! Oh my God, I can hear my thoughts out loud!
And I can't stop thinking!
Quick! Say something out loud. Hurry!
What the fuck was that? Did I just make noises?
Shit!
It's still happening. Say something out loud, a- a sentence! A complete sentence!
"The boy went to the store"!
That's my sentence?
Shit! Still here.
Okay...!
Okay, why- why- why am I hearing my own voice?
Where- Where is my voice coming from-
Did that get bigger?
Oh, shit!
It's my cut!
It's reading my mind and then saying it out loud!
Clear your mind.
Clear your mind, clear your mind, clear your mind...
This is so weird...
Fuck! Stop! Fuck it! Ignore the hand.
Think. Think...!
April's a demon!
She's always been a demon. Does that mean she really didn't love me?
Of course she loved me! I know she did.
And yet here we are: sitting in some dimensional pit-stop,
hearing stories about her slaughtering men for sport.
Well, that's just it: these- these demons are liars. Lo admitted that.
But what about the book?
Yeah...
The book.
A human wouldn't have a book like that.
She could've only gotten it one place.
Hell...
Hell.
She was from Hell.
But...
She loved me.
Did she?
Maybe you were just a refuge from the demons, the perfect patsy to lie low with.
That bitch!
I know!
I'm... having a conversation... with my brain through my hand...!
Miss me? Shut up!
Shut up, my brain!
You're silly.
Where were you?
I went to get my smokes.
Demons smoke?
We do anything we want to do.
It's cool.
The circle is closing in on you.
The more you sit in there, the more the brain leaks.
So...
I found something for you.
April?
No, no way, brother. She's in some serious lock-up right now.
I brought a couple of kids to speak in her place!
I named them for you:
May... and June.
What are they?
They used to be human.
Guess which one killed them.
Now they live here.
May! Tell them what they do to you here.
Well...
I am laid down on what appears to be a very large cheese grater.
There, two beasts...
one on each end, grab my hands and feet with their mouths...
and pull me back and forth...
slowly.
Shredding my back into little peelings.
Then, my eyelids are sliced off with a rusty razor blade!
And a demon stands over me...
and urinates into my eyeballs.
A funnel is placed in my mouth...
And pounds of broken glass are forced down my throat.
My neck is then sledgehammered flat and rats are brought in to gnaw it off!
It takes the rats about 12 minutes to chew through.
But I can't always be exact with the time.
As I often lose count...
Due to the high volumes of pain!
My head, then, still living...
Is placed into an oversized blend-
And thank you, May.
Okay...
But there's more.
What is this?
Why are you showing me this?
This is good stuff!
This is the biz! How we operate.
You want me to find you April, I want you to know what April is.
It tricked us.
What?
The demon... It tricked us.
It promised us a baby.
One piece of life,
for our eternal souls!
Cut with the dramatics!
Oh, yes! Sorry, June. Some of us still feel!
Oh, fuck you!
Silence!
Idiots...
The baby.
The demon...
It gave us what we wanted.
And for nine months, I knew my true purpose in life...
It was to raise this child,
and love it.
We should've tried in vitro first.
What? Before consulting the Devil?!
You're the one that said we needed candles!
"You can't summon a demon without candles!"
Well, if we're gonna do it then let's do it right!
I'm really sorry about this.
The torture down here turned her into a real mega bitch.
What?!
What!
Bitch.
Shut up!
It's on!
Sorry.
Sorry!
The child.
It died...
Hey! You.
Get us out of here.
I- I'm sorry.
Please! Take us with you.
Yeah! Please, mister. It really sucks here.
I'm s- I'm sorry, I can't.
Take us with you, we can't go back there!
Please, mister!
Hey, look! If you can only take one, take me.
No! I'm a woman. I can repay you in ways you'd like to be repaid...
I can do that too!
I mean, I will!
I'm not helping you! Go back to hell and leave me alone.
Now that's funny.
Think about all the times you told someone to "go to Hell".
And now think about exactly what it is you're wishing upon them.
Just get her for me.
I can't!
And it's not because I'm "a cripple".
You wanna know why my legs drag behind me like a serpent's tail?
I promised I won't say.
I don't care.
April.
My legs were crushed when she was returned.
You helped her?
A demon...
heart or not...
should never entertain the idea that love is the answer to its questions.
She's back home now, but no longer free.
Held in the deepest pits and fed the sharpest pains.
If ever a woman was detained, it's her.
Would you really want to see her again given all you know?
I don't know what are lies and what aren't.
Nor were you meant to.
Would you like to see her again?
Then think about her.
A book?
Have you ever read it?
No.
Well, it's good!
It's a- I mean, you know... I figured you liked rare books since you keep that one locked up, so...
It's a- It's a 1663 reprint.
So, you know... Not one of the oldest but... still pretty old!
You thought I might like this, so you bought it for me?
Yeah.
I mean...
Do you like it?
I think I do!
I've never read a book before! Except mine.
You never read a... book?
Except mine.
Nothing, never?
Not even in school?
Well... yes!
Well, yeah. In school!
I read a couple hundred in school...!
No, I meant: other than school!
What's it about?
Uh... It's about a guy who sells his soul to the Devil for knowledge and power.
What stupid...!
There's nothing to know...! Nothing worth that much pain, at least.
Oh, yeah? You- You've been there?
No.
Never!
You're so bizarre.
Well?
Well... What?
I can't take the tease anymore!
"The tease"?
I want my present now, please!
Your present?
Right, right! Nice try, lady. Where is it at?
I want the goods, bring it out.
You... really didn't get me a present?
Oh, my God! No. No, baby.
It's fine, I- I- I didn't mean to expect one. I just, you know...
With Christmas I thought it'd be the whole... You know...
thing... I have no clue. Baby! It's so not important.
I'm so sorry...
We never celebrated Christmas.
I thought it was just an all-month party that ended December 25th!
You're serious?
Do you hate me?
I think I might... actually love you a little more now.
That's so weird...!
I told you. I'm a weird girl!
Good.
I do have a present for you!
Wait...! Wait!
You can't wrap something I already own. That's now how it works.
What, you're giving me your book?
Well, you have me a book.
Touché.
No.
That is something you can never do.
Open it?
Never!
Do you promise me?
Pray April, it's a-
Justin, no!
You have to burn this book. No questions.
No looking.
Just someday, when I'm not around,
burn it!
April.
What is this?
My past.
Never ask me that question again.
Burn. This. Book.
And wish me a Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas...
Demon~
Why wasn't she honest with you?
She obviously didn't trust you enough with the truth!
She was ashamed of it...
Or she had an agenda, and she knew exactly how to play you.
No.
Come on! You know what you are: you are a pushover!
Ridiculously bad social skills, and zero friends or family.
All you had was her.
And she knew that.
No. We worked because we were different.
You worked because that's the way she wanted it. She needed a place to hide!
You were nothing but a fake mustache!
Shut up!
The circle's closing in on you...
I can deal...!
You kids crack my shit up!
If any of you knew what was actually going on up there in that tin you call a brain!
Idiot...
True on so many levels.
The circle's closing in on me...
May I take your order, sir?
Perhaps a drink to start with?
I know you...!
I doubt that.
You are my waiter!
I'm the waiter, sir.
Now... How about that drink?
No.
I assure you, sir, I'm the best bartender in this room.
I believe that...
But I don't want anything except April.
I will make you the best drink you have ever tasted.
I don't want a drink.
I want April.
I will call it... "April".
I don't want it.
It's not poison!
It weakens the pity.
I can't bring April to you. You have to go to her.
It's the only way.
Do you... actually want me to go on to Hell?
Yes, I do!
That drink looses the soul, allowing you to travel... relatively unharmed through the fires and the pits.
It's the only way a living man can pass through Hell.
Now... Is your April worth what you have to do to see her?
What's so funny?
It was poison.
Just me, buddy.
Dear.
I heard you just fell for the old "drink this and you can walk through Hell" bit.
Bring back Lo.
I ain't that demon's keeper!
Am I dying?
Absolutely.
But slowly.
Demons like to use slow poison, so they can... watch you twitch.
Is there anything I can do?
Leave!
Get to a hospital. Pump it out.
I'm not leaving here without her.
Ain't no "her". Stop calling it female.
That's a human cage.
We are not defined by sex.
So this whole "love" thing...
Give me the breakdown.
I don't know what to tell you...
Well, pretend I'm April.
Hi, Justin! I'm April!
Blah blah blah blah blah!
One time, I tortured a guy who said it felt like a lump in your throat that you couldn't swallow.
Sounded annoying.
He was wrong.
A lump is too simple... Love is more complicated than that.
Oh! Oh, so the lump theory is just bullshit?
Every theory is bullshit!
There's no way I can define something you will never feel.
I'm a demon. I can do anything.
Except love.
Well, maybe I can! But I don't want you to know that I can.
That's a childish way to go about it.
Not being capable of love is a gift! I present exhibit "A" as ultimate proof:
One poor fool slowly dying in a circle!
What's that about?
That's my secret.
Justin, let me offer you some really groovy advice:
Read the chant, close the dimension, get to a hospital and finish your life!
Cause this shit? Blows!
Stop that!
You look like a child who just proudly shit his pants!
What's the matter, Jeez?
Can't handle the fact that you don't know everything?
Warning! You die here, and you belong to us.
You got a song about that?
Actually I do.
But... it's missing the baseline and hasn't been mixed yet so you don't get to hear it!
You're dying.
I guess I am.
You're terrified of death.
More than anything.
And you're dying.
Should I go?
Abandon all this? Leave her?
I don't wanna die.
But I don't wanna live without her.
You had to say that out loud...
I need to get rid of it. If I don't it'll keep talking to me, it will betray me and lie to me. I have to get rid of it!
Am I considering cutting off my hand...?
I am... I am! Oh, shit! But I have to!
I have to...
It's just as manipulative as they are. I can't trust it!
Oh, God! This is gonna hurt... Do I do this? I have to!
There's no choice, oh my God. I'm gonna cut my hand, okay. Okay, don't be-
Do it, do it. Do! Do! Do! Do! Do! Do!
Hey!
Dumbass!
You looking to speed up the death process or what?
You poisoned me...
And?
Why you?
Why did she mark your page?
Maybe it was a coincidence.
Or maybe she thought I was cute.
You're so afraid to give me a straight answer.
If I'm just a stupid human then why do I scare you so much?
The safety of that circle has swelled your ego something fierce.
Why did you help her escape?
What I do on my own time is no concern of yours.
They crushed your body.
And rightfully so!
I paid my price!
There's no need for you to be involved in demon affairs...
You are not built for Hell, trust me.
I'm touched you're so concerned with my well-being...
There's nothing you can do for her.
She broke a sacred law!
She is a vile creature!
Maybe I don't care about that.
Oh, brother, you really should.
That's who she was here.
That's not who she is in my world.
And escaped murderer is still a murderer.
It's okay.
It was a bad one.
Do you wanna tell me about it?
Maybe it's time to see a doctor.
I've been reading about night terrors lately.
Fuck. Justin. It's just a dream, everyone has them.
Not like you do.
You've been talking more in your sleep lately.
What am I saying?
Mostly you just apologize.
April.
I think-
Shh.
Tell me you don't smell anything.
Weird.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What?
I think I smell sulfur.
Shit.
This guy?
Jeez.
Nice costume.
Go back.
Oh, I plan on it.
I'm stronger than you are.
Sister, you're long time out of practice.
Justin.
He's dying...
Well, I should hope so!
I don't scratch.
Let me help him.
And I'll go with you...
April... April...
I have to leave.
I'm sorry...
The book...!
April...!
April... April!
You came here for love.
You're no better than Faust!
Faust sought power and knowledge.
Which is all you seek!
Love would have had you destroy that book as you had promised!
A demon cannot harm it, only a mortal can.
You betrayed your love.
That's the difference between you and me.
Humanity is allowed to make mistakes. It's expected of us.
Well, that's just stupid.
What do you know of how we feel?
Except what you get out of us through torture.
You demons claim to be all-powerful, yet you're beaten by your own jealousy towards us!
Now that shit was funny.
Demon!
Foul, horrible, disgusting demon!
I am your Master!
You are my dog!
When I summoned you, I summoned the power to command you.
When I say you'll roll over, that is exactly what you will do!
I have seen you toss yourself around this room...
In a dozen different forms, planting seeds in my head and laughing as you watch them grow!
But I say "no more"!
I am done with the games and the trickery!
I will not go away, no matter how many times you poison me!
I summoned you...!
Now I command you, demon Lo!
Scour the depths of Hell... Find my girl... Sit her right down in front of me.
And fuck off.
Justin...
Baby.
Hi...
Hi.
Strange place to be picking up girls.
Yeah.
You kept my book.
Yeah...
I tried to burn it.
I actually... don't know why I couldn't.
It's okay.
They were pissed when they found "Faust" in the case.
I'm here to take you with me.
I know.
I'm giddy, can't you tell?
I need you to... tell me the chant I need to use.
To take you back with me.
You still want to save me...
... After all you've heard...?
"Hell's MVP"...
I don't believe that.
I know your true heart.
I know it's not capable of that.
But it is.
Tell me... you won't eat me...  and I'll make you my wife.
You'd love me?
Page 1108.
Tiana.
... Tiana.
Fait simei.
... Fait simei.
Neft tiana simei.
... Neft tiana simei.
Tan corsé si.
... Tan corsé si.
I can't go with you...
Of course you can.
We'll hide, they won't find us.
No, they will.
And next time, they'll kill you.
Then let me stay here.
No...
No.
This is not where I will let you spend eternity.
You have no choice at all in this matter.
I have nothing worth in my life without you there.
I'm not a woman... Justin.
I'm not human.
But you... love me.
Keep your word to me.
You're going home...
April!