Not too long.
Okay.
Don't get too close
to the water.
- What?
- I said don't get too close to the water.
- Why?
- You never know what could be in there.
Piranhas, maybe.
I don't know.
That's just the point,
you never know.
It could be necrotizing
fasciitis.
- What's that?
- A germ that eats your living flesh.
- Ew, that's not real.
- Is too.
- What's your name?
- Peter.
My mom and I just moved here.
Hi, Peter.
So, do you come here just to
warn people about piranhas?
No. This is my place.
No, this is my place.
I found it.
Um, I don't think you're the
first person to find it ever.
No one else has never found it.
I did. Besides, this place
has a name already.
I know that.
I guess we'll just have to
battle to the death over it.
- You're crazy.
- That's what they call me. Crazy Maggie.
Well, Maggie,
prepare to meet thy doom.
- My snail won again.
- No way.
- It totally did.
- Mine never wins.
- Yours is too distracted.
- Yours has a rocket boosters or something.
Just skills. That's
all my snail needs.
So how come you moved here?
So my mom could work
at the college.
We used to live a
few towns away.
Do you miss your old home?
Sometimes. I'm kind of glad we moved here
though because my friend lives here.
What about your dad?
That's the other
reason we moved.
Oh. Sorry.
- It's okay.
- Do you like it here?
I guess. It's a little
quieter than I imagined.
I like this place though.
How long have you been here?
- A long time.
- Do you like it here?
Sometimes. Right now, I do.
- Be free.
- Stay together.
I don't want them to get lost.
I think I have to go home now.
It's getting late.
- Do you have to? - My mom gets
worried if I stay out too late.
Okay.
Hey, I was wondering...
Maybe we could hang
out again sometime.
- Yeah, definitely.
- I live across the woods.
Where do you live?
How about you come here again?
To my place.
- My place.
- Our place.
Okay, cool. See you tomorrow?
Yep.
You know, turning your broccoli
upside down on the plate
isn't fooling anybody, bub.
What?
Well, you can leave it until
you've finished everything else,
but sooner or later, you're
gonna have to bite the bullet.
- Broccoli.
- Yes, broccoli.
- So go ahead and bite it.
- Broccoli is gross.
You're gross, but you don't
hear me complaining.
Well, somebody's just gonna
have to choke it down
if he ever wants to see me
make pumpkin cupcakes again.
- Mom.
- Mm-mm.
Hmm. Oh, so who's this
girl you met today?
- Just a girl. - Well, come on.
You have to do better than that.
- What's her name?
- Maggie.
- Maggie what?
- I don't know.
- Well, you should ask.
- I will, I will.
- Where's you meet her?
- At my place by
lost creek. She was
playing there, too.
Hmm. Your secret lair. I love that
you're hanging out with more people.
It's not like there are any
people to play with anyway.
- It's weird.
- Hey, hey.
What about the kids
in school, huh?
That's the other side of town.
There's only bill,
and even he's hard to get to.
Pete, you know why
we moved here.
It was tough to find this job.
- I know.
- And we talked about this.
We had to get away from
your bleeping father.
Don't say bleeping.
I didn't. I bleeped it.
I could tell what it was.
- Could you really?
- Um...
And we are lucky that grandma and
grandpa let us have this house
- for so little money when they moved.
- I know.
Even though mommy swore after college
she'd never move back here again.
- Mom, it's fine.
- It's okay.
I mean, I think this
is important for us,
and I just need to know that...
That you're okay.
- Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
"I'm okay." I mean it.
I think this is
important for us,
and I need to know that
you think so, too.
- Do you think so, too?
- Yes.
Good. I love you.
- I love you, too.
- Good.
Now can you take that box of cups down to
the basement like I asked you yesterday?
Okay.
Peter?
Dad?
Where are you?
I'm in here.
I miss you, Peter.
Can you find me?
This way, Peter.
Peter.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hey, hey, hey.
Easy, honey. It's okay.
It's just me.
Easy, baby. Easy.
You had a bad dream. It's okay.
You're awake now.
- Mom.
- I know, I know.
It's over. It's okay.
Since when did you start
sleepwalking again?
Has this been happening
for a while?
Okay, well, it's over now.
It's okay.
- Tough night, huh?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
I mean, it was so scary and weird.
It was so real.
I think I'm in love with pop-tarts.
Like, actually in love.
That's great, bill. I could smell things,
you know? Like rotten leaves and stuff.
- Like, I could actually marry one.
- I actually felt cold.
Or a cheese Danish. Yeah, a
pop-tart may be a girlfriend,
but I'd marry a cheese Danish.
Have you been listening
to anything I'm saying?
Yeah, sure, scary
dream, blah, blah.
No, not just a scary dream.
More than that.
I've had scary dreams a
million times before.
This was... different.
Ooh, different.
- Never mind.
- Exactly.
- Peter Roland.
- Oh, sorry. Here.
Ah, there you finally are.
William dury?
- Bill.
- Excuse me?
It's bill.
Are you William dury or not?
Yeah, that's me.
Thank you.
- Anyways, what's your costume?
- It's a secret.
- Oh, don't be a dork.
- You'll see.
Fine. I'm going as the cat.
- The cat?
- Yeah.
The cat from... from what?
From nature. From
our neighborhood.
- The black and white one?
- Yeah.
That's adorable.
No, it's not. That's
just what it's not.
You don't understand. You
don't live on its street.
It waits for me. It's
always so quiet.
You're supposed to go as something
scary, so that's what I'm doing.
- I hate it.
- It's a she.
Okay, class, settle
down, settle down.
My name is Mr. Vernon, and I will be
replacing Mrs. "mc-creddy" for a while.
- Mrs. Mccready.
- Oh, thank you.
Mccready, thank you.
What happened to Mrs. Mccready?
How should I know? Shut up.
You're gonna get us into trouble.
Here we go.
Yes, uh, Peter?
Um, Mr. Vernon, what happened to Mrs.
Mccready?
I don't know. She's not
able to come in today.
But she was fine yesterday. She promised
to talk more about the field trip.
- Maybe she's sick today.
- She didn't seem sick.
- Peter, I only know
what they tell me,
and I don't know why
she's not here today.
But I'm sure she's gonna be
fine, so don't worry, okay?
- Okay.
- Okay, great.
Wow, you sure are a
talkative class.
- I told you not to be weird.
- So, I'm still new here.
Can anyone tell me something interesting
about living in brackenvale?
- Yes?
- There's a big college here.
Very good. That's true.
Thank you.
Anyone else?
Ah, bill, not William.
The woods near my
house is haunted.
- Ah, yes. - Yeah, I heard the
story at camp,
like, summers ago.
Someone is supposed to have died out
there in the woods, like, 20 years ago.
It's supposed to be
haunted or something.
Oh, yes? Anyone else?
- Yes?
- There's a shark in the lake.
There's a shark...
Well, not in the lake.
At the beach.
- All the time?
- Not all the time.
But they're in the ocean, so they
sometimes have to be near the beach.
Oh, well, that's very true. Very true.
Good, thank you.
Okay, good, good. Okay.
So, let's continue with the reading
that Mrs. Mccready assigned.
- What happened to Mr. Raimi?
- I don't
know. The sub said
he was just gone.
- Every year?
- You never see it coming.
You're like some poor, little, innocent
baby chick just walking into it.
You're such a heel.
- A what? - I heard it in
english. It means a giant jerk!
You're such a dork.
- It's so close.
- I know.
And now that you're here,
it's gonna be insane.
We're gonna need a plan...
All the prime candy routes.
Pillow cases this year. No
more wimpy plastic bags.
This year, we're all
gonna be candy monsters.
Where do you get all that
Halloween stuff anyway?
Some kids at the cafeteria.
They didn't want it.
Yeah, I can see why. Some
of them are really scary.
Yeah. They're gonna look
awesome at my house.
- Can I have some?
- Yeah, but leave this one.
Hi!
Our pillowcases
are still packed.
Mom said they're
lost in the abyss.
Oh, don't worry. You can
borrow one of mine.
You know Mr. Queeg? That old guy who
lives by the market value time?
- Yeah. - I don't think he
can see too well anymore.
I bet we can go to
his house twice.
Bill, why do you do
this to yourself?
- Do what? - You threw up 2.35
pounds of chocolate last year.
Whatever. It wasn't that much.
- We weighed it.
- Whatever.
- I was impressed.
- Whatever!
Anyway, are you still gonna
hang with this Maggie?
- Yeah, so?
- So how come I haven't met her before?
Well, you will.
- Where are you meeting her?
- By the creek again.
You know, my mom says we shouldn't
even be in lost creek woods.
She says some parts
are dangerous.
It's not dangerous.
I bet your mom would
be mad if she knew.
You're a loser, and
it's not dangerous.
It's, like, special there.
Oh, special.
Shut up. Anyway, I'm gonna ask
Maggie to trick or treat with us.
Great. A girl to slow us down.
We got work to do.
She won't slow us down.
She better not. The Wilkins' house
had the good candy corn last year.
If we don't make it that
far, I'm blaming you.
I don't want to go by the
Wilkins' house anyway.
What? Are you still
thinking about those kids?
Bill, they were huge, and they
chased us for, like, an hour.
Don't be a baby.
You were just as scared as me. We
were lost and we were both crying.
Yeah, but they
really got to you.
- They were really scary.
- Yeah.
Anyway, she better
not slow us down.
Maggie's cool, you'll see. Anyway,
if anyone slows us down, it's you.
- You run like a grandma.
- Nuh-uh. A race car grandma, maybe.
- That doesn't even make sense.
- You don't make sense.
Gotta go. Bye, weirdo.
Hey!
Where were you?
Jumpy much?
I didn't see you.
I thought maybe you didn't come.
Nah, don't worry.
I'm always here.
You scared me.
I can't help it if you're blind.
I've just been right
here the whole time.
So what are you going as?
- For what?
- Halloween, duh.
- I don't know.
Oh, come on. You have
to have some idea.
Well, I remember for
the last Halloween,
- I went as a werewolf Princess.
- What?
You heard me.
What does that look like?
Well... whoa. I had
the best fangs.
And my mom had this fake
bearskin rug that I cut up.
She was so mad. I had a
crown and a dress, too.
I was beautiful.
Sounds lovely.
Well, I bet it's better than
whatever lame thing you're gonna be.
Oh, just you wait.
I love Halloween.
- It's...
- It's the best.
Yeah.
- Do you ever think about it?
- -Think about what?
Being a kid. Like, one
day you're not anymore.
I guess.
It feels like we've
been kids forever.
- Yeah.
- But one day, you're not anymore.
And it's not that long, really.
That's really weird.
Do you want to grow up?
- Sometimes.
- I guess.
But I like this so much.
Come on, let's go across.
- Come on, it's not even that
deep over here. - I can't.
- Don't be a...
- I can't!
- Why?
- I just can't, okay?
Okay.
Besides, there's a monster
on the other side.
What? No, there's not.
Yeah there is. I heard it.
It's true.
It's a ghost, not a monster anyway, duh.
I heard it in school.
They told it wrong then.
It's definitely a monster.
- You're making it up.
- No, I'm not. I swear.
I heard that there's a monster that
lives really deep in the woods
on the other side of the creek.
It's really old and it waits
for kids to come out at night.
- That's stupid. There's no...
- I don't want to go across.
Okay.
I had this weird
dream last night.
What was it?
A little bit like some of
the other dreams that I had
after my mom and dad...
You don't have to talk about
it if you don't want.
It's okay. This one was
different from the others.
Why?
I was in the woods,
but not this part.
Somewhere else.
It was creepy. I heard this...
voice.
Do you remember what
the voice said?
Yeah. It said my name.
Don't go across
the creek, Peter.
- Why?
- Just don't, okay? Promise.
Okay, okay, I promise. Why
are you so weird about this?
Some things don't go away
when you stop pretending.
My pumpkin.
- Mom, mom, I have to tell you.
- Hi, honey, not now.
But, mom, the
neighbors are gone.
Well, maybe they
went out somewhere.
- All of them?
- Honey, do I know?
- I... - look, can you
tell me about this later?
I have a million things
to do right now.
I realized the heat
was due this month,
- and somehow I've got
to figure out how
we're gonna... - there's
something wrong.
You bet there's something wrong.
It takes a lot to keep this
little ship afloat, bub.
- But...
- I said not now!
There's food and dinner and
stuff on their tables.
Well, maybe they went
out for something.
How do you know there's
food on the table?
Were you looking in their house?
- But...
- Were you?
- Just listen for a second.
- Why would you do something like this?
We just moved here. We're
trying to settle in.
We're trying to
make a new start,
and you're spying
on the neighbors?
Peter, you know how
hard this has been.
Why would you try
and make it harder?
I'm not trying to
make it harder.
Would you please listen
and stop being so stupid?
That's it, up to bed.
Now.
Vamonos.
Hey, Peter. Come in here.
Peter! Peter!
Peter? Peter? What's wrong?
Oh, oh. It was just a dream.
It was just a dream, okay?
Are you okay?
I heard you again.
I'm sorry I got so
angry earlier, babe.
Oh, no, no, no, no. Please, don't cry.
Don't cry.
It's okay. God. Oh,
it's a mess, isn't it?
I'm a mess, and...
And you're a mess.
But... but we're okay, right?
The two of us, we're okay.
I'm telling you,
something is wrong.
You were dreaming. You
always sleepwalk.
You really freaked me out the
first time you stayed over.
I swear I wasn't sleeping.
Ah, so you're trying to tell me
that the basement talked to you
and then a monster tried
to break in your house.
Well, yeah.
Did your mom see the monster?
The monster was gone
before my mom got there.
Ah-ha.
Well, what about all
the missing people?
- What missing people?
- My neighbors.
Your neighbors aren't missing.
Well, something's going on.
You're right. You've got
a crazy imagination.
Remember the time when you tried to make
me believe that my toys came to life
and you only ended up scaring yourself
and locking all your toys in the closet?
This is totally different.
I'm not making this up.
Maggie said there was something
weird about this place.
There is something weird
about this place... you.
Maggie said there was a monster or
something that lived in the woods.
Not a ghost, by the way.
That's not what I heard.
Well, Maggie knows
more than you.
And you are scared of
your toys coming to life.
- Hey!
- Well, the point is
that I used to believe
that, well...
Well, you shouldn't believe,
'cause it's not real.
There's no such thing as monsters,
ghosts, bigfoots, or any of that stuff.
There might be aliens.
We just don't know.
- Bill, I'm trying to tell you...
- Okay, um, sorry. I gotta go.
Uh, you go home and get some rest or...
Something.
Uh, see you tomorrow.
Well, just remember
to be careful.
You do you know that this is how
my crazy uncle Bruce sounded
before they took
him to the home,
but my mom pretended
he moved to Florida?
Peter.
Peter!
Maggie? What's going on?
- We've got to go.
- What? Where am I?
Come on, you're in danger.
We've got to go!
It's here.
It's okay. I don't
hear anything.
I think we're safe now.
Come on, we can head
back to my house.
Back that way?
No. We can cross the
creek and follow it
on the other side to the road.
Come on.
What's wrong, really?
I lied before.
What?
There is a ghost.
What do you mean?
She died here.
No.
No, you're a kid.
I used to be.
- Stop lying!
- I'm not lying. I'm not.
You have to be because
that's crazy.
Why do you think no one
has ever seen me before?
Why do you think
I'm always here?
No.
No. I don't believe you.
Look at me.
Really look.
Believing is seeing.
How can you be dead?
Because no one came to help,
and the water was too strong.
And I couldn't keep it out.
Please don't be afraid of me.
So that's why you can't cross.
We can stay on this side if we
cut through the playground.
Come on.
What's it like?
It's... lonely.
After they found me,
my mom came to the creek
one time to visit.
She was crying.
I wanted to tell her
I was right here,
but I couldn't.
Grownups can't see.
Later, my mom and
dad moved away,
but I couldn't go with them.
When I was little,
my dad made up these
great bedtime stories.
He used all these great voices.
But I didn't know
dads could be liars.
I don't know what
I'd do if he died.
You must miss them a lot.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
I thought maybe...
You'd leave me.
Never. We're best friends.
Right?
Do you like to know
how it happened?
It's a scary story.
There really is a monster.
My sister told me to scare
me, but she was right.
I saw it.
It takes kids away.
It tried to get me, but there
was a storm, and I got lost.
It wants you next.
It's calling you.
And I don't think it's gonna
stop until it gets you.
Why me?
Because you're the kid
who finally came.
Haven't you noticed there aren't
any other kids around here?
Yeah, I guess.
Bill said the last time
kids lived around here
was when his mom was little.
People don't know
the real reason,
but they learn. This
is not a good place.
Maybe that's why all the
grownups are leaving.
That's what grownups
do sometimes.
I think this is different.
I think the monster
is taking them away.
We've got to do something.
What?
My mom and I are used to moving.
You can come with.
Your mom won't believe you.
You know she won't.
And... I can't leave.
Oh, I'm sorry.
What are we supposed to do then?
I don't know.
- Peter?
- Bill?
What are you doing here?
Oh, you know, just going for a
run in the middle of the night
because my toys are
trying to kill me.
- What?
- All right, you win.
I just had to crawl out
of my bathroom window
because a doll was trying
to break down the door.
All right, calm down. Calm
down, you're safe now.
Safe? Somehow, I don't think so.
Anyway, what are you doing here?
Escaping from the monster.
That's real, too, by the way.
Great. "Calm down," he says.
- Ahem.
- Uh, bill, this is Maggie.
Hi, Maggie, I'm bill. Not Billy.
Hi. Why not Billy?
'Cause then the people take me
more seriously if I'm bill.
There are plenty of bills
that people respect.
Bill Clinton, bill
nye, the science guy.
- Does it work?
- Not really.
My mom just calls
me the unpaid bill.
Look, I hate to be rude,
but what the heck are we
supposed to do about this?
Would you be quite for a second?
I'm trying to think.
This would all go away if the
monster goes away, right?
- How does she know?
- She just knows, okay?
But that's right, right?
We've gotta fight it, don't we?
What? Are you crazy?
Maybe.
But I think we have to.
We're a bunch of stupid kids.
Bill, it's after me, and
it's not gonna stop.
None of us are safe now.
What?
It tried to get you, too.
Did you try and get him to help?
- Yeah.
- That's why.
It doesn't want
you to have help,
and it's just going
to get worse.
- Great.
- She's right. You're right.
Grownups won't ever believe
until it's too late.
It's up to us. Are you
going to help or not?
Fine. But if I die, I'm
going to be so mad at you.
Okay, tomorrow
night's Halloween.
That's when we'll do it.
Our parents will think we're
going out trick or treating,
so wear your costume.
We'll meet at my house. Come on.
This was all gonna be so good.
Get a ton of candy, scare
the pants off of Peter...
I hate to tell you this,
but if we fight it,
I think it will know,
and it will be angry.
I picked the wrong people to
trick or treat with this year.
Do you... sleep?
Don't worry about it.
I'll see you tomorrow.
So the monster might
still be out there,
because Victor Frankenstein
never finds him.
But he wasn't really
a monster, was he?
He had turned into a monster
from loss and fear
and loneliness and anger.
That's the sad part.
Had someone actually
taken the time
to get to know the
person inside,
maybe things would have
turned out different.
Okay, class, that's
it for today.
Remember your math
homework for tomorrow.
And, hey, I know
tonight's Halloween,
I know we're all
excited, but remember,
be safe out there.
- Are you ready for this?
- No.
- Are you?
We've gotta do something.
Just look around.
This is Halloween. There
should be people everywhere.
This has gotta stop
before everybody's gone.
Remember, meet at
my house at eight.
And bring your costume.
Don't tell anyone.
Even if they did believe us,
they'd just try and stop us.
Maybe that's not
such a bad thing.
Promise?
All right, all right.
See you later.
Here goes nothing.
Mom, what time is it?
It's a quarter till eight. Are you excited?
It's finally here.
- Yeah.
- Well, you could have fooled me.
- No, I am.
- Honey, what's wrong?
- Nothing.
- That's an awful big nothing.
It's just this year...
Don't open the door.
- Huh?
- Just leave the bowl of candy outside.
Well, I thought you
said that was lame.
I thought there were rules.
I know. This year's different.
Besides, you've been stressed.
You should relax.
Are you sure there's
nothing wrong?
I'd just rather you
stayed in tonight.
Peter?
Anyway, I have to put on
my Halloween costume.
Okay. Do I finally
get to see it?
Yes.
Mom?
Mom, do we have any flashlights?
Whoa, nice costume.
She's gone.
- What?
- It took my mom. She's gone.
Come on. We have to save her.
Well, guys...
Here we go.
Nice costume, Pete, though
I could have guessed.
I almost brought pillowcases,
but I guess we don't
need 'em now.
No.
Are you sure about this?
It took my mom.
I bet if you went to your house,
your parents would be gone, too.
Okay.
Hey, I thought you
were going as a cat.
It annoyed my neighbors.
Skeletons are good, too.
Cat was better.
Hey, where's your costume?
Oh, believe me,
she's wearing it.
- Huh?
- Well, guys.
That's my pumpkin.
Did you carve it like that?
No. It disappeared a while ago.
I told you it'd be mad.
Run!
Look.
I wonder if there's
anybody left at all.
I don't those kids are
from our neighborhood.
- I think we should go.
- Yeah.
Go!
Don't look behind you!
I said don't look!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Come on!
Thanks.
Now I see why you like
Halloween so much.
- This is great.
- It's not normally like this.
Come on, guys. We gotta go.
This way!
- I think we lost them.
- Not for long.
Where's bill?
What are you doing?
- Go, Peter.
- Come on.
- No.
- What?
Get to those trees. Go, hide.
- Bill!
- You and Maggie gotta stop this.
If you can't, no one can.
Someone's gonna have to stop these
things from being on your tail.
Those things will kill you.
- I run fast.
- No, you don't.
Just go. Get to those trees.
Hide, doofus.
Here goes nothing.
Hey, creepy kid demon!
Over here.
You make me want to throw up...
On your face.
That was a good one.
Gentlemen...
Start your engines.
What is all this?
I don't know.
These are bill's dad's glasses.
He borrowed them once.
They made everything look funny.
And those are his mom's shoes.
That's my mom's.
We have to figure something out.
I don't know.
Okay, so why does
it even want us?
'Cause we scare easily.
- What?
- Think about it.
All this is meant to scare us.
No one believes like kids.
I wish your sister told
us how to kill it.
She didn't know it was real.
Peter!
I know this place.
This is where I was in my dream.
I know this, too. This is it.
This is where it lives.
Stay together.
Peter?
You can't hurt the
people I love anymore!
I... I lost you.
Maggie?
What's going on? Come on.
It looks like in my dream.
Exactly like.
It's meant to scare us.
What are you talking about?
- There is no monster.
- What?
- Stay away, Peter.
- What are you doing?
It's me. It's coming from me.
Maggie, what?
It's from my bad dreams.
They're coming true.
You're not making sense.
Think about it. Bill said it
started when his mom was little.
When I was little.
It started when I died.
Bill doesn't know anything.
Maybe when something
bad enough happens,
it can change things.
Stop it. You're not doing this.
Believing is seeing. I
think it's real, so it is.
Just stay away from me
before you get hurt, too.
Watch out!
I was wrong.
You should be scared of me.
No, you're just a kid.
It can't be from you.
I mean, how?
I don't know, but it's true.
Besides, it doesn't
look like a monster.
It looks like kids, like,
trick-or-treating.
It's a monster. It has to be.
I'm not afraid of
trick-or-treaters.
No, but I am.
Last Halloween, I was chased
by older kids in masks.
They scared me really bad,
and bill was always scared
of toys coming to life.
I'm not scared of that, either.
- That's it.
- What's it?
- It's all of us.
- What?
It must have started with you,
but now it's spreading
to all of us.
Spreading? What do
you mean, spreading?
Like a germ or something.
Maggie, believing is seeing.
You said it.
No one believes like kids,
so no one gets scared like them.
Don't you see? It's not you.
It's the fear.
It's alive.
We're all feeding it.
We've still gotta stop it.
I don't know how.
It's taking over the whole town.
But... it's fear.
How do you stop that?
What scares you most?
Come on.
That's why all the grown-ups
are disappearing, isn't it?
You're scared of that, too.
I don't like this.
- Ready?
- Okay.
Go!
We've got to cross.
I don't think I can.
- Don't let go.
- I won't.
I remember...
I was mad at my mom, because
she wouldn't let me stay over
at a friend's house, so I
snuck out and got lost.
I think we won.
I forgot it could be pretty.
It's a great spot.
I didn't mean to scare you.
I know.
So this is where you
played before...
Yeah.
Well, do you want
to play with me?
Hey, come on.
It's over now.
I know, we did it.
I think I have to go home.
No. You can't go. Together
forever, remember?
I can't stay. It had
to end sometime.
- No.
- You know that.
It's not fair. I want
it to be forever.
Every kid does.
Maybe it should be.
Then you'd just be like me.
When I was with you,
I wasn't a ghost.
I was just... Maggie.
I'm really glad I finally
found you, Peter.
You were my best friend ever.
I'm going to miss you so much.
I'm going to miss you, too.
Your turn to be free.
See you later, Pete.
Just wait.
Peter, what's wrong?
What's going on?
It's good to see you, mom.
Yeah. I, uh...
I think we all came
out to see the sun
come up or something. I
don't really remember.
It's okay. It's over.
Oh? Is that why you're crying?
Oh, I know that Halloween's
over, but, hey,
did you know that today
is all Saint's day?
What's that?
It's the day that you
honor the dead, honey.
Honor the dead?
That's right.
I think I feel good about that.
That's what she deserves.
Who? What's gotten into you?
Just... the season.
- Let's go home, mom.
- Okay.
Well, now everything's
back to normal.
Yeah.
My mom didn't remember anything,
even when they woke
up in the field.
I guess they just forgot.
My mom, too. I guess grown-ups
just wanna see what
they wanna see.
Yeah. It's weird.
So where's Maggie?
- She moved away.
- What? When?
Is she gonna come
back and visit?
- I don't think so.
- This is stupid!
What was with her? Really.
Come on, I'm not that dumb.
All this? A monster?
Something was weird.
- She was the best ever.
- Okay, okay.
Look, I'll talk to you later.
Hey, where are you going?
There's just something
I have to do.
Thanks again, for everything.
No big deal.
All right, all right.
Don't get crazy again.
- I won't.
- See you.
I'm glad you're happy now.
Who are you talking to?
What?
- Uh, no one.
- Uh-huh.
Don't get too close
to the water.
What did you say?
I said don't get too
close to the water.
You might fall in.
Because piranhas?
I think piranhas only
are in the Amazon.
I'm Lilly, by the way.
Hi, Lilly. I'm Peter.
Nice to meet you.
We just moved here.
Well, my mom lived here, but she
moved away when she was little.
There was an accident where her
sister died a long time ago.
It's weird. I feel like
I've been here before.
Anyway, wanna play?
Yeah, I think I would.
Great! Can you help me
look for some snails?
I would pick them up, but they're
totally gross and slimy,
and I think that's your job.
Hush, now creature
dry your eyes
I know a place where
a body can hide, oh
a body can hide
last time I saw you,
our table was bare
if you hurry and join me,
I will lead you there
oh, sink beneath the waters
sink into the deep
in a pond just off the road
that feeds this muddy creek
oh, in a pond
just off the road
that feeds this muddy creek
though my days are over
you know where I'll be
swim that lost river to me
though my days are done
the waters will always run
swim that lost river to me
Though I'm gone
don't be afraid
we'll meet again on
the river someday
the croak of the frogs
will lead you true
wear a skirt of greenstone
so I know it's you
oh, wear a skirt of greenstone
to drag you to the blue
though my days are over
you know where I'll be
swim that lost river to me
though my days are done
the waters will always run
find the la-la-lost river
find me
Lay your head
on the riverbed
drink from the river and
find your way to me
oh, rest your head
on the riverbed
drink from the river and
find your way to me
oh, lay your head
on the riverbed
drink from the river and
find your way to me
come rest your head
on the riverbed
drink from the river and
find your way to me
oh, drink from the river
and find your way to me