Downloaded from
YTS.MX
[Buzzing]
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
[Deep exhale]
[Vocals shuddering]
[Eerie vocalizations]
♪♪
Man: So, I did hear back
from the publishing house.
Unfortunately, these aren't
selling like the last one.
And they said
this is pretty much
gonna be the last
printing of this.
But they said they'd get back
to me soon about the next one.
I think they said
the same thing a month ago.
Takes people a long time
to say yes in this business.
Or no.
You know, if they
don't like the book,
they should just say so.
That's not really
how it works.
Either way, I want you working
on a title for the next one.
"Go It Alone...
Together."
I may be better
at titles than you.
All right,
thanks for the update.
I'll figure it out.
You always do.
I'll let you know
as soon as I hear anything.
♪♪
Don't let this
get you down.
♪♪
Shit!
[Sighs]
♪♪
[Trunk closes,
woman screams in distance]
[Ignition clicks, beeps]
[Music plays loudly on radio,
volume decreases]
♪ Cried out for yesterday ♪
♪ But the clock wouldn't
give her the time of day ♪
♪ Can't go back to yesterday ♪
♪♪
[Engine, music stop]
[Faucet running]
[Dishes clinking]
♪♪
[Faucet stops]
[Squeaking]
[Plate cracks]
[Door opens in distance]
♪♪
[Lock clicks]
[Crowd cheering on TV]
This is a good bite.
For me?
Mm-hmm.
Lots of chocolate chips.
Mm, I think you're confusing
what you like with what I like.
We are very
different people.
Everybody likes
chocolate chips.
But everyone has
different tastes.
The individual is a collection
of one's unconscious --
I'm not one of your freshman
philosophy students.
Mmm!
See? Fuck Nietzsche.
Signing?
A talk, which always
leads to a signing.
Could you just
pre-sign and...
hand them out,
avoid conversation?
It's not really
how it works.
This could be dangerous
for someone.
♪♪
Definitely.
I just...
want to focus
on other things right now,
not the books
or the signings or the talks.
What else would you
focus on?
Us.
That's melting.
Is it?
Mm-hmm.
Huh.
Because it's still
really cold! Feel.
Oh, my God! [Laughs]
Your hands are freezing.
Oh, maybe you're
too sensitive.
[Laughing]
What? What? You want me to
hold the ice cream, right?
♪♪
[Faucet running]
[Faucet stops]
♪♪
[Cellphone vibrating]
It's late.
It's Edie.
Edie: Apologies, but you said
to call when I knew
what time your talk is
on Wednesday.
-And?
-1:00 p.m.
Just text me next time.
Will do.
Sorry.I'm already asleep again.
♪♪
[Exhales]
[Lock rattling, keys jangling]
[Eerie music plays]
♪♪
Ted.
Ted!
♪♪
[Music stops]
[Exhales]
May: Ted.
Ted, wake up.
Ted: What?
[Whispering]
I saw someone outside.
What?
A man was in our backyard.
[Groans]
Honey, that's the man.
[Inhales sharply]
[Normal voice] What?
Mm, the man...
who comes every night
and tries to kill us.
[Glass shatters in distance]
Okay, well, get up.
[Claps hands]
You don't want to be
caught in bed.
That's the worst place
you could be.
[Thudding, clatter]
Wow.
He's really getting to it.
Not wasting any time.
May: Who is that man?
Better hope he doesn't have
any good weapons tonight.
♪♪
May, come on, get up.
We have to fight
for our lives now.
What -- Ted, what are
you talk--
Shh!
May.
♪♪
[Whispers] Ted.
Ted.
Ted!
[Breathing shakily]
♪♪
Ted.
[Glass crunches]
Aah!
[Breathing heavily]
[Exhales][Footsteps thudding]
♪♪
[Floorboards creak]
[Keys jangling]
[Breathing heavily]
[May gasps]
What are you doing here?
Aah!
Get out of my house.
Aah! [Whimpering]
[Ted grunts][Thud]
[Sobs]
You didn't even check on me
in the living room.
Come on, let's go.
Ted: You okay?
We're just gonna
leave him there, or...?
Oh, I'm sure he's
already gone.
Woman: How did he
enter the house?
Um, from what I could tell,
he smashed through the
front window in the dining room.
Then I came down the stairs,
and -- pff -- I was out.
How are you
feeling now?
I have a nasty headache,
some cuts. I'll be fine.
You're lucky you woke up.
Both of you are lucky.
[Police radio chatter]
Do you know this man?
No.
Never seen him before
in my life.
How about you?
Uh, I...
don't know him either.
Okay.
Can you describe
what he was wearing?
We'll have the local guys
keep an eye out.
♪♪
[Birds chirping]
Oh. [Chuckles]
You slept late.
Probably needed it.
Yeah. Mm.
[Inhales deeply]
What?
[Exhales deeply]
I think I'm
losing my mind.
Must be how he got in.
I thought that was a dream
or maybe a hallucination
or something.
What a crazy hallucination
that would be. [Chuckles]
So that was real?
The man who broke
into our house?
Yes.
It was very real.
Yeah, but
you said something.
Something weird.
Maybe I misunderstood, but...
I need you to explain
to me what's going on.
What do you mean?
You said a man comes
into our house --
Every night
and tries to kill us.
What?
Actually, more you than me,
I guess, but what can you do?
Ted, what are you talking about?
This is not a funny joke.
May, pull it together.
How can I possibly pull it
together when a man
broke into our house
last night?
I'm scared.
I mean, who was he?
[Sighs] May, come on.
What the fuck is
wrong with you?
What are you even trying
to do right now?
I'm trying to help.
Well, you're doing
a fucking terrible job.
There you go.
You probably blame me
for this, don't you?
I can't change it, May.
This is just how things are.
This is not
how things are.
Yes, it is.
Every night, a man
comes to our house and tries --
No, shut up!
Stop talking!
Okay.
I'm gonna go.
I can't be with you
when you're like this.
I'll come back
when you've calmed down.
Wha...
But wait, what -- what if
he comes back?
May, don't be ridiculous.
It's the middle of the day.
Ted, where are you going?
Ted?[Car beeps]
Ted.[Engine starts]
Ted, where are you going?
Ted!
[Sighs]
♪♪
[Glass crunches]
This is Ted.
Leave a message after the beep.
Ted, you can't just
leave me here. Come back.
Or call me or s...
Fuck!
[Sighs]
[ "Sign of the Times"plays
on overhead speakers]
♪ So many bullies ♪
♪ What are they all
fighting for? ♪
[Keys jangling]
♪ They throw their punches
from computers ♪
♪ Behind closed doors ♪
♪ So this is life ♪
♪ All this high-tech ♪
♪ Stupid guy ♪
♪♪
[Glass clattering]
Edie: I don't think I put
window repair on my résumé.
We both know you lied
on your résumé.
But you still hired me.
I must be charming.
Very.
Where's Ted?
Can't he help with this?
We don't need Ted.
I just need you to hold it
while I nail it in.
Wow. Youneed help?
There's a first time
for everything.
[Soft music plays on radio]
I can see why they put glass
in these things.
But the plywood
looks nice, too.
So, you all set
for your talk tomorrow?
Yep.
And you'll be able
to sleep tonight.
Yeah.
I could stay.
No.
No, I'm fine, really,
but I appreciate you coming.
I just don't know what
I would do in that situation.
Think on your feet.
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, I guess so.
I'll -- I'll see you
tomorrow.
Mm.
♪♪
[Sighs]
[Cellphone dings]
♪♪
[Line rings]
Hey, it's Ted Ryer.
Leave a message.
Ted, where are you?
Call me back.
[Line rings]
Woman: Hey, May.
Sarah, hi. Um, did Ted
come there by chance?
No, uh, I haven't seen him.
Everything all right?
Yeah, we just got into
a fight earlier,
and I was hoping
he came your way.
I haven't seen him all day.
You know my brother.
He can be very stubborn.
Just like my ex-husband.
They're stubborn,
and we're crazy.
[Laughs] Isn't that
what people say?
I don't know.
Well, anyway, I'm sure
Ted will be back soon.
Yeah.
A man came to
the house last night.
What do you mean?
A man. A stranger.
I don't know.
He broke in, Ted got hurt.
Is he okay?
Yeah, he's fine.
Are you?
Yeah.
Ted hurt him, and...
he left.
[Exhales] Wow.
That's wild, May.
I can't believe
that happened.
Yeah.
You're lucky you
didn't get hurt.
You want to come here
for the night?
Um...
No, I'm fine.
Okay.
I'll just wait here for Ted.
Call me if you
need anything,
or just come over
if you feel nervous.
I am really sorry
that happened.
Thanks, and thank you
for listening.
And, um, if you see Ted,
tell him I called.
Okay.
[Sighs]
[Floorboards creak]
♪♪
[Keys jangling,
dog barking in distance]
Ted?
Ted, is that you?
[Stairs creak]
♪♪
[Floorboards creak]
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Aah!
[Dramatic music plays]
♪♪
[Lock clicks]
[Door hinges creak]
♪♪
[Grunts]
Aah!
[Thud]
♪♪
[Keys jangle]
[Grunts]
[Thud]
♪♪
[Dialing]
Dispatcher: 911.
What's the emergency?
Hi. My name is May Ryer. Someone
just broke into my house.
I live at 1933 Grove Street.
He's unconscious,
but could you hurry?
The same man was here
last night.
He is definitely dangerous.
Hello?
Hello, ma'am?
Are you still there?
Hello?
Man: Mrs. Ryer? Hi.
Officer Pace. You mind if
I ask you a few questions?
Sure.
Can you tell me
what he looked like?
He was wearing...
a mask.
Mm-hmm.
Some kind of coat,
sort of.
Mm-hmm.
Do you think your husband
could know how him?
No. I mean...
[Dog barking in distance]
I guess he could. I...
I don't know.
Okay.[Pen scribbling]
He's been here twice.
Is there anything else I can do?
Well, uh, have you thought
about getting some mace?
It's very effective.
I tried a golf club,
but it wasn't effective.
Yeah, try the mace.
Okay.
That's all I need for now.
Thank you.
And, um, I'm sorry, where did
you say your husband is?
I'm not sure.
You're not sure?
Is there a history of problems
in the relationship
that maybe I should
know about?
No.
[Pen clicks, scribbles]
Look, in these
domestic-dispute cases,
it's really helpful
if we can have the victim
come down to the station,
you know, just in case.
I'm sorry, what victim?
That's you, ma'am.
This isn't a
domestic dispute.
A man broke into my house.
Yeah, no, no,
I got that written down here.
♪♪
Wow, that could be
really dangerous.
My husband and I
just got into a fight.
And he left,
and that's all.
Okay.
Does he have a history of
leaving for stretches of time?
Yeah.
Does he have
a history of violence?
No, nothing like that.
Look, I don't think
you're understanding.
That's not the problem.
Hey, where do you work?
Maybe you call in
to your work tomorrow.
You take the day off to just,
you know, decompress.
I work from home.
Okay.
I'm a writer.
Oh, what kind of stuff?
My daughter -- she loves
that, uh, young-adult fiction.
I write...
business books, how-tos,
and I'm home by myself all day.
What -- What if he
comes back?
Yeah, I doubt he's gonna
come back in the daytime.
Really?
You know, my husband s...
[Exhales]
What about your husband?
[Softly] I don't know.
[Birds chirping]
[Line ringing]
Ted Ryer,
philosophy department.
Leave a message.
Ted, I don't know where
you are, but come home.
[Knock on door]
Sarah:
Hey, May. Come in.
Hey. Uh, where is he?
Ted?
Uh...
You just missed him.
He's at our parents'.
Great.
Why would he go there?
[Soft rock music
plays on radio]
I just need to talk to Ted.
I don't understand why he's
so angry with me
or why he's avoiding me.
Same as last time?
No. That was different.
You know, when you guys
almost split,
he was really
torn up about it.
You know how he gets.This isn't like that.
Last time was my fault.
This was just a small fight.
These things
get complicated.
It's not that complicated.
I didn't mean
to upset you.
If you talk to Ted, will you
just tell him to call me?
Mm-hmm.
Okay, thanks.
[Seatbelt clicks]
[Keys jangling]
May: The truth is,
change is hard.
It's hard to change
ourselves, right?
But we, as women,
need to quit focusing on
our gendered narratives
and start creating our own.
That's how you problem-solve.
Most of us would rather
be comfortable
than try something new, right?
Say a new social-media platform.
[Chuckles softly]
A new job
or a new life change.
Uh, but it's easy
to change a pattern, right?
So focus on that.
Sorry.Focus on the patterns
you can change.
It's okay.
That's my assistant, Edie.
[Chuckles softly]
Because unless we
face our fears
and confront
those unhealthy patterns
that are holding us back,
we will get nowhere.
No one is helped
who can't help themselves.
Thank you.
[Applause]
Thank you so much, May,
for coming to our little group.
You mind if we take
a few questions?
Yeah, sure.
Hi, May.
Um, my name is Marie.
I'm such a huge fan
of yours.
So, uh, I was just wondering
why you're not
writing your blogs anymore.
I mean, they were such a big
inspiration to all of us.
Yeah, I-I took a break
from those.
I'll get back to them
at some point.
They're not as easy
to make as you would think.
Will you be writing
another book anytime soon?
Yes, I am working on a new book
right now, actually.
What are you researching?
Uh, what's inspiring you?
Um...
What am I researching?
Um...[Cellphone vibrates]
Oh, uh...
What am I researching?
Um...
Uh...
I'll have to get back
to you on that.
Oh.
Okay. [Chuckles]
Any other questions?
Uh, I was thinking about
what you said about how women
bond over their failures.
I know I do that.
[Chuckles]
And I focus on the bad and
I never think about the good,
and I am trying
to change that.
But do you think
that men and women
deal with these things
differently?
Are women trained
to respond
to the things
that we fear differently,
or do we just run
to each other for help?
I mean, that's not
healthy, right?
♪♪
Yeah.
Um...
Men and women do respond
to things differently.
Um...
The important thing...
♪♪
is, uh -- What's
the important thing?
The important thing...
is to remain calm and...
Go it alone?
[Laughter]
Yeah, do that.
[Chuckles nervously]
Uh...
That's -- That's all the time
we have for today,
but don't forget to sign up
for our mailing list,
and we are actually doing a
book signing in the back, so...
Yay.
[Applause]
[Indistinct chatter]
[Soft rock music plays
on overhead speakers]
♪♪
♪ Navigate the world your way,
they have a say ♪
♪ You can do whatever
you want to do ♪
♪♪
Come on, Ted.
Come home.
♪♪
[Creaking]
[Eerie music plays]
♪♪
[Gasps]
[Screaming]
♪♪
[Grunts][Mace hissing]
Aah! [Grunts]
You creepy son of a bitch.
[Dialing]Dispatcher: 911.
Hi, a man just broke
into my house.
I live at 1933 Grove --
Hello?
Hello? Ma'am?
Hello? Are you
still there? Hello?
Yeah, I'm still here.
Pace: So you say it's
the same guy?
Yes.
You sure?
Okay, well, I'm gonna have
my guys look out for him.
Your guys must be pretty bad
at looking out for him
because you said that last night
and he still came back.
You know,
you're very lucky.
Him coming into your
bedroom like this,
he was probably coming after
more than just robbing you.
I'm gonna put some more
patrols in the neighborhood.
Don't ever be afraid
to call us.
I haven't been
afraid to call.You know what I mean.
It's tough to tell
with these guys.
You don't know what they --
what they want.
I mean, you know,
bad childhoods, I guess.
Really can't get them
for anything other than rob--
I should also report
that my husband is missing.
You said you just
got into a fight.
Yeah, we did,
but if I report him missing,
you'll go get him, right?
He's at his
parents' house.
Then he's not missing.
He needs to be
home with me.
All right. Okay.
I'm gonna have someone
call you about that.
And you say that you
don't know this man --
guy that broke
into your house?
Most of these attacks are
perpetrated by people we know.
You sure?
Yeah.
Do you have
anyone else you can stay?
I mean, I really don't think
this guy's coming back,
but it might
make you feel better.
You don't think he's
gonna come back?
He's been here
three nights in a row.
Okay, I'm gonna put some
more patrols around just --
just in case.
Yeah, you do that.
Mrs. Ryer, you seem angry.
I am angry.
Okay, being angry
is really not gonna help.
You just need to stay calm
and let us do our job.
Just stay vigilant.
Stay calm and vigilant.
I can do that.
Perfect.
Hi, I need you to cancel
all my calls today.
Edie: Yep. You want me
to tell them why?
Uh, nope.
Just make something up.
Are you okay?
You left in such a hurry.
Yeah, I'm fine.
Just personal things.
Are you okay?
You're never late.
Of course, yes.
Also personal stuff.
Hey, this one?
Got to go.
No.
Everything okay
with Edie?
Yeah.
I cannot believe
that guy came back.
What did the cops say?
They haven't been
very helpful.
Just gonna have to
figure this out on my own.
Thank you for being here.No problem.
I wanted to see you,
and I felt kind of shitty
after the way
we ended things last time.
I didn't mean
to make you feel bad.
Thanks.
I just want
to make sure you feel...
Safe?
Yeah.
This one?
Mm. It looks complex.
I'll figure it out.
These things are tough.
It's just the way
things go sometimes.
Life is hard. You just
take one day at a time.
Yeah.
Hey, are you sure
you don't want to come over
and stay at my place?
Um...
No, thank you.
I'm not gonna let this guy
scare me out of my own house.
♪♪
[Beeping]
[Exhales deeply]
[Eerie music plays]
♪♪
This is Ted. I can't take
the call right now.
Leave a message.
♪♪
[Keys jangling]
[Door hinges creak]
♪♪
[Keys jangling]
[Grunts]
[Thud]
♪♪
[Thunder rumbles]
Woman: [Echoing] Unfortunately,
Mrs. Ryer, the blood tests
came back inconclusive,
so we're not gonna be able to
actually identify...
♪♪
[Pills rattle]
[Lock rattling, keys jangling]
[Door hinges creak]
[Exhales]
♪♪
[Screams]
[Grunting]
♪♪
[Gasps]
Aah!
[Screams]
Look, if the alarm goes off,
it is definitely an emergency.
Okay, ma'am,
I understand.
Actually, can you have someone
stationed outside of my house?
Is that hard to do?
Well, we typically only
consider...
No, there haven't been any
verbal threats.
He doesn't have a...
Can I speak to your boss,
please?
Sure. Can I put you
on hold?
Yes, I'll hold.
[Knock on door]
Hi.
Sorry to bother you,
but I, uh,
found this box of books
hiding in the office.
I thought that maybe
you could, uh...
I'm sorry. Did I come
at a bad time?
I tried to call, but...
Yeah, I'll --
I'll take those.
Okay, uh...
[Box thuds]
And I come bearing news.
[Claps hands]
They finally got back to me, and
they want to do another book.
I got you a killer advance.
They just had a few gentle
suggestions based on
where the women's movement
is going right now.
You know, I mean,
got to keep us relevant.
Cutting-edge, you know?
They just want you to
incorporate some of the
catchphrases
and the buzzwords
that the women's market's
responding to these days,
Latinx -- that sort of thing,
you know? You get it.
Plus, that stuff is so easy
to incorporate anyway.
This is great news. I wanted
to come and tell you in person.
Plus, you're not returning
my calls, so...
It's great. Thanks.
Great.
You have no idea.
You're so lucky that they want
to do another book with you.
Sorry, what?
I said...
you're lucky that they want
to do another book with you.
I mean, the market's
a mess right now.
At least you know
they love you.
No, I'm not lucky.
I-I'm not.
Come on. I didn't --
I didn't mean to say --
I-I worked my ass off
for that book.
I wrote, and then I rewrote,
and I toured,
and I signed God knows
how many fucking copies.
And I came up with little
buzzwords and catchphrases.
And I did talks for free.
And I answered the same goddamn
question over and over again
with the exact same amount
of enthusiasm
as I did the last time
that I answered it.
And I am not lucky.
I just work really,
really hard.
You're right.
You do great work.
Thank you for waking me up.
And thank you
for being my client.
Okay.
All right.
Yeah.
It's great news.
All right?
Congratulations.
Go team. Yeah?
[Softly] Go team.
♪♪
[Lock clicks]
[High-pitched whistling]
♪♪
[Whistling stops]
[Keys jangling, footsteps]
Fuck you.
What do you want?
What do you want from me?
I'm not scared of you.
You haven't
killed me yet.
You know...
a wise woman once said that
unless we face our fears
and confront
our unhealthy patterns,
we will get nowhere.
That wise woman was me.
I wrote that, and people
paid a lot of money to read it.
And honestly, what the fuck
do I have to be scared of?
♪♪
All right, fine.
Let's do this.
[Screams]
[Grunting]
♪♪
Aaaah!
Shit.
♪♪
[Groans]
[Gasps]
Hey, hey! Help me!
He's in the house! Hey!
Hey! Help!
Hey, hey!
He's in the house.
He's right there.
Stay right here.
Woman: Hi, May. I'm your
state-appointed social worker.
Let's get started.
Is there...
Is there anything you
need to tell me?
[Chuckles softly]
What's funny?
Nothing.
Go ahead.
You can talk to me.
I think I'm
losing my mind.
And what makes you
say that?
[Police radio chatter]
If I told you that something
weird was happening,
like something...
[Whispers] supernatural...
would you believe me?
Possibly.
I don't feel like I'm living
in my world anymore.
Look, Mrs. Ryer,
I'm familiar with who you are
and what it is you do.
Is this -- Is this about
one of your books?
No. No, no, no, no.
I feel like I don't know
how to play the game anymore,
like I don't understand
the rules.
I used to be really good
at the game
and now I feel
like everything is...
different.
Let's just stick
to the facts.
Is there anything I should
know about your husband?
Has he ever had
a drinking problem?
Has he ever been abusive
towards you physically,
emotionally, verbally?
No. This has nothing to do
with my husband.
Has he ever been very,
very angry with you?
Has he ever acted out in a way
that was maybe inappropriate?
What happened?
I don't -- I don't know.
Can you try
and explain it?
[Sighs]
Okay.
About a year ago...
I cheated on him.
I was on book tour.
And I thought our relationship
was over, and I cheated.
And I told him,
and he was angry.
And he hit you.
No.
You just asked me
if he was ever
really, really angry
about something.
He wasn't
physically violent?
No, he was sad.
I...
I ruined our marriage.
He...
It was an awful thing to do.
I cheated on him.
So you think you ruined
your marriage?
I didn't think so, but...
I don't know now.
And have you heard from him
since this whole thing
has started?
Look, I don't feel like
you're listening to me.
I hurt my husband
emotionally, but...
I'm not in danger
from my husband.
I'm in danger from the man
that comes to my house
every night
to try to kill me.
Hmm.
Okay.
Anything else?
[Birds chirping]
[Cellphone ringing]
Hey, Sarah.
May.
Hey.
[Soft pop music plays on radio]
Do you think
I'm being punished?
For what?
I don't know.
The cops don't know
who he is?
No.
They really
can't help you?
[Scoffs]
That's so scary.
Yeah.
It is, but I've
already said that.
I've already said all of this.
Are you even listening?
[Glass shatters]Oh. [Chuckles]
[Chuckles]
No problem.
Empty bottle.
You are so brave
for staying in that house.
Sarah, what is that scar?
What?
On your back.
I've never seen it before.
[Ominous music plays]
♪♪
Just an old thing.
I forget.
Just a part of living
in this world.
It happened so long ago.
♪♪
Any reason he might be
targeting you?
They don't know.
♪♪
You know, I've hurt him.
Every day.
I know.
You are so brave.
No, I mean...
He should be dead.
I have really hurt him.
There has been so much blood --
pools of blood,
more blood than
I have ever seen.
That's disgusting.
And I have stabbed him
in the back and in the head.
And I threw him down the stairs,
and I think he broke his neck.
May, that's very graphic.
But he keeps coming back.
Are you sure you're
really hurting him?
No, I am, definitely.
But he's stronger
than you, right?
♪♪
Yeah. I guess so.
I honestly don't know
why you stayed in that house
as long as you did.
I guess I didn't think
he could hurt me.
But he is
hurting you, May.
Yeah, but...
I'm still alive.
I'm gonna get you!
Pew, pew, pew!
Aah!
Not if I get you first!
[Laughs]
Okay, I am gonna clear out some
of the stuff in Cooper's room
so that you could sleep in it
because you don't want to
accidentally step
on a toy or a fake gun
because it actually
really hurts.
[Laughs]
Okay.
Okay? All right.
Bathroom's open if you need it.
All right?
Come on, love.
[Chuckles]
♪ I'm not afraid ♪
♪ Does it have to end? ♪
♪ Darlin', please,
oh, please, oh, please ♪
♪ Don't break my heart ♪
[Cracking]
[Glass cracks]
[Keyboard clacking]
[Glass shatters]
♪♪
Mom?
Cooper.
[Thudding][Gasps] Go to your room
and lock the door.
Go to your room
and dial 911.
♪♪
I hurt you.
[Softly] I hurt you.
♪♪
Hey, hey, ma'am, ma'am,
it's okay, it's okay,
you're okay, it's okay.
You need to calm down,
all right?
We're all here
to help you, okay?
[Police radio chatter]
It's all right.
It's okay. You're safe.
Where -- Where is Sarah?
Where's Cooper?
Cooper called the police.
He said you told him to.
He's fine.
I examined him myself.
He's not hurt at all.
He's a very brave
little man. Okay?
Let's just have a seat.Where --
He's gone. He's gone.
Okay? We don't know
where he went.
But he can't be far.
All right?
Now, I'm just gonna check
all of your vitals,
and then I'm gonna give you
a sedative, all right?
It's gonna help you
go to sleep.
I-I don't want
to go to sleep.
It's gonna help you heal, okay?
You're hurt pretty bad.
I mean, it's definitely
gonna leave a scar.
Where is Sarah?
My sister-in-law?
They rushed her to
the hospital. I don't know.
But we'll find out her
condition for you, okay?
Um, you know, I should, um --
I should go check
on Sarah in the hospital.
Ma'am, I really need
to check your vitals.
This man could be anywhere.
He's not here, okay?
Where is he? I don't know.
Can we just breathe, okay?
[Breathes deeply]
There we go.
There we go. All right.
Now let's actually
just, uh...
Let's get away from
the crime scene.
♪♪
May: No.
Excuse me?
We've already
been over this.
Of course.
I know that.
Then why haven't
you helped?
I have to ask you
a few questions.
It's -- It's my job.
What could you possibly
ask me that's new?
I've been fighting
this man for...
how long?
How long have I been
doing this?
Doing what?
Surviving this man
over and over.
You've been there.
You know.
I don't know, May.
I assume since
the parking garage.
What parking garage?
You know, the one where you --
Come on, you dropped your books,
and you couldn't find
your keys.
But I didn't tell you
about that. You weren't...
What are you
talking about?
Well, it's always how
these things start, right?
Alone in a public place,
isolated.
See, that's why you have to
always stay vigilant
because, you know, a man could
appear at any time.
Sure is scary.[Chuckles]
Very.
Okay, I got to take care
of something,
but we can chat in a few.
[Smacks lips]
Man: Mrs. Ryer, can I
ask you a few questions?
Mrs. Ryer?
Yeah.
Do you know the man
who attacked you?
Ma'am, do you recognize
this hammer?
Yeah, that's mine.I'm just gonna take
your blood pressure.
Can I have that back?We're gonna have to
keep the hammer.
Mrs. Ryer, I just need to
take a little blood.
I'm a social worker.
Do you have a moment?
I was just sent
because of the trauma.
Can I ask you some --Questions.
All: Have you ever been
alone at night?
It's not safe for --For a woman.
And where is your...Both: Husband?
Are you aware of the dangers
of rust poisoning?
That hammer looked rusty.
-Yes, very rusty.
But a good way
to save yourself.What is happening?
-I'm going to ask you again.
-What time did you go to sleep?
-Do you usually go to sleep?
-Who's the kid?
-That's Cooper.
-That's my son's name.
Great name.
I'll have to write that down.
Man: What time did
Cooper go to sleep?
Your sister-in-law --Sarah. How is she?
-Haven't heard.
-No word.
-Nowhere.
-No one's heard.
Can you stay still?
-Okay.
-Have you had problems?
-In your own home?
-With your medical history?
-History of mental illness?
Why are you not at home?
What if Ted comes back?EMT: Open up.
-Where do you normally...
-Find men that chase you?
-This has been a problem lately.
-It is a problem.
Spit in this vial.
-♪ Can you be clear? ♪
-Stats seem normal.
What is normal?♪ Are you worried
about Sarah? ♪
Can you establish what your
relationship is with the man?
I can't be here.
This is too much.
Let me ask you a question.Sure.
[Keys jangle]
[Eerie music plays]
♪♪
[Engine starts]
[Music plays on radio]
♪♪
[Engine, music stop]
[Ignition beeping]
[Gasps]
Fuck.
[Edie screaming]
♪♪
[May screams]
Edith, come on!
Let's go! Come on.
May, wait!
What are you doing here?!
Come on.
My car's just over here.
Fuck! Okay, come on.
Let's go. Keep going.
May, wait. I don't -- I don't
understand what's happening.
-Why are we here?
-Edie, we have to keep going.
We can't keep going.
He finds me anywhere I go.
I know. I know.
Have you killed him
every day?
Yeah.
How do you know that?
'Cause it's happening
to me, too.
I don't know what I did
to deserve this. Do you?
[Footsteps, clatter]
[Gasps]
Get down, get down.
♪♪
Come on, go.
Get that, get that.
♪♪
Wait. He's gone?
Okay, okay.
Let's keep going.
[Woman screaming]
♪♪
[Screaming]
[Grunting]
♪♪
Wait, wait!
We have to help them!What, all of them?!
Yes, of course,
all of them!How could we do that?
How can we help all of them?
-The way you just helped me.
I helped you
because I know you.
If we work together,
maybe --
This is just
how things are now.
Can't fix it for myself,
so how can I possibly fix it
for everyone else?
We are being attacked
in our homes
and in our friends' homes
and in our parking garages
every goddamn day
for the rest of our lives.
There's no rationalizing it,
and there's no saving us.
So get used to it.
I'm gonna go, and then
I'm gonna go to sleep
so I can wake up
and start it all over
again tomorrow
because I'm gonna do this
again tomorrow.
I'm gonna fight for my life
once again tomorrow.
So good luck.
But what do I do now?
Just make a plan.
Try to stay calm.
That's it?
Yeah, that's it.
[Breathes deeply]
[Keys jangling]
[Edie screams]
Edie!
No!
Help! Help!
Is anyone still...
Fuck!
♪♪
[Panting]
Aah!
Help! Help!
No, no, no!
There's someone trying
to kill me! Please!
Stay away from me!
Wait.
Hey, a little help here?
Aah!
♪♪
Fuck.
[Keys jangle]
[Exhales]
[Engine starts]
♪♪
[Thud]
Fucker.
♪♪
[Tires squeal]
Hi, May.
Jesus Christ, Ted,
you scared me.
You think you'd be
used to that by now.
What are you doing here?
The police called,
so I came as fast as I could.
To the back of my car?!
Yes.
Get out.
Why?
Get out of my car, Ted!
Fine.
[Ignition beeping]
No, no,
don't get near me!
Okay.
-How did you get back there?
-I was waiting for you.
How is Sarah?
Have you heard --
No, no,
stay away from me!
I'm your husband, May.
How could I possibly hurt you?
I never said you were
gonna hurt me.
Just stay back.
You're being ridiculous.
What's your plan?
To go inside?
What do you mean go inside?
We're...
I didn't drive here.
Sometimes you just end up
where you need to be.
[Exhales]
Ted, I've been
waiting for you.
Where have you been?
Remember when
we were fighting?
I was trying to come up
with solutions, talk rationally.
And then you just
lost it on me.
You got really
mean and crazy.Okay, that's...
And I said that I would
come back if you calmed down.
Here I am.
You hurt my feelings.
Do you understand?
I do understand.
See, I thought I was being
punished for cheating on you
and ruining our relationship,
but then I saw these
other women and I realized...
I'm not being punished
because all these other women
aren't being punished, right?
So I understand now.
I'm not a bad person.
Ted, can you tell me
who he is?
You know.
I do?
You know that
it doesn't really matter.
Doesn't matter who the man is
or how to fight him
or how to fix it.
This is just
how things are.
Right.
Let's go inside.
You know we're not
safer there.
Yeah, I know.
I do know that.
♪♪
I just -- I...
I want things
to be normal again.
♪♪
I'm just tired.
These last few days
have been hard on you.
Hmm?
I guess so.
I just want to give up.
But I know
I have to keep going.
Going it alone.
[Chuckles softly]
Don't go anywhere, okay?
I need you.
[Keys jangle, Ted gasps]
[Ted moans softly]
♪♪
Ted? Ted?
Ted!
[Panting]
♪♪
God! I fucking hate you!
Go! Just go away!
♪♪
[Keys jangling]
No, no, no, no, no.
That's not fair.
[Door hinges creaking]
You killed Ted!
And you killed Edie!
♪♪
What do you want?
[Softly]
I don't deserve this.
I don't deserve any of this.
♪♪
[Keys jangling]
Okay.
Come on.
[Screams]
[Grunts]
♪♪
♪ Black cat, he said,
"Don't, don't you do it" ♪
♪ Don't, don't you do it ♪
♪ Black cat, he said,
"Don't, don't you do it" ♪
♪ Don't, don't you do it ♪
♪ Black cat, he said,
"Don't, don't you do it" ♪
♪ Don't, don't you do it ♪
♪ Black cat, he said,
"Don't, don't you do it" ♪
♪ Don't, don't you do it ♪
♪♪
[Vocals shuddering]