Gadis, it's me Dewi.
Dis.
I can't help you this way.
Gadis, why don't you ever meet us?
We need to stick together, so we don't forget.
Together we're strong. You understand, right?
But none of you ever believed me.
You said 'he' attacked you, Gadis.
I felt everything, Dewi.
We are free from him.
A long time ago.
We're stronger than him.
Who did this to you?
Why don't you believe me?
I don't know.
Trust me, Dewi
I felt him, the same way I'm feeling you right now.
What do you mean?
He's dead. Remember that day, right?
He's staring at you right now. Smiling.
I'll stay here tonight.
Yes, Budi?
You're with her?
Yes, with Gadis.
Something's wrong with her.
Bruises all over her body.
Kept saying she was abused.
She said Ayub did it to her.
Ayub? She mentioned that name again?
15 years passed and she hasn't moved on-
No one can truly move on from that!
She needs a psychiatrist.
What she needs is our support.
Understood, but she's always been different since we're
kids.
If she's acting up, it's not your responsibility
Hello, Dewi?
Bud, call you back.
Dewi!
Dewi.
Wait!
Okay, come in.
..Alfie.
Nara.
I miss him too.
But we have to move on.
We only have each other.
Sleep tight, okay?
I love you.
Devil's child..
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Wait! Please!
Alfie! Alfie!
Careful! Nara might get hurt.
Who are you?!
We meant no harm.
Kristi, are you okay?
Everybody's alright?
I'll go first.
I'll bring the car to the front.
Kristi, stay.
Watch for anything suspicious.
Come.
Are you guys crazy?
You put her in there since Jakarta?
She could die!
She kept putting a fight.
The small one is at the front.
She's alive, right, Sis?
Marta, Kristi!
Take the little one inside.
Yes Sis.
You guys take her.
Okay.
Hold her head.
Nara!
Rise and shine.
Where's Nara?
She's outside.
What do you want?
Don't ask too much
You're in my room, right?
How's your head?
Still hurts?
Bitch..
You like being electrocuted?
Here, want to get even?
What do you want?
Why did you take us here?
You'll find out!
What's wrong with her?
Guess she fell.
My name is Budi.
Alfie, I'm Jenar.
That's Leo.
First, let me apologize.
- If there's any other way
- One more time!
Where's Nara?
Calm down, Alfie.
I wasn't asking you.
She's with the others.
She's okay. Trust me!
What do you want from us?
We have nothing.
That's not it.
Do you know this place?
Bahtera Orphanage.
This was once a place for orphans
built by a childless husband and wife.
This place was once filled with warmth.
Who were abandoned by their own birth parents.
But everything changed.
Since the wife passed away.
At that time, there were 7 kids who weren't adopted yet.
Years passed.
They grew older.
And they were still living here.
There they realized.
Not all adults have the intention to keep them safe.
Gradually.
This home turned into a terrifying place.
Sir!
Please open the door, Sir!
- The one person they considered
- Sir! Please, Sir!
- Became a figure that turn their childhood a living hell.
Anyone dared to disobey were locked in the kitchen.
Without food. Without water. Without lights.
In total silence.
Even for days.
Alfie, do you know how it feels going through a nightmare.
That never ends?
I know how it feels to wake up from a nightmare.
And realize that real life is worse.
Why don't you just cut to the chase.
After this place was closed down.
The children were separated to live in different orphanages.
Living their own lives.
But promised to never forget each other.
So, the Police didn't know all of you killed the foster
father?
Where was the Police when we were locked up?
- Tortured?
- Leo!
- Forced to naked? Forced to
Don't worry.
You're facing with someone who burnt her own step sister.
Let's go downstairs.
Bud? Cheeky bastard!
I'm okay. It's okay!
That's for this morning.
From your closet.
Are you okay?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
She's taking too long.
Find her would you?
There she is.
Its all neatly cut.
Here, eat.
Nara! Nara!
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Alfie.
Sit down.
This is Gadis. Marta. And Kristi.
Again, I apologize.
We mean no harm to both of you.
We're desperate
What do you mean?
We believe.
Our foster father, Mister Ayub,
Has returned..for vengeance.
Returned from?
Death.
Gadis encountered him, she was the first to be attacked.
We did'nt believe her. Until
Until he killed Dewi.
Not 100 % proven, though.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Dewi was killed by..
Something.
Let's get things straight.
There was no other witness, you were alone with Dewi.
What did you say?
Have you seen what's done to her body?
None of you ever trusted me.
And look what happens.
- Because you've always been strange
- Kristi!
If you canÃ•t be supportive then leave.
Just because I doubt, doesn't mean I don't grieve.
Enough. What do you all want?
Nara and I just want to go home.
You testified to the Police that your father dealt with
witchcraft
And you witnessed it with yourself.
There must be a reason why Ayub's able to exist here.
Gadis.
Sorry, Alfie.
These must be unpleasantly familiar.
Have a drink.
Where did that Book come from?
I was a kid then, but I remember..
A woman came over.
She gave the Bible to Ayub.
A woman?
I never found out who she was.
As Jenar said.
Every day was torment for us.
I don't know why Ayub gets himself entangled with these
things.
In my father's case
..Greed.
But Ayub,
Perhaps something to do with his late wife?
Would that kind of ritual brings his wife back?
Bud, come in. How is she?
Everything is okay. Over.
Okay.
Cellphone's useless around here.
Let's go inside.
Wait!
I need to know what you want from me?
After Dewi's death.
Marta researched the Bible..
And she believes,
Dewi's death is just the beginning.
That something embeds in all of us after we killed Ayub.
What is it?
A curse.
Back then, this room terrifies us the most.
We always felt there's something down there.
Ready to come out.
None of you ever go down there?
Only Ayub did.
Leo, help me out.
Keep pushing.
Let's go.
I'm not going.
Thought you don't believe in this.
Oh, you're brave huh?
Don't want to know what he did down there.
Then, take Nara with you?
Nara, stay with Kristi, okay?
Marta.
I need you down there.
I'll go first.
Jenar.
Alfie, you're truly the one we've been looking for.
- Let's speed things up.
- Where do we start?
We start from where he ends.
There's an ancient belief, in the occult world..
Its basic principle, that all humans who worship Demons.
Are obliged to surrender their souls to their Demonic
deities.
There are certain demons that demand
sacrificial offerings.
These sacrificials is one's proof of ultimate servitude.
What is this figure?
An ancient demon.
Known as the figure of enlightenment and immortality.
It's name is
MOLOCH
We believe Ayub's plan was to sacrifice all of us.
- But before it could happened
- Alfie.
You're able to feel it right?
To see and sense the unseen?
Alfie, the curse that a demon worshipper cast on us
will never disappear.
Unless revoked by human who survived
from the Devil himself.
Alfie, if you can read this 'spell', you can terminate the
curse.
I don't understand this.
It's alright, Aflie.
What are you kids doing?
Little pests! Give me the stairs!
Master will never let none of you go.
- Alfie! Alfie!
- Alfie!
- Now what?
- Marta, what happened?"
- Alfie! Alfie!
- Alfie!
It's freezing.
What are you looking at?
Hello, Budi?
Leo?
Hello?
Kristi?
Kristi belongs to me now, Leo.
Budi, look out!
Jenar..
Look!
What is it now?
Jenar.
What happens to Jenar, Alfie?!
Alfie, what happens to her?!
Alfie! What do you see?
Jenar.
Jenar!
Alfie.
- Budi, Leo?
- Big sis.."
Hello?
- Big sis!
- What the hell?
Listen, big sis..
- Sis
- Wait here.
Close the door!
Budi, hurry! Hurry up!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Budi!
Nara, run!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Alfie!
Budi!
Leo, move away!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Come here, you little shit!
Nara!
Sis?
Alfie, your father sends his regards.
- From hell!
- What did you say?
What the fuck did you say?
- Do it Alfie, Do it!
- What did you say?
Alfie.
Who are you?
He's still waiting for you, Alfie.
Got away once, be damned..
Alfie condemned!
No!
She was not your friend anymore.
She was like my own sister!
Should've made sure before you murdered her!
I've known Kristi all my life!
Then why didn't you stop her?!
Show some respect!
Please!
You know, Nara?
They're just like my own siblings.
Even though, they often disregard me.
I know, big sis.
I lost my siblings too. My mother.
My Father
You're stronger than me. Nara, I'm sorry.
And forgive me for getting you involved.
No one should go down there again.
Best if you seal that door shut.
Now!
Shit!
This is a fucking mess.
Once everything's over, we'll give them a proper funeral.
Help me Leo.
You!
You told me to recite that specific spell!
You said that spell could revoke Ayub's curse.
But look now!
It's true. It can revoke the curse, Alfie.
If I was the only who could read the verse,
how would you know which page to read?
How?!
Why would I lie? I researched everything and I...
It means either you're wrong or you're lying
Alfie!
- You, shit!
You piece of shit!
Marta has tried her best!
I trust her.
Yes.
You trusted her,
Now two of you are dead!
Why should I trust her?
Why?!
She trusts you, Alfie.
Let me go!
Nara, let's go!
Alfie!
We're leaving now!
But you have to help us, Alfie
What else huh?
I've done everything you asked me for.
Okay,
You're right, you did.
Budi, are you for real?
This is our problem, we have to figure it out.
- I'll take you to the nearest train station.
- Alright
We're getting out of here.
Go inside.
Hurry!
Its not usually like this.
Are you serious? You promised.
Okay, hold on.
Sis?
What's wrong?
We weren't supposed to be here.
Calm down, Alfie, take it slow.
Relax, we're not going anywhere.
What did you say, Nara?
Devil's chid.
What's wrong, Alfie?
Nothing, Nothing.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Nara?
Budi?
Alfie..
Devil's child.
Lesmana?
Since when?
Be careful, Alfie.
It still wants you.
- Who?
- You know its name.
No!
All these happened to Nara and I because of you!
This is all your fault, Lesmana!
I've tried my best to stop it..
But it didn't work.
It demands your soul, Alfie
He dragged you into this place..
Leave! Alfie, leave this place!
- No
- Leave!
Alfie, are you okay?
After we lost everything.
Nobody really believed in us.
Police. Psychologist. Whatever that is.
I began to believe in nothing.
Not knowing what's real and what's not.
I'm afraid I'm losing it, Budi.
But twhat's truly scary is realizing..
That this madness is actually real.
Alfie! Your arm.
How did I end up back here?
You passed out in the car.
This was ages ago. I failed..obviously.
When Gadis hit a rough patch.
I told her to see a psychiatrist.
I'm no better than the Police.
Or the psychologist who didn't believe you.
Well, I'm crazier than all of you.
Leo's a drunk.
Jenar and Kristi are mostly shut off.
Marta's too consumed within her own walls.
Myself? I'm no catch.
We never had normal.
It's not your fault.
I saw it myself.
Bud..
Ayub will never let you go.
A demon who demands sacrificial children.
Why now though?
Alfie, when I tried to fix the car,
The wires were slashed.
Is it possible that these 'things' do that?
I don't know.
Until we know what we're dealing with,
I need to see that Black Bible now.
Leo,
can you come over here with the rest?
Bring the Bible.
Leo. About the car, I've nothing to do with it.
Best for you not to say anything right now.
- Okay?
- But you trust me, right?
Marta.
You know about this more than me.
I need your help.
Please!
Where's Gadis?
She was with us.
Best we stick together from now.
Always poor old me..
Dis..
Gadis.
Are these spells?
More than that, Alfie.
From what I've researched,
This Bible has been used by a number of people.
To summon things.
Things beyond comprehension of logic.
Marta, you should not be messing with these.
Dis,
Gadis.
I'm tired!
Shit, what a mess.
Should've been a homeless kid instead.
What's wrong, Alfie?
What is this?
Fuck, you fuckin' weirdo.
Who's a weirdo?
Gadis!
Open the door!
Leo, always putting up a fight..
Why are you doing this?
Father Ayub says you're punished, Leo.
What do you mean?
Just like when we were kids.
Let's see now.
How long will you last?
Let me out of here Gadis!
Gadis!
Budi!
This is Gadis right? Sitting on Ayub's lap.
It is..
Do you know what Stockholm Syndrome means?
Look at their hands.
Sir!
Open the door, Sir!
Sir Ayub!
We'll die here.
It can't be..
Sir Ayub will never let us out.
No! Impossible!
Bud!? Budi?!
Bud?
Son of a bitch!
Marta!
That spell has ressurected Ayub.
- Am I right?!
- Alfie!
- Marta, answer me!
- Alfie
Leo? Leo?
Leo is with me, Budi. You'll follow him soon..
Budi, help me. Come on!
Gadis!
Gadis, open the door!
Oh, my father.
I am ready.
To be in your servitude
As you are to 'him'.
I am ready, Father.
I am ready.
My child.
I am ready, Father.
I am ready! I am ready, Father.
Gadis?
Gadis.
Budi!
Gadis, what are you doing?
Budi, don't!
You'll be joining Leo, Budi.
All shall be together again.
What have you done to Leo, Gadis?
Why?
- You're our sister
- Shut up, Budi.
You're all blind.
Blind towards his greatness.
What awaits us beyond these..
You never believed it, right?
Father loved all of us.
- You're insane!
- He begs Moloch so we can be unified.
Forever.
Yet, you all killed Father.
We all loved you!
Dewi died for you!
Dewi..
I'm staying over tonight.
She always wanted to be the hero.
After studying the spells over and over again.
I was finally able to summon Father.
Even if only for a moment.
Father Ayub cares for me
He showed Dewi,
her soul belongs to him.
But to permanently resurrect Ayub,
she needed someone who has ties with something even
stronger.
And that person is me.
Right?
Correct, Alfie.
This was all destined.
You know how fortunate you are?
To be chosen by the great one.
Gadis!
On your knees Budi. Now!
Before it's too late for you.
To hell with you and Ayub!
Fuck your spells!
Budi!
- Budi!
- Gadis!
Look!
Budi!
Gadis, stop!
Gadis!
Budi!
Budi?
You bitch!
Fucking deranged bitch!
Just so you know..
I survived something much stronger than Ayub.
Your spells are useless against me.
Alfie, watch out!
Nara, you hurry run! Run!
That child belongs to Father Ayub.
Enough, I want all these to be over. Please!
Marta!
You lied to me, Gadis.
You said this will make our lives happier.
I'm happy, am I not?
Father Ayub opened the way for both of us.
You remember, right?
Let's go upstairs.
Marta!
Marta, don't listen to her!
Remember?
How I loved brushing your hair.
After all these,
we'll be together again.
Yes, we'll be together in hell.
If you truly survived the devil,
this should be nothing for you, Alfie
Marta! Snap out of it!
- Marta!
- I'm Sorry.
Use this Bible. To stop Gadis. Stop Ayub.
But I don't know how.
You're chosen, Alfie.
Find the symbols. Read the spells.
Marta! Marta!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hello, Nara.
I'm sorry.
Nara.
You're a feisty one eh, Nara?
Get up, Budi!
Hurry! Come on, hurry!
Marta!
We have to get out of here. Now!
Careful!
Don't move.
Its all over.
My friends, they're all dead.
Yet you're still here, alive!
Trust me, Budi!
Trust me!
I have to find Nara. You fix the car, okay?
Please..don't die!
- Please!
- I will try.
Help me, Alfie!
Nara?
Moloch..
You're in my world now, Alfie.
Nara?
This is not real.
Alfie!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Leo?
This is a dream, right?!
Alfie!
A dream, right?!
Kristi?
Jenar?
Did you see a girl..your age?
Alfie!
Nara?
Get out of there!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Nara?
- Alfie, I'm sorry.
You didn't do anything wrong.
Marta, she..
Marta wants you to be save.
Alfie!
We have to go now. Hurry!
Go! Hurry!
Let's go, Nara!
Alfie!
Nara!
- Nara! You go. Go!
- Let's go, Alfie!
Alfie!
You belong to him now..
Ayub! I'm not afraid of you!
Gadis..
This won't work, Alfie.
If you don't know how to use it.
Still, you're the perfect offering for Father.
Alfie! Get up!
Nara?
Alfie, you naive silly girl.
I can possess anyone!
Please..one last time..
Shatter you bones. Shred your flesh.
On my signal, you run straight to the ladder.
But we have to stick together.
Nara, you need to trust me, please!
Once I separate your soul from your flesh,
You'll be the ultimate offering for him.
Then, we can be forever together, Alfie.
Just like sisters..
Gadis!
Satani Levitas, you fuckin ghoul!
Alfie!
Alfie, hurry!
It's all over, Alfie.
Alfie, move away!
Budi! Budi!
You both okay?
Budi, don't!
Father!
Father don't leave me, please.
- Gadis?
- Don't!
Alfie, move!
Sister!
Nara!
Ayub, over here! Bastard!
Insolent!
Alfie? Are you okay?
We survived the devil. Remember, Nara?
Alfie!
Alfie, don't! No!
- Alfie, don't!
- I love you, Nara.
Alfie, don't!
Alfie, wake up! Please wake up!
Child, do you know where you are?
You.. You're Moloch?
Do you know where you are?
What is this?
You know what this is, the question is..
Are you ready?
Ayub. Where is he?
In eternal damnation.
Come on then!
Do it!
Are you so foolish, to escape from your own destiny,
even after losing so much.
Even after everything?
You choose to selfishly extinguish your own life.
As if your soul belongs to you.
As if your soul belongs to only you.
No!
Your filthy soul has been mine since you were but a child.
Only I shall claim it!
Your soul belongs to Moloch!
Alfie..
Alfie, let's go.
Budi.
Now you can start to find a decent job.
So, you can buy a nicer car. Okay?
Anyway, do we still need this?
Or is it too dangerous?
Dangerous? What's that?
Nara, seat belt please.