Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
I'm not gonna
suck your dick.
That's not what this is.
I don't do drugs either.
I'm just trying to help.
What about money?
You got any money?
No, I don't.
I thought you said
this was a shelter.
It is.
Looks like a house.
It used to be.
Let go.
Get the bucket.
Thomas.
Four hours,
commercial-free.
This next hit comes from
Miami's First Lady of Soul.
Miami's own Deep City Records,
released Helene Smith's
"I Am Controlled By Your Love",
almost...
No, it's still cold.
And it certainly
stood the test of time.
My name is AJ Steele,
and I invite you to join me
as we travel through the
best Soul Music of the '60s.
I can promise you,
you won't find it
anywhere else.
♪ My heart can't beat, baby ♪
♪ Unless you tell them to ♪
♪ My eyes can't see,
baby, baby ♪
♪ Unless you tell them to ♪
♪ There are things I should do ♪
♪ But I know it's just no use ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm controlled
by your love ♪
♪ I'm controlled by your love ♪
Can't sleep?
There we go.
So now,
the other airplanes
will know where it is.
They're called beacon lights.
Can I keep it?
Try it.
What else you got?
I need you to go.
Can we talk?
Okay.
What do you wanna talk about?
That's it?
I can't sell this stuff.
There's like ten shirts
in there.
Thanks.
Does that thing still work?
What are you doing
after work?
Can I get you something
to drink?
I'll have water
and a sweet tea, no ice.
No ice.
- Water.
- Great.
We're ready to order.
Okay,
what can I get for you?
I don't know what I want yet.
Okay...
How's the Denver
Omelette?
Ah.
I'm sorry,
I thought it would fit.
It's okay.
Now, the big one.
♪ If I reach out,
and turn off everything ♪
♪ There's much to blame ♪
♪ My word's in vain ♪
♪ And when they get out
and turn to everyone ♪
I'm not good at this.
Look at the screen.
♪ I surrender to fall,
but if at just one wake ♪
♪ I'd risk it all ♪
Get the blood!
There was a prostitute
working outside the diner today.
How do you
know she was a prostitute?
I've seen her before.
She'd actually be
a great catch.
She probably knows
a lot of people.
I doubt any of them
care about her.
Jessie, I don't know.
I don't think that I can keep
doing this.
He's our brother.
I know, I know.
Then, what is it?
He's sick,
he's not getting any better.
We shouldn't be doing the
things that we're doing.
So what do you suggest we do?
I don't know.
Don't worry,
there's more food.
Everybody's hungry.
You gotta eat, guys.
Hey.
Please leave
a message after the tone.
I heard some kids playing
outside today.
When?
When it was bright out.
You're not supposed
to be awake at that time.
You know this.
Sorry.
Why were you awake?
'Cause they woke me up.
What did you hear?
Voices, and...
and...
yelling, and laughing.
Do you think
they're still out there?
Everyone's asleep by now.
We should get some
work done anyway.
Do you ever think about
going somewhere else?
I need to get some ice.
Why do you ask?
Just thinking.
About leaving?
Maybe.
Maybe?
Yeah.
Well, where would you go?
I've never been to the beach.
I went to Miami once
in the '90s.
Yeah?
It's nice.
It's not what it looks like
on TV.
What's it like then?
It's crowded, hot.
But you can be naked all day.
Here.
Did you break it?
No.
There.
What if we just left?
To Miami?
Anywhere.
We could...
We could get in my truck and...
Okay,
time's up.
Equals six
over two.
It's quicker, you could...
- Yeah. Mm-hmm.
- Mm-hmm.
Okay, hands up.
1880.
- Mm-mm.
- No?
Try again.
Oh, 1875.
Dwight?
Huh?
Where were you?
I went to the thrift store.
I don't know, 1950?
You okay?
Yes.
Are you gonna leave us?
What?
I don't know what I'd do
if you left.
I'm not leaving.
I know this is hard
but we can't do it
without you.
It has to be the three of us,
together.
Do you understand?
Tomorrow, you'll go out again.
Yes.
And don't take
so long this time.
Okay.
You ready to order?
Hello?
Can I get 10
breakfast burritos?
Where are you from?
Uh...
What country are you from?
I don't understand.
Oh, right.
What's your name?
Uh... "nombre".
My name?
Yeah.
Eduardo.
Oh.
Dwight.
It's okay?
Yeah, it's okay.
It's good.
I just... have to get
something from the back.
Fuck.
Eduardo!
Eduardo.
Eduardo, come out.
Goddammit.
Stop!
Please.
Don't kill me.
Look at me!
I'm begging you.
Please don't kill me.
What the fuck?
Make sure you
mix well.
Then, you put in the oats
and blend.
What are you doing?
What happened to your leg?
This'll hold him over
for tonight.
I'll go out again
in a couple of days.
- Jessie!
- I'll be back in a few hours.
You can't.
Jessie.
Wait, Jessie!
Wait!
Fuck, fuck.
I'll take room 117.
Just one night?
Yeah, that's fine.
Hey, you don't have a wheelchair
I can borrow, do you?
It's fine, honey.
Oh yeah?
Hey.
Would you mind if
I used your bathroom?
Uh... my toilet's broken.
You look familiar.
Everybody tells me that.
I wouldn't ask
if it wasn't an emergency.
Okay, come in.
Thank you.
- Thanks.
- Mm-hmm.
Is this your blood?
Dwight?
I know it's messy
but I saved the blood.
What's wrong?
I noticed this
when she smiled.
I wonder how much it's worth.
Stop, stop,
stop, stop.
My sister's going to hear you.
That's a very bad thing.
Look, I wanna feed you
but you have to be quiet.
Sorry.
Here.
Let me go, asshole.
I won't tell.
I won't say anything.
I swear.
Who's this?
Is that your son?
Please let me go.
Your brother?
I don't even know that guy.
He was supposed to help me
when I got to this country.
He never did.
And now...
Look where I ended up.
Do you miss him?
I'm cold.
What is "frío"?
Well, okay.
I gotta get some ice.
I have this friend...
Had this friend, who was
always chewing on ice,
no matter how cold it got.
It was nice,
having someone to talk to.
People look so strange
when they're dead.
Please.
No, no.
I'm begging you.
I'm sorry.
Is Dwight gonna eat with us?
You know, I was thinking
maybe we could all
go out sometime.
Where would we go?
Anywhere.
I mean, I think it would
be good for all of us.
I was just telling Jessie
that I think we should all
go out somewhere together.
I'm too tired.
Okay,
I can go with Dwight.
There's no one out
at this time.
Not here.
Not anywhere.
No, that's not true,
that's not true.
It's three o'clock
in the morning.
I need friends.
- You have us.
- No, no real friends.
Not family, real friends.
You have no business
going out at this time...
I can make friends
with those kids
who are always outside.
I bet we'd be into a lot
of the same stuff.
Yeah, and where would
you find them right now?
Well, when tomorrow morning
when they're out there,
you or Dwight,
- you could go out and you can
- Can we talk about
tell them to come back
at night... Dwight.
something else?
Listen,
that's not happening.
Dwight, you could
tell them, right?
Right?
I don't know.
You don't know.
Hey.
I have a lot of things
to do tomorrow.
Okay, well...
No, Thomas.
No, what if we
just went around
for a little drive together,
- all of us, on a little...
- No.
You never listen to me.
What?
- That's not true.
- That is true!
Lower your voice.
Eat your food.
Jessie, please.
Don't.
Do you have any idea
what we do
to get that blood?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Do you have any idea
how stupid you are?
I don't wanna live like this.
We have to.
Oh, we have to.
I don't...
I don't wanna be sick.
Take me outside.
- It's late.
- I don't care.
So healthy, too.
It's a good idea to keep
your pantry full of them,
just in case
you get a craving.
Who is this?
♪ I'm controlled by your love ♪
♪ Oh, yes, I am ♪
♪ My heart can't beat, baby ♪
♪ Unless you tell it to ♪
♪ My eyes can't see, baby ♪
♪ Unless you ♪
♪ Tell them to ♪
Who was that
and why was he in our house?
♪ There are things
I should do, but... ♪
Who was that?
Answer me!
♪ I'm controlled by your love ♪
♪ Yes... I am ♪
♪ Now, I can't breathe, baby,
unless you ♪
I'm going to work.
Let it go!
Oh my God,
that's right.
Hey!
You're gonna get lost.
Yep.
I'm sorry about last night.
Would you get me some blood?
Ready to order?
Um...
Yeah, could I get the turkey
and Swiss toasted please?
Oh, and could we get
some of those chips?
No, sorry.
They don't
just come with the meal?
Only on Sundays.
The other girl always
just gives them to us.
You really should try smiling.
Holy shit.
Oh my God, oh my God.
Sorry to bother you,
excuse me.
Yeah.
Do you know how to
get to Murray from here?
Murray, sure, sure.
- At the next intersection,
- Mm-hmm.
just make a left.
You'll be on 700 East.
That'll take you all the way.
- Would you mind showing me?
- What's that?
Would you show me?
- Hey.
Thanks for coming.
Hey, I saw you
all earlier.
Do you wanna come in?
Hey, hey.
Hey, I'm Thomas.
I saw you earlier,
and I thought,
I thought you guys
wanna come over?
Hey, what took you so long?
Are you okay?
What was that about earlier?
Oh, I was just playing
with my brother.
And, uh... this?
Where are all your friends?
Why do you have
Christmas decorations up?
Oh, it was just Christmas
a few days ago.
It's April.
Would you like
to come inside?
So you get gifts in April?
Every month.
That's pretty cool.
Did you go to West High?
No.
I learn here at home.
Are you sick or something?
I just...
I've never met someone
who's homeschooled before.
Trust me,
you're not missing much.
Would you like to play a game?
Yeah, sure.
Sit.
I'll play a song.
You have to tell me
what year you think
it was written.
Okay.
Okay, hands up.
Why?
Because you have to have
your hands up.
I don't know.
I don't really know
music, man.
So are your parents home?
What is that?
Try it.
What are you
doing in here?
- No, Dwight.
- Who are you?
Dwight, please...
Answer me!
I don't know,
he invited me in.
That's true.
Don't move.
You shouldn't be in here.
No, let him...
Let him go.
No.
Who is he?
I...
He's my friend.
Go to the living room.
- No, Dwight, I...
- Now!
How did you get here?
My bike.
Come on.
Stay on the main roads...
Fuck.
Be quiet.
Now, we don't
have to go out for a while.
You gonna help me this time?
Huh, yeah.
Who spilled that?
Huh, oh.
We shouldn't waste it.
No, no, no.
Jessie, wait!
Don't open that door.
- Jessie?
- Get out!
Go get him.
No, we have to get you
to the hospital.
Get him.
- We have to go.
- Dwight.
I'm not leaving!
Go get him, kill him.
- I can't.
- Listen to me.
Listen to me.
If you let that kid go,
that's the end of us,
that's it.
Do you understand?
Go!
Is that your dad?
Yeah.
Is it just the two of you?
I know what
it's like.
To be alone.
You know what'll happen
if we see each other again.
Go.
I'm cold.
We shouldn't waste it.
I'm sorry for being
mean to you.
We're friends, right?
Yes, of course.
It's okay.
No.
No, Jessie.
No, Jessie, no, no.
No, don't go.
Don't go, Jessie.
Don't go.
Get off of her!
I'm sorry.
Thomas.
I'm leaving.
And I'm not coming back.
There you go,
can I get you anything else?
Uh... No.
Come on.
That's like more dirty
than funny.
Yeah, it is,
I told you it was awful.
Yeah, but like....
Thomas.
Hey.
I thought you left.
No.
I thought you weren't
coming back.
I'm here now.
I'm here.
I'm so sorry about Jessie.
No, it's okay.
That's okay.
Open the window.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull