We're all around you.
Living right under your noses…
And you have no idea.
Things were a lot simpler in the old days.
We hunted you,
and you hunted us.
In Los Angeles,
no one fought harder
than a place called Boyle Heights.
So, we struck up a truce
to maintain the peace
between our kind and yours.
We lived in secret,
and you convinced yourselves
you had never really believed.
You forgot to be afraid.
You made books and movies about us
and got most of the details wrong,
while we became richer
and more powerful
than you could ever imagine.
To this day, there are some
who still uphold the truce,
who keep our secret.
As long as we stick to the three rules.
Don't let humans know we exist,
don't feed on the unwilling,
and never ever enter Boyle Heights
without permission.
- Jay!
- Sorry.
- You scared me.
- I got distracted.
How sorry?
I'll-make-it-up-to-you sorry.
Oh, you'll-make-it-up-to-me kind of sorry.
How are you gonna do that?
What?
Nah, you look nice.
I look nice?
You're so stupid.
What the...
- What is it?
- They shouldn't be over here.
Oh my God. Jay, who is that?
A dead man.
Put the gun back.
We cannot do this.
Holy shit, please keep driving. Jay.
Jay, it's green, just go!
- Jay, what's going on?
- I gotta warn my guys.
I need you to take the car
and go to your brother's. Okay?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Maria!
Good morning, Mr. Perez.
What were you dreaming about?
Sorry. I…
Hey, uh, B-plus, 60 bucks.
Thank you, sir.
You're a lifesaver, you know that?
You're saving my ass with this paper, bro.
We're gonna check out
this club downtown, Three Kings?
Table, bottle service.
- Right.
- It's 300 a head. You wanna roll with?
Shit, 300 a head? Uh…
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Nah, I already got some stuff
I gotta get into.
- I bet you do.
- Next time, my bad.
All right. Stay easy.
Yo!
Yo, what's good, Benny?
Hey, what's up, slick?
You got that kit for me?
Let's call it an even 40, bro.
40, like 40 bucks?
That's what I said.
I'mma put The Heights
on the map. I'm telling you, bro.
Step one, finish this track.
Two, set up the label.
Three, world domination. It's simple.
Building an empire,
but you can't even play me one track, bro?
Hey.
When it's ready, it's ready, all right?
Hello, Benny.
Hey, Grandma.
You came at a good time.
Yeah? Why's that?
I just took out
some flautitas and some empanadas.
Nice!
Are you hungry?
- You know it.
- But why do I bother shopping
if you're never
going to cook me a sancoche?
You know I don't cook that.
You know that one of these days
I'm going to buy you a house.
I don't need
my own home, my love.
What I do need is for you
to finish your studies
so you can take care of yourself.
Because someday
I'm gonna die, and so will you.
Ay, Ma, why you gotta talk like that?
So negative. I don't like it.
Well, that's life, son.
We all come tumbling down.
Bro, you told me
you could handle it.
No, I told you. This is...
Come on, Jessie,
you're really gonna do me like that?
I need someone to cover the car tonight.
It's about Maria.
Yeah, well, I thought I could rely on you!
Yeah, fine, whatever.
Why are you creeping?
If I'd know you was coming through,
I would've rolled out the red carpet.
I have to pick up some things,
check in on Grandma.
- Check in on your punk ass.
- Ha.
Oh, wait a minute. What's this?
Bro, that some gray hairs on your head?
Hey, I'm serious.
You're getting old, papi.
Just wait. It's gonna happen to you too.
I don't know if you're working tonight,
but maybe we could go to Mario's,
grab a pizza, watch the game.
I got something else tonight.
All right,
then who's covering the car, then?
I had to cancel.
Everyone's booked up.
All right, but you see,
I was thinking, like, what if,
you see, what if I take the car? Right?
- 'Cause I could use the money.
- No way.
- Why not?
- One, you're a bad driver.
Bad… That's bullshit.
When was the last time
you were west of K-Town?
Hey, Jay, my man, look,
I am way more responsible
than all them dudes
you got out there at the depot.
Yeah, except them dudes at the depot,
they got chauffeur's license,
they're insured by the company,
and they actually own a suit.
I… You see, the thing is, though,
Jay, I got a suit. I got a suit, Jay.
What, you and Maria been fighting?
That's what it is?
You having some relationship issues?
If you want to talk to me,
you can talk to me.
I give great advice.
That's what people be saying.
Yeah, right.
Man, whatever.
Where'd you get that?
Don't worry about it.
- What's this thing you gotta do tonight?
- I said don't worry about it.
- All right. Fine, man.
- I didn't even…
So secretive, man.
Hey, Benny.
Scratch it, I'll kill you.
Yo. You serious?
Man! I'm gonna need me one of these.
You can't afford it.
Well, I'mma flip my beats,
and I'mma get me a better one.
- What do you think about that?
- Listen to me.
Take them where they need to go,
come straight back.
- Understand?
- Yeah, I understand.
Check it out.
Oh shit.
That's pretty cool.
Insurance and registration
are in the glove compartment.
Chauffeur's license on the visor.
Everything's under my name,
so if anyone asks, you're me.
- I'm going to Beverly Hills?
- Hey, pay attention.
If anyone asks, you're me, got it?
- Yeah.
- Dispatch says it's an all-nighter.
Probably a twentysomething
director wannabe high out of his mind.
Act professional, and he'll give you
a fat tip at the end of the night.
Hey. Don't blow the sub, Dr. Dre.
Look, if the subs want to bark,
you gotta let 'em bark.
No, the subs don't wanna bark. Okay?
I'm serious. I'll yank you out of here.
- I'll take the no-show penalty.
- Okay. No barking, you got it.
Thanks for doing this.
Hey, just, um, be careful, all right?
I'm always careful.
I got… I got the car!
Huh? What?
Oh!
That was a cop. That was a cop.
What? I went in front of the guy!
Wow.
Wow, wow.
Okay.
Um, good… good evening, Miss Moreau.
You're the driver?
Uh, yeah. Yes. Yes, I am.
Miss Moreau is running a little bit late.
I'm her friend Blaire.
Okay, cool. I'm… I'm… I'm Jay.
Hi, Jay.
Something wrong?
No.
Mm-mm.
What?
Your zipper is down.
Oh shit.
Wow.
Sorry, I… I… I don't…
I don't mean to be unprofessional.
I just… I should…
I had no idea that it was down.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
I'm just gonna stop talking 'cause I feel
like I'm making it worse now.
Well, how about you open the door for me,
and then maybe we can call it even?
Thanks.
You know, if you need me
to adjust anything, like the…
- like the AC, I… I can do that.
- Hmm?
Or… or more warm, if you're like…
if it feels chilly for you 'cause I know...
- Okay.
- You know, women's bodies...
Women's bodies?
I'm good. Thank you.
Like, I know
people get cold, so whatever...
Yeah. Thank you.
Yeah. I got you.
She's gonna be pissed
if you don't open the door for her.
Oh.
You're right. My bad. Thanks.
Hello, Miss Moreau.
I… I'm Jay. I'll be your driver tonight.
You're adorable.
Do you need help with your bags?
You don't look like a driver.
- Okay?
- Mm-hmm.
Uh…
Are you sure you know
what you're doing there, Jay?
Um, no, I was just trying
to put the address in.
Except I haven't given you
the address yet, have I?
Right. Yeah. I know.
We're hitting every one
of these parties tonight,
and we need to get
to the last stop by morning.
That's nonnegotiable.
Are we clear?
Yeah.
Oh, and Jay, can you turn the air on?
Yeah. Make it icy.
Hey, driver. You wanna put on something
that doesn't suck?
Yes, ma'am.
Actually, Jay…
let's play a game.
What would you do if you knew
tonight was your last night on Earth?
Wow, uh… I never really thought
about it, to be honest.
Okay. Well, think about it.
I mean, you must have some fantasies.
I don't… I don't really like
to think that way, you know.
Like, to fantasize?
Yeah, you know, it's like,
I'm doing things today.
I'm building things for the future.
You know what I mean?
- I'm not sure you understand how to play.
- I do. What I'm trying to say is...
Last night on Earth, Jay.
Drugs, women, men,
old enemies you're just waiting to pop.
Nah, sorry,
I'm a pretty chill guy.
You know,
I go to school, live with my abuela...
You live with your abuela?
- Yeah.
- That's cute.
New game. Fuck, marry, kill.
Me, Blaire, your abuela.
S… sorry, what?
- I know you know this game.
- No, I do. I… I know this game.
It's just, you know,
I'm trying to be professional.
- Look, Blaire. Me, the Pope, the driver.
- You're not even trying.
- Personally, I would bang me.
- Fine. Okay, you could get it.
Kill the Pope, which I guess
puts me marrying Jay, the driver.
- He seems like husband material.
- You hear that, driver?
Come on, fess up.
Me, Blaire, your grandma.
I'd definitely kill you.
Finally, he bites back.
Maybe he's not a total dud.
I don't know. Maybe not.
Hey, driver. Keep your eyes on the road.
Thanks.
Some party.
You wouldn't know a party
if it fucked you in the face.
What's up, G?
What's the word?
Three generations deep,
and I'm the one to break the peace.
That's on him. Not us.
Victor knows we're off-limits.
He's starting a war with Boyle Heights.
He took Maria… to get to me.
There's no turning back.
We have until tomorrow morning.
After that,
either Victor's dead, or we are.
Let's go put this work in.
Back in the car, driver!
Yo, Jay.
You want some?
Uh, I… I can't really do that.
- Sorry.
- You can't?
- I can't.
- That's boring.
Zoé!
- That's gonna be a fine.
- Oh, there's a fine?
- Yeah.
- Don't worry, driver. We can afford it.
Stay.
See you soon.
Hey, it's Jay.
Leave a message.
Yo, it's Benny. Um, look,
I don't know what you're up to,
but, um, I… I think there's
something… something weird going on,
and just whenever you get a chance,
just hit me back, aight?
Serious.
Whoa.
What the… Oh my…
Oh, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
Hey!
How may I help you, sir?
Hi. Uh…
- Sir, you are sweating.
- Oh.
- Is everything all right?
- Yeah, yeah.
- I, um… I was just…
- Mm-hmm.
- I… I was outside and...
- What's that on your shirt?
- Huh?
- Your shirt.
I…
I… I got, um…
This is a members-only establishment,
so perhaps I should call somebody.
- No, no, no, I'm fine. It's just...
- It's okay. It'll just be one second.
No, no, no, no, hey, hey.
It's… it's okay. I just… I, um…
Please accept
my most sincere apology, sir.
May I?
Yeah.
Mmm. Will you be meeting anyone upstairs?
Mm-hmm, yeah. I, um…
I'm… I'm meeting the… the two girls,
uh, Blaire and… and… and… and Zoé.
Of course, sir.
They're with Daniel and Max as we speak.
The owners, sir.
- Great.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
- Allow me to escort you to the elevator.
- Mm-hmm, yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
Please, I don't…
I don't… I don't have all day.
Should you need anything at all,
there's a phone located in your room
that links directly to my desk.
Myself or a member of my staff
will be happy to assist you.
And, please, drink responsibly.
Hey.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
H… hey.
- This isn't what it looks like.
- Okay. I'm just…
Oh my God.
He's shaking.
I love it when they shake.
It's so cute.
Max over there tasted like motor oil.
I bet Jay gives good blood.
Don't you, Jay?
I'm not Jay.
- What?
- I'm not Jay. My name's Benny.
- I'm just… I'm his brother.
- I'm just covering for him.
I knew it.
What did I tell you?
I knew this little shit
couldn't be Jay Perez.
All right.
Let's drink the driver.
What? No, no, no, no.
- I don't know. He could come in handy.
- Handy for what?
I don't need someone
to hold the door for me tonight.
- No.
- Wait, wait.
I bet he could take us to Jay.
Benny, do you think you could do that?
You think you could show us
where your brother is?
That was great.
Oh, is he okay?
Hey, Max, buddy!
- Did they go a little too hard on you?
- You had one thing to do.
- Just one.
- I know. I'm sorry.
I got a little distracted
because someone walked in on us.
Max!
Hey, what's wrong with him?
Max.
- What… what did you do?
- Max?
Hey, Max. You okay?
Yeah, man, I'm fine.
I'm living my best life.
Are you crazy? Is he…
- Is he...
- He's dead. Yes, Daniel.
Yes, he's dead.
I killed him.
- No, you can't do this.
- No?
We're protected. This place is protected!
You're protected?
How protected do you feel right now?
Hmm?
Blaire, finish your drink.
We're running behind schedule.
- Hey. You stupid bitches.
- Mmm.
They're gonna come after you for this.
The bosses will burn you alive.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
You can't kill in here. It's off-limits.
Oh, are those the rules?
You can't. You're gonna ruin this place.
Well, that's the point.
No more happy endings.
No, wait, hey!
Wait, no, no, no. Don't, please, wait.
You can't kill me.
You can't. What about the truce?
- The truce is dead, handsome.
- Wait. Wait.
Hey, uh, officer, listen. Um, I…
I need… I need your help. I… I got this…
It's an emergency.
There's these two women, right?
- And they're after me and...
- Two women?
- Mm-hmm.
- After you?
Yeah, I've been… I've been driving them
around all night, but I think that's...
Is there anything
you want to tell me about, son?
- No, listen, I'm trying...
- How much have you had to drink tonight?
- I haven't drank anything.
- Any drugs?
- No drugs.
- Weapons on you?
Listen, there's
this secret floor in there, okay?
There's this crazy shit
that's going on in there.
I need you to call backup.
I need you to call everyone, call...
Exactly what'd you see up there?
They killed these two guys, all right?
They were drinking their blood, man.
Okay, that's enough.
Put your hands behind your back.
Put your hands behind your back!
Hey!
Come on. Take… take me to jail right now.
Get me… get me out of here.
Mm-hmm. Let's go.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa. No, no.
- What happens upstairs stays upstairs.
- No. Okay.
- You should know better.
- Yeah, I'm not gonna say...
- Get in the trunk. In the trunk!
- I won't say nothing!
- I'm not gonna say anything!
- Excuse me, Officer Anderson.
You girls.
Yes, us girls.
This kid is saying
you killed two men upstairs.
- That can't be right, right?
- Of course not.
Benny here has no idea what he saw.
Do you, Benny?
We just gave those boys
the best suck they're ever gonna get.
Let him go. He's ours.
Yeah. Victor know about this?
What do you think, dipshit?
We're just making our collections.
Business as usual.
- Well, I didn't get a call.
- Oh, you didn't get a call?
Maybe you're not important enough
to get a call.
Yeah, maybe I should just call Victor now.
Why don't you do that?
I'm sure Victor would love to hear
from his favorite little piggy.
Hand him over.
Okay, all right. Fine.
Go turn the car around.
Huh? Hey!
No more funny games.
Wait! No.
Don't go! Wait! Don't leave!
Yeah.
Yeah, you count this out?
Back in the car, driver.
Hmm.
Don't get up. I know where the bar is.
- What the hell are you doing here?
- I'm having a drink with my bosses, Eva.
Better make it a good one.
- It's gonna be your last.
- I'll keep that in mind.
We told you what would happen
if you stepped foot in Boyle Heights,
and yet, here you are,
being reckless as ever.
Drinking blood cocktails
on white upholstery,
and I'm the reckless one?
You need to remember your place,
Victor. You're middle management.
Give me one reason
why I shouldn't call Martin right now.
- Because I've had a change of heart.
- What heart?
I deserve that.
This view never gets old.
Yeah. But now we're gonna have to ruin it
with your dead body.
I should have let her do
what she wanted with you.
I wanted to barbecue you
the moment you fed outside the lines.
But Grace said that would be impulsive.
I think the word I used was tacky.
Well, I'm glad you didn't.
I know you've never trusted me,
never given me any real power.
But if you hadn't tried
to run me out of my own city,
I wouldn't be seeing so clearly now.
- Are you on something?
- You violated the truce.
It's the one thing that's kept
our kind safe all these years,
and you just pissed on it.
For years we've been told
who to feed on and where
and treating humans
like they're our equals.
It started to feel like a prison.
So I got frustrated
and did something impulsive.
Should we say
tacky?
Tacky?
You fed where you weren't supposed to
and started a war with Jay Perez.
If he comes for us,
Boyle Heights will follow.
Do you like your fancy clothes
and your concrete mansion?
Because if we get exposed,
that all goes away. For all of us.
I know.
I put you two in a terrible position.
Do you think that I don't get frustrated?
Do you think that when my pool boy
leaves a leaf in the pool,
that I don't wanna string him upside down
and suck him dry?
But if I pitch a fit every time
somebody pisses me off,
what does that make me?
A man.
Stupid as shit.
Like I said.
I'm sorry.
No, a ban is a ban.
You're gonna have to do a lot better
than that if you want me to reverse it.
You know, forever is a very long time.
Give it 40, 50 years.
Who knows? Maybe this will blow over,
and you'll be able to come back.
Oh, I think you've misunderstood.
I'm not going anywhere.
In fact, my girls
are down there right now,
ripping your entire network apart
one neck at a time.
So, everything you see belongs to me.
After I kill both of you, of course.
Martin!
I, uh, think you might
have to speak up a little.
This is not real. This is…
Come on. She's here, then she's there.
- You need to calm down.
- Calm? Be calm?
- You want me to calm down?
- Yeah.
- I'm calm.
- Oh, you're calm?
- Yeah. This is me calm.
- This is you calm?
- You seem kind of worked up.
- What do you want me to do, huh?
I'm here… I'm here in this car with…
with you and whatever the hell you are.
Oh.
- This is… this is stupid.
- Oh, wow.
- I… I honestly...
- So dumb.
I don't expect people to understand.
- It's a lot. It's a lot.
- Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, especially for you.
What is that supposed to mean, huh?
It means you're a kid.
Like, you…
You… you think majoring in economics
is gonna solve all your problems?
Do you think
that this is how the world works?
Okay. All right.
Well…
Don't worry.
It'll all be over soon.
All over? All over? How?
Is… is my brother… is he like a, um…
No, it's not like that.
Then what's it like, then? What's it like?
Let's just say your people
and my people don't really get along.
Who do you think runs the city?
Cops?
Politicians?
We do.
We?
Right.
And… and our kind, like your kind,
answer to leaders.
All right.
There are five bosses that control
most of the major territories of LA.
- It sounds like the mob.
- Please. We're not amateurs.
Victor's, what, like, your boss?
Your boyfriend?
Oh, twist. Benny's the jealous type.
No, no, no. I just…
I don't… I don't know what's going on.
So, Zoé and Victor are together.
And then, Zoé's my girl.
So, she and I manage money
at the different businesses
and blood clubs.
- We manage the...
- Blood clubs?
Yeah, but Victor's sick
of not having any real power,
so tonight, we're making our move.
The problem is you can't make a move
against one of the bosses
without the rest of them
coming for your head unless you...
Unless you take them all out
at the same time. Same night.
Exactly.
And… and my brother?
Jay's crew runs Boyle Heights.
They know what we are and how to kill us.
Victor thought he could use him.
Just turn Jay's crew loose on the bosses.
Jay kindly instructed him to go to hell,
which Victor didn't like very much,
so the plan was for us
to bring Jay to Victor
after all of this was done.
That was the plan
until you showed up.
So, Benny, you know
where your brother is tonight?
Hey, no, you can't smoke that in here.
It's gonna…
It's gonna get in the leather.
That's funny.
Mmm.
You wanna hit this?
- Honestly, it might make you feel better.
- No, I'm… I'm okay.
Here. Let me.
So, how did it go?
Well, my shirt is ruined.
I think we might actually pull this off.
Yeah.
Three bosses down.
And two to go.
Ah, you should've seen
the looks on their faces.
I wish
I could've been there with you.
So, how's Jay?
Yeah.
About that.
I… I need to tell you something.
What is it?
We, um, got his little brother instead.
I'm sorry. We didn't know.
It's okay, baby.
It's okay. We can use the brother.
Really?
Really. It makes it more fun.
Think of him like insurance.
Okay, babe.
- Do you think he gives good blood?
- Yeah.
I think he gives real good blood.
I'll take care of Jay.
I don't want you to get distracted.
Clear downtown and Venice.
Then the city is ours.
We can't let them regroup after tonight.
You sure about this? I don't like him.
I don't even like breathing
the same air as this vato.
This is the only chance we got.
What if we don't know where Victor's at?
Gio made Victor.
He'll know.
- I want him alive.
- All right.
Shit.
What the hell happened in here?
Sweep the house.
Split up. Three and three.
Watch out.
Don't move. Move, I gotta put
this knife through your heart.
I don't think you want that, do you, Gio?
Right, baby. I don't want that.
Yo, what the hell happened to you?
Oh, don't look at me.
I look hideous.
- You know what I need?
- Hmm?
I need some blood.
Can you get me some blood, Jay?
First, you gotta tell me
where Victor's at tonight.
That snake.
He's coming for all of us.
All the bosses.
All the territories.
He's clearing the board.
Victor did this?
His girls did this.
- You know the ones.
- Haven't had the pleasure.
His little monsters
left me like this to suffer.
Hey. Hey, wake up.
Rise and shine, come on.
- I'm awake.
- Where were they going?
I'll tell you if you give me some blood.
You gotta tell me what they said first.
Three Kings.
Get the boys. We're going downtown.
But first, give me some blood!
Can you hear that?
What did I just smoke? I…
I feel weird.
Angel dust.
- What?
- Relax.
- I'm joking.
- Are you?
Uh, maybe. Maybe not.
Ask Blaire. She rolled it.
That girl really needs to get laid.
Well, that's a different kind of service
than the one this car company offers, but…
That's good, Benny.
Can I call you Benny Boy?
No.
You know, it's not your fault
that she likes you.
She likes everyone,
so don't feel special or anything.
Yeah, I know,
it's not… it's not like that.
I… I mean, I'm not…
I'm not saying she isn't attractive.
I'm just not really looking
for a relationship right now.
Is he looking at me?
Who?
The clerk.
I… I don't think so.
You sure?
Yeah, you know.
Nobody's looking at you, Zoé.
He's calling someone.
Zoé.
Zoé, chill, yo. Hey. Chill.
…three bodies appeared
to have been drained of all blood.
Wait.
Just a slushy?
- Yeah, just the slushy.
- Okay.
- Is that…
- Okay, that's gonna be two...
Who was on the phone?
- Do we really have to do this?
- Take the money!
Get out of here, okay?
I don't want any trouble!
You a tattletale?
What? You're insane!
- Get her off of me! Do something!
- Just do what she says, man.
- Who was on the phone?
- It was my mom!
Okay? She just wanted me to pick up
more cat food on the way home from work.
I swear to God. I just…
Jesus Christ, are those…
Shut him up!
Shut him up?
What do you mean, shut him up? No!
That's my girl.
Let's go.
What?
What is wrong with you?
You can't be alive for 200 years
and not go a little crazy.
What should we do with Benny?
I mean,
we can't just leave him in the car.
Hey, so, um, listen,
I… I got this idea, right?
And I… I was thinking,
maybe why don't I just go?
You guys can just take the car,
and… and… and… and I'll find my way home.
I'll find a bus.
- It sounds like you're trying to ditch us.
- No, I'm not...
Hey, you know what? I actually think
that's a really smart idea.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Yeah. You know,
'cause, you know, all… all this shit,
I'm not gonna say nothing about all this.
I just think this is a time where I feel
like we should go our separate ways,
and… and believe me, it was…
it was great meeting you guys, you know.
- It was great meeting you too.
- And the secrets, they're safe with me.
- It's me, you know.
- Okay.
Well, if he says
he's not gonna say anything,
then we can trust him.
Right?
Sweet. Uh, okay, great. I mean...
You're gonna stick around
a little while longer, Benny Boy.
We're not quite through.
You remember what I did
to that guy at the hotel?
I tore his neck open like a bag of candy.
If you do anything stupid inside,
I'll start stacking bodies.
I think what she's trying to say,
Benny, is we would love
if you came with us.
Good?
Fun! Fun!
Hey, uh, your friend over there?
Yeah, she's insane.
I'm talking next-level crazy.
Yeah. You wanna stay out of her way. Okay?
I gotta get out of here.
I can't do this shit.
I need you to be smart. All right?
If you do anything stupid,
like try and run or tell anyone about us,
I'm gonna have to kill you. Okay?
And I don't want to have to do that.
- Bruce!
- Hey.
You don't want to have to kill me.
Great, I mean, that's fantastic.
I'm looking out for you.
- You call this looking out for somebody?
- Benny! Come on.
- Hey.
- Excuse me.
- Benny?
- Go on, man.
Oh, no way.
Hey, um, do you think
you could help us out?
You know, tell them
that we're your friends.
Like, we're with you or something?
Please?
Sorry, I don't know. I… I just, uh…
He can't help you because he is the help.
I mean, look at him.
Looks like a butler or something.
Uh…
Oh shit.
I was right?
Benny has his hands full tonight.
Maybe find someone else to leech onto.
Do us a favor.
Send the Gen Z
off to the back of the line.
Back of the line. Let's go.
- You kidding?
- Wait. No.
- You heard me. Not tonight.
- Look, no...
What are you looking at?
I don't think
I've ever met anybody like you.
Well, don't get weird.
I was just trying to make you look cool.
Yeah, well, it worked.
I don't know why you care what they think.
I don't.
You're never gonna remember their faces.
They're insignificant.
What does that make me?
I guess we're gonna have to find out.
Whoa.
Busy night.
Yeah.
And not a lot of friendly faces.
Let's keep this cool and quiet.
- I hate going in quiet.
- Zoé.
You wanna get the bag, I'll get Big Lou?
Mm-hmm.
It might get a little messy in there.
Drink up. You won't feel a thing.
There'll be
a lot of sharp teeth in there.
Nobody makes a move
until we see Victor's girls, all right?
Y'all hear that?
Good evening, ladies.
Who are you? Where's Big Lou?
Big Lou is no longer with us.
Don't you recognize me?
I don't think we've had the pleasure.
I don't like this. We should move.
We're not going anywhere yet.
Lost a lot of friends
to things like you.
You don't remember me?
Remember what?
I gave you that,
but I didn't get to finish the job.
LA was always off-limits.
Yeah, I think it's brave
what you're doing,
stepping out on your own like this.
But, if you break the rules,
you lose certain protections.
I mean, with the truce falling apart,
it's open season on you freaks.
See my friend here?
She can drain your whole body
before you even pull the trigger.
You think I'm here alone?
Oh…
What were you saying?
Ah. Look at them.
For once,
they're helpless.
Kill them.
Who still uses crossbows?
Night Legion.
- What?
- You asked who still uses crossbows.
Night Legion does.
They like to hunt things like us.
They've been at it for centuries.
And Benny, like, totally bottles them
in the face, apparently.
Yes, he does.
Come on.
These scumbags are like cockroaches.
When there's one, there's many.
Benny!
Is there a problem?
- You know you're not allowed to be here.
- Move.
No.
Oh shit!
- We gotta get off the streets.
- Yeah, we need to lay low.
Is there some place safe you could take us?
No. We're not going anywhere
until I find out
where this Victor is
and what he wants from my brother.
Well, look at you.
Benny Boy. Making demands
like he's running the show tonight.
Yeah. Yeah, I am.
I like you, Benny.
I think you're kind of sweet,
so I'm gonna let you in
on a little secret.
Victor's gonna find Jay tonight,
and when he does, well…
Well? Well, what?
Well, if you stick with us,
then maybe we could get to Jay first,
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
and we could convince Victor
to go easy on him.
So, Benny, what's it gonna be?
You wanna see your brother,
or you wanna piss off?
Shit!
Run!
Come on! Try and get me, dickheads!
Crazy night, huh?
Tell him to put his gear down.
It's all right.
You see the light now, don't you?
I heard what they did to your girl.
I know what that's like.
We all do. That's why we're out here.
We got resources. We got a network.
Wake up, Jay.
You can't beat them on your own.
Yeah, I don't wanna beat them.
I want Victor.
Okay.
If you survive the night,
come find me.
Hey, uh, Benny?
Are you sure that we're safe here?
Yeah, of course. Nowhere safer.
I've lived here my whole life.
- I know, I just meant maybe...
- Listen, um…
So, my grandma works nights,
but sometimes she comes home early.
So, all I'm asking
is that you guys be quiet, please.
- I got it. Yes.
- You got it?
We will be on our best behavior.
Right, Zoé?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Well, this is quaint.
- Shh.
Hey! It's me!
Oh my God!
I almost killed you!
All day by myself!
If you're gonna be studying...
Hello.
Can you please put the bat down? Please?
- Where have you been?
- I...
These two
don't look like college students.
Look, I…
I lost my phone and, uh…
Blaire, Zoé, this is my grandma, Rosa.
Grandma, this is Blaire and… and Zoé.
- 'Sup?
- Hey.
Okay. Good night now. Have a nice evening.
Listen, they're waiting for a ride,
so I was thinking maybe they could,
you know, wait here a bit.
What happened to your hand?
No, it's fine.
I'll get a Band-Aid...
What Band-Aid? No Band-Aid!
- You're gonna need stitches!
- Ma, it's okay. It's okay.
Who did this to you?
Nothing. It was an accident.
Yo, that was a bloodbath, G.
We keep going like this,
it's suicide for sure.
Damn.
Hands on the dash.
Eyes forward.
You. You got any weapons
or drugs in the vehicle?
No, sir.
Hey. Hands.
- My ID.
- I don't need to see that.
I know who the two of you are.
Victor would like to meet for a drink.
Rosso Puro.
Thirty minutes.
We're free to go?
Oh yeah. I almost forgot.
Benny says hi.
How did this happen to you?
Grandma, that is a long story.
But I swear I'll tell you later.
Okay?
Do they speak Spanish?
I don't know.
Is this little Benny?
Yo, put that back.
No. It's so good.
You know,
Benny's never brought a girl home before.
- Let alone two.
- Abuela, seriously?
What?
Can I help you out with that?
I… That's okay.
I… I think we're fine here.
Thank you, dear.
Yeah, all right,
you know what? I think we're good here.
You know, I feel good.
Hand feels good. Uh…
You… uh, you… you… you feel good?
Do I feel good? You woke me up
in the middle of the night, Benny.
I'm… I'm sorry, but maybe
you should get back to sleep?
I like this one better
than the other one.
But be careful.
I don't need great-grandchildren.
Good evening, Rosa.
It was a pleasure.
- What's wrong, baby?
- We got jumped downtown.
Night Legion was all over us.
At least they took care of Big Lou.
How many did you kill?
Three.
Maybe four. Boyle Heights was there too.
I thought you said
you were gonna take care of Jay.
Don't worry.
I'm on my way to meet Jay.
Just stopped for a drink.
Okay.
I don't know. I'm getting worried.
This night's going sideways.
We can't stop now. We're nearly done.
I'm gonna drain the kid.
I'm gonna smother the grandma,
and we can hit Venice tomorrow.
We need to clear Venice tonight.
Rocko is too unpredictable.
If we mess this up,
there will be no tomorrow.
Venice is the last kill.
I know you can do it.
Just keep a hold of the kid,
and we'll party at dawn.
The world will be ours, babe,
just me and you.
Yeah.
Let's get it done.
Now,
where were we?
It's kind of cool.
Huh.
All right.
This is super cool.
Yeah, all right.
You… you can put that down.
Sorry.
This is all just leftover
from when I was a kid.
I was gonna get rid of all of this stuff.
I haven't really had the time to upgrade...
Yes. Did you build all of this?
Yeah, but you know,
can we just maybe turn this down...
Mm-mm. No.
Why not?
'Cause I like it.
I think it's really good.
I mean, I'm assuming
B's Session Number Three, that's you?
Oh yeah. You know,
this is actually… it's a… it's a classic.
Oh, this is a classic?
Oh yeah, yeah. Everyone says so.
- Oh, everyone says so?
- Mm-hmm.
People, like who?
You know, people like… my grandma?
Yeah.
So, when are you gonna play this
for other people?
Well, I'm planning on it. I… I want
to do something… something with this.
It's more than fun.
I wanna turn it into something real.
And when I do, you know,
then you could tell people
that you're my first fan.
- So, in a way, you're welcome.
- Oh, I can?
Yeah, you know, if you want.
Well, I mean, for what it's worth,
I believe you. It's really good.
You're really talented.
And you're a very good driver.
- Thanks.
- Mmm.
Well, what… what about you?
What about me?
You know, is there anything that you like?
Anything you're passionate about?
I mean, like, in a past life.
Zoé and I are always talking
about, like, the shit we're gonna do.
- You know?
- When did you two meet?
Um…
She had this place
in Laurel Canyon in the '70s,
and she would throw these parties.
So, they would go
for like three or four days.
Everyone was there. And she loved Bowie,
so she had this, like…
the Bowie haircut, you know.
She was cool, man.
The queen bitch, that was her.
Yeah, that checks out.
And I was, like, just like a stray
when I first moved here,
and I didn't feel like I fit anywhere.
And it was like she saw me.
She told me everything could be beautiful.
She said a bunch of stuff.
And then she turned me,
and she gave me this life.
Honestly, you should take this
to a producer.
- Yeah.
- You could make real money.
I know, I know, it's just
I don't think it's where it has to be yet.
Where does it have to be?
What's it missing?
It's missing a little something
before it becomes like a...
- Like, what? A classic?
- Yeah.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Mmm.
- Yeah, a classic.
We need to leave.
Yeah. Cool.
Hi.
We're done with Benny, right?
He can stay here.
I don't think so.
- Well, this has nothing to do with him.
- He's coming. That's how it's gotta be.
Why are you being like this?
Do you want to be the one to tell Victor?
Hey.
I'm coming with you.
Good.
Let's go.
Anything happens to me,
you take care of Benny.
You protect him.
Consider it done.
Where's Benny?
Jay. So glad you could make it.
You put a hand on him or Maria,
I swear to God...
Is that her name? We'll get to her.
But first, sit.
- Where are they?
- Sit.
It's funny to think, though.
Almost a hundred years ago,
my kind sat across from your kind,
much like you and I right now.
And then they came up with that truce.
Well, you broke that truce.
You took people from my neighborhood.
Innocent people.
Did you think we were gonna let
you get away with that?
We? Who's this "we" you're talking about?
Everyone's gone. I had them all killed.
You should have taken my offer.
Now it's all going to be mine.
You see, you're the last piece.
Once you're gone,
this city's just one fat neck
waiting to get sucked.
You want me?
Fine. Fair game.
Maria and Benny
have nothing to do with this.
Let them go.
That's not how this is going to go.
Nobody walks.
You know that.
How do I look? Do I look okay?
Do you want some?
I saved her for you.
Your sweet Maria.
What?
I saved her for you, Jay.
No. No.
Don't go soft on me now.
We haven't even gotten started yet.
Last kill.
Let's do this.
Maybe lean close. This guy's a freak.
Look what the night dragged in.
Couple of strays.
Good morning, Rocko.
No such thing as a good morning.
Mmm, maybe not for you.
I don't know you, do I?
No, but I'm… I'm with them.
That doesn't really change
your problem, amigo.
- I don't know you.
- Don't worry about him. He's cool.
Yeah, chill, he's with us.
You cool?
Cool, dude.
Rough night?
You look a little, uh, banged up, bro.
Yeah, I'm… I'm a little banged up, bro.
Oh, I'm just messing with you, man!
I'm goofing!
Mi casa es su casa!
Enter at your leisure.
- Madam.
- Mmm.
Oh, you smell nice.
You give good blood, don't you?
I can tell.
I have a nose for these things.
I see things, man.
Visions.
Some people say
I'm like a… like a psychic or something.
- Yeah, I… I bet they do say that.
- They do.
Rocko.
Yes?
Not this one.
Oh, whatever, man.
I'm not into virgins. You know that.
- I'm… I'm not even a...
- Hey. Don't lie, man.
Third eye sees all.
This is weird.
You guys didn't call.
You showed up unannounced.
Is this like a booty call or something?
I'm not that kind of girl.
We just wanted
to surprise you, Rocko.
What, you don't like surprises anymore?
You know I love surprises.
Surprises are tight.
Do you want to leave us for a minute?
Yeah.
Yeah, why don't you guys, uh,
leave us to it for the minute
and go out to the pool?
Let the grown-ups, uh, conversate.
We'll be out there soon.
Bye, virgin.
Drink?
What?
I don't know how you could be
so chill about all this.
You know? It's like,
you're out here every night
doing this Kill Bill-type shit.
It's crazy.
- It's kind of… it's kind of crazy.
- It's not every night.
- It's not?
- No.
If I'm still alive tomorrow,
I am sleeping all day.
- Mmm.
- Sounds nice.
Mmm.
It is.
What's it like?
Hmm?
You know.
Honestly…
Sometimes it feels awesome.
You can do whatever you want.
You don't have to hold back.
You're completely free.
Sometimes.
I just killed this dude an hour ago.
Mm-hmm.
Fresh type O.
Clean blood.
Can't beat it.
Cheers.
So,
what's with the late-night hang?
You girls never cross the 405.
We were in the neighborhood.
Figured we'd stop by.
Knew you'd be up late.
So, you got any family?
I got Zoé.
She's got me.
No, but like…
like real family.
You know, my, uh…
My grandma scooped me up
after my mom passed,
and it was me, and it was her,
and it was Jay.
And Jay, he… he…
He took care of me.
He… he didn't have to.
You know, he's… he's just my half brother,
but he's… he's like
the only father I've ever had.
I'm sorry.
You're not like her, you know? Like Zoé.
I mean, I… I see you, you're…
You're alive.
Can I ask you something?
Are you gonna kill me?
No.
I don't want you like that.
So how come
you never come to visit anymore?
We had a good thing going back then.
Reagan was president.
Shit, it was that long ago?
- Mm-hmm.
- Wow.
Time flies.
What?
Is something wrong?
No. No. Nothing wrong.
Oh, it just hit me.
Maybe just this one thing.
The part where you and Victor
decide to kill and steal
from your own blood.
You wicked bitch.
Oh, you bloodsucker.
What?
- I have to tell you something.
- What happened?
Your brother. Victor has him.
Benny, get the car.
Tango down!
Drive! Drive!
Babe, you're okay. We did it.
I'm sorry.
The night's over.
We'll go home, and you'll be okay.
Benny, she needs blood.
Oh God.
We have to get to the last stop.
Okay. Okay.
- Okay, let's get her inside.
- No. Hey, you take the car and run.
- Okay?
- What are you talking about?
This is Victor's house.
Okay, and he has Jay,
so I'm not going anywhere.
I'm sorry. Okay?
I'm sorry, I am. But it's too late.
No, it's not too late. If there's a chance
that he's in there, then I'm going in!
You're dead the second you go in there.
Don't you understand?
Not if you help me.
It's over.
Promise me.
Okay. Come on. Come on, come on, come on.
You're good.
All right. Ready? Ready?
Okay. Come on.
Jay.
Hey, Jay.
Hey. Hey, yo, Jay.
Hey, it's me. It's Benny, hey.
You see me? Hey.
I'mma get you out.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I'mma… I'mma…
I'mma get you out of here.
I'mma get you out.
Look who's decided to join us.
Benny.
Did you miss us? You missed us.
I'm sensing some tension here.
Yeah, Benny's had a busy night.
I've heard so much about you.
Why don't you join us? Take a seat.
- I'd rather stand.
- Oh.
So, tell us, Benny.
What are you doing here?
I'd like to make a deal.
Let Jay go. Take me instead.
It's an interesting proposal.
Benny.
Hey, Blaire.
What's wrong?
I didn't say anything.
Benny, have you ever tried fresh blood?
There's nothing like it.
I remember when I first came here.
The blood tastes different.
I had to get used to it.
I had to develop my palate.
Now I can't get enough.
After considering your proposal,
unfortunately,
I'm going to have to decline.
But here's my counteroffer.
Because I run things now,
you will be our appetizer.
Jay will be our main course.
And I think I'll save abuela for dessert.
Hey! Don't you fucking touch him!
What are you doing? He saved us tonight.
Well, then I guess
we'll make it quick, then.
Hold him down. It's time to drink.
- Don't.
- Oh. This is interesting.
She's just confused.
- You're not confused, are you?
- Not at all, actually.
Hey.
Everything's okay. What's going on?
- We won! We won!
- We won?
Blaire, stop. You don't gotta do this.
- I'll tell you when you can talk!
- I don't work for you anymore.
So I'm not gonna listen
to any more of your crazy bullshit.
You're gonna let him
talk to us like that, Blaire?
I can't do this.
No, no, no, no!
Everything is finally good.
- We're finally good.
- I'm telling you, I'm done.
Hey! I need you.
I can't do this without you.
I don't want to do this without you.
- I want out. Oh!
- No, Blaire, no!
You were nothing!
I made you! I made you!
You can't leave me.
- You need me.
- Not anymore.
- No!
- Look at what you did, Benny.
Look at what you did.
She's had a weak heart.
Put her out of her misery.
This was supposed to be our night.
No.
Night's over.
Benny.
Jay?
- Hey. Jay.
- Run.
- Jay. Where is he? Where is he?
- Run. Run. Now.
It's a trap. Benny...
Benny, you're okay. No, Benny. Benny.
Hey. No. You're okay. You're okay.
It's okay.
Here.
- I, uh, spoke to the depot.
- Right.
"Jay, you can never ever drive
for the company again."
- I told you not to scratch it, fool.
- I did a little more than a scratch it.
Yeah, you did, man. Yeah, you did.
But, um, I wouldn't be here
eating this fine slice of pizza
if it weren't for you.
Well, you'd do the same for me so…
Things are gonna be different, you know.
The whole world's changed.
And everyone's gonna have to take a side.
Just don't forget where you came from.
I know where home is.
Oh, I, uh, left you a little something.
Come on. Ask him what happened.
Yo.
Benny, man. Hold up.
What's up?
Where you been, man?
We see you at the club,
and then you went MIA.
Yeah. Um, Benny.
Are you okay?
Never been better.
Hey.
Get in. We're running late.
Yeah, I gotta go,
but I'll see y'all later, yeah?
- Yeah.
Y'all want a ride?