NETFLIX PRESENTS
Hey!
Is anybody there?
Jesus Christ...
Grab my hand.
Reach out.
All right.
Try again.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Come on!
I'll get some help.
30 YEARS LATER
Dust it off.
Morning, guys.
Time to get out and get rid
of all the unnecessary stuff.
You know what I mean.
Just as the rules say.
Follow me.
All electronic devices, please!
- Julek Rosiejka.
- Spell it.
- R-O-S-I-E-J-K-A.
- Just kidding.
Sokołowski.
Like the sausage brand I don't like.
- Next!
- Kowalczyk.
- Thanks.
- Czajka.
- Move! We have things to do.
- Hold on!
And the tablet.
Come on. Chop chop!
- And if it gets lost?
- You get lost.
Aniela Turek.
- Wait!
- Aniela Turek.
- I'll take it.
- Check.
Wójcik.
- Speed it up! Name?
- Wrońska.
Why so sad? You are at camp.
- Zosia Wolska.
- Another one.
Take your luggage and gather here!
Move along, buddy. Come on.
Next.
Take your luggage off the bus!
Chop chop!
Put some life into it. Move it!
Some of you are here
for the second or even the third time.
Robert.
I am not surprised.
It makes me happy, though.
You know it's worth it, and it's fun.
I want this camp to be
kind of a holiday for you.
We'll have fun. We'll make new friends.
We'll enjoy nature
while dealing with our problems.
Why are you here?
Because you're addicted
to your smartphones and laptops!
To electronics, to technology!
Is it really so hard be offline?
This camp will demonstrate
that apart from it being easy,
it is awesome, pleasant and fantastic!
You'll learn new skills.
You'll rediscover yourselves.
Kids, a hearty welcome
to our offline survival
and trekking camp, Adrenaline!
Bravo!
- Here you go.
- Draw your numbers!
Go on.
The numbers represent
different groups.
What's the best one?
Each group
has a different task,
but there is one goal
and common objective...
Adventure!
You'll be off into the wild, on your own.
Away from civilization.
- I'm four, too.
- Facing the wildlife dangers
every step of your way.
You will meet savage beasts.
Maybe even some local madmen.
A week of adventure, great fun,
and many opportunities.
All of which is going to be offline!
Adrenaline!
It's out of tune. Check it out.
Robert.
- Mustard only.
- Is there any vegan sausage?
Fuck, I don't eat meat!
It's all right.
Play it.
- With mustard.
- Mustard and ketchup for me.
- Smaller or bigger sausage?
- A bigger one.
Let's sing together now.
- Ketchup? Mustard?
- Mustard.
You all know this one.
- With bread or without?
- With.
- Join in.
- With bread.
A week off Instagram is really cool.
You don't get the updates
about who's in New York,
in Bali, in Sri Lanka,
who's running the marathon,
who's having halibut
with sun-dried tomatoes and green pepper.
This makes me feel stupid,
because I only run
when the elevator is out of order.
I stay home and eat pasta with ketchup.
Mmm.
And here you know nothing.
Pure detox.
Hey.
Ewa, come on!
Attention, campers!
Fifteen minutes to lights-out!
ADRENALINE
OFFLINE TREKKING CAMP
Wake up!
- Hot water is on!
- Coming!
That's my toilet paper!
MEN'S ROOM
God Almighty, I'm asking you,
through the blessed virgin
and all the holy angels,
grace us with the will
to chase away the evil
from those young hearts
addicted to dangerous technology.
Through the passion of our Lord Jesus,
His holy blood which He shed for us,
through His wounds and His agony.
Jesus, send down your angels,
so they may drive, uh...
the sinister forces of civilization
into the depths of hell.
Let your kingdom
enter the hearts of your servants
and relieve them of their evil addictions.
Hi!
I'm Iza, the leader of your group.
Girls, are you comfortable?
Thank you.
We're off for a three-day hike.
It's a heck of a trip,
so we stay close, we make an effort,
we keep up, and no one lags behind.
Is that clear?
Who is the slowest one in the group?
And why is everyone looking at...
What's your name?
- Julek.
- Julek?
He'll surprise you all, you'll see.
Well, off we go!
Hi, there.
Your necklace looks just like T-800.
Excuse me?
T-800. Arnold from The Terminator.
Oh.
No, it's just a family memento.
But it really looks like T-800.
And you look a bit like Sarah Connor.
Wasn't she a blonde?
I mean your face.
"I'm a cybernetic organism.
My mission is to protect you."
"I'll be back."
- Do you practice any sports?
- Nope.
- Do you?
- You know...
- Not much.
- You look athletic, though.
You know...
In my spare time...
Right!
Gym and pool every day,
and weekend marathons?
Yeah.
A bit of swimming,
a bit of cycling.
Hey, Daniel?
What?
- Are you a selfie fan?
- Jesus!
What?
Do you like taking selfies?
- Fuck off, pal.
- You do, don't you?
Do you shave your legs, too?
Bartek, let him be.
- Daniel?
- I'll shave yours.
Cyclists shave.
Maybe you are a pro.
- Bartek!
- Maybe you like sucking dick.
Jesus... Bartek!
- Are you nuts?
- What was that?
Everything okay?
You're no better than him.
Okay...
All right. Let's get it cleaned up.
Right, so... enough.
Give me two of those.
You're not so eloquent now, are you?
Okay. Uh...
And now...
Gosh, I have no scissors.
All set. Let's move.
Can you get up?
- Sorry.
- I got carried away.
Can I go for a quick pee?
Hurry up.
Let's get ready.
Backpacks on.
Help me.
Oh, shit!
Fuck me!
Shit.
Hey! Come over here!
- Hunters?
- Nope.
Not hunters.
A carnivore of some sort.
A big one.
Fifteen thousand people
disappear in Poland each year,
a third of them in the woods.
- We can add to the statistics.
- That's not funny.
Is this your first time in a forest?
- Relax.
- That's right.
Animals don't attack for no reason.
And Totter-Tot will protect us.
Let's move on!
Ew.
That deer was something else,
wasn't it?
Have you watched
An American Werewolf in London?
It goes like this...
Two guys go hiking through the woods,
just like us now.
They walk and hear a kind of growling.
Like a dog or a hare or a wolf.
They ignore it and walk on.
And there's that growling again,
kind of circling them.
They keep walking,
and one of them gets attacked!
He gets his arm bitten off...
Daniel?
Yeah?
I have no idea how to do it.
Maybe like this?
I'll do it.
I need to bathe.
I feel icky after that walk.
Julek, why are you here?
- Gaming.
- Computer gaming?
Console gaming as well.
Go on, Julek.
Everyone shares.
Go on.
I play games.
I'm the second-best player in Poland.
I stream. I run a YouTube channel.
- I was going to fly to...
- How many subscribers?
- ...Korea for championships, but...
- I have a channel, too.
- Exactly 900,334.
And you?
- More or less the same.
- Julek, go on.
You mentioned Korea.
Uh...
I was planning to take part
in the championship games,
but my parents cut me off the internet
and sent me here.
- On probation.
- There are camps in Korea, too.
Joke.
You can win half a million dollars.
So, you dropped out of school because...
you spent too much time on the web.
Who else had problems at school
for the very same reason?
Nobody.
Just like I thought.
And I heard that all of you did.
And it's Zosia's turn.
Zosia Wolska.
What have we here?
Zosia.
Uh, Zosia...
Um...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Let's leave that for tomorrow.
Or whenever you'd like. Okay?
- Did you hear that?
- What is it?
Something's out there.
- Sit!
- Ow!
Stay put.
Miss Iza?
- Yeah?
- Be careful.
Good idea.
What a cutie.
A little fox.
- I wish you'd seen him. Enough for today.
- You all shit your pants.
Bedtime!
Puffety puff.
That's better.
Jesus.
Wanna give me a heart attack?
I can't sleep with all that noise.
What noise?
All those crickets, owls,
ticks and whatnot.
Uh-huh.
And how about you?
- Just chillin'.
- So I see. Give me a hit.
You smoke?
We have similar names.
- Really?
- Mmm-hmm.
Daniel, Aniela. Add a D, take away the A.
Coincidence? I don't think so.
Do you have a girlfriend?
No. I mean, yes.
Sometimes.
You know how it is.
No, I don't.
Well...
I date several girls.
Depends on the day.
I've got something, too.
You know what it is?
Mmm-hmm.
So?
- Meaning?
- You want me to help you?
No, there's no need... I mean, uh...
No.
I don't need help.
What's wrong?
Nothing. Uh...
You're gay?
No.
I just...
It's the nerves.
I don't know...
No!
You're a virgin?
- And you said you had someone.
- I did.
- Over the internet.
- Mmm.
So you've had cybersex only?
Sorry.
In that case, call me "Teacher."
How was it?
I need to crash.
But we'll do it again, right?
We'll see. Goodnight!
Thanks.
Wait.
Let's get this out.
Right.
Before falling asleep.
Oh.
Mmm...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Julek! Wake Zosia and Daniel up.
- He's not here.
- What do you mean?
He is not here.
He's not in his tent.
- Maybe he went to shave his legs.
- So where is he?
Anyone seen Daniel?
- Did he say he was leaving?
- How should I know?
- Who's seen him last?
- Maybe something happened to him?
All right.
Who was the last person to see him?
Me. We sat by the water together.
And?
"Now I'm pregnant."
Show me the exact spot.
Uh, that's not mine.
- What else did you two do?
- Nothing.
You had to do something.
We sat. We chatted.
I went to bed.
That's cool.
- What did you talk about?
- Just piss off.
- Why won't you tell me?
- Fuck off.
Hey!
Take a look.
Looks like blood.
- That's massive.
- What's up?
Blood.
No, that is...
- What?
- That is probably sap.
- Sap of that color?
- Sure. Lots of trees secrete juices.
What are they called?
- Their color is similar to...
- They don't grow in Poland.
- They sometimes do.
- Like where?
- Like here.
- That's blood.
No.
No. That's...
Listen, stop panicking, all right?
- We should look for him.
- Or head back.
Okay, go back. We'll look.
Let's take a vote. I say we get back.
Stop panicking. All right.
Bartek and Aniela stay here
in case Daniel shows up.
Don't go anywhere. Clear?
- Zosia and I will look around.
- So we split up?
- We have to.
- Can I say something?
- Be brief.
- In horror movies,
when groups split up, people die.
- Julek, please!
- Relax.
I'd feel more relaxed
if we called the police.
We have no phones.
If we don't find him in an hour,
we'll head back to base. Clear?
- Yeah.
- Let's go.
- And what about me?
- I don't know... Stay.
Wait for the police.
What a bummer.
Daniel!
- Can I say one more thing?
- No!
In horror movies,
there are six deadly sins.
Curiosity. "I wonder what's inside.
Let's take a peep."
Disbelief.
"It's just my imagination.
No need to fear."
Confidence. "I'm going inside.
Why shouldn't I?"
That was number three.
Number four,
unattractive people never survive.
Five, sex.
Sex is a death sentence.
And six, splitting up,
just like we are doing now.
Let me.
Thanks.
What if they don't come back?
Why shouldn't they?
No idea.
Hypothetically.
If we were to be left alone here...
what would you do?
Hmm...
What's that?
Let's get in.
- But it's private property.
- Julek!
Give it a break.
Maybe they've seen Daniel.
I won't squeeze through.
Hello?
What a fucking mess.
Good morning!
Is anybody here?
Excuse me.
No one's here. Let's get back.
- Did you hear that?
- Yes.
Oh! Hi, little one.
Wait, wait...
Miss Iza...
Zosia, be careful.
Oh, Jesus.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Someone's coming!
Let's fucking run!
- He's coming!
- Hide! Quick!
Someone's fucking coming!
Quiet!
Be quiet.
- Calm down. Get a grip.
- Fuck.
Quick!
- I can't climb!
- Julek!
- Hurry up!
- You can squeeze through.
Hurry!
Miss Iza!
Run!
Come on, you pimply dumbass!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Fuck...
- Miss Iza?
I always knew I was gay.
You just feel it.
But I still need to hide it.
Try being gay in this country.
It sucks.
Don't take it to heart.
Seriously?
You're a nice, intelligent guy.
I am constantly being labeled, too.
A dumb bimbo, a blonde.
Just good enough for a fuck.
But I just ignore the rules,
and I'm happy with it.
But deep inside...
I wish I could find...
true love.
A real true love.
Is he chasing us?
Now what?
I don't know.
Game over.
It's fucking over.
What are we going to do?
Fucking locals, Poland "B."
What is this? What am I doing here?
I told you all not to come here!
- But nobody listened! I want to go home!
- Julek!
Get it together.
Julek...
It will be all right, okay?
Just calm down.
- We should go back for Daniel's phone.
- No, let's not do that. Please.
Okay, listen. Here's what we'll do.
We move on. We find some help.
We can do this.
Promise?
Promise.
My father is blind to everything...
He'd sooner believe I was
a far-right extremist than a faggot.
I guess that's his fantasy of me.
Even when I invite a boyfriend home...
he thinks it's just a friend.
If I ever grabbed the friend's butt
in front of him,
he'd be likely to think... I don't know.
He'd take it for a macho goodbye.
The guy is...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
so fucking out of touch with reality.
Let's get back to Aniela and Bartek,
if they're still alive.
- Don't say that!
- We wouldn't find them anyway.
We have no idea where we are.
We're running in circles.
Even if the fat guy doesn't kill us,
starvation will.
I can't imagine us fishing,
eating moss, hunting, or mushroom picking.
Poor Miss Iza...
Shut it!
Hello?
Open up!
Morning.
Will you help us?
Our friends are dead.
There was an accident. We need help.
Will you let us in?
The door!
Is there a phone here?
We need to make a call.
Tell me what happened.
I don't know how to say it,
as this will sound weird...
- You won't believe us anyway.
- I've seen many strange things.
We found this fucking huge man,
all crooked and deformed.
He attacked us, and then killed
our friend and our guide.
What? "Killed"?
Something is fucked up
and people are dying.
Have you been drinking? Taking drugs?
No.
All right.
Calm down.
I can't calm down!
I need to call the police or somebody!
Or else we're doomed.
Sit down.
I don't have a phone.
I have a mobile.
But we're out of range.
Let's try the landline.
No signal.
We've been having
some violent storms recently.
Maybe we should go
to the police station together.
But you claim that people
are getting killed.
So would that be really safe?
Calm down.
Come on.
There.
Hi, again.
I remember you from last year.
I know your kind.
Clingy.
Enticing.
Ready to lure others in.
You are a bit like...
the plague.
Wait here.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Jesus!
You don't know who you're dealing with.
I first encountered them...
a long time ago.
I have a souvenir from that meeting.
I'll keep it till death.
"Them"?
Uh-huh.
Two of them.
What?
Once...
there was a family living in these parts.
A mom and her two boys. Twins.
They led a rather poor life,
but they loved each other dearly.
They were happy.
And everything was fine
until one fateful afternoon.
Whoa.
"Once upon a time,
in her gloomy hut
there lived a witch as ugly as a bat.
She ate little girls at morn.
On little boys she supped.
She'd ride her broom
to the village and back,
to stuff plump little children
into her great big sack.
But before they reached the pot,
she would sing this to the lot.
♪ Nobody sleeps in the woods tonight ♪
♪ Nobody sleeps in the woods tonight" ♪
Goodnight.
Goodnight, Mommy.
♪ Nobody sleeps
In the woods tonight ♪
♪ Nobody sleeps in the woods tonight ♪
In the name of...
Boys?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
She was in shock.
She put them in chains
and locked them in the cellar
so that no one ever found out.
And so that they'd never come out.
Years passed...
and she fed them and hid them.
Until she lost her mind.
Anyone would go insane...
Poor dear woman, innocent as a lamb.
Completely nuts.
We really have to go and fetch some help.
Stay here if you want to survive.
I have a gun. I have food.
And we would just wait?
- Maybe it's not such a bad idea?
- You're free to go.
You'll reach the nearest village
in two days.
As you wish.
Your choice.
We can't just sit around.
Let's get Daniel's phone.
We have no choice.
Zosia, be careful.
- What's he doing down there?
- Get back!
- Is he there?
- Shush!
Get a grip! Here's what we'll do.
- We wait for him to leave.
- What if he doesn't leave for a week?
Do you have a better idea?
Julek!
I'll make some noise out front.
You get in.
- All right.
- I distract him. You grab the phone.
Okay.
No, wait!
- And if he chases you?
- I'll run.
- See you in a moment.
- Julek...
can you run?
Mmm-hmm.
Zosia, we will do fine, right?
We will do just fine.
All right.
Wait!
Take this. Just in case.
Open up, you fat asshole!
Hey!
Let her go!
I'm sorry.
Julek!
Fuck!
Wait. I'll call for help. Just wait.
It will be all right.
Julek...
What?
I don't understand.
I don't understand a word.
Everything will be fine.
It will be fine.
Sarah Connor...
That's not from The Terminator.
That's Captain Walrus.
I found him on a summer holiday
I spent with my parents.
My sister called him Captain Walrus,
you know?
Put an end to this, please.
Finish me off.
No, I can't. I can't.
Come on in... you motherfucker.
The last call I had,
a panicked guy phoned
saying a black guy
was repairing the waterworks.
Or a woman was driving a bus.
A woman behind the wheel?
Once in a blue moon,
something serious happens.
I catch a drunk shithead driving.
And it always turns out
that his father is someone important,
and I get a massive pile of shit
instead of a medal.
Dear officer, this is Poland,
not Miami Vice.
Last time I used a firearm?
At training in 1992.
My brother joined the force, too,
but he said, "Fuck it,"
and opened a repair garage.
Which is good, 'cause I can fix
this car there. On my expense.
I keep applying for a new one.
Nothing.
And that's how I serve the force.
Fucking life runs through my fingers
day in and day out.
And I achieve nothing.
Right.
So... I'll be going, hon.
See you on Tuesday.
Thank you, Janeczka.
237?
237, over.
Keep your eyes peeled
for Mariusz and his brother.
Someone's seen them
in World War II uniforms
celebrating Hitler's birthday
in the woods.
Over.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- God!
- Help!
Help me!
- Please help.
- Child...
What happened? What's wrong?
Are you hurt?
Shit!
I'll be right back.
Officer!
Mister?
Are you all right?
Officer!
Son of a bitch!
Drop it! Police!
Fuck!
The anthem.
How does it start?
♪ Golden rays glow all around us ♪
♪ The white eagle upward goes ♪
♪ Let us raise our heads in pride ♪
♪ See the emblem, see the cross! ♪
♪ We shall build a brand new Poland... ♪
Wait. Here's the tricky part.
Uh...
♪ We're... ♪
Well?
♪ We're the future
We're the hup! ♪
The "hub." "Hub."
God, honor and fatherland!
- I hear you.
- I love Poland.
Hey.
A boar?
A boar. Light it up.