Nocturnal animals
By the way, dear, that your cleavage
I ought to put my dick
greater than that guy has!
And as I recall,
told me when he came
That was sparse
such as coconut water! Honey, this is the reason for termination!
It is so rare.
I see that now, and we meet with less!
This is too...
Mrs. Morrow,
a package arrived for you.
Thank you.
I found him lying in the mailbox this morning.
Can I know who you would like
on duty this weekend?
Why not give everyone a free weekend?
Are you sure? -Yes.
Maybe we go to the beach house,
Otherwise it would be nice to spend a weekend alone
.
I will inform everyone.
-Thank you.
Hell.
Christopher? -Yes? -Sorry.
Can you help me open this?
I cut myself on paper.
Course. Give it to me. -Thank you.
It's only a paper cut.
There are messages.
-It's fine. You can read it.
Nocturnal
EDWARD Sheffield
Dear Susan, I wrote a novel
which will be released in the spring.
It's different from what I
wrote when we were together.
Set.
In the end, you left me with inspiration
I had to write from the heart.
I wanted to read it first.
So I send you a copy.
I'll be in LA until the middle of the business and it would be nice to see
and after so much time.
My mobile number and email address
below. Edward.
Thank you.
Good morning.
-Good morning.
What is it?
-Tropisms To me by Edward sent.
Wrote a novel.
What Edward?
Edward, my first husband. Remember him?
I did not know that he can write.
Ume. He wrote a novel when we
you and I connect, just can not remember.
Have you talked to in 20 years?
Nineteen.
Yes. I tried to call him several times before
years
But we hung up.
I think teaching English in
a preparatory school in Dallas.
It's sad. She did not remarry.
Where were you last night?
You did not come to the site.
I'm sorry, really. When I left the office
I was late for dinner...
It would have taken away 15 minutes.
15 minutes would mean a lot to me.
It does not matter.
You did not come to bed last night.
I did not want to wake you.
Yes.
Well, I have not slept.
I was too nervous about the opening.
By the way, it went well. Obviously.
Good.
-Yes.
Listen. Why do not we go
to the beach?
We can go tonight and come back on Monday.
Perhaps
to spend some time, just the two of us?
Why do you wear this blazer on Saturday?
Because I have to go back to the office
Then I have to go to the airport,
but have to go back to New York.
You just come from New York.
-I know. Do I have to go back
If you want to complete the job.
I do not want to have to sell something else.
Shit.
-It's fine.
The funny thing is...
I no longer care about art.
It's not like you.
-I know. But that is the truth.
I care.
Irritates me.
I know this irritates.
Do not worry.
Can fill the walls with some new artists from LA
And people will think we are
step ahead of time instead of going broke.
You will not have to blush.
Are things any better?
He's got a problem with the business now.
Carlos told me.
I'm surprised.
I thought that hiding pretty good.
Hutton would be very upset
to discover that someone knows.
I do not like to lose.
Are you sleeping?
Did you call my psycho pharmacology?
Did you call him?
You should mail a genius.
I'm worried about you.
Seriously.
Look at me for a moment.
Look at me.
You scared me when we talked last time
.
I'm fine.
I'm all right. I'm...
I can not believe I
I told you everything.
I'm embarrassed about it.
What right do I not be happy?
I have everything.
I feel happy that I am not ungrateful.
Same right as the others, Suzanne.
Same right as other
because everything is relative.
You are incredibly hard on herself.
How do you do it?
You mean Carlos?
I do not mind it.
It's not so bad to have a gay man.
We are best friends.
We love to all beings.
I'm sure that I'm the only woman in his life.
And it lasts longer than lust, is not it?
Lasts forever.
Hutton and I do not have to.
Have you ever had?
I think we want different things.
Or I want different things.
Do you still love him?
Called me. Sorry.
Mira to catch a plane.
I have to say goodbye.
I hope you enter into this business.
Really.
I know it's necessary.
Us necessary.
-Not.
You need that.
Hi.
-Hi.
So I said,
"My mother always said
if you rub your goldfish
spray cooking" Pam "
A month before the baby is born
do not need a rejuvenation of the vagina! "
I have to get a little spray.
And she will get a nomination this year.
Nomination?
'S Going to win.
Let's talk about your opening.
my favorite subject.
and not mine.
opening was spectacular last night.
Really?
is that what you think?
you're not? No.
.
thought
item that is incredibly strong.
So perfect with all this garbage
-culture in which we live.
Are the garbage. garbage
. Totally rubbish.
Honey, you're very successful.
None of us really do not
loves what he does.
Why are you dealing with it?
Because we are urged.
Maybe a little insecure.
Avila things when we are young
Because we think that means something.
A then discover that you do not mean.
Susan, enjoy
absurdity of our world.
Much less painful.
Believe me, our world is
a lot less painful than the real world.
Nocturnal
Edward Sheffield
FOR SUSAN
Why do we have to go this
old miracle in Mara?
Because it is fully restored.
This is a classic.
There's a horrible sound system.
You'll have to tolerate it.
You've got two pairs of boots, India?
Do we have that we stop tonight?
I prefer to get there?
Okay, ask your mother.
She's the boss.
I turned on the alarm.
India hanging on that thing for hours.
I thought you wanted to drive all night?
I wanted. But what to do, sing
songs that are sung around the campfire?
How much?
-I do not know.
Approximately three, three and a half hours.
Tara will realize your wish.
Network has just disappeared.
God. Can you believe that there is no network
here? How is it possible?
Two things I love about the most
western Texas:
No phones and no people.
Give me a break.
The real jerks.
Are we lost them?
India, do not do it! What?
What did she do? He showed them the finger.
Mama, I'm afraid.
-Toni. Speed up.
It's all right. -Shit!
-Not. I do not like this.
Pick it up, Toni.
Shit!
-Everything is fine.
Just let them go.
Let them pass.
India, do not look at them.
But they...
Do not give them an excuse.
Why are you laughing?
I do not know, honey.
Everything is fine.
Crazy!
God.
-Oh my God.
Shit!
You jerk, stop!
Stop! God, Toni.
India, did it work phone?
No, but I wrote them
registration number.
Yes.
Oh, no.
Stop, stop fucking!
-Dad!
Asshole, stop!
Yes.
-What do you want?
Beware!
Stop!
Shit!
Do not mess!
Do not worry, honey. It's fine.
You probably have a gun.
Please, Toni. Go.
I can not move.
Blocked the car.
What is he doing?
It's okay.
Do not get out of the car.
I'm not going to get out of the car, honey.
Good evening.
-Good evening.
You know you need to stop when it comes to
the accident, right? -I know.
Why do not we?
It's not going to work.
There's no signal here.
Do not leave the scene of an accident.
This is a crime.
After the way you drive?
I'm sorry, what did you say?
Just that you were driving crazy.
Turk!
Do not approach higher.
It's okay, honey.
It's okay. You know what?
I pray you return to the car. Ma'am.
Leave us alone. -Calm down.
I need to report an accident, that's all.
Relax. Ma'am, ma'am.
It's just a flashlight, honey.
Only a flashlight. It's fine.
God. -OK.
Let's exchange information.
Information? -Yes.
Exchange of information. -OK.
Open the glove box, honey.
I'm an identical twin
Favorite color is delicate pink,
I love long walks and kittens.
You must be... You know what,
we should call the police.
Yes. Really?
-Yes. It's a great idea.
You were to blame, right?
-Re? What?
It does not matter who was at fault, Toni.
Ray, the guy dropped the rubber.
-You bet.
What a surprise.
-What did he say? What?
Do not fall for that, Dad.
He said we dropped the tire.
-What did he say?
Do not believe him,
we do not let out of tires.
What? What? -Yes. Left tires you
dropped. You bet. Totally.
You must have it drilled
when you graveling us the way.
Give me a break. We have not you pushed me
the way! You are us!
That's a lie. You think I'm a liar?
-It's fine. It's fine.
She's just a child.
Do you think I'm a liar?
No, do not think that, man.
She's just a child.
You have discharged rubber...
Go and drive.
Start the car and drive.
Please, drive. Just drive.
Ride on it, asshole.
No one will stop you. Ride.
Go. Fuck off, you idiot.
Shit! Damn it!
God! God!
It's okay, do not worry.
It's not right, we are in the middle of nowhere.
What do we do, Tony?
What we do?
You know what?
Replace her instead of you, is not it, guys? -Of course.
Really? Yes, just to show that we will replace the
good for you.
You will not have your finger to move.
Then we'll go to the police
together. Right? You and me.
To report your car accident.
-OK. -Thank you.
Can?
-Yes. -Thank you.
Do you have a tool, sir?
There is no need. Our will. Come on.
Do you have a spare tire, mate?
We can not change a tire without a spare.
Will you give me the keys to the trunk?
-Not. What do you think you are?
Open up the trunk.
I will.
It's okay, I'll do it.
OK.
Below. Here.
There below.
There are many things inside.
I apologize.
-Bring The woman out of the car.
Come on, get them.
Come on, man! We need to raise
auto crane, so bring them up.
Comrade! We will have to raise
your wife, child and car?
Good.
-Bring The woman out of the car.
It's okay, honey. Step out.
I need to repair the car. -Not.
Relax. Replace the tire.
-OK dear.
Come here.
Come here. Have you seen what you've done
my car? You think you're a guy, right?
What are you?
-One Must think you're a guy.
When?
-You are serious? Your bitch. Who else?
No, do you think you're something special.
You can hit the borrowed car. -Not.
I want to leave the scene of an accident.
-Playing A wacky game...
God. God.
There goes your cops.
It has to be more
try to stop them.
Do not worry.
Well we take care of you.
You fucking bitch.
Arrogant rich bitch. I'll teach you a lesson.
It's okay.
What is it? What are you looking at? Dude.
How do you mean?
What were you trying to do on the road?
What?
I... What are you?
Listen.
We... We...
We're just trying to get
where we were going.
Where is it?
I said, wherever you go.
-Mara.
What is Murphy?
You jerk!
Leave my daddy alone, asshole!
Leave me alone! Fuck you, baby.
It's not what I meant. She's just a child.
Dad will tell me,
why would not you? -Let me!
Why do you ask? We're the good guys.
Do not touch anything my daughter!
We just want to know where you're going.
You want to play? Do you want to play?
Building a house.
Really? That is all?
Look at your father. He thinks he's
much better than me. What do you think?
Have better. I mean, seriously.
Look at him. -Let her go!
He's a wimp.
You're a bastard, you know!
Let her go!
Make sure you fucking assholes!
Do not move! -You Do not have rights
not talk to me!
For God's sake, help me changing a tire!
India.
-India.
Do not cry, baby, it's okay.
Are you okay?
Do you need a handkerchief?
Damn! It looks bad.
Maybe you need...
Honey, do you have a tampon?
Your nose looks terrible.
-It's fine. I'm all right.
I really think it looks terrible.
-I'm all right.
Really bad.
Are we done?
We're done. We're ready. Can we go
. -Here we go. -Okay. -OK. -Yes.
How much down the road we will get a network?
Why would you want to drive down the road?
If you could once again escape the scene of the accident?
Leave him alone!
U Bailey you have a network. -Okay.
How do we get there?
Our car.
-Which Car?
With both cars.
Sir, I do not play games with me!
What?
You heard me. I know what you're doing.
I know that's your plan.
-What is wrong?
Do not try to mess with me.
-Not. What's the matter, man?
What's your problem?
How do I know you're not going to give
pedal to the metal and delete me? -Okay.
Get in my car and we will follow up to
there. Fuck you! No chance!
You'll get into my car. What?
-Not. -cheap You with us. -Not.
You can drive your car.
-Not. I will not do it. Not.
Good. OK. You drive my car
a girl will come with us.
What? Not! No, I'm sorry.
You're coming with us, sweetie. -Not.
Listen, honey. I do not want your ass.
Do not touch me... Do not touch...
We will not do it!
Yeah, baby! -Let me!
-So Do you like?
Stop!
What are you doing?
Stop! Get down!
Please! -Come here!
Keep your hands off her!
India!
Hi, honey.
I love you.
India.
-Let me. Please.
Get your hands off her!
-Let me!
Shit.
-India! Come on.
Look what you did!
It's okay. She's the boss?
She's the boss in your family?
Lora?
-Do You have a vagina?
-Do You fucking vagina in there?
Lora! You guys with the vagina!
-Get In the car!
Get in the car! -Stay Away!
Will trouble, boy! -Stay Away!
Toni?
You want trouble? -Toni! Lora.
Get in the car! -Okay. Here.
Let's go with both cars! Lu!
Tara! Dad!
Stop! Not!
No! Please! Not! Not!
No! Please!
Suzanne? Why did not you call me
to tell me that you arrived safely?
For the 4 in the morning.
I did not want to wake you.
You can not sleep. Why do not you drink
one of your pills?
Where are you?
I've just walked through the door of the hotel.
What floor, sir?
-31, Please.
It's not a normal floor.
-Our Common room was not free.
You should have seen what I did
scene in the lobby.
I hope you got some sleep on the plane.
I'm worried about you, though
do not care, but I care.
You must be exhausted.
I hate that flight. It's really...
-31, ma'am.
I arrived on my floor. I have to go. I'll call you later. Right? Suzanne?
Suzanne? Can you hear me?
Yes.
I heard this.
Get some sleep.
You're going to drive.
Is this the way out?
For what exit?
For Bailey?
-Go on.
Set speed up.
What can you do?
-Here. Turn down here.
Fuck you.
I'm not going down that path!
Listen, sir.
Do you want to see your wife and child?
Then turn left on the road.
You will cry now?
But we've just passed my car!
It's not your car, man. Go on.
There's no need to worry
for his wife and child.
As I said there is no need to worry
for them. -What do you mean?
What does it mean? -Calm down.
No one has so far not killed.
Just to think.
At least not that I know of.
Killed! Why are you talking about killing?
I said that nobody ever killed.
If you had listened to me,
to hear what I was saying.
So, it looks like
we ran out of time. They're not here.
I wonder if I'm wrong.
It's time to get out now.
OK?
Get out!
-What are you doing?
Get killed if you're not careful.
Stop.
Stop!
No! Stop! Stop!
No! Not!
Shit!
Why did you leave here?
Lord?
Your wife called.
Get in the car!
Lord! Your wife!
Lord!
Shit.
Can I use your phone?
Mr. Hastings, no
nearby town named "Bailey".
That's what I was afraid of.
-Motel Is across the street.
Do you have money?
I have a credit card.
It's still early, G. Hastings.
We'll call if we had something.
-OK. Thank you.
Hello?
-Here Lieutenant Graves.
They found your car in the dry streamlined at
topping.
What's with my wife and daughter?
I still have no news.
They were in the car.
We leave this case
lieutenant Andes.
He wants to know if you can come
after you for a few minutes?
Yes, I'm ready now.
Good morning.
I'm glad you came.
I'm Bobby Andes.
I'm conducting an investigation here.
You found my car?
-They Found him in the streamed.
You know what?
If you go back to the house where we picked you up
Can I go back to the same
through there? I can try.
Well, then, try.
Here we go.
I understand
these guys were not armed.
Yes.
Good.
Do I understand this.
Guy named Lu
Brought you into the bushes, leaving
you there? I made them me drive.
He made you to drive.
I went to see when you're
them to come back. -Yes.
What kind of car was it?
I think it was mine.
Do?
What do you mean?
Based on his appearance, sound.
He sounded like my car.
Are you able to see them in the dark?
Not good.
Are they something?
They said:
"Sir, your wife asks you."
You did not go with them?
Why did not you go with them?
I do not know why I did not go.
Good.
Can you take it from here?
I came highway.
I walked for a long time.
No one has stopped.
Sergeant, slow
go backwards to the edge.
Start the rotation.
Stop the car.
Stop the car!
I slipped through that fence
barbed wire. Right there,
Near the limelight.
I remember that.
Let's go out to walk.
You said you were walking there, is not it?
I came right here because I
walked over there along the streamed.
This is part of the estate of the old Valdez.
There's an old station for cattle
Down that road not far from where
burn their trash.
This road leads there.
Is she okay?
Mama? Is that you?
Is everything OK?
Yes, everything is fine.
I just wanted to hear your voice.
I miss you.
You woke me. I'm still in bed. Sunday morning, Mom.
Can I call you back? -Yes. Invite
me later. Go back to bed, honey.
You sound strange.
Are you OK?
I'm fine.
Back to bed.
I love you. -Me too.
I'll call you later. -Okay.
Edward? Edward?
Hello.
-Susanna. Hello. God.
How are you?
It's nice to see a familiar face.
I'm glad to see you.
You look beautiful. As always.
What are you doing in New York?
I'm here to talk to
scholarship to Columbia.
Colombia? I thought you
at the University of Texas
Where you become a great writer.
A big writer? I do not know.
I do not think so. That's right.
Are not you at Yale, where
become a great artist?
I graduated from Yale, Columbia
or the finishing master.
Yes, the history of art.
-Great.
Do you know anyone else in New York?
Just you. -Just me?
-Okay. Would you like for dinner?
Course.
-Okay.
Great. Let me...
Just to leave the bags in the apartment.
Will I bring them?
Yes, great. Thank you.
I miss Texas gentleman.
You know, we do not have such a snowstorm in Texas.
No, you do not have.
You know, you were my first crush
in Hastings.
The only reason I spent so much time
with your brother
Was to be close.
And you were his first crush.
What?
-Yes.
I had no idea that Cooper is gay.
I do not think he did not know,
but he was obsessed with you.
Yes.
If I had not noticed that so much looking at me,
I thought I would not sleep with him.
I feel terrible that he did not call
years.
I have a feeling that I was a bad friend.
I hope that it is not affected.
You're good. Do you know that? Really.
Most guys would panic when they find out
That their best friend
in love with them. Very nice of you.
You need to call him.
I would love to. My parents have it
to speak up. We no longer speak.
Why? -Why?
Are you serious?
You know my parents.
The religious, conservative,
sexist, racist...
Republicans, materialistic, narcissistic
. Racists.
Can I continue... Yes
I just want to know what you really think, Suzanne.
It's true, I know.
They look at us as his reflection.
Why can not I accept
Cooper as it is.
I'm not sure how I'm going to go.
Are not you a little hard on them?
Yes.
They have outdated ideas about how to
to live my life, especially the mother.
I understand.
I always liked your mother.
Really?
-Yes.
Super acted according
me when my dad died.
Both have the same kind of sadness in his eyes.
What?
You and your mother.
It's weird to say, Edward.
I'm sorry. I did not mean to offend you.
I was just...
I always looked sad.
There are sad eyes. This opinion
I have since childhood.
You have the same eyes.
One su...
Divine.
Just do not say I'm like my mother.
I do not want to be like her.
I've always envied your family.
I felt like an intruder in a large school.
You feel the same way?
I thought that the only way I feel. -You? -Yes.
I have always been preoccupied with time
to be perfect. I... do not you feel so?
Yes. That this administration
seems so perfect.
You'll be a great novelist
because you created a fictional character in his head.
Yes. -Yes.
-Not. -Yes. -Not.
I do not believe it.
Why have you given up on
addition to becoming an artist?
Because I'm too cynical
to be an artist.
To be very good, you need to you come from
Someplace within
that I do not think I have.
You underestimate yourself.
Do you know that?
Edward...
Will you come home with me?
It's a little intrusive.
Yes.
I would not expect from
Texas debutantes.
You know that all the debutantes sluts.
You were my first crush.
I know.
We have a report from Ozone.
Someone else is bullied at
highway last night like you.
If it is not a problem, I could come
us your fingerprints.
More? He's got a lot of prints
the trunk of your car.
It might help
identify them.
There's something else.
Do?
We got the cause of death.
Your wife has fractured skull.
Probably was hit with a hammer,
or a baseball bat.
Probably once or twice, but...
Your daughter has gone through much worse.
Stifled it.
Also  her arm is broken.
I both were raped.
Turns out you were right
and barracks. -How?
These guys have taken your family
there as you thought.
How do you know? -We Found your fingerprints
women on STUBICA beds.
Whose is this shack?
He's clean.
Tip do not even live here.
He's in El Paso.
The hut was broken into.
Some lived in it.
The prints are all over the barracks.
We'll have to compare them with the fingerprints of the owner,
To see if they can be sorted out.
-Okay.
But lay hope.
The owner was not there since last fall, so...
Looks promising.
Promised...
Promising?
Why did you not tell it?
Will leave New York
I'll move to Austin to go to class
cursed University of Texas?
Why are you doing this?
I mean, where is this going?
How to think where this is going?
I will marry Edward.
That's where it goes.
This is a stupid conversation.
You're too young to be getting married.
Really?
Mama, last year you tried to convince me
I have to marry Basa.
This was different.
Bass is like you.
God, did you just say that?
Did you really say that?
That came out of your mouth? It's...
Why do you always think the worst of me?
I did not mean it.
I thought...
If you were a very determined...
A Edward besides being cute,
it is too bad for you.
I do not think Edward described as poor.
I would use the word sensitive,
What is the word I used the
to describe anyone from this family,
Except maybe Cooper.
No Cooper pulls into this.
I'm sorry.
Come on, Susan.
I know you think that we do not care about
to the same things, but you're wrong.
For several years, all of these "bourgeois"
things that you like to call them
You will be very important.
Edward will not be able to provide them to you.
He has no money.
Not motivated. It is not ambitious.
I can promise you, if you marry
Edward is not your father's will not provide.
No, you're right, he is not motivated
the way you want it to be,
Or is strong.
He's Stronger than me in many ways.
Just...
He just has a different kind of power.
That is all.
A different kind of strength?
What kind of power?
It has the power to believe in yourself.
Do not believe in me.
Suzanne...
Set to see him if you must.
Lives with him. I do not care
But do not marry him.
I understand what you see in Edward.
I understand. -Not.
No, wait, I get it.
I do not understand.
I see. I do not understand.
He's a romantic.
But it is also very fragile.
I saw that when his father died.
Do not...
Do not do that.
You'll be sorry.
I'll only hurt Edward in the end.
Things like about it now, you will hate
for several years.
Perhaps do not see that but...
You and I are a lot alike
than you think.
Yes.
You're wrong. You and I do not like.
Really?
Wait.
All
eventually turn into their mothers.
Dear Edward, I read your book.
Shocking. I am deeply touched.
It's wonderful to be written. Let's meet on Tuesday evening
. Tell me if you're still free.
I have much to tell you.
Love, Susan.
Do?
-Toni Hastings?
Yes. Who is this?
-Robert Andes.
I sent you an email.
Did you get it?
Yes.
Do you recognize this man?
-Shit.
Hell.
Are you sure?
The entire event is confusing me.
The prints of the man they were
all over your car.
We found them in the barracks.
His name is Steve Adams.
There are records in California, stealing rounds
s acquittal for rape.
I betrayed warrant for his arrest.
He is the only clue we have, Toni.
I'm sure that there are no other witnesses.
Sure you do not recognize?
Yes.
Holy shit. What's up, man?
Do not you want to send this
guys in jail? -Of course I want.
The whole event is just...
My mind froze.
I know it was him!
That may be, but nobody
it is not just about video here.
Listen, I have to be honest with you.
At the moment it does not look good.
Sometimes in these cases no
shift for months, even years.
You have to prepare for it.
Why are you so motivated to write?
I guess in that way
keep things in life.
Rescuing
things will eventually die.
If it down
Then it will last forever.
Good afternoon. -Hello.
-I apologize for being late.
Wry traffic on the interstate
way. -Does not matter.
You look different.
I do not have a beard.
Yes.
I'll tell you what we have.
We have attempted robbery supermarkets
At the mall last night just before closing
. We caught one.
One was killed and one was wiped out.
What do you want me to do?
See if you can identify
guy we caught.
You look at the dead, although I
it's not necessary. We know who he is.
When?
-Stiv Adams.
The one you called "Turk" and whose
I sent you a picture on the mail last year.
Get in.
Are you afraid to look
of this type in the eye? To see?
Yes.
That's good. I think this will help you to sing
.
That's him. Type the left.
First on the left. That's him.
No, no. Hold on, son.
You're not that lucky.
Come here.
This guy?
-Yes. I understand.
I do not understand.
Lu.
Lu. Hey you.
Name is Lu?
You know my name. I told you.
Really?
About what is it?
I want you to tell me
have you ever seen this man.
Carefully consider.
Have you ever seen him?
Yes. I do not know him.
Who is he? Why do not you try
say, Tony? Tell him who he is.
Last year, this one Lu and his comrades
pushed us out of the way
Interstate on the way. Then the two of them
forcibly entered my car
With my wife and daughter and then
is this man... Why this man? Lu?
Yes. Lu made me
to drive his car
He took me to the middle of the desert
and left me there.
Later, my wife and daughter
found dead near the same city.
It's not right.
What have you to say about
wife and daughter of this man?
I do not know anything about it.
I never saw him.
What are you going to tell me about Ray and Turks?
-About whom? -About whom?
What are you, an owl?
Are you an owl, Lu?
I have never heard of them.
You've never heard of them?
No, sir.
Good.
Officer.
Lock him.
Are you sure this is the man?
Course. Yes.
I could have sworn in court
under penalty of perjury?
Yes.
Good.
Well...
I have Lu.
Accuse him of murder.
-You Have enough evidence?
Course. We've got you,
his fingerprints on the car and barracks.
He returned to the barracks after
you left me?
Yes, so it seems. Probably
returned to tell them where you are,
So they returned with the bodies.
They wanted to kill you.
Understand? Yes. I bet it's your friend Ray
the third robber.
What now?
You'll wait for the trial.
I'll find Reja.
Do not forget that you have a meeting
committee at the museum in three.
I'm sorry. What did you say?
Again did not sleep, did not you?
You know me.
I do not sleep.
My ex-husband called me
"nocturnal."
Which ex-husband?
I did not know you had an ex-husband.
Since when?
A few years ago, when I was
diploma studies.
It's strange to think of it
a lot lately
Recently sent me
book written and it is...
Violent and sad. He called it
"Night Animals" and dedicated it to me.
Did you love him?
-Yes. I loved him.
He was a writer and...
I did not believe in him.
I panicked and done something terrible to him
. Something unforgivable.
Really. -Then You?
-Then It.
I left him...
in a brutal manner.
Because the handsome and dashing Hutton.
What is very convenient...
-I dashing. Yes.
Do you sometimes feel that your life
into something you did not intend?
Yes.
Of course not.
You've only just begun to live your life.
I really have not slept at all, is it?
Yes.
REVENGE
Where did this picture come from?
What do you mean where did she come from?
You bought it for us. You remember?
As part of the items that were exhibited
8 years ago.
It's great, is not it?
-Yes.
What is it?
God is awesome. Applications using
to watch Willow while in the cradle.
Really? Do not trust your nanny?
No, I believe, only hate.
I love that I'm more involved around Willow
during the day, but...
View. Here she is.
I sound amazing.
You can hear her breathing.
I can not tell her if you want.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry. I...
Are you okay?
-Yes.
Yes, I just...
I thought I saw someone.
You really see anyone.
It was Willow. And she was in the cradle.
Sleeping. Really I
sorry for your phone. Can...
No matter. New outputs
next week or sooner. -Thank you.
Will we?
All of us are waiting.
In any case,
should be let go.
It is no longer the same as it was when we hired
. -I do not agree.
I think we should keep it for now.
-Why? Because it's great.
I love it all. She just needs our support
. I some time.
But it does not work.
We have to let go.
There's an excellent candidate who can steal
"Hamer" If we act quickly.
I agree with Linda.
We are engaged is supposed to support her.
New Doctor?
No new haircut.
But, Susan, you are initiated on this
last meeting to seek a change.
I know, but now I think
we should keep it.
Sometimes it's...
Sometimes it might not be such a good idea
much changed things.
I do not understand.
What are we doing here?
-Shit.
Are you all right?
Yes.
I'm all right. For me.
It's Ray Markus.
Characterized as a frequent contributor
Lu Bates and Steve Adams.
Works part-time as an electrician and plumber
, hence smart toilet.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Fits your description
and the guy from the heist.
No prints but that we already knew.
I wonder why no fingerprints.
His hands are probably
were on your wife.
His files are clean.
In addition to charges of rape
which was rejected.
I heard from the bartender from the bar "Line Camp"
Re to live here with the girl Leila,
But it also has another place where
leads the girls that she does not know.
Probably the barracks where
was murdered family
Before it became notorious.
Does it feel that this is the right man?
-Yes.
That's him.
-Okay.
Let's talk to him.
Ray.
What the fuck?
Who are you?
Get off my property, man!
Shit! I'll call you.
I want to ask you some questions.
Fuck you.
I'm busy now.
What is it?
Just a few questions, that's all.
You need to come with us.
-Why?
I did nothing.
I did not say you did.
Ask me here. -Not.
You have little to take a ride with us.
Come on. Finish what you're doing and go.
Can you turn around?
Believe me, I wish I could, but...
Unbelievable.
OK. Enough.
Come on.
Come on now.
Okay, come on. Get dressed.
Come on.
Interrogate me?
-Yes. We do, right?
You have not read the law.
Do you know your rights, Ray.
He needs to read them out.
I read you, eh, Tony?
I read these rights.
It's not legal, man.
You need to have a lawyer.
Take it easy, sunshine.
This is just an informational hearing.
That's all. You help me.
I've never accused of anything.
If you want a lawyer, I can take you to the station
i blame you for something.
No kidding. No need for bringing me.
I answer the questions, right?
Come on. -I do not know. -Set
Me some questions.
I will answer them.
I do not know anything more about that robbery
Than before
I knew before I met you.
You know what, let me ask you another question.
Do you recognize this car?
What kind of car?
-This.
It in which to ride.
Why should we be familiar with this car?
They did not know each other?
On anything and does not resemble? In the past?
Why?
I do not remember that they're driving?
I think I know.
-Yes. A driver?
What? This guy? This guy
behind the wheel, my friend Toni.
Do you remember it?
I do not see it.
One turned.
Stop the car, Tony.
Turn around and look at this garbage.
Who is this guy?
Do not remember it?
I can not say that I remember.
-Remember You know him, Toni?
Yes.
-refresh His memory.
Last year the interstate road.
Tell him remember what he did.
You killed my wife and daughter.
It's crazy. I did not kill anybody.
Tell him the whole event.
You and your buddies on the interstate
you pushed us out of the way.
Tell him who his buddies. - On the Turk.
Do you remember that? Remember monkey
On the interstate road with friends?
Plays a coward with other cars?
You're crazy. It's crazy. -I made You
us to stop and we had discharged the tire.
Lu i Turk had been replaced. Then you and
Turk got into the car with my wife and daughter
But you forced me to get in your car with Lou
. What was it, Tony?
Lu took me into the bushes and kicked me.
Then you went back to my car.
You called me and tried to make me
retract into the trap. You're back
Where I was Lu left.
Because you're back there, Ray?
You're crazy!
Tell him what we found there, Toni.
You tell him. -Do I have to?
Do not you know, Ray?
You're crazy. He's crazy.
The body of my wife and child,
Which you took back there
And germs.
You're the one.
I know you.
What do you say, Ray?
You're crazy. You're making a big mistake.
I do not think so.
I do not think so, Ray.
Stretch out your hand.
You have no rights.
I have no right? Law, law, law
. You and your rights.
Speaking of rights, know
to record the whole conversation.
Here.
Understand? OK.
Come on, Toni.
Let's go to a place that you might remember.
Can I help myself
so what are you going to tell me about it.
But if you do not remember,
Toni remembers.
OK? I'm sorry you lost
family man.
Pity.
But I had nothing to do with it.
What is this place?
You know you here.
I swear, I do not know.
You want to get out, Tony?
You want to look in there, Ray?
-Why? Come on. Let's look.
OK.
I suppose you
them raped her on the bed.
No one I never raped her.
Do not be stupid, Ray!
We've seen your file.
We know that girl in Lubbock.
The charge was dismissed. I've never raped anybody
. I want to know, Ray.
I want to know what they're doing exactly.
You'll have to ask someone else.
I want to know what you were saying.
I want to know what my wife told
and what my daughter said.
I want to know how you kill them.
I want to know if
know what happened to them.
I want to know how they felt!
I want to know if you have suffered!
Answer me!
Answer me, you fucking bastard!
Is it better?
You're going the wrong way or
I think you should write
about something else and not of themselves.
But nobody writes about anything else
care of themselves.
My mind began to wander as I read
and it's not good. Is not it?
I do not know what to do.
May have something to write about.
Give yourself a little vent. Do something else.
Can you not do that? What?
Because I feel that because you do not believe me
. -Edward, I did not say that.
No, you said it, but talking about
to his face, sighs,
Whatever you say, talking about
me to go back to college.
I have to go back to college.
I do not see anything wrong with that.
I'm just realistic.
You will work in a bookstore i'll write a novel
As if it
what you want from your life?
It's very romantic.
Is this it?
This is it? This is...
You sound like your mother.
You always said this much
remind her, but...
This is why I do not want to read your work
because you take a defensive stance.
Of course I am taking the defensive!
Do you know how to put all creative
And then someone you love
says it does not understand?
No, I do not know because I'm not creative.
Because you so chose.
I do not want to fight.
I'm tired, nervous.
I wrote the whole night.
I just wanted you to enjoy. OK?
Thank you.
I have news that you will not like.
They let Reja Markus.
What? How do you think you play him?
The district prosecutor says
do not have enough hard evidence,
We have only indirect.
He needs irrefutable evidence.
I'm really sorry, Toni.
Really counted.
Bar banged him well.
No, it's not enough.
What else can we do?
I can think of something.
Although better come here quickly.
Will not be long here.
Good. I'll go.
What?
I told you. I have lung cancer.
Metastasized.
Do you smoke all the time.
-Yes. So it goes.
Why have to interrupt?
I'll be dead in a year.
Court awarded Ray lawyer
behalf Jenks. Wise guy from Dallas.
He and the DA concluded an agreement
and Ray out of jail.
Politics.
When did you tell me you were sick?
Trying to forcibly evict me.
Already have the other type
planned job.
I do not understand what you mean.
Rejected would murder case to do so? -Yes.
It gives them a reason and ammunition.
They said that my case
not well prepared.
That investigation was sloppy and superficial
. Without evidence.
The evidence was not properly collected,
will not hold up in court.
Prosecutor too afraid to be
accept cases that can not lose.
There will dismiss the case against Lua.
There is no benefit from the addition
if not middle of Reja.
Good.
I was hoping you'd say that.
They want to retire and enjoy the blessings of my
cancer elsewhere.
Fuck you.
-I Have not told me the cancer.
Problem with Ray is his alibi.
You got a family?
Ray claims that he was with the little...
-Bobi. Bobi.
What is it?
Do you have someone in your life?
Yes. I do not have a wife.
I have a daughter in the Corps.
Is that helpful?
She does not know.
What can be done about it?
In any case, Ray says he was with
the little Leila, whatever it's called,
And she confirmed his story.
Her aunt confirmed her story.
What are we going to do?
The question is how serious you are
that justice is carried out.
Do you understand me?
I can not eat. Maybe throw.
How are you going to do anything if you can not eat?
Sometimes I eat, sometimes not.
This restaurant is a disaster.
You have to eat something.
Let me ask you something personal.
Unofficially. Between you and me.
What do you want to do with Ray Marcus?
What can he do?
-Everything you want. -Okay.
I thought you said...
Listen.
I have nothing to lose.
I will not let this asshole prosecutor
to screw up my last case.
You will not keep aside
and watch how the murderer is drawn.
Video'm too sick
morons like Reja Markus
How are released over the years.
Are you ready to get out of the frame
Strict procedures when it comes to this? -Yes.
Are you sure?
-Yes.
Andes online.
Are you kidding? Okay. Thank you.
Ray appeared in the "Line Camp".
I'm gonna let that little idiot
to surprising and drinking,
Then I'll get him
and returned to my camp.
I want you to come with me.
We will keep it for a while.
We'll handle it.
It will become a little violent,
we will make him suffer.
A then we'll see what to do.
Would you like to?
You have to understand that this is not working.
We do not go. -Susanna
Too... we are different.
We're not right for each other.
-Susanna Stop.
We're not right for each other? We're not.
-What Are you talking about?
We're perfect for each other.
We're not, Edward.
Perhaps we were perfect for each other
that we do not live in the real world.
Do I live in the real world
i need a structured life
Structured future.
I want to be the person who
want me to be or not.
You did. You did.
I can do it. No, stop it.
I really wanted to be a person
that you thought you did.
Really, but I'm not that person.
I'm cynical. No, listen.
I -Pragmatic.
No, I did. No, you are.
I'm a realist. -You are scared. -I'm not afraid.
It is not our first time.
I'm not scared.
-OK. -unhappy Himself.
I'm just very, very unhappy.
You're so...
You are so wonderful, and you're so...
The sensitive and romantic, and...
Slab. What? -There What you want to say.
I did not say you were bad.
You've already talked about.
Why not say again?
Slab.
I did not say you were bad.
I did not say that you are weak.
-Do you love me?
It's not about that.
No, not about that!
No, it's not about that! -It's About it!
-Not! -You did not answer me!
Yes, I love you.
-When You love someone...
Amends.
Do not turn your back.
You have to be careful with that.
It may never get.
I can not do this to
work with you, Edward.
I can not keep doing this.
Susan.
You can not turn your back on
problems all the time.
Come on. Come on.
-Shit.
I told you I do not know.
Why do not you ask me there, man?
I'll see you soon. OK?
Hi, honey.
Let's go to my camp.
It is located in White Creek near
barracks where they took your family.
Follow me.
Sit down.
Jeez, I'm sick.
Toni, come here quickly.
Here. Use this. OK?
Shoot him if exaggerated.
Bu!
Man, this is illegal.
Yes it is legal, it took me
the cell, not in the shack.
We can not be more legalistic.
No new evidence.
Really? Why do not you arrest me
if you have new evidence?
I like it here.
Is relaxed.
It seems to me that you are trying
this trick before.
If you think that this type of
to break me,
You've already seen it does not work.
-Yes.
What if I told you that your drug
Lu Bates connected with the murder of Hastings?
If Lu did it,
arrested to me.
Do not worry. We'll take you to the station.
Do not worry.
Who is this?
Look at that. Get in!
-Son Son. -OK.
OK. Come on, boy.
Come here.
Lu, what did you say this guy?
Nothing.
He said you told him I
I killed a woman and a child from that type.
What? It's the same thing for you.
You're supposed to be representative
Act. What is this shit? Fuck off.
Both.
Have you two last
words you want to say to each other?
Toni, I think it should be
to kill them now.
It will be tough for them outside,
Since they will not know how to handle them.
Maybe Ray is killed
while resisting arrest.
Came home late at night...
Burglar could kill him.
Uneasily with you, boy?
Get up!
You look uncomfortable.
I'm sorry.
What? -I'm sorry. -What did you say?
I will not kill you, son.
I'm a cop.
What is it? Plakae?
Are you going to cry?
Well, since you feel so uncomfortable...
Toni, come here.
Take this.
Come here. OK?
-Please.
Fuck.
Exactly here. Right here. OK?
OK. -What about me? Maybe
is me uncomfortable.
Here.
Really?
Good. Come on.
Here. Free as a bird.
OK? What do you say to that?
What do you say, Tony?
What do we do with these two?
What are you gonna do?
What are you going to do, son?
Come on.
Let's go.
He's got a gun.
Bobbi? -Shit!
Shoot him, Toni!
Come back, you little bastard!
Yes.
No, please.
Are you okay?
'll Repent for this.
I repent now.
I'm a Catholic. I do not believe in abortion.
I'm so sorry.
I feel so useless.
You are all but useless.
You always know what to do.
Thank you.
I think I will never be able to look
Edward
After what I did to his
child. He will never know.
What did I do?
I promise I'll be all right.
I will do everything to be in order.
God, no.
Edward.
Toni.
You know I had to shoot him, right?
I do not care what you
had to shoot him!
I'm glad you shot him!
I'm glad he's dead!
It was supposed to prevent!
I was supposed to protect them!
I should have expected this!
It was supposed to prevent!
-Enough.
It's okay.
You're supposed to stop it!
Okay.
You're supposed to stop it, Bobby!
Look at me.
You're a good man.
Come on, we have to stand up.
If Ray came to the road, they will have to hitchhike.
We have to catch him before
than catching a ride. Listen to me.
When you come to a fork road, turn left
.
This will take you back to the
place where you took the family.
I doubt that
headed for the highway.
I will go in that direction.
Take this.
I have one in my car.
Bobbi.
-What is it?
Are you in trouble about all this?
I do not know.
I do not give a fuck.
I'm dying, do you remember?
What the fuck!
Ti. Where's your friend?
-Ariving.
Your cop friends?
Around are.
Are they here?
Just me now.
You and that fucking gun
who do not know how to use it.
What happened Luu?
Dead.
What?
Fucking son of a bitch.
This is a big problem for
your friend, you know that?
I do not think so.
Do not you know?
What the fuck do you want?
You and that stupid gun.
I saw how much you're handy with
miracle. -Sit down. Have a seat.
Sit down or I'll kill you.
Listen, man.
Why is a nice guy like you hanging out with a guy like
Andes? He kills people.
You kill people.
Deserve it, your wife and child.
You mistake me understand.
It was an accident. -Accident?
People have to come to me
with a certain respect.
Some things can not tolerate.
When someone accuses me of something,
I take that as an insult.
It gives me the right.
If my fish accuse
to fuck another,
Then go to fuck another.
If your daughter thinks I'm
rapist, then being raped.
No one will get away with
what you did to us.
Niko.
Really?
Then you just have to kill me.
Do not you?
You need to kill me.
You have no idea.
It's fun to kill people.
You of all people should be
to try it sometime.
Fun?
It's fun to kill people?
Did you have fun while
You killed my wife and daughter?
Get up.
Get up. Come on. Come on.
Come on.
I remember your fucking wife.
I remember fucking your wife.
You're too weak.
Too fucking bad.
You're too weak to do something about it.
Son of a bitch!
Edward.
Edward Sheffield Information about new email's
Tuesday evening. Dear Susan,
just tell me when and where. Edward.
This way, sir.
tatily