Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
♪ Raindrops ♪
♪ So many raindrops ♪
♪ It feels like raindrops ♪
♪ Falling from my eye, eyes ♪
♪ Falling from my eyes ♪
♪ Since my love has left me ♪
♪ I'm so all alone ♪
♪ I would bring her back to me ♪
♪ But I don't know
where she's gone ♪
♪ I don't know
Shot that one myself.
Really?
He was a tough old
son of a bitch.
Shot him nine times.
But I got him.
Are you all finished?
Yes, sir.
Ah, you can call me Ed.
Follow me.
You ever work at a
gas station before?
No.
You own your own car?
Uh, not yet.
But my friend can drive me
here, and I can get the bus.
Okay.
Well, what we're
looking for is someone
to work the night shift.
From ten to six in the morning.
Just to let you know,
we don't get a lot of
business during the night.
You will get some hunters
and farmers rolling
in around four or five.
These hours work for you?
Yeah, I can work
whenever you want.
I wish you had a
little more experience.
I'm a really fast learner.
And a hard worker.
So, you were
convicted of a felony.
Yeah.
Did you go to prison?
For a little while.
For what?
I set my boyfriend on fire.
Did he deserve it?
Yeah.
When did you get out?
Two weeks ago.
My parole officer told
me about this place.
So you have a parole officer?
Tom Doogan.
He's the one told
me about this job.
I know Tom.
I...
I really need this job.
Well, I had an
interview this morning.
And to be honest, I
didn't like him too much.
He reminded me of my
daughter's husband,
and he's an asshole.
I go a lot on my gut feelings.
You promise you won't
give me any shit?
Yeah, I promise.
All right.
You got the job.
Thank you.
I've just been, I've looking
for a job since I got out.
So, this is really great.
You won't regret it.
Can you start tonight?
Yeah, absolutely.
Do you have a number
I can reach you at?
No, I don't have a
cell phone right now.
Home phone?
Get here around 9:30.
Bobby will give
you the walk-through
and show you how to
run the register.
Okay.
It's good meeting you, Mary.
And good luck.
Thanks.
Tell Tom he
owes me a six pack.
So?
I got it.
Oh my God, Mary!
Congratulations.
It doesn't pay very very will.
And I'll have to work
the graveyard shift.
But, I'll take what I
can get, right?
Absolutely.
You need a job.
It's a great first step.
So, when do you start?
Tonight.
Wow, that was fast.
Yeah.
I'm going to take you to
lunch today to celebrate.
What are your plans?
Uh, I need to meet my
parole officer at 11.
Let's meet at Canton
Square at like, 12:30?
Okay.
I think this is the
start of a new life.
12:30.
I'll see you then.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Stop!
Oh my God.
I did it all for you, Mary.
♪ Raindrops ♪
♪ So many raindrops ♪
♪ Falling from my eyes ♪
Watch me, Mary.
I know you like to watch.
No.
You're not real.
♪ Falling from my eye, eyes ♪
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah, yeah.
I'm fine.
Why, why didn't you knock?
You can't just walk
into people's apartments.
The door was open.
Is it 11 o'clock already?
Yeah.
Who's in the bathroom?
Nobody.
Who were you talking to?
I wasn't taking to anybody.
I tried calling you.
What's wrong with your phone?
It's not plugged in.
Why?
Because I don't want a phone.
Plug your phone in.
This isn't a request.
If I can't get hold of
you things are going
to get very difficult.
Listen, I know all about
you and your boyfriend.
I'm sure you're going
to carrying that
around with you your whole life.
But you have a chance now to
do something with yourself.
So don't fuck it up.
I'm not crazy, you know.
The file says paranoid
and delusional,
who suffers from hallucinations.
You know, I didn't do anything.
Then why are you here?
You need to save the denial
speeches for someone who cares.
I got a job.
Good for you.
Where?
Deer Gas Market.
I see.
You took my advice.
Ed says you owe him a six pack.
Yeah, I owe that old bastard
more than a six pack.
When do you start?
Tonight.
Well that's good.
Thanks.
I'll check in with you tonight.
Just to fill you in
on a little secret.
There were a lot of people
didn't want you released.
They think you're
still highly unstable.
A lot of families and
officials want you to fail.
They'd like nothing
better than for you
to do something stupid.
So they can use it
against you, lock you up
and throw away the key.
Just like your boyfriend.
And guess who's their only
source of information?
- You.
- That's right.
So walk the line, report
back to me everyday,
and I'll make sure
you stay out of jail.
Is that understood?
I thought you didn't care.
I don't.
Hey.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
What were you looking at?
Oh, nothing.
I just thought I saw someone.
Who?
Nobody.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
You want to go to
Harmond's or the Mayflower?
Mayflower is fine.
♪ Make up my mind ♪
So come on, tell
me more about this job.
What do you want to know?
What did the owner say?
He wished I had more experience.
It's a gas station.
It's not like it's
rocket surgery.
Yeah but, I've never worked
in a gas station before.
Well, my cousin does.
And he's a fucking idiot.
So you'll be just fine.
I can't eat, I'm so nervous.
What the Hell are
you nervous about?
I don't know.
Well, if you're not going
to eat it, can I have it?
Sure.
Remember outside when you
asked what I was looking at?
Yeah.
Someone was staring at me.
Who?
He looked like James.
James is in jail.
Yeah, I know.
And, even if by some
miracle he got out,
I doubt he could even walk.
You burnt the guy to a crisp.
Hey, are you sure you're okay?
Uh, yeah.
Are you taking your medicine?
Yeah.
Yeah... but?
I'm still having those
episodes every now and again.
Jesus.
Don't tell your parole officer
or your doctor any of this.
I won't.
They'll throw your
ass away for life.
Do you think I'm
going to be alright?
Listen, you've been
through a lot of shit.
I can't even imagine
what it was like.
But you can't keep
living in the past.
You did your time.
And what's done is done.
You have to move on.
Yeah.
You're right.
Everything's gonna be great.
Come on.
Let's get out of here.
Hello?
I'm glad you
plugged your phone in.
I told you I would.
Good job, Mary.
I hope your job goes well.
Thanks.
Bye.
Yes, Tom?
You
watched my daughter die.
And now I'm going
to watch you die.
♪ My image in a
computer screen ♪
♪ You got no one but my own ♪
♪ Sticks and stones... ♪
Hey.
♪ Stimulation, baby,
I need more, 'cause ♪
♪ I am a sociopath ♪
It's supposed to rain tonight.
Mary...
We talked about this.
You can't freak out
every time it rains.
You know that old '50s
song, "Raindrops?"
No.
♪ Raindrops ♪
♪ So many raindrops ♪
♪ Feels like raindrops... ♪
Okay please, stop singing.
Yeah, I know the song.
Well...
James would call
me every time it rained
and play that song
over the phone.
That's how I knew he was
going to kill someone.
God, that's so fucked up.
Is that why you
don't want a phone?
One of the many reasons.
You know, you're the only
one who has stuck by me.
I never would have been able
to do any of this without you.
So, thank you.
You don't have to thank me.
We've been friends
since we were five.
You're like family to me.
I'll never turn my back on you.
I know what everyone
says about me.
Yeah, well you know
what I say to them?
What?
Go fuck yourself.
Are you sure you
want to work here?
I don't really have a choice.
This place is in the
middle of nowhere.
I don't like you being
out here all by yourself.
I'll be fine.
What are you doing?
I'm coming in.
I need to see what this shithole
looks like on the inside.
Hi.
Can I help you?
I'm Mary.
I'm supposed to
start work tonight.
Oh, right.
Hi, I'm Bobby.
- Hi.
And this is Deb.
Oh, hi.
Do you sell beer?
Oh yeah.
It's right in the back.
So, Ed says this
is your first time
working in a gas station?
Yeah.
Okay. Well, it's
pretty easy.
So, you don't have to
worry about a thing.
Do you want to see what's
going on back here.
Yeah.
So this is the cash register.
And this is the scanner.
You just scan the item.
Press this button
and this button.
And when people pay
for gas they have
to come inside because
the pumps are old
and they're not automated.
I'll take a pack of Spirits.
Okay.
Just make sure that you card
because I got in
trouble once for selling
to a 12-year-old.
You sold cigarettes
to 12-year-old?
She had boobs.
So, it was confusing.
Uh...
Yeah, so you want
to ring her up?
Uh... uh sure.
All right.
And, is that
debit or credit?
Uh, is that debit or credit?
- Debit.
- Okay.
That will be $9.75, please.
See?
Easy as that.
Good job!
- Thanks.
- All right.
Okay, so I'll get
you a set of keys
and I'll show you around
the rest of the store.
- Okay.
- All right.
He's kind of cute.
For a guy that works
at a gas station.
So, are you going to
stay here all night?
No, I'm leaving.
I just wanted to make sure
everything was all right.
Everything's fine.
I'll call and check
up on you later.
Okay.
And don't get too drunk.
You have to pick me up at six.
When have I ever
gotten too drunk?
Ok.
Fuck!
We only have five channels.
That's fine.
I'm not going to be watching
that much television.
You say that now,
but by three a.m., you're
going to be begging
for some crappy
TV show to watch.
Trust me.
Okay.
Here are the keys to this store.
This round one opens
the front door, okay?
So if you leave the market,
you're going to have to
use this to lock the
door behind you.
This thin one opens the back
door and the bathroom door,
and Ed likes to keep that
door locked at all times.
Okay?
And what's that one for?
What do you think it's for?
Outdoor bathroom?
You are a fast learner.
Alright, I think
that's pretty good.
Uh, I think you're ready
for your first night.
Uh, it should be a slow one.
Monday's are always slow.
Mmmm.
Just call me if you
have any problems.
Okay?
Ed wants me to check in
on you later on tonight,
to see if everything's okay.
Okay.
Got anymore questions
before I go?
Uh...
has this place
ever been robbed?
Uh, well...
I mean...
only by me.
Now, you can eat and
drink anything you want.
Just keep your hands off,
these babies are mine,
and I have seniority.
I'm okay, thanks.
Ed never notices.
Leave it in the
dumpster out back.
Uh, and if you smoke,
do it outside.
Okay.
Well, I guess that's it.
I'll see you later, Mary.
See ya.
I hate the rain.
Ew, gross.
The brain is ready.
The patient is ready.
Good.
Ugh.
Hello?
Deer Gas Market, this is Mary.
How late
are you open until?
We're open 24 hours.
Thank you.
Deer Gas Market, this is Mary.
How late
are you open until?
Didn't you just call?
Deer Gas Market, this is Mary.
How late
are you open until?
You already...
Do you like
watching people die?
Hey, this is Debbie.
Thanks for Calling.
Hey Deb, it's me calling.
Could you call me at
the number I left?
I really need to talk to you.
Get a grip.
Shit.
Hey.
Hi.
Is Ed here?
No, he's not in until morning.
Uh-huh.
Uh, fill her up, diesel.
Um...
Is that pump number two?
Yes ma'am.
Okay.
It's not a good
night to be outside.
I'll tell you that for free.
I haven't seen you
around here before.
Oh, it's my first night.
How do you like it?
Yeah.
It's good.
So what are you?
You a student or something?
No.
Well, it's about time they got
someone pretty working here.
So, why does a beautiful
young woman like yourself
work in a dump like this?
'Cause I needed a job.
You should get a boyfriend
to take care of you.
I don't have a boyfriend.
Oh.
Now how come you haven't
got a boyfriend?
Because I tried to kill him.
That'll be $159.75, please.
Hot damn.
I think I'm in love.
Is that debit, or credit?
Credit.
If you ever get tired of
not having a man around,
you know, I'm always
open 24 hours.
Thanks,
but I'm not going to be
dating anyone for a while.
Ah.
What a waste of machinery.
Oh, shit.
Hey, hey, you forgot
your credit card!
- Oh!
- Oh, my God.
Oh, shit.
What the Hell are you doing?
I was screaming your name.
I thought you'd hear me.
I didn't.
What are you doing out here?
Someone forgot
their credit card.
God damn.
Oh my God.
Your lip is bleeding.
Well, yeah, no shit.
You punched me in the face.
Sorry.
Come on, let's go inside.
Shit.
That is some right
hook you got there.
I'm sorry.
I thought it was somebody else.
I'd hate to be
that somebody else.
Yeah.
You would.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Sorry.
So, what are you doing here?
Ed said that he wanted me
to come check up on you.
How's everything going?
Well, I've had one customer.
You know him?
Big, tall, bald-headed
guy, drives a truck?
That's him.
Yeah.
He left that here on purpose.
Why would he do that?
Well, because he fucked the
last girl that worked here,
until Ed walked in on them.
Ugh.
How could anyone
sleep with that guy?
He paid her.
That's disgusting.
He used to fuck her right there.
Oh!
So how is everything going?
I'm fine.
Ed told me you were in prison?
Right.
So that's why he wanted
you to check up on me.
Make sure I'm not
stealing anything?
No, he just want to make
sure everything is okay.
So?
Looks pretty good from
where I'm standing.
Can I ask you a question?
Sure.
Why did you set your
boyfriend on fire?
I guess word gets
out pretty fast.
Do you really want to know?
Do you want to talk about it?
Not really.
Yeah, okay.
My boyfriend was, um...
James Lincoln Fields.
The Rain Ripper?
Yeah.
He killed like 30 women.
35.
So I guess that makes
you The Watcher.
Yep.
That's what the press called me.
You watched all those
girls get killed?
Not all of them.
How'd that
make you feel?
Like I wanted to die.
I still want to die every day.
You don't have to
talk about this.
No, it's fine.
How did you find out?
You know, that he was...
Killing people?
Can I get a sip of that?
Thanks.
I came home from work
one night and...
the house smelled really bad.
I thought
it was an animal
or a backed up sewer pipe.
So, I want down
into the basement.
And...
it was completely flooded.
The smell was...
too much to take.
So, I was about to go
upstairs to get James.
Then I saw.
The body parts.
That's when I knew.
He'd been burying bodies
underneath our house.
And I turned around
to get James.
And he was waiting for me.
That's how you knew it was him?
I always thought there
was something going on, but...
like, I guess I didn't
want to believe it.
Gosh.
What did you do?
Nothing.
I just let it all happen.
Why didn't you run?
Why didn't you go to the cops?
He said he was going to
kill me and my whole family.
I'm not making
excuses or myself, but...
I was young and scared,
and... I didn't know
what else to do.
He made me watch after that.
What made you stop?
Her name was Christine Rogers.
She was so young.
After that I didn't
want to live anymore.
So...
while he was sleeping...
I set the house on fire.
With you inside?
He's still alive, right?
And why the rain?
So their souls
could be cleansed.
I got really sick.
I couldn't tell what was real,
what was not.
I was seeing the
victims everywhere.
How are you doing now?
Good days and bad.
But I'm getting better.
That's good to hear.
Could you, uh...
Could you not tell anyone?
I won't tell anyone.
I think people are going
to find out though.
Yeah, I know.
Look, I gotta go.
- Okay.
- You going to be okay?
Yeah.
Got any questions
for me before I go?
Does anyone actually eat those?
Oh, these little things?
Let's see here.
Mmmm.
Oh, ewwww.
You don't know what
you're missing.
Oh, God.
That's so gross.
Thanks for the
pig's tongue, Mary.
I'll tell Ed you're
doing just fine.
Thanks.
See you later, Mary.
See you.
Do you have a bathroom?
Yeah, it's just outside.
There you go.
♪ I'll take you ♪
♪ Yes, I know you want it too ♪
Shit.
Fuck!
Do you have ID?
Sure do.
Thanks, Tom.
Not a problem.
That will be $11 please.
There you go.
Thanks.
Excuse me.
Deer Gas Market, this is Mary.
♪ Raindrops ♪
Are you okay, Lady?
Just to let you know your
bathroom is totally flooded.
Let's go.
Shit.
Fuck.
Great.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Help me!
Why won't you help me?
You're not real,
you're not real.
You're not real, you're
not real, you're not real.
You're not real.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What are you doing here?
I was driving by
and I thought I'd
see how you're doing?
It's kind of late for
you to be out, isn't it?
I don't sleep much.
Don't the phones work here?
You know you really don't have
to keep checking up on me.
I'm not checking up on you.
Ed called me and asked me
some questions about you.
Great.
Did you tell him everything?
You know what?
Why don't you just send me back?
Is that what you want?
For your information, I told him
that you were a good person
caught up in a bad situation.
And now trying to put
your live back into order.
Thanks.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm going to use the
bathroom, where is it?
The one outside's out of order.
You'll have to use
the one in the back.
The thin key will let you in.
Thanks.
Can I help y...?
Hello, Mary.
You're not real, you're
not real, you're not real.
I'm real.
I heard they let you out,
so I thought I'd come
see how you're doing.
You still don't think
I'm real, do you?
Mmm.
You still seeing things
you don't want to believe?
Well, you're just like me, Mary.
You liked watching them die.
I'm not like you.
You're worse.
You could have stopped me.
But you didn't.
You let people die.
Innocent people die.
I was sick.
Still believing in your lies?
Still.
This is not happening.
You will watch
people die tonight.
And I'll bet you 10 to one
that you will like it.
And then
I'll watch you die.
And there is nothing
you can do about it.
You know, my parole
officer is in the back.
You don't think I know that?
Well, I'm going to tell him.
Mmm.
What if I'm not real?
They'll put you
away forever, Mary.
I know you're not real.
And I'm going to
prove it to you.
I'd like some gas, please.
Sure.
Can I have $10 on
pump number three?
Okay.
It's really coming
down out there.
Yeah.
And $10 is your change.
Thank you.
How late are you open until?
Why do you keep calling me?
What do you mean?
You called me.
Earlier.
I know it was you.
I'm sorry, do I know you?
You know who I am.
What the fuck do you want?
I think you are mistaking
me for someone else, dear.
Don't you lie to me.
I am on to you.
- I am fucking on to you, lady.
- Hey!
What's going on?
This woman has been
calling me all night.
I don't know what
she is talking about.
She's one of them.
One of who, Mary?
Okay, someone has been
calling me and making threats.
You think that lady was her?
I don't know.
Well, why didn't
you tell me this?
Because I'm paranoid
and delusional.
Remember?
Well, you should
have told me this.
Look, you need to
tell me everything
and be honest with me.
That's the only way
this is going to work.
You understand?
Okay.
It's late.
Have a nice night.
Thanks.
Debbie?
You've
reached Tom Doogan.
Leave your name and number.
Tom, I need you to call me.
I think something's happening.
Please call me.
9-1-1.
Everything's fine.
Nothing's happening.
Hello?
This is Sam from
emergency services.
We received a call
from this number?
Sorry, I thought I hung
up before I connected.
Do you have an emergency?
No, I didn't mean to call.
Sorry.
If you'd
like to make a call...
Fuck.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
You're not real,
you're not real.
Mary.
Oh my God.
Help me.
Help me, please.
Hey, settle down.
We need to call the police.
He's trying to kill me.
Everything is going
to be all right.
You don't understand.
Oh fuck.
The phone's still dead.
Do you remember her?
She was 18 years old.
She was a freshman in college.
She was gonna be a doctor.
But you and that monster,
you took all of
that away from her.
I didn't.
You watched him
kill my daughter!
When I heard they let you out,
I just had to come and
do something about it.
No!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Is she dead?
I tried to call you but
the phones are down.
I know.
She said that I
killed her daughter.
Her name is Carol Rogers.
Her daughter was Christine.
No.
Is anyone ever
going to forgive me?
No.
Fuck.
What's wrong?
We have to get
hold of the police.
Why did you come back?
I have something to tell you.
What?
Come on we have to go.
No, tell me what it is.
There was an accident
at the prison.
What kind of accident?
A major storm shut
the power down.
Some prisoners escaped.
James was one of
those prisoners.
He's real.
They didn't want me to tell you
because they didn't think
he would come after you.
He was here.
What?
No.
Don't.
Please.
I told you I was real.
I'm sorry for hitting you.
You okay?
I've been watching you.
I really thought that woman
was going to kill you.
Then Tom did me a favor.
He killed her so
I didn't have to.
And now we're together again.
Just like old times.
What are you going to do?
You know what I'm going to do.
No, please don't.
Debbie.
You don't have to do this.
Yes I do.
I trusted you.
And this is how you repay me.
I'm not afraid of you anymore.
You should be.
No.
Watch me, Mary.
Watch!
No, no, no.
Please, please don't.
Please, please.
Debbie.
Please stop.
Tell me you love me.
No.
Tell me you love me and
I won't let her die.
I love you.
I love you too.
I love you so much.
Fuck!
I do this all for you.
You know that, don't you?
Debbie.
Phew.
You like to watch, don't you?
Say it.
No.
You disappoint me, Mary.
You like watching
people burn, don't you?
Fuck you.
Soon we'll be together again.
I will never be with you.
Help me!
Ed keeps a gun in his locker.
What?
In his locker, 37.
It's right there.
- Go get it.
- Ok.
Go get it before he comes back.
The one with the lock.
Do you have a key?
No.
Fuck.
Mary, Mary, there's
a pipe right there.
There's a pipe right there.
Hello?
Shit.
Hey, darling!
You here?
I forgot my credit card.
Hey.
See that little
lever, on the top?
That opens the rifle.
Put two shells in.
That's a girl.
Hurry up.
Hurry up, hurry, hurry.
Shit.
Oh, Jesus.
Untie me, untie me.
There you go.
Come on.
9-1-1, please
state your emergency.
I'm at Deer Gas
Market, off Highway Six.
I think someone might
have robbed the place.
You better send a car down here.
Sir, please
stay in your car
until the authorities arrive.
Uh-huh, will do.
Just keep that rifle
trained on the door.
As soon as he walks
in, pull the trigger.
I won't die here.
I won't fucking die here.
I'm supposed to
pick you up at six.
Keep it covered.
As soon as he walks
in, blow him away.
Shit.
Get ready.
Come on, you fucker.
- I shot him.
- Come on.
Oh, no.
It's not him.
I shot someone.
It's not your fault.
You didn't know.
I did, I pulled the trigger.
Give me the gun.
And the shells. Come on.
It's my fucking fault.
If he walks through that door,
I'll blow his fucking head off.
No, no we can't stay here.
We'll die.
Come on.
Stay close to me.
How many rounds you got?
Two.
Okay.
The Police are here.
Yeah.
Okay, let's go.
Come on.
Oh fuck.
This is Officer Collins.
I'm out on Old Cold Bank
Road, Deer Gas Market,
responding to a 9-1-1 call.
Hopping out to have a look.
Oh, please!
Get on the ground!
He's gonna kill me!
- No, on the ground.
- Please.
Calm down.
Is anybody else in there?
Yes, he's coming.
We need to leave now.
Stand up.
Slowly.
Tell me what's going on.
He's in the store.
Who's in the store?
James Lincoln Fields.
He's coming after me.
Get in the car.
This is officer Collins...
No, no!
Hello?
Hey!
Stop, stop, stop!
Hey, stop!
Please, stop!
Mary!
Fuck.
Stay with me.
I'm not leaving here
without you, Mary.
It's time to go home.
9-1-1, Please
state your emergency.
I love you.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org