Septembre 1988
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I'm scared.
Don't be scared.
Who is he?
He going to be your teacher.
This is a very good day.
You know why?
Because today is
a beginning. Your friend Tobi...
I've known him for a long time.
I've known him by other names.
Well Louis knows him too.
I had to learn too.
It was hard at first
But worth it.
Christi going to grow up.
And your going to have
a son who is one of chosen.
Now Katy, your strength is your gift
Alot is going to be asked of you.
Your going to have to take care
of your sister, And alot of others.
There's a very special
girl out there alot like you.
And he is going to bring her to us.
What did you draw sweetie?
Uncle Mike.
It's nncle Mike?
Screaming.
Screaming?
Uh, Huh
Remember what we're
going to do when he gets here?
Boo!
Like real big.
You Want practice
again before he gets here?
Boo!
Oh!
Hey Hey!...Hey
Remember what we're going to do okay.
Ooh...Spooky,
Why is the door open
-Boo!
-Hah !Hah!
Oh, my Gosh! That's my favorite niece.
What's up bro?
What's on that face of yours... Uncle Mike?
What?
You like this?
You fertilizing it?
-Is that Marna Santa?
-That's funny.
-Is this a rental?
-This is ridiculous.
I Can't wait to show you my room.
It's nice and cozy in here here.
Do you have...
You have two rooms?
-Hi mommy!
-How are ya?
What are you staying for
a month that bag is massive?
How are you?
You're running for
months? This bursa is huge.
There's something in your bag for me?
It's good to see you
We love
Hello.
Remember Skyler, right?
How are you? Long time no see.
All right. Yes.
It's not European. It is American.
The term bride with
by email. This waste.
Watch her suitcase.
It's your department. It is huge.
Has many...
It was the rainbow.
No problem forgiveness.
We did not like that vase.
Here's Uncle Mike.
That funny
Why I am old?
So you're going to see when you're old.
It buemsimo.
Do not incites.
What do you mean?
Baby, baby, let a little
for the talent show.
You must come to the talent show.
I'll be there.
While I have an appointment.
Because leave Chicago.
's What happened with me and Chandler.
A Ijo and I did not want...
If?
Or if I want. if I'm going.
And then leave.
But if you try to tell him as...
Children are the future.
See that small artist we have here.
I ermine my tamDien card.
Yes.
Si. Merry Christmas.
Happy holidays.
Festive Que.
These  for retirement? Ol
.
Rehabilitation are here for, right?
No. I'm not in rehab.
Let's be honest.
I'm here for a yoga retreat.
Vodka?
Do not.
Is only yoga.
And I thought that would be nice to come here and stay
With these guys for a week
strangers.
Ready?
I'm seeing on the computer.
Expected.
Lie back.
This is lovely.
You need to tie the knot now.
Christmas Tie the knot.
Really has an eye.
I know. I know.
I say this every year.
No you do not.
It is beautiful
My grandmother gave it to my mother. Your grandmother.
And your grandmother gave it to me.
And you someday you'll have.
You got it?
That Angel is precious.
I think it ends here. friend.
Oh, yes.
It's not abstract
I think it seems Christmas.
Yes. Looks great.
It's good for the yard.
The neighbors will love.
You know two...
A wasted deer sled.
Yes. Two guys for it.
Hey friend. I do not judge.
And if you do a real job and bring...
I'm doing real work.
There is a string of lights in that box.
This box?
This is only sealant
What?
Sealant.
I think you have the wrong box.
6SA ene
That must be the
people who used to live here.
There are also videotapes.
Than?
Video cassette.
For real?
It works.
Good.
Ladies and gentlemen.
The award-winning cameraman.
From outer space.
Pope.
Where did you get that? It is giant.
It's so big.
It is very large.
You look so funny. People wearing that? Ol
.
This is so cool.
We are owners of that. Look at the box.
Si. It's okay.
Drink. this is...
Do not know if this unfocused or
But this is old...
There are traces in the lights and
I see a kind of...
Strangely in the middle of the room like a blur
.
I think is out of focus.
This is so great.
What?
It is so extrarïo
I'm seeing something in the other room.
Probably only this old.
It is strange.
Is so strange.
It seemed to be under water when from here.
What are receiving this camera?
What I have.
Mike is going to go crazy with this.
Okay affection
Okay, marl...
You forgot to check.
First the closet. I'm going here.
The closet seems fine.
Under the bed.
I do not see anything except you.
I see a television.
I do not see a TV
There is no TV in your room. Lila.
You mean in the shop
pink bell?
Everything is ready here. One last thing.
You can stop this.
But that heavy is this.
Sleep well. Sweet Dreams.
I expect to come Easter.
You can not.
You know what? He gives nirias
extras that go to sleep gifts.
Good night, baby. I love you.
Marna  Good night.
Where did he go?
Ryan.
You coming to bed?
Now I can not see that thing
. I think he's gone.
Well, great. The fixed it.
Come to bed. Leave that to Matiana.
No. Do not fix anything.
We went upstairs. I came back.
And now it has completely gone.
If you come to bed now
your wife is going to have sex with you.
Sex?
Also.
... I... I'll have sex with you.
Anti That was sexy.
Okay. I'm going there.
This thing is absolutely spectacular.
Looks pretty spectacular.
I know.
The thing is... you found anything?
Is completely original.
I've been like 15 websites.
And nothing looks like this camera.
This usually has 3  photo tubes.
This has 6.
Oh, God mi'o.
It seems to have as a multiple range
approach.
I see arrows to focus.
But this here
Ol.
I have no idea what it does.
By
much you like this? It's just a camera.
I do not know. I was in my house.
I have never seen any of this.
This case... I have never before seen. Mike.
This type ...
Definitely...
Hey, Dad.
Hey.
It is the same thing?
Who were you talking about?
My friend.
Your friend?
Where is your friend?
Pope. I play the hidden
. Count to ten.
Count to ten.
It's okay.
One.
Two.
Très .
Where did he go?
Well, the girls came out this
night. We have the house to ourselves.
Why do not you take the night off?
I have to finish this game
before Christmas Day. friend.
Was checking my bursa.
Yes? What did you find? Your underwear?
I have a little souvenir of my trip to Belgium.
Good Belgian chocolate ..
Wrapped in foil?
Believe me. Does not look much...
You've been in your pocket for weeks.
It's not about the presentation.
They put a lot of time in the chocolate.
Ryan. for real?
I expect it is because of me.
And I appreciate it.
You know very well.
I've been living with you for long.
Fair enough. I swear to God.
You can eat.
You're talking about.
Santa is the best.
He has a festive attitude.
Simply
work one night and fly with his sleigh.
With magical deer. Sign me.
I want to be like Santa.
Why still have a VHS...
I ever tell you
Old pornography steal potatoes?
And needed a way to see this, so...
Oh, he had so many European rare.
It is where the guy
eggs tied with leather.
All are from 88 to 92?
I do not know.
Let's see what we have here.
Yes.
Lie back.
It's not your house, man. Where is that?
I do not know.
88.
There he is.
Oh my goodness. This will be so sexy.
Why are we seeing? Oh, God rrrio.
Shoulders. I am a kind of shrugged.
Oh, no.
Here is where it gets really good.
No Mores.
Back to where was your Marna.
Goodbye.
What horror
Tell me when you return  women.
I'll put another tape.
Find someone with small shoulders.
Cbmo go play?
Who is winning?
Why are not you talking about?
I'm one of you.
I think this...
It's wild, man.
If?
Now I put another tape.
Let's see those shoulders.
Are you sure you're ready for this?
Oh, my God. This is perfect.
's An earthquake.
Oh shit.
No. No. No.
's an earthquake.
What is this?
How about a inside?
They filmed everything?
This could be a porno.
Okay.
Think of it.
Well, Christi. Do not use your eyes to see.
Use what is within you.
This is something different.
I'm doing, mesmerizing?
Focus Christi.
I need you to concentrate.
Concentrate on that, Christi?
Your time  through it, Christi.
Let me show you what he sees.
What the hell...
Let it take you there.
Let me show you.
I hate this family.
One room.
This girl is taking minutes?
Many colors.
I also see colors, man.
Butterflies.
There is a large bird in the door.
Why are you laughing?
There is a tent.
A tent?
Than?
Ryan?
As where we camped.
Entered the room of the girl.
Why are you looking like this?
Think I missed?
A teddy bear half the
room. Butterflies. A bird on the wall.
You sound familiar?
Bored?
She described Lila's room, Mike.
No brother, what happens? Are you high.
Mike. is describing
Lila's room.
Corniste more chocolate than me?
Is there, Christi?
Ryan. please. and turn it off.
It's in the room?
Is in the house?
Can you see it?
Why do the forces? Who is EP
Is there.
You stepped on something.
Are u serious?
No, do not disconnect anything.
What was that, a fuse?
By using that old cassette player?
The electricity returned.
How odd.
You hear that?
Yes.
Come With Me or .
Bring your camera. Go see your own.
According .
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Focus. I want you to concentrate, Ryan.
Shut up.
I'm imitating video.
Wait, that's the same thing the other night?
Where did he go?
Mike.
Mike, it's not funny. Are you?
Shit.
Mike? Mike, are you?
Mike?
It scared me a lot, Mike.
Ryan  think...
This is rare.
I think my camera begins to see.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I think I'm seeing something
It is a.
A jerk.
You saw the jerk?
There participate of imbecility in your aura, no?
This  around you. You're a jerk.
There they are.
Hello.
Hello love.
Like that?
Estan?
Is Uncle Mike.
That's not good.
Wait.
Mike looks like a huge pile of...
I do not look like me at all.
And that's what you do for a living?
It is similar to Feng Shui.
Is moving furniture.
So that no energy is blocked.
Should do with your home.
Hey.
Why?
Feel different
Your energy is blocked Mike?
I flow smoothly.
If you want to release my energy.
I... no longer what we mean.
Tell them... Tell them
night we had.
Was just...
We saw and heard strange things.
I heard about photographing spirits.
But I have not seen one in person.
What do you see?
Only  forms.
Could be a spirit. I suppose.
Usually these cameras do not see spirits.
Rather other pianos of existence.
Places where energy would travel displaced.
But it also might not function.
I do not know, it's weird.
But I do not think it's a failure.
I saw Lila's room and then
He was in the hallway.
Hey. Lila is asleep. And let us go.
Back at 11. Good night.
Hey, watch the camera.
Seriously.
Relax Ryan
I just want to see what it does.
You do not seriously think or see ghosts?
Si. I think it's very possible.
What?
The lights look beautiful with this.
You should try them with fungi.
Yes, I need wine.
Sure.
Red, white, Cabernet?
Pink.
Sauvignon.
Right back.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hello
Is anyone there?
Hey, you scared me.
Just me. I have the wine.
I think there's something here.
Than?
I think I felt something.
Ah. Yes?
Yes. Look through the camera
But I saw nothing.
They turn themselves off. Wait, I think that has night vision
.
There he is.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
It Must have been the wind.
You see something?
No.
Mike. do you see?
I go inside now.
What the hell is that?
Flew out of the pool.
Shut. You'll scare him.
What? I'll scare him?
Let's go.
Give me the camera.
What is this?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Mike  something here.
This is crazy.
Lila.
Hello beautiful. What are you doing here? It's cold.
Come inside.
It's cold. Let's go
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What the fuck
The pool was weird, but she was scared
more.
Perhaps we saw something,
but that camera is useless.
We turned the corner.
We turned and was there.
They asked what to here?
It was like in a coma. I do not know if you heard.
If it is sleepwalking. I do not know what I was doing.
Not sleepwalker. Always sleeps well
Hey look at this.
If?
There is heard here.
This is yours? Hey if
It is my rosary.
How odd
The burying saw these things here?
No. we did not see. But it is possible.
What are you doing?
You know papa has a new toy?
As you've got yours.
Yes.
Turns out my toy...
She saw something very interesting last night.
I think...
I think.
And you do not feel anything?
I do not want to talk about it.
About who love?
What does this button do?
The spiritual photography.
Hello?
Hello.
What happens to me? I'm going crazy.
Lila. what are you doing here?
Carino. that's blood?
You have in your hands? You're bleeding?
What happened?
Daughter, answer me, what happened? You're bleeding?
You're saying?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I do not know.
You hear that?
This talking backwards.
Bloody Mary said.
That which signif'ca?
It's a game. Niiios a game.
What kind? The game originally
You say it three times.
then he appears and tells you who you're going to marry.
But when I played,
as most plays.
You say your name  très times, and a damn
witch appears and takes you by the neck.
As Lila heard of that game?
No way.
I have no idea.
Old were you when you played?
I do not know. Was a girl. Such
once they told her friends.
Come see.
Than?
Look at this. Look.
Come see. Decode the case.
I look?
This Trente look.
Lived here? It uramente
.
But why you are here? Of 87
It is the same house where they recorded everything.
The place was burned in 92.
No bodies were recovered.
Whole family disappeared, including.
Including their hij as Katy and Christi.
And you think our daughter
Is talking to ghosts.
Elias being awakened in the night
. Playing with something that only she
And the camera can see.
The nirios are.
Not mean they have ghost.
Those who lived here
20 years ago, they put cameras
And they caught all kinds of crazy things.
And our house is built on them.
It's a joke of you and Mike?
No, look at this.
I feel that every time Mike comes
They are crazy to do together.
No. Not so. I swear.
I just want to know if there is something here
Or if I'm going crazy.
I'm going to feel better.
Well, I do
If? I can do it?
Have permission.
But not for many days.
As Mike. With this will suffice.
You put two cameras?
Is that is the control
To see if it is recording something special.
We have to turn the other here.
Just you gonna see your daughter sleep all night
. Nothing unusual about that.
Oche December 2013
2 dicieabre oche 2013
Okay.
Where?
Lila, that doing up?
It is very cold here.
Snuggle right, Lila.
Let me help.
Try to sleep.
What was that?
No problem.
Well, Lila.
Go to bed, good night, okay?
Now he goes to sleep.
Hello my love. I saw something in your room last night
you and Skyler aunt.
Linda?
What woke you last night?
Tobi did.
Tobi did?
Who is Tobi?
Lila, who is Tobi?
Lila?
There was a dark shape that was floating
I call and Tobi.
Not given any fear.
And I know it sounds strange, but I think it's our
ghost.
Emily  believe me crazy. But remember that you
comment
Lila said Tobi awoke last night?
Well look at this.
88. Is the
Do not sit there. Tobi is the place.
Oh. forgiveness. Tobi is sitting now?
Are talking about Tobi. Sorry
Tobi.
Is it a coincidence.
And in 4 years.
The girls grew up a little and we
ponytail.
Here comes.
So they kept contact...
Tobi.
That pretty.
No Mike.
This is before Facebook.
It is hard to keep in touch with people.
Think it's a boy or girl?
Because Tobi would be a great name
stripper.
In our center court.
Strong applause. It is Tobi.
Listen to the bed if it works.
Record things that others do not.
It is crap. You hear?
Addition Tobi is not a common name.
Perhaps she saw the video.
Mike is very pequeha.
You have no idea who is a VHS.
You think was there, shoved and gave
play? Found the cassette think?
You make me feel old.
The children do not know is VHS.
What is that?
You heard?
Really?
Yes. Ryan.
These seeing something?
What is that?
That viewing something?
Ryan.
Than?
I think is...
freezer making ice.
Do not give me...
A Tobi likes the ice?
We should remove it from the freezer.
Perhaps this is why a bad mood.
Is too coincidental.
's What I think.
Mike.
Shut up, everyone is asleep.
That noise came from beyond Ryan.
Well, give me the camera. Give me the camera.
Mike. there is something up. But it's different.
It moves.
Ryan, let's go. You'll wake her.
So I want to see where it went.
Can you see anything?
No. I'm not sensing anything.
God!
Daddy what are you doing?
Pardon my love.
Sorry, sorry. Everything is fine. Quiet.
Back to sleep.
I cry because...
Your strong yelled.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Your you yelled before the face of your daughter
. Also shout. I could not see anything.
You know who shouts Mike?
Why?
Because I saw this with the camera.
It looks more concentrated.
Have more shape. This dark.
And Mike. I felt this thing through me.
I think it's a face.
It's not human but is crazy.
Why we still need two cameras here?
Not just a camera covering the room well.
This
talking to her and telling her to do things.
And not alone in his room.
It is moving around the house.
I just want to know where you are going and wants.
This better.
December 2013
What are you doing? Put that down. Let it go.
What are you doing?
You can not play with matches
or turning on the gas.
What were you thinking?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Ryan. Ryan.
This is my bible. Always up.
I was in the fireplace.
's What I wanted to burn.
The rosary
treatment was also burning in the fireplace.
What kind of game is played with matches?
He said he was playing a game with Julie.
Only use the first one I found.
She sabla you had the book up there, you probably know where this
.
He does not even know it.
She sabla you had the book up there, you probably know where this
.
I do not know. I went to bed, return here.
The angel is then falls.
I do not know, I went to bed and when
And then the angel falls.
Got things had fallen.
I do not know. I went to bed, return here.
I do not know. There she seems.
No, it does not seem like her.
It seems to be different.
And I did not want to believe it but I think Ryan is right.
Initially
perhaps not believe it, but Ryan is right.
It seems to be different.
And I did not want to believe it but I think Ryan is right.
There is something in our house.
Please, I need you to tell me
going to stop talking to Tobi.
If you stop to talk to Toby.
Lila. I need you to tell me
Lee.
Lila?
Read. Look at your mother.
Lee. Look at your mother.
Read.
Lila, look at your Marna.
Read. Look at your mother.
Read.
Lila. look at your Marna.
6Me can look?
Tobi is my friend.
Toby is my friend.
Can you look me please?
He is not your friend
He is not... No.
Toby is not... no.
Toby is not your friend. all right?
He is not your friend.
He is not... No.
Toby is not your friend, right?
Toby is not... no.
Okay? And mom and dad want to talk
no more with him.
And marl and potato
no longer want to talk to him.
It's okay? And mom and dad want to talk
no more with him.
And marl and potato
no longer want to talk to him.
Lee promised you'd stop talking. You promise me
'll stop talking to Tobi?
I promise.
Lee promised you'd stop talking.
All right.
I promise.
Lee promised you'd stop talking.
All right.
Good.
I promise.
All right.
So the tapes start at 88.
A lot of things for Christmas
and live with their marl.
Sure
I have not seen them all. but suddenly jumps
footage and everything is different.
6No see anything, just...? No.
Mom and boyfriend
are totally absent in the video.
... They are gone anywhere?
Not appear in any tape.
And it's like this weird cult
deal with these girls now.
And Maman Marna this other woman.
6Qué is that, a milk Baho?
Who are these people? Oh my God.
It Is  I had another dream.
And fell on the stairs.
Toby says that since these Carino way.
These progressing well.
6Qué all mean?
I do not know. But such is their leader.
It is as if the girls
prepare for something.
The need them.
We approached.
Dicembre 2013
• Ami 2013
Even with the tapes?
Bi.
I try to see if there is a connection.
6Son that we saw the other night?
No, it's a different night, but does the same
. Literally they do.
Every night, like a ritual.
Not a normal home video.
It's like a training tape.
6TE what this show?
I'm not sure. It is very fuzzy.
Dejale show only what he sees.
Let it guide you.
'm Sure it's food.
Is so blurry.
I see... a TV.
What?
I see many TVs.
What demo ..
I seeing this.
I see toys.
Colleague ...
I see many toys.
I see people.
Brothers.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I'm sure you are brothers.
Colleague , <j, what the hell?
I think they see me.
Keep the
Only he can be there.
6Que doing up?
6Que happens? Tell me
Are making a lot of noise.
6Hago much noise?
Pope will rise and will ensure that...
Www.gnula.nu
Good. What the...
www.gnula.nu
Www.gnula.nu
Ryan, you...
www.gnula.nu
Www.gnula.nu
This is the tape that
I spoke last night. Look at her.
Www.gnula.nu
Expected, play it again.
Look, put it slower.
Lee sneezes and she says "Health".
These people, I think watching us.
And these tapes are from 20 years ago...
But they can see what happens here with us
and Leela.
6Todo  I have to do is draw?
Good.
My God.
What is all this?
I not think they're just random.
I think there's a pattern.
Some are made known to me.
I know I've seen this before.
Emily, these symbols on the wall
are on tape too.
Were in the room the girls. And that there
symbol is used by a coven...
Ilamado midwives.
... What are witches?
These midwives egan to the Middle Ages.
Emily, they were in worship the devil.
Also used symbols to open...
Carries them to different places and times.
My God.
I know.
What is that?
I do not know.
Lee.
There's something different with her.
What the hell
Lee, are you okay.
Carino.
Linda, breathe. Breathe cute.
Calm down.
Well, good girl.
Breathe... good girl.
What were you doing?
The take me.
Who? Who?
Who?
What the hell.
What is that?
No, I see nothing.
There is nothing out.
Ivam, get out of here
God. Curse.
Hello.
6puedo please talk to Father Langley?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Our house has been...
we believe it is a cult or something and affects our daughter.
I was waiting but seek
talk to Father Alessio.
Well I will call again at four.
She's been acting weird
and more and more things have been happening...
We not know what to do.
Ten other.
Have a special baby.
So is.
It will. You remember what happened last night at
your room when you were in the corner?
Well...
We come and put you in bed
again and said...
The take me. "
Who?
6It Toby? Please tell me.
Lee, tell me
Lee, tell your Marna.
Lee. where you take?
With the other.
Hello. I'm Emily.
We are so grateful that you came
, thank you very much.
I just hope poderles help.
Yes. I think it can. And we explain.
This camera captures
things that none of the other sees. It is crazy.
sure nothing unusual happened in a house before?
No.
I view this camera tapes...
Those who are 20 years.
It is as if they too will use the camera...
To see these things too.
Father, see this.
I started small and
thought it was a failure.
It is dark when the camera focuses.
And big, as if it grew more.
Has anyone ever experienced this before
elsewhere?
Nothing like that. Y
found these tapes these...
Girls playing Bloody Mary.
The same game Leela played the other night.
6de where he learned that?
They recorded themselves doing all these weird rituals
.
You do it very well.
Toby will be so proud of you.
They believe that this is the Toby
Leela speaks?
Si. We think so.
6Hay addition to some other name Toby? No.
Only No.
Toby.
Why?
Well, sometimes the spirits tend...
Hide their identity.
is your... true nature. And they use another name.
As described and what I know, which is very little
...
It seems as if her daughter was harassed by a demon
or demonic presence.
If this is so we should go.
Leave house.
We have to go, right? We have to go.
've Never felt anything like it.
Spirits do not haunt houses, but
people. If you leave this house will follow.
Demons feed on fear.
The more attention given.
Stronger it becomes.
Larger. If flee
We can not ignore what is happening father.
It would be nice if I talk to your daughter?
You think?
A bit shy.
That name mean anything to you?
Should not?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Here it goes. This is your friend?
As Marna?
Let me... do not tell me. let me see.
Griselda.
It Géraldine?
Is Bubba. does not read?
I like that name.
I think it's great.
Bubba looks hot. I can bariarlo?
I wet it something?
Let me sprinkle a little.
A Bubba likes. This very pleased.
6Puedo put some in your head...
To make you feel cool?
How about that?
Much better, <j, no?
Yes. <J, you feel better now?
Well, <j, what are you and Bubba tonight?
Do you have a secret to me?
What is caririo?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I'm sorry, it is not.
Well, I'm fine. I just want...
Take care of your daughter, right?
All right.
I will return soon. Just stay calm.
Rela that.
Cursed  useless cure.
After what the father said
I went back and researched further.
I found this tape in the camera.
I thought it was blank, but look.
This is your home.
Yes. look at the date.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Three days before we moved.
You hear?
I believe that the leader is speaking.
No, perhaps only a contractor or someone
.
6Ves he talks about the house?
It Is all of what he speaks.
No, says entry point.
The fact that we moved to this...
Home in specific
all that we saw did not seem coincidental to me.
No, no, no Higgens. Hubber.
H-U-B-B.
Exactly Hubber. Katie Hubber,
is what I've been trying to tell.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
That's impossible.
Because I'm watching your card and your number is on your card.
They say you never heard of it.
Never worked for them.
6Por we looked at in this neighborhood? And
deal. It seemed too good to be true.
Remember?
Si.
6de where wine? As you meet her?
I Call today to the agency and have no record
who worked there.
No one ever heard from her.
Than?
But that's... that's...
What if.
If someone put us here on purpose?
What if the hoever cons iro
to bring us to this house?
Think it's possible?
Where he came from?
Sure you wanna do this?
Ol, dl.
You need sleep  affection.
Just wake me if anything happens, okay?
Well, I will remain alert if something happens.
December 2013
• 2013
What the hell?
Emily wakes.
You hear that?
You heard?
Something knocked the camera in the hallway.
Not you hear anything?
Do not.
Hello. Hello caririo.
Sorry, go back to sleep.
Back to sleep.
No Marna issues.
Ryan
Stay here. <J, passing colleague?
What is that noise?
I do not know.
What do you see?
There's nothing here.
I think I heard something.
Where?
No.
You see anything?
You hear something?
Mike  stay calm. <J, okay?
You hear what the father said. Not good fear.
Mike. move on.
What the hell was that?
Mike was huge.
Holy shit. I do not know where it went.
Curse!
What was that?
Fuck. What the hell colleague?
Wait, wait, I see. It is in the tree
What the hell is?
No.
IColega!
Where is Mike, you see?
Stay up Emily. She locks the door.
Where is it?
Curse Ryan.
Next I stay with marl.
(Do not touch me like that fellow
moved Dress
What the hell What the hell is going
This at the entrance
What is
Do not let the kitchen
Cque?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Okay, okay Let
What the hell
? jVamonos
! Go go go
curse.!
Colleague curse! <J, What the hell was that?
What happens to your house?
Scailar come soon and Mike and I
go as fast as we can, <j, si?
Good.
Just stay here.
Well, I love you.
Back as soon as we can, <j, si?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)