Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
Captain, where are you?
I'm heading there with my sister's family.
We're almost there, so hang on.
Is this the right way?
I drove through here dozens of times.
All the other roads would be packed with cars.
Oh...
Please give us a ride.
I have a little girl. I have a wife too.
Please take us to the port.
I'm begging you...
I wasn't bitten! It's not a bite!
If we look dangerous,
at least take our girl. Please.
Sir?
Please! I'm begging you!
Sir! Please!
Jung-seok...
Don't say anything until we're on the ship!
Can you tell us
why this dreadful virus has spread, Paul?
Well, unfortunately, we don't have much information
other than the fact that it started
out of a bio-factory in South Korea.
Uh, it's unclear exactly
how this unidentified virus initially began to spread.
Of course,
sheer pandemonium broke loose in South Korea.
And many people began to believe a rumor
that was circulating online
about a safe region somewhere further down south...
Busan? Is this the correct pronunciation?
That's right. People were evacuated there.
But in the end, no place was truly safe.
But there is an absolute safe place
on the Korean Peninsula.
That's correct.
I believe you're referring to North Korea.
Perhaps it's fortunate
that this happened before the reunification!
So it turns out.
So how long before the Korean government
lost all control?
Just one day.
Please move slowly!
This is Alpha One.
Move on!
Be careful!
This is Alpha Two.
We have about 50 civilians waiting for boarding.
Uncle.
Are you all right, Dong-hwan?
Yes.
Where's Chul-min?
He went to get some relief aid.
But shouldn't we have arrived in Japan by now?
I'm sure we're almost there, don't worry.
Captain!
What is it?
We're being rerouted to Hong Kong.
Why all of sudden?
They're not telling me why.
I have to go check something.
Excuse me.
I'll ask about it,
so go and check what's going on.
Yes, sir.
Excuse me.
Uh.
Sir!
Is it true that we are rerouting to Hong Kong?
Please return to your seats.
We need to understand the situation, sir!
Everyone's getting nervous.
Please return to your seat
and await further instructions.
Sir!
We have a problem.
We've found an infected person
on the lower deck cabins.
We get ramen too?
Come in. Leave your bag here.
It looks good.
Please come in.
- Infected!
- What?
What is it?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
It's okay, I'll be right here.
Breathe, Dong-hwan. I'm not going anywhere.
It'll be okay.
Look at me.
I'll be right here with you.
What do I do?
Your uncle's here, Dong-hwan.
Sis...
- What do we do?
- We have to go.
We have to go now, come on!
- Let's go!
- Your uncle...
We have to go!
We must leave.
Come on!
Sis!
Sis! Sis!
Honey!
No!
There is even a case of infected hosts
that were found on the last lifeboats
to leave for Hong Kong.
After that, the neighboring countries
decided to no longer accept any more refugees.
In effect, Korea became completely quarantined.
Yes, it's been four years already.
Yes. Four years.
Wake him up.
Hey! Wake up!
That's enough!
We are not here to fight.
The boss wants to see you.
Hey!
Come on.
What are you doing here?
Let's leave.
Let go of me.
Hyung!
"Hyung."
It means "brother," doesn't it?
You two brothers? Huh?
No, no, no.
He is my dead wife's brother.
Not brother.
That sounds like a real tragic story.
Have a seat.
I don't know what the hell is it
with you people from the peninsula?
You, uh... have an air about you.
You have a lot of sad, sad tales...
Let's get down to business.
Should I say "your country"
or "the peninsula"?
Look, I, I heard a rumor...
There seems to be some people
that are going back down
into the peninsula
to make their own fate.
Zombies don't give a damn about all
that gold and money,
which is just laying around there unguarded.
I think it's ingenious.
Wow.
You want us to go back in there?
Have you lost your mind?
My brother,
my mind is completely sound, thank you.
Okay.
So...
the neighboring countries around the peninsula
are controlling every ship
and plane that crosses the border.
How would you get in or out?
It's been done.
You don't need to worry about the coast guard.
As long as we keep paying them,
the ships go in, the ships go out.
As a matter of fact, technically,
we had the money and the truck.
Twenty million dollars.
Until we went missing halfway here.
Where was the last time we...
On the Omok Bridge.
Mok-dong?
What?
Look, I don't think it's too difficult.
You just go in at night,
you get the truck, come back with the money,
and don't worry about those zombies.
I hear they are practically blind at night.
So...
How much money we get?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, that's the question, isn't it?
Half.
That is, if you come back alive.
That's 2.5 million dollars per head.
Now listen to me.
You have no idea when or even
if the government is ever going
to grant you any refugee status,
so you might as well make your own goddamn future.
Think!
We just have to hop on a boat,
and bring the truck back.
What's so hard about that?
It'll only take half a day.
Are you nuts? You want to go back there?
Then do you want to keep living here,
getting treated like scum?
You should have let me die
with my son and wife!
Why did you do it?
Had I let you die, everyone on
that ship would've died.
Am I wrong?
It was a sensible decision.
Sensible decision, my ass.
Did you even try?
Jung-seok...
You're tormented too!
You just gave up!
Whatever, forget it.
Okay.
Well, I'm going to go there,
so you can do whatever you want.
Let's just not bump into each other.
It's hard for both of us.
Bye-bye. Bye-bye.
Aren't they bastards from the peninsula?
- What?
- Where the virus came from!
Should you be letting them in here?
Move aside.
- Let go of me.
- Stop.
Do you even care about the others?
Stop it.
Is he infected?
Come on. Stop.
I won't take your money, so just leave!
You go ahead.
You're entering the peninsula waters.
Turn back.
This is Z055 Chungpyung.
- Hello?
It's all good if there's no response.
Almost there!
No need to be so serious.
Soon, you'll be rich!
Take what you need.
Don't forget, the zombies are blind at night
and sensitive to sound.
And the important thing.
We'll drop you off
and stay at sea nearby for three days.
Take these.
One for you.
And... another.
Call me when you get to the port with the truck
and we'll pull up the boat.
And lastly!
You escaped out of there alive,
so you know better...
Don't screw up trying
to save each other for nothing.
Don't worry. We know.
Great!
Do not let us down.
It makes me nervous that you two know each other.
I know.
We have to pull this off no matter what,
so don't let your personal emotions
get mixed up in the way.
We won't even see each other after this,
so don't worry.
Fine.
Whatever, man.
GOD HAS FORSAKEN US
We're not on a tour, you know.
Let's hurry things along,
we should leave before sunrise.
All right, let's get it over with.
Jeez.
Is it working?
Nice!
It's unrecognizable now. My goodness.
The city became a ruin in just four years.
Did you live near here?
I used to drive a cab.
So I pretty much know all the roads.
At the very least,
those jerks put together a good team.
A HEALTHY, CAREFREE COUNTRY
Could that be it?
Where?
The plate number is 6431, right?
We'll find out soon.
You stay here, I'll go alone.
What?
Hey, hey, hey! Wait!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Come on, come on, come on!
What's with you?
Is that the truck?
No, it isn't.
It should be nearby.
Let's look around a bit more.
There, I see one more.
Let's check it out.
Okay.
I'll go have a look. You stay here.
Stop it!
I'm not on a tour, you know.
We'll go together.
Mister.
Let's take a look.
Are they Unit 631?
No. They're not.
Jackpot, we found it.
It was true...
What they said was true.
It's all in US dollars. How much is all this?
We confirmed it, so let's get going.
Okay.
Jeez.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hey! Over here!
He must've been the last person to make contact.
How unfortunate.
He could've been a millionaire.
But it's good for us.
Let's pull him out and go.
Oh, jeez...
He stinks...
Move your leg. Thank you.
Thank you.
Idiots.
Are you okay?
I'm fine, I wasn't bitten.
Gosh, what are they up to?
Get in the car, go!
Back it up!
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Come on, come on, come on!
All right!
Let's go!
Go! Go!
We're clear, we're clear!
Thank you...
So the money's really there?
You're a millionaire!
Yes!
Awesome!
What will you do with the money?
Me? Uh...
Maybe I'll hire a chauffeur.
Like a real millionaire!
So we just have to get
to the harbor and call them in.
This is a piece of cake!
Give me the satellite phone.
Huh? Sure, hold on.
Here.
What's that?
Just drive!
Go, go, go! Just go!
Hop in, if you want to live.
Sorry!
You must've been scared.
Yu-jin, I told you not
to act so friendly to strangers.
Sit back properly.
Dang, he passed out.
Did I not tell him to buckle up?
Joon-i, can you drive through them?
I'm not sure.
Then what? Do I need to get involved?
Ooh...
Ooh.
Uh?
Really?
The ground was weird, it wasn't my fault.
Oh.
I really liked that one, though.
CITY NIGHT CLUB
It's a grocery truck. Nice.
It looks new.
- Who's that?
- He's alive!
- Please, help me...
- Be careful.
- Help me, I'm begging you...
Help me, please.
What the hell's going on?
He's just an infected, you jerks.
Have you never seen one before?
Please...
It's all right, come here.
Sir, please, help me...
I'm begging you...
- Give it to me.
- Here you go!
Sir...
Nice shot!
Wow, he killed him properly.
Damn it!
It got on my pants. I should get it washed.
Here.
Let's get back, the sun will rise.
Shit...
- Let's go.
- The zombies are coming!
Huh?
You little rascals!
You brought something dangerous instead
of what you were supposed to get.
Hey!
You'd have been locked up for insubordination
if it were the old days!
Lieutenant Yoon! Captain Hwang!
Assemble!
Aren't you going to make a report?
Did you get what I asked?
Salute! Division commander, we did not get it!
Hey!
How could you not get it?
The ROK-US Combined Forces Command
is waiting for my call!
Without batteries...
Come on!
- Are you having fun?
- Joon-i!
- Captain Hwang!
- Grandpa!
How long will you go on with that army stuff?
Aren't you sick of it?
No, it's for real this time!
The newly appointed Major Jane
is totally different.
She and I get along.
And it seems like we'll get rescued soon.
Listen to me, I'm good friends with her, so--
- Stop it! I'm sick of it!
- Yu-jin, you believe me, right?
Who are you?
I guess you've never experienced
a wild dog hunt before.
You should've known that such trucks
would attract their attention.
"Truck"?
Who's that?
Mom!
Sir! Please!
He was almost caught by Unit 631.
You went outside again?
I convinced her to go.
Why don't you ever listen to me?
I'm sorry, Mom.
They're batteries. Grandpa, she got batteries!
Okay! Okay!
They fit.
Hi, Jane? Jane? Major Jane?
Oh, Jane! Oh, Jane! Okay!
Are you okay?
- I'm okay! Yeah!
- You should turn it on.
We are strong soldiers! No problem!
I'm Yu-jin!
When are you coming?
- So people still live here...
- They said they're coming!
Who are you?
Are you with Unit 631?
I don't know what 631 is.
I came to Incheon by boat yesterday.
From Hong Kong.
What?
From where?
Damn, the sun is rising.
Let's hurry up.
The third platoon is returning!
Open the gate!
There are one, two, three,
four, five, six boxes of cookies.
That's all correct.
Scrap soup again?
Eat if you want to live.
That looks good. Have a great meal!
Have a nice meal. Have a nice meal.
The third platoon is back!
They're here!
- They're back!
- They're here!
Great work, everyone.
Look! Isn't it awesome?
- Yeah!
- It sure is.
My boys worked so hard!
Bring us a can of tuna, that's all I ask!
- I'm sorry, sir...
- No, bring one.
We were told to keep a tight lid on supplies.
If I keep handing out stuff,
there won't be anything left.
And Captain Seo is...
One can is too much?
That's not it...
Bring it.
They're serving food at the cafeteria.
Get it!
I said bring it!
So I should just have scraps?
That's not...
Do you want it?
I have to report to Captain Seo first.
Just bring it, asshole!
Report to a guy who's never even fought before?
He's my commander.
- Sergeant...
- Piss off, you bastard!
- What was that?
- I'm talking here!
- Hello?
- Where is it coming from?
- I heard something.
- What? A person?
- Hang on.
Sir, we have a wild dog here.
- What?
- Get him.
What's a wild dog?
Are you soldiers?
Help me, I'm not from here.
Get up, you bastard.
Has the game started?
It hasn't, sir.
Take him to the arena.
- Yes, sir.
- Let's go!
We have a new player!
Keep sucking up to Captain Seo,
and I'll kill you both.
Got that?
You little...
Hey! Hey!
He probably wasted all the flares
without knowing what to get.
That idiot.
He brought so much useless crap last time.
What the hell?
We are strong soldiers!
Strong! Strong!
Strong. Strong.
No one ever came to rescue us in four years,
but some chump change was all it took?
What about your group?
They're all dead.
Everyone.
We got a fresh one!
Hey there, cutie!
Who were those soldiers?
They're called Unit 631.
They used to be a military unit dispatched
to rescue civilians.
You were with them?
We lived there before we escaped.
At first.
They sent out SOS signals for a few years,
which were left unanswered.
After that, they gave up everything,
and now they're all crazy.
Hm.
I'm leaving.
Yes?
Bang!
Awesome, that's great.
I'm not someone who takes bribes, take it back.
Gosh, you're making me sad.
I don't take bribes!
Look at it, it's Black Label.
Thanks, I was finishing my last drink.
Here, accept my drink.
Nothing to report again?
No, nothing happened.
Sergeant Hwang stole a truck
from wild dogs overnight,
and was boasting like crazy,
acting all high and mighty...
So where did our valiant sergeant go today
and what adventure did he have?
What did he bring in?
Captain, that's the weird thing.
The truck was full of US dollars.
US dollars?
How much?
It was quite a bit.
About 20 bags full of them.
But why do you think those idiotic wild dogs
were transporting completely useless money?
Where is it now?
So they took the truck.
What about the satellite phone?
It should be by the driver's seat.
Sir, I'm not from here!
I'm from Hong Kong!
This is brand new.
It's rare. Today is your lucky day.
Got anything else?
I have... a satellite phone!
With a satellite phone,
we can all get out of here!
- Show us!
- Right here!
- You lying sack of shit!
- He doesn't have it!
Where do you think they
were heading with this money?
Sir, where's the truck?
Stop that!
Stop! Please!
Ah...
He's really fresh!
This guy's in good shape. He's a Grade A!
Can you run well?
No?
What should his number be?
Give him Park Chan-ho's number.
Number 61!
Number 61 it is!
Major League pitcher!
That's a great number!
Turn around!
I'm betting a chocolate bar on him.
Sir, where's the truck?
Sir! I'm not from here!
There's money in the truck! Go check it out!
We can all leave if we have that, you idiots!
What...
Hello?
Where are you? The sun is out.
What's going on?
Hello. Who are you?
What?
Who the hell are you?
Where's the money?
Where are you going?
I don't think we should go out...
Number 61! Get out!
Get the hell out!
I don't care who you are.
Just bring the money.
The terms are the same
as the guys we sent in...
Half the money to anyone
that brings it out. Okay?
Are you saying we can get out of here?
We are waiting around Incheon Port.
You call me when you get there.
It's so easy!
Easy, easy. I can do it. I can do it.
All right.
You can drive, right?
Let's just go now, Mom.
I'll bulldoze them all with my car.
You'll just go in there? In broad daylight?
Run faster!
It's time for us. To say goodbye
Let's meet again soon
Hey, buddy!
If you don't hurry, the doors will shut!
You must be tired.
You did great.
How about a feast?
You want it? Really?
Have some ramen!
Eat slowly! Share them with your friends!
Greedy bastards.
You should share them!
It's too dangerous now.
Let's move after sundown.
I think we can go now, though...
Go? Go where?
Grandpa, we're moving. Let's pack up.
Move?
Where?
We're going to Incheon Port.
Incheon Port? Are we going to ride a boat?
Okay!
No, no, no!
We must stay here until Jane
comes to rescue us.
It was so hard convincing her!
If Major Jane is coming,
tell her to come to the port.
No way!
You said you two are close.
I guess you aren't.
We're close.
Okay, it's doable.
Incheon? Incheon Port?
- Grandpa, hurry!
- Okay.
You'll take a crazy old man and little kids
to steal a truck from armed soldiers?
Then should I continue living here with my girls?
If you're scared, stay here.
I'll give you this place at a cheap price.
Get him a first aid kit,
and get some sleep. We'll leave after sundown.
Why did you save me earlier?
I was going to leave, but she wanted to save you.
Dad told us we should help the weak
before he went to heaven.
You looked weak.
Stop yapping and go to bed.
No!
I'm going to bed soon too, so go to sleep!
I don't want to!
One! Two!
She's always like that...
She thinks she's so big now.
Maybe we should've left you there.
You're complaining when we saved you.
You look like a zombie.
Mm...
How long does it take to get to Incheon Port?
If we find an unobstructed route,
it'll only take thirty minutes.
Thirty minutes, thirty minutes, thirty minutes...
What about zombies? Wouldn't it be dangerous?
They bite and stuff.
- Captain.
- Yes?
We need to get out of here.
Forget about the zombies!
Should we bring Sergeant Hwang?
He's more dangerous than the zombies.
You're right.
I can keep the gatekeepers off our backs,
but sharp-witted Sergeant Hwang
might get suspicious.
Yes, you're right.
Then I just have to find a way
to distract him, right?
Sir? Sir!
Sir! Please!
Sir! Please just take my girl!
Jung-seok, why are you the only one alive?
Put it down.
You'll drain the batteries.
Did Major Jane say she's coming to Incheon Port?
Huh?
She should. She has to.
She better rescue my little darlings.
My treasures.
Yu-jin and Joon-i,
they're the beacon of hope in this hell.
I'll get them out of this hell no matter what.
Major Jane is coming, right?
Are you okay?
We stole these when we fled. Take what you need.
I actually saw you before.
I...
came across your family
when I was fleeing to board the ship.
You begged me to take your girl.
Why are you telling me that now?
Because you feel guilty?
There were 31 cars.
There were 31 cars that drove past us.
I thought the first car would stop to help us.
Or maybe the next one...
All 31 cars just drove by.
You're indebted to my girls.
Yu-jin, I'm buttoning you up.
Stand up straight!
Are we going on a boat ride now?
Yes, we just have to get something first.
What about my cars?
No way, we can't take them all.
Then just this one!
Put it down.
Please, just one!
Let me take one!
Let's go.
Joon-i.
Stay here. If I'm not back by sunrise,
head back home.
Just the three of us?
What about you?
How will you come home?
I'll find my way somehow,
so don't worry and head home.
And don't ever leave the car, got it?
Answer me.
Okay.
Yu-jin, come here.
I'll be back soon. Listen to your sister, okay?
You'll really be back soon, right?
Of course, I'll be right back.
Commander, take good care of my girls.
Let's go.
It's an emergency exit that we found
when we lived here.
What the hell?
Is that it?
Yes, that's the one.
Let's move quickly.
Ah, ah, ah.
I brought good news.
Last night, the third platoon led by Sergeant Hwang
brought home a truck.
There was enough food for everyone to eat
for an entire month.
You've worked so hard, I know you did!
So tonight... there'll be an unlimited game
for 24 hours!
And remember.
Have fun like there's no tomorrow.
Have a great time!
There will be no tomorrow.
Stop cheering. Doesn't he seem strange?
I think he's high.
I'm not sure. Let's enjoy this!
Hey, look over there.
Shouldn't we report that?
There aren't that many. Why bother reporting?
Forget it, don't mind them.
Listen.
Since you owe my girls,
do me a favor later.
Johnnie Walker Black Label!
You're back.
Are you supposed to have booze here?
Well...
The game is about to start. What brings you here?
I haven't seen your face in ages.
Could I have a sip?
Sure, help yourself.
- Really?
- Sure.
So why are you here?
Do you have something to report?
No, I was just curious
what gets you up in the morning.
Hm?
It's good?
So good!
If you love it that much,
you can take the bottle.
It's my gift to you.
- What's with you?
- What?
I begged for some snacks
for my boys to boost morale,
but all we got were scraps.
You were acting so cheap.
So why the sudden generosity?
I think I told everyone with my speech earlier.
We owe so much to you and your men...
Bullshit!
I was just kidding.
Captain Seo, are you hiding something from me?
No, of course not.
Captain Seo, I...
Private Kim?
Do you visit Captain Seo's quarters frequently?
No... I do not.
Ah.
You two are a thing?
- Yes.
- My apologies!
I'm so clueless.
I'll leave you two alone.
Just the two of you...
Hm?
I'll tell the boys to avoid dropping in,
so have a great time.
Have a hot time, okay?
All right.
Love, love is...
Sir, the preparation is done.
Shall we get to the truck?
You go ahead. I have something to do first.
Yes, sir.
Does he have a death wish or what?
Joon-i, look up ahead! Quickly!
It's a march.
That road is too close to Unit 631.
Aren't we going to go greet Mom?
The money is intact.
Hey, can't you take me with you?
I really want to get out of here.
Go where? Who told you about that?
I overheard Captain Seo talking
on the satellite phone.
Please take me with you.
Satellite phone?
Where did you get it?
The wild dog we found in the truck had it.
Private Kim!
Aren't you going to see the game?
Answer naturally.
I'm all right.
You always say that. Oh, right.
That wild dog who came with the truck,
that guy was no joke.
He was struggling so much to survive.
I bet all my canned goods on him!
I'll see you later.
Where is the phone now?
It's not with me.
Captain Seo has it. He'll be here soon.
Get going.
I can't wait long.
Act naturally when that bastard comes, got it?
Okay...
Number 61!
What are you doing? Let's move!
Captain...
Long time no see, Captain Seo.
Min-jung, you were alive. Gosh.
You have the satellite phone, right?
Hand it over.
The satellite phone...
Give me a second.
Mm. Oh.
Wasn't that a gunshot?
Like hell it was. Just shut up and eat this tuna.
Hey!
Oh.
Let's go get Mom.
Look! That bastard!
Gun! Get the guns!
- Are you okay?
- Yes...
Can you get up?
Yes, I can get up. I can get up.
Stay behind me.
Hey, where did he go?
Jesus Christ...
Min-jung, I was so worried...
That's mine, give it back...
Sergeant!
Where did that bastard go?
Go look for him.
Block the entrance!
Move!
Fire! Fire!
Hey. Go forward.
Damn it!
Jung-seok!
Sergeant!
Come on!
Hurry! Get in!
Get in! Come on!
Snap out of it!
Come on!
Hurry!
Go after them!
Captain, are you okay?
What do we do now, sir?
Captain!
You did all you can.
That's what matters.
Get it together.
Sergeant Hwang!
Step on it!
It's time for us. To say goodbye
Let's meet again soon
Grandpa, hurry!
Okay!
Open the window.
Mom!
We came to greet you!
Why don't you ever listen to me?
Come on!
Yee-haw!
- Hold on.
- Okay!
Hey! Stop with the damn flares!
Just kill them all!
They're behind us!
Hold on tight!
Come on!
You asshole!
He's not bad.
Pull up closer, asshole!
This way, move up!
Kill him!
Watch the front, asshole!
Hold the wheel!
Hey!
Turn on the lights.
To our right!
Beside you!
Watch out!
Hold on tight!
Go over to the right!
Hey! Back up, back up, back up!
Back it up!
I said back it up, asshole!
Just step on it!
Back the shit up!
What the hell are you doing? Back it up!
You bastard!
We're almost there.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
We arrive at Incheon Port in 15 minutes.
Joon-i.
Is that the boat? Oh, yes!
Yu-jin...
Yu-jin, are you okay?
Hi.
Joon-i!
Put down your gun! Come on!
Drop it!
Do you want to see her head blown up?
Put it down!
Kick it! Kick it away!
Yes, that's it.
I can finally get off this peninsula...
When I leave, I'm going to live
to the fullest in Hong Kong.
They won't know what I did here.
I'm going to be a good man.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
I'll thank you every night.
I really mean it. Thank you so much.
I love you all!
Now!
Okay...
No!
Grandpa...
Grandpa, are you okay?
Mom! Mom...
The sun is rising.
A horde's coming.
We have to depart!
The money's here.
Huh?
It's not him.
How many times did they switch?
Nice to meet you...
- Nice to meet you too.
- Thank you.
Get rid of the body!
Hey, stop!
Get the money!
Shut the back hatch! Zombies are coming!
Grandpa...
Okay, I'm okay...
I wanted to pull you out of this hell...
No...
We were together all along.
Why would this be hell?
Thank you...
Grandpa...
Grandpa!
I'm sorry...
for making you live in this world...
Grandpa...
- Grandpa...
- I'm sorry...
Grandpa.
Grandpa!
Don't die...
Grandpa! No!
Grandpa...
Girls! The fireworks!
Hurry!
Joon-i!
You promised to do a favor for me.
Take the girls with you no matter what.
Got it?
Promise me, okay?
Get going!
Now!
Commander, thank you.
Mom's falling behind!
Are you all right?
You're safe now!
Jane...
Jane!
Jane! We have to save my mom!
I'm sorry. It's too late!
We can't put you in danger.
We must leave now!
Please, help my mom!
Please! Just this once!
Go! Let's go!
Let's go!
You must wait!
Please...
Remain calm...
Don't wait for me...
No...
Mom!
Don't do it, Mom!
Let go of me!
Mom!
Mom, please!
She made a very sensible decision.
It was for the best! For everyone...
Sensible decision, my ass.
Did you even try?
Jung-seok...
You're tormented too!
You just gave up!
We have to save Mom!
I'll bring back your mom.
Wait right here.
Mom! Run!
- Mom!
Mom!
Don't worry. She'll be okay.
She'll be fine.
In a few hours, a new world will be waiting.
The world I knew wasn't bad either.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org