Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Banzai!
Get your hands up!
Get down! Get down!
You, get down! Get down!
Put your hands
where I can see them!
Give me the money!
Stay there!
Come on!
Fuckin' hurry up!
Stay there!
The money! Hurry up!
Come on!
Go, go, go, go!
Get it all in there!
- These are delicious. I'll give you some.
- Come on! Come on! Let's hurry!
Come on! Come on!
Come on!
Hey.
This is a bracelet of hope.
Thank you!
Bernice, what are
we going to do?
Whatever we want to do.
We've never been
outside our house before.
Are we free?
Is this what it feels like?
I think it feels
much better than that.
I'm not a prisoner!
Kagome kagome
The bird in the cage.
When, oh, when will it come out
In the night of dawn
The crane and turtle slipped
Who is behind you now?
Good to see you children.
The Governor!
Come on, let's move!
Cocksucker, motherfucker.
Let me see your balls!
Don't mess my white shoes up!
- Is this him?
- Yes, sir, Governor.
He's a mean looking cuss,
ain't he?
They say...
you're a veritable phantasm,
that you have slipped through
the firm grasp of the law
more than any other man
on God's great earth.
They also say...
you're the one who robbed the
Bleufeur National Bank in P29,
killing, among others,
three tellers,
two security guards,
a retired Navy colonel,
his mother,
and a small boy,
whose only crime was masticating
a sweet cheery cherry gumball.
Suit, please, Yasujiro.
My granddaughter, Bernice,
has been lost to us, sir.
Ah, thank you, Yasujiro.
Bernice.
I have a fondness
for black leather.
I tell you truly, sir,
my granddaughter,
my sweet sugar pie,
I would have her returned to me.
I would have her
returned to me posthaste.
And you, sir...
you, sir, I am told,
are the man to do the job.
Bernice.
Bernice!
Bernice! Bernice!
Uh, Yasujiro.
Bernice...
Oh, my gosh.
I've seen better.
♪ My grandfather's clock
was too large for the shelf ♪
♪ So it stood 90 years
on the floor ♪
♪ It was taller by half
than the old man himself ♪
♪ Though it weighed not
a pennyweight more ♪
♪ It was bought on the morn
of the day that he was born ♪
♪ And was always
his treasure and pride ♪
♪ But it stopped,
short never to go again ♪
♪ When the old man died
♪ 90 years without slumbering
♪ Tick tock, tick tock
♪ His life seconds numbering
♪ It stopped,
short never to go again ♪
♪ When the old man died
My, my!
Don't that fit nice and snug.
Just beyond the point
where we now stand
lies a stretch of highway
where evil reigns.
It's ghost!
Ghost, I tell you!
Ooh!
In the way of the road!
- They can be anywhere.
- Shut up!
Now you see them.
Now you don't.
I said shut up!
Oh, it's alright, Sheriff.
I know many who subscribe
to that...
supernatural mumbo jumbo.
Ghosts...
perhaps.
Or, maybe, it's a bunch
of godless sodomites
that have taken
the land prisoner.
I fear my sweet Bernice
has fallen
into their perverse lair.
I can see why you
want her back.
What did he say?!
I'll kill you!
Yahhh!
No man is yet to be
a worthy opponent
for my Yasujiro.
I warn you, sir,
to quarrel with me is a mistake
many men have made
never to make again.
Better zip up there.
You don't want
to catch a cold.
It's a remarkable device,
isn't it?
Let me point out some
of its finer qualities.
Each arm is equipped
with an explosive device.
Oh, it's a protective measure.
These devices are connected
to a neuro sensor,
which can recognize the impulse
of a man intending
to strike a helpless woman.
Should that impulse be detected,
an alarm will sound
and if unheeded,
detonation will occur.
Your trousers are also
equipped with explosives.
The one at each testicle.
Boom!
Really?
I would have my Bernice
returned to me unsoiled, sir,
so best mind your manners.
Oh, now, I'm sure you've noticed
the charges around your throat.
You attempt to remove
or alter in any way
this magnificent wardrobe...
well,
I think you get the idea, sir.
If you can crawl your dog's hide
into the unknown and the unholy,
rescue my Bernice,
return her to me unscathed
to this very spot,
you will walk away a free man.
No!
Don't give my sister to him!
He's the devil.
A real devil!
Da-da-da-da-da-da!
Well, I assume you have
accepted my offer.
Shin?
Give the man the keys
to his automobile.
What is this?
Each bulb
on that colorful display
indicates
the passing of 24 hours.
at the conclusion
of three days,
Bernice must speak her name
into
the spectrograms microphone.
It is programmed
to identify her lovely voice.
Once voiceprint recognition
has been achieved,
the device will reward you
with two extra days
to complete your task.
At the end of five days,
if you have not
returned with Bernice
to get your suit
unlocked and removed,
the explosives will
detonate all at once.
I am certain this will prompt
a speedy execution of your task.
You got me, son?
What are you
gonna unlock it with?
Why...
right here.
Godspeed.
Any God can bear
to look upon your face.
Wait!
You cheap villainous maggot!
What a badass.
He's so cool.
Not much time, huh?
Alright.
It's alright!
Don't worry!
Don't touch my arm,
you fuckin' vermin.
I'm not vermin!
I'm a man!
Man right here!
What happened to Stella?
Bernice?
- Bernice?
- I'm not Bernice.
Where did you come from?
Do you want to join us?
There are so many of us.
What's your name?
Can't you speak?
Say something!
Hey! Talk!
We are almost there!
Hang in there!
Keep the time from moving!
If time starts moving...
...everything will explode again!
Keep time from moving!
Thick red blood!
He has thick red blood!
The Prophecy!
Time will move again!
Thick red blood!
He has thick red blood!
It is time!
Thick red blood!
Maybe someday...
...these children can drink
wonderful water...
No! No, no, no.
Don't touch me.
- Don't touch me. No, no, no.
- ...breathe wonderful air. live in a wonderful world!
Let go. No, no.
- No, no, no, no, no.
- Feel the fresh blood on their faces!
No!
I'll karate chop you!
Stop it!
All is in pain.
You must surrender to fate.
You have wandered off your path
and stumbled
into unknown danger.
You were fortunate
the Ratman and his rat clan
found you along the highway
and brought you
to the Ghostland.
Perhaps you should
offer him gratitude.
Hi-fucking-yah!
Ratman! Get the fuck out!
You know something?
You people...
are all fucking nuts.
What brings you to our land?
Who wants to know?
I am Enoch, leader of our tribe.
Who are you?
Nobody.
Just a guy looking for a girl.
Soon as I find her,
I'm out of here.
This is the Ghostland,
my friend.
The land of no escape,
only... endurance and survival.
This is the girl
I'm looking for.
Her name's Bernice.
She disappeared out here
while joyriding with her friend.
Any of you whack-jobs see her?
She was with me!
Still run from home.
But Bernice wouldn't go back.
Did anyone else see her?
- I saw her!
- I saw her, too.
Where!? Where is she?
She's up in the mannequins.
Go find her yourself!
No! No, stop doing that.
How dare you?!
I said, don't touch it!
Treat it gently.
That's my masterpiece.
She needs darkness to comfort.
Cover the light!
The ghosts
saves souls like hers.
The sweetest and youngest
at first.
The ghosts exploit their fear.
They want power and freedom.
The ghosts are prisoners, too.
But I protect them.
I hide them!
We are not the ones
who hold her captive.
You're coming with me.
Little cookie stay with us!
She can't go out there!
Let's go.
Then I will have
that child instead.
What's wrong with you?
Talk!
She cannot.
That power has been
taken from her.
This prison has taken
something from us all.
Our voice.
Our hope.
Our courage.
From these innocent children,
the demon has taken the most.
shaken them with such
terrible horror
the the children,
they lose all will to live.
She must reclaim it herself.
If she is to survive.
Everyone!
It's time to read.
Your grandpa sent me to get you!
Now it's time to go
the fuck home!
Alright. Alright.
Alright. Okay.
Let's just, uh...
Bernice...
we're friends here, right?
Let's just...
go the fuck home.
Look. Look.
It's your friends.
Your friends, remember?
Bernice, it's your friends.
See?
N-Now, wait.
Good.
We'll have you singing karaoke
in no time.
Take me with you!
Take me!
- Me, too!
- Don't take this girl!
The demon is too powerful
to escape.
But the demon!
She murders anyone
attempting to escape.
Turn around!
What are you doing?
Do you work too hard?
Well, that's right.
Power!
It has a lot of power!
I've been working on my truck.
They hear an engine.
They hear anything
with an engine.
They say...
an engine attracts the demon.
Is that so?
Cool. Cool.
You got any fuel for it?
I have fuel, yeah.
I've been taking it from
every car that comes through.
And right there is my oil can.
Nice work, Ratman.
I'll borrow one.
I'll give it to you,
but I won't go with you.
Never! Never!
- Say your name...
- Alright.
Let's take care
of this right now.
Speak your name
into the microphone.
Speak into the microphone.
Come on, say your name.
Speak your name
into the microphone.
Say your name, Bernice!
Say your fucking name,
or tomorrow, we'll explode.
Alright. Alright.
Fuck it.
I'll have you home
by tomorrow night.
Why don't I help you
take it off?
Come on.
Take it off.
Take it...
Take it all off.
Baby, take it off.
Take it... Take it off.
Take it off.
Well, that's quite
a scar you got there.
You get that roller skating?
Whoo!
Take it off.
Take it... Take it off.
Open your mouth.
Oh! Yeah!
Fuck you!
Oh!
Banzai!
Get your hands up!
You get down! Get down!
Put your hands
where I can see them.
Give me the money.
Say there!
Give me the money!
Come on!
Fuckin' hurry up!
Stay down!
The money! Hurry up!
Come on!
Come on! Come on!
Go, go, go, go!
Come on!
Get all of it!
These are delicious.
I'll give you some.
Come on! Come on!
Alright.
What the fuck,
you're gonna shoot a kid?!
- Did you take your medication?!
- Did you take yours?!
You coward! Traitor!
Bernice.
It was me.
I'm the one.
I'm sorry.
Bernice, no!
Don't touch me!
Who's rubbing up on me?!
Let go of me!
Stop! Get away!
Many years ago,
when I was just a child
There was a catastrophic wreck,
at mile 244...
It was the age of nuclear towers.
There was a massive reactor,
strong enough to power an empire,
...or destroy it.
Beneath it all...
the waste, the boiling toxic waste.
Buried, hidden, unclean.
The hidden secret legacy.
A mighty tanker burdened with
molten nuclear sludge.
On the searing highway
outside of the city... lost control.
It struck a transport carrying
deadly convicted men.
Covering them all with
the scalding atomic disease.
The burning!
The hideous burning!
The fire crept into the soil,
the ancient polluted earth
Every stone and tree had
sucked up the buried poison.
The entire city burst into flames!
Why didn't anyone help?
We called for help!
We called to the powerful
men in the atomic towers.
But the men of the toxic
empire could not confess it.
They must deny it...
Deny them all.
How do I get out of here?
You found Bernice. The innocent soul.
Gave her a chance.
You are a hero.
Speak your name.
Bernice, this is grandpa.
I order you to say your name.
Speak your name
into the microphone.
Say your name
and get in the car, Bernice.
This gentleman will
escort you back home.
Speak your name
into the microphone.
Say your name to
Grandpa's friend, Bernice.
I am Bernice.
Speak your name
into the microphone.
I... am... Bernice.
Speak your name
into the microphone.
I am... Bernice!
Speak your name
into the microphone.
I am Bernice!
Get up.
Get up!
Hurry up, ladies!
Come on!
Everybody, drink!
It's empty!
I'm sorry!
Governor, you command all the time.
You are the time!
You are the greatest and
most powerful clock.
And your second hand is sharp and
more dangerous than a knife!
Please!
No.
Come sit on grandpa's lap.
I won't!
Get over there!
Make her move!
Hey, Susie. Come on.
Come on.
It's been two days already.
It's been two days,
and still, she is missing.
He'll get the job done,
Governor. I promise.
- I will...
- Bring me America.
Governor?
Do you understand anything?
Yes, Governor!
Yasujiro.
Yasujiro!
Here, go... go... go
toss those around some.
Make it rain, baby!
Make it rain!
Yeah! Yeah!
Make it rain, baby!
Make it rain!
Bring everyone!
Bring my nice young daughter.
Bring Susie
and her fresh young body.
Stop!
Did you know
when Bernice is coming back?
Do you?!
Bernice will come back!
Oh, is that so?
Well, tick-tock, tick-tock.
Time waits for no one!
Say it!
Tick-tock, tick-tock.
Tick-tock.
- Tick-tock.
- That's good!
That's good!
Now the second hand.
Tick-tock, tick-tock.
Tick... tock. Tick tock!
Yeah! Louder!
- Tick-tock, tick-tock!
Yes, you will be
my clock until Bernice returns.
- Tick-tock, tick-tock!
- Louder!
- Governor. Governor!
The traitor has returned.
Did you seduce her?
Give her notions?
Did you tell her to run from me?
No!
It was her idea.
That's a lie.
Yasujiro!
Believe me, Yasujiro.
Please.
It's beautiful.
I'm so happy.
Tick-tock. Tick-tock.
Tick-tock, tick-tock.
Tick-tock! Tick-tock!
Tick... tock.
"My great miseries in this world
have been Heathcliff's miseries,
and I watched and felt each
from the beginning..."
She must be dead!
They never should have gone.
They could have broken free.
- No way!
- Quiet, everyone!
Listen to the story.
He's dead!
Your voice.
How did you manage
to reclaim it?
Those... those things!
They came out of nowhere.
They cut anything
on that highway.
No one escapes the Ghostlands.
You hear?!
No one!
I always had the same dream.
What did you see?
The ruins.
The people standing there...
...suffering.
All the people...
I harmed.
But yesterday...
...they came to me.
And they helped.
And I know why.
I understand.
They help me...
because...
I...
am...
radioactive.
What did you see?
You have a duty to complete.
We will give you another life.
Ahh!
Hello girls!
Good evening.
There are so many pretty girls.
Don't I deserve a girl tonight?
You?
You are a pretty one, too.
Hey!
Yasujiro!
Who should I pick?
Did you pick already?
Yasujiro-chan!
Brother?
Brother, are you here?
Is this your sister Yasujiro?!
Show yourself now!
Brother!
Brother, are you here!
Show your face!
Kill him!
Brother wait!
I know everything!
You work for the Governor
because of me.
He promised if you did then
he would let me go, didn't he?
That's a lie!
He is a liar!
Brother...
Please leave him.
My sweet little cookie.
With this peace,
you will finally be mine.
Forever... and ever...
and ever.
Hey! Hey!
We have to keep
the clock from moving!
Where did you come from?
Where are you from?
Thank you.
Where did you come from?
Where are you from?
Where I'm from
is not much better than here.
But I'll get you out of here.
I'll get you out of here.
Please.
Thank you very much.
Mmm.
Delicious.
Oishi!
It's time.
Where are you going?
Wait.
I'm coming with you.
Where are you going?
Hero! Hey! Hero!
Hero!
You hear this?!
Ghostlanders!
Tomorrow...
we're getting out of here!
Impossible!
It's impossible.
Impossible? Ha!
If you had told me
three days ago
I'd be standing here
with one arm and one...
testicle...
trying to reason
with you bitches...
I would've said impossible, too,
But I'm telling you,
there's a way.
There is no way.
Yes, there is.
And if we don't stop them,
they'll break free.
They'll rule the world.
Terrorizing and killing!
We'll be their prisoners
forever!
No, don't be afraid.
It's just telling the time.
Now, you could stay here,
suffer, survive.
I don't have the time!
I got one day
to tear this shit apart!
Now, you can either help me...
or rot.
Ratman!
Hey, Ratman!
I want to make a deal with you.
I know you're intelligent.
You make the deal,
I give you some cheese,
maybe some pickled fish.
Where are you? Ratman!
There you are.
Come on out.
Would you take it easy?
I don't want to hurt you.
I just want to talk to you.
Come on!
What's it going to take
to fire all these cars up
and get the hell out of here?
Hero!
I found something cool!
Here!
The last poor you are.
I knew him well.
Step aside!
We all die!
Everyone dies! Dies!
What's the meaning
of blue butterflies?
If you touch blue butterfly,
you're gonna die.
It doesn't matter anyway!
Ahh!
Forward! Forward!
This is great!
"...and the wild green park,
the valley of Gimmerton,
with a long line of mist
winding nearly to its top...
Hey! Ratman is having fun.
Let's go!
You really going?
He must go.
Everybody, let's go!
Let's go!
Don't you recognize me?
This face...
is not familiar to you?
Psycho.
It crashed into the bus
carrying violent convicts.
It covered them in nuclear waste.
The burning!
The hideous burning!
You're... dead.
Burning in nuclear hell,
like everybody else.
You ever do that?
You ever burn in fucking hell
because your friend
betrayed you?
You were always so much fun
when you had a...
couple of shots of whiskey
in you.
We used to have
so much fun, didn't we?
Yeah.
We did.
But then you...
started blowing up little kids.
Oh, come on.
Come on.
Ah, Psycho,
all the people we hurt...
ghosts.
They're ghosts.
I always thought they hated me.
But they needed me.
They came to me for help.
Let me help.
Alright.
But I want you to know...
the real predator in this...
is The Governor.
So, you go to The Governor,
you and Bernice,
and you finish it.
Time for us all to be free.
Okay.
Hey!
Thank you.
Da-da-da-da-da-da!
- Is he really coming back?
- Maybe not.
Maybe it's a lie.
Who knows?
Here they come!
Listen up!
For the sake of me,
birds will fall from the sky,
lions and tigers
will bow before me.
For the sake of me,
mountains and forests
would burn themselves down.
For the sake of me,
everything will be mine.
Welcome to my animal farm.
Long live the animal farm.
Forever!
Good! Good, boys!
Alright!
That's great.
There. There!
Bernice!
Oh, my lord! Oh, my God!
My girl!
My sweet honey bee!
Oh!
The key.
Time to come home, my pet.
Give me the key!
I wouldn't give you a drop
of my piss, you degenerate!
Give me the fucking key,
or I'll slit her throat!
Give him the key.
Yasujiro!
Yasujiro! Yasujiro!
Bernice.
Susie.
Don't leave me alone.
Get out of the way!
Bernice, am I gonna die?
No, sweetie.
Here.
Bernice...
am I gonna die?
Don't be a fool.
You're strong.
Run away.
Leave me and run away!
You're safe here.
You're safe.
I will come back for you.
You're not a prisoner anymore.
I'm not a prisoner?
That's right.
You're not a prisoner.
I'm not a prisoner.
I'm not a prisoner!
Yes.
Hey, bitch!
Fuck!
What the...
What the hell is going...
What are you doing?!
Governor, I thought there was going to
be a statue of you in this town!
You're such a loser!
You don't have any money!
You are useless.
Loser!
Susie!
Susie-chan!
Susie?
Susie! Susie-chan!
S-Susie, it's Grandpa.
It's okay.
I'm not here to hurt you.
Susie, plum, it's grandpa.
Bernice!
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Susie? Susie?
It's Grandpa.
Get the fuck away from her.
You betrayed me, you dirty slut!
Dirty dog bitch,
you back alley trash!
I don't need you!
I get me a new girl
same place I got you.
Bernice!
From all the sweet bitches.
Yes!
"But when I got to
the part where Mr...
The Governor is dead!
The Hero won!
Hero!
Yeah! Yeah!
The Governor is dead!
Hero!
Hero won!
Everyone!
We are free!
We are free from time!
You can let go!
Look, they did it!
Time is starting again! Quick!
Look, it's time!
Get going!
Am I still alive?
Yeah.
You're still alive.
Samurai Town is gonna be
a beautiful place one day.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull