No detailed information has been received
from the centre of Barcelona so far.
A whole building has been closed off
as a preventative measure
due to an unknown virus...
...more than 20 people are trapped
inside the building.
Other than the residents inside,
there are police officers and fire fighters
and among them, two TV reporters
that are accompanying them...
It has not been clarified as to
what type of virus it is.
Neither the authorities
nor specialists have yet been able...
...according to the last contact with the
inside, there may be only one survivor.
It appears to be the TV reporter
who entered the building with the firemen
in order to cordon off a secure area
of several blocks around the building.
We can confirm that the situation
is now under military control.
We're in.
Roger, proceed.
Let's go.
Guzman, Lucas, third floor.
Cover me.
In here.
All set...
2nd floor, devices planted...
Going up, third floor.
Lucas. Lucas. Shit!
- Lucas. What the fuck were you doing?
- Done.
- Devices planted.
- Roger!
Let's go.
- What's that?
- Shit, shit, shit.
Proceeding to activate detonation.
You have four minutes to evacuate.
Go, go, go!
Come on, let's go. Let's get out of here.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Are you okay? Can you breathe?
Let's get out of here.
Now!
Shit!
I don't have a shot!
Shoot! Shoot!
Shit!
You're a doctor,
you can help me.
Evacuate. Three minutes remaining.
The rules.
Do it. Do it. Do it!
Come on, we have to get out of here.
Help me! I'm up here!
It's her. We can't leave her here.
No, no, don't even think about it.
There's no time!
- Get out of here! I'll handle it.
- You're crazy.
Fuck!
Okay, okay, it's okay.
You have to trust me, okay?
One minute until detonation.
Look at me. Look at me!
We're going to get out of here.
APOCALYPSE
Hello, Angela.
It's okay,
they're to stop you from hurting yourself.
That's it.
Do you remember anything
about what happened?
No.
Stay still.
No. No.
It's all right.
Where am I?
We just want to make sure you're okay.
Let her rest.
Pardon me.
Could you tell me where the wedding is?
I think I must have drunk too much.
My daughter-in-law sent me for a lie-down,
and I think I've overslept.
Sorry, but I don't know
what you're talking about.
I don't know where I am. It must be my head.
Okay, neither do I know where we are.
Then we're in a bit of a fix.
Have you seen anyone else around here?
Okay, how about this?
I'll go and try to find out where we are.
You stay here. Stay calm and wait.
Someone will come and get you soon.
Okay, but if you see my daughter-in-law,
tell her I'm here.
- Don't let them forget me.
- Yes, yes, I'll tell her.
How is she?
She's awake. She seems calm.
We're wasting our time.
This is the third test
and all have come out negative.
The girl's fine. There are no signs...
She was exposed for over six hours in there.
We have to make sure.
They really hurt.
Okay. I'll loosen them a bit.
Stop!
We've got a problem in the infirmary.
The girl's gotten out.
Get her. Use your weapons if necessary.
How much longer?
It's processing, two minutes.
- I've got her, she's heading upstairs.
- Hold it!
Come on!
She's heading for the dining room corridor.
Stop! Don't move!
Run.
Go, go, go!
Go, go.
Stop!
- You!
- Out of the way!
We've got her. I said move!
Can't you hear me?
- Help me!
- I said move!
- After them!
- Hold it!
Shit.
Come on, come on!
Let's go, move it!
Stop! Hands up! Don't move!
Stay there! Don't move!
- We've got her. Awaiting orders.
- What is this? Where the hell are we?
Lower your weapons.
We have the test results. She's clean.
- Who are you?
- Take her to her cabin.
- You should get some rest.
- No!
It's okay, no more restraints, I promise.
I asked you who you were.
Please accept my apologies.
I'm Dr Ricarte, the medical protocol...
I want to speak to my superiors.
- Your superiors sent you here, I'm afraid.
- And my partner?
I assume you're referring to Corporal Lucas.
We had to carry out some extra tests.
Just routine.
You'll be able to see him soon.
Why? What the hell are we doing here?
This wasn't part of the operation.
It's the only way to ensure total isolation
and you know it.
Isolation from what? We're clean, aren't we?
You've obviously already checked.
The situation is more complicated
than you think.
There was another outbreak
close to Barcelona.
Luckily, we have it under control,
but we can't make any more mistakes.
Don't tell me, a wedding.
Only one survivor,
but I see you've already met.
Well! New passengers. How wonderful!
And now if you'll excuse me,
I'm sure Captain Ortega would be delighted
to show you his boat.
Captain.
I imagine you boarded with that group
at the last minute?
- So it would seem. I'm Guzman.
- Come, I'll show you around.
So you're in charge here?
Don't be fooled. The ones in charge
are the ones with the money.
And those doctors are paying me
enough to retire on.
Forty years at sea are a lot.
So after this, I'm going home.
So the doctors are in control.
And just so we don't forget,
they've brought their own little army.
I believe you've already had the pleasure.
How are we doing?
28 knots.
North-easterly wind coming in stronger.
In a few hours
we'll be entering a low pressure area.
Very good.
Reduce speed to a minimum,
with any luck it'll pass us by.
Sure. We're not in any rush.
Gorostiaga is our bridge officer.
From Bilbao.
- A good man!
- "Pilot," it's easier. And call me Goro.
- That bruise doesn't look good.
- This?
Tell the imperial soldiers out there,
this is their work.
- Have you put something on it?
- No.
I think you should put
some antiseptic on there.
Listen to the man, he's a doctor.
Specialises in viruses and things like that.
Here we go again.
I'm afraid this boat's too old
to throw such a party.
No. Not too old.
The problem is that
they're overloading the generator
with all that medical equipment
they've got in the hold.
- What happened?
- Power cuts.
It's been happening since we set sail.
It's worse at night.
Sometimes it goes down for a long time.
They're setting up
some kind of lab down there.
- What medical equipment?
- Like I said, it's none of our business.
Pardon me.
I don't mean to trouble you.
But, have we met?
No.
With so many people I get confused.
Are you on my grandson's side
or the bride's?
Did you have a bit too much to drink?
Don't worry dear, me too!
Nic. Nic!
- What are you doing?
- Nothing.
Nic is the radio operator,
despite his appearance.
Yeah, though there's not much for me to do.
Those assholes coded the frequency
as soon as they got here, so...
You're saying we're cut ofF?
So much so
that we don't even have lifeboats.
I guess they hadn't told you that.
They're inoperative.
They blocked the offloading mechanism
before we set sail.
Those were their conditions.
Yeah, what was it?
Security... Security protocol.
Pure bullshit.
How are you getting on with the camera?
I'm working on it,
but it's going to take time.
The camera still works,
but the hard drive's pretty busted,
so I'm going to have to do it
frame by frame.
A pain in the ass!
Nic is also our IT man.
The doctors asked him to recover
the recording from the camera.
They seem very interested in it.
I found it next to the girl.
God knows what's on it.
No way...
So you're the guy who saved Angela Vidal?
Something like that.
You don't know how happy you've made him!
I'm such a huge fan of that chick.
When I'm on land, I never miss her show.
And when you're not, she comes to visit,
isn't that nice?
Let's see.
So if you saved her,
you must know her pretty well, right?
Well, more or less.
I mean, maybe you could introduce me?
Sure. Of course.
Check this out. We've got a Filipino DJ.
They come cheap apparently!
The chef. That's the dinner bell,
you'll get used to it.
- Depths ofthe sea, how can I help?
- How's it going down there?
Worse and worse.
I don't even know where to start.
You'd better tell them
to keep calm up there.
Calm is not an option, I assure you!
Come up and get some dinner.
You can carry on later.
Okay, whatever you say.
Here.
It's all there is!
I don't usually eat much dinner.
A glass of warm milk is more than enough.
Right. Hey, you!
Could you bring this lady a glass of milk?
Milk?
And some cookies, if you have any.
While you're there, see if there's
anything else to eat.
Some meat, or sauce even.
This isn't an all-inclusive cruise!
Don't forget it.
Take it easy.
- Where the hell were you?
- And you?
Yeah.
- Have you spoken to my daughter-in-law?
- No.
I know it's one of those modern weddings,
but this is too much.
- Milk and cookies.
- Wonderful! Thank you dear!
Ma'am. There's sugar over there.
Really? I'll go and get some.
A little bit won't hurt.
She's completely disoriented.
She's got no clue where she is.
Somebody should talk to her.
Yeah? And tell her what?
That her whole family's dead?
I've just seen the ship's captain.
They made him immobilise the lifeboats.
And cut all radio communication.
What?
That's what I heard.
And they've set up a lab in the hold.
This was supposed to be
a precautionary quarantine, right?
- What kind of lab?
- They're hiding something.
Otherwise why so much security?
Haven't you seen the cameras?
They're all over the boat.
You can't even take a piss
without them watching you.
They're pissing me off.
Maybe it's not such a bad thing.
So, looks like you got it working. Good job.
You know you could work
for naval intelligence. Maybe I could...
- Seriously?
- Well, you never know.
Wow! Naval intelligence!
Listen, I was wondering...
Do you think you could access
the security cameras from here?
Who do you take me for?
Well, it's just that before,
I saw you looking.
That was the first thing I did!
I keep myself entertained!
How do you think I knew she was here?
Unbelievable!
Don't forget to
introduce me. You promised!
Yeah, yeah, of course.
And the lab?
The door's locked and security coded.
Seems they don't want us
sticking our noses in.
They've done a good job down there,
but they didn't count on Nic.
Go, Nic! There you have it.
Any idea what they're up to in there?
No idea, but I saw them
taking a load of cages in there.
- God knows what they need cages for.
- Cages.
And that door? You know what's behind it?
No idea, there are no cameras in there.
But look.
This is the maximum zoom we can get.
-200%. Not bad, eh?
- No, not bad at all.
- Can you do that with all the cameras?
- Which one do you want?
No, not now. Here we go again.
What the hell is going on?
I don't know what the fuck you do
down here all day,
but that should be fixed by now.
The whole system's down.
Really? I hadn't noticed.
Is he fucking with us?
Maybe where you come from,
people don't know much about hard work,
but here we do things differently.
So fucking sort it out!
I'm from Spain and here things are done
however I fucking feel like it!
You heard what I said.
Hurry up and sort it!
No, no, it's all right, it's me.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What are you doing here?
I got scared.
Everything's okay. I'm with you, okay?
- Let's go back to the cabins.
- Wait!
Don't tell them, please.
Listen to me, nobody's going to hurt you.
Nobody.
Let's go.
This is going to be a force eight,
I bet you.
And it's coming straight for us.
- Looks like it.
- Shit.
It's going to be here before expected.
What did you expect? It's my last voyage...
I couldn't go out without a bang!
I don't like the look of it.
- Excuse me.
- Morning.
- This is Angela.
- Hello.
- We've heard a lot about you!
- That over there is Goro.
And over there is your number one fan.
Or so they tell me.
Indeed he is.
Well, sometimes I watch your show.
I'm Nic.
- Hi.
Nic's downloading the images
from your camera.
Well, trying to.
My camera? It's here?
Do you normally watch them later?
I mean on TV?
- No.
- No, of course not.
My favourite was the one
with the garbage men, it was so funny!
When you jumped
in that container,
the guy couldn't believe his eyes!
Brilliant TV!
- Want one?
- No.
Sorry to ask, but you wouldn't mind,
would you?
What?
If you could do that "Hi, I'm Angela Vidal.
Welcome to..." thing,
but personalised for me.
I know it's stupid but it'd make my day!
No, leave it, maybe later.
You must be sick of people
asking you to do it, I understand.
- Damn it!
- Sorry.
What a klutz. No, it was me. It's okay.
It's waterproof,
or at least it's supposed to be.
In case we sink!
- Have you seen it?
- I saw some of the images.
I don't know what it's all about,
but I'm glad I wasn't there.
That's it!
Done!
Now I just have to put them in order.
Twenty-five frames per second,
it'll take a little while.
- How long?
- Not long, an hour or so.
Maybe less.
Sure you don't want one? It tastes good.
Let's go.
It's gone! The host is gone!
What the hell are you talking about?
- Raise the alarm!
- No!
We need to stay in control.
Close everything down.
The restraints aren't broken.
Someone let it out.
That's impossible.
They couldn't have got round
the security system.
- We'd have seen them.
- Not if it was during the blackout.
What about the security code?
- How many people know the code.
- Very few.
Who would do such a thing?
It makes no sense.
Come with me.
Get the Taser and the retroviral.
- What are you going to do?
- Find it before it attacks someone.
We'd better hope this works.
- Hey! What's up with the food?
- What do you mean?
That Filipino's fucking about. We've been
here 10 minutes and still no food.
Edwin?
What the hell? Have you seen this mess?
At least it looks like
you made an effort today.
Are you high or what?
The dining room's full
and they're starting to get hungry,
so you'd better get moving.
I'll take this to the dining room,
but get a move on or
the shit will hit the fan.
Yes! Nice one!
Go, Nic!
Lamb! Now we're talking, gentlemen!
I hope you've left some for us.
Second shift starts in 20 minutes.
If you hurry, you'll miss the jarheads!
What?
How are you feeling today?
They think I don't know what's going on.
They've put me in a home
without even telling me.
Are you feeling hungrier today?
No, it's not a question of hunger,
it's a question of my stomach.
Could you talk to the waiter?
See if he could make me some pasta,
or an omelette?
I'll go see. But I can't promise anything!
Hello? Hello?
Hi, sorry, I was wondering
if there was anything else?
The old lady's got a delicate stomach.
Something grilled would be good or...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Shit!
Come on, just have a taste and then decide.
It doesn't smell half bad.
Credit where credit's due.
- No! No! Don't eat it!
- What's wrong?
The chef's like the people in the building!
He tried to bite me!
Lucas, did he?
No. No.
- Has anyone eaten anything?
- No.
Okay, stay here.
- Wait! Wait!
- Stay with her!
Don't move!
- What happened?
- You tell us.
This was supposed to be
a precautionary quarantine.
Tell me what happened.
The chef tried to bite me,
that's what happened.
Do you know what this means?
Where is he?
In the kitchen.
I managed to shut him in the refrigerator.
Okay. Come with us.
Just you.
It's here already.
This is going to be a hell of a party.
- Are you okay?
- I don't know. I don't feel well.
- Must have been something I ate.
- I'm not surprised.
- Probably that worm you get from raw fish.
- Anisakis.
- What?
- The worm's called Anisakis.
- Whatever you call it.
- But we didn't have fish today.
You should go and lie down.
I'll take care of everything.
A retroviral. That's what we've been doing.
We've managed to control two outbreaks
in 24 hours,
but we might not be so lucky next time.
How did you do it?
We don't know anything about the virus.
We know more than you think.
We have a sample.
We injected it into a healthy host
and waited for the symptoms to appear.
Hang on. A sample?
Where did you get it from?
That's not important. What's important
is that someone let the host out,
and now we're in big trouble.
- Fucking awesome!
- Give him the Taser.
There's no more time to lose.
- What are you going to do?
- Test the retroviral.
As soon as I open the door, shoot.
The shot will paralyse him,
- but only for a few seconds.
- Okay.
Ready? Now!
Out of my way!
Come on! Get out!
What the hell happened?
The virus is feeding, getting stronger.
- Shit! That's not possible!
- Obviously it is!
It should have worked.
We followed all the steps.
You've obviously lost control.
So call whoever you need to
and get us the hell out of here!
- He's right. Tell them to come and get us.
- You know the rules.
Nobody's coming to get us.
Not now.
Let's get back to the lab.
We have to find out what went wrong.
Hey! Wait a minute! And what about us?
We don't know if the food is infected.
We can't take any risks.
No, no, no. No one's eaten anything.
- It's true. I got here in time. I swear.
- Then there's no need to worry.
- No need to worry? We're the second shift!
- You can't leave us here.
As I said, we can't take any risks.
Let's go.
Wait, wait!
I brought you what you asked for.
You can't do this to us.
- What the fuck is he talking about?
- I'm sorry.
- Let's go. There's no time to lose.
- Lucas? What have you done?
I took a blood sample from the building.
They told me I had to, for all our sakes.
You took infected blood?
Just a small sample. They said they
needed it before blowing up the building.
Who?
It's not just a simple virus.
Some priests came to see me. I saw photos.
Things you can't even imagine!
That shit's not what you think.
- What else?
- They know what they're doing.
- They're financing this whole thing.
- Son of a bitch! And now what?
Okay.
I don't know what's going on here,
but where are your manners?
You don't know what's going on here.
Well maybe it's about time you knew
your whole family's dead!
Dead!
- Leave her alone!
- Enough!
I don't care what that shit is,
but if the food is infected,
we're really screwed.
Okay, we'll go up to the bridge
and stay there.
Captain Ortega will help us.
Really? And how? We're unarmed!
Grab anything that we can use. Hurry!
- Here.
- That's not going to help us.
Well, it's all we've got. Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go!
I don't mean to be rude,
but I think I'm going to go and lie down.
- Get back, get back.
- Go, go, go!
Get back, get back!
Get off me!
Get back!
- Come on. We have to reach the bridge.
- Go, go, go!
They're all over the ship.
It's like a fucking plague.
- Where's Goro?
- I don't know. He wasn't feeling well.
- I told him to go and rest.
- Shit!
- Depths of the sea, yes?
- Everything okay down there?
I haven't even stopped to eat,
if you call that okay.
Good, stay there.
Don't move until I tell you.
What's going on?
Do as I say.
Lock the door.
- Come on, this way.
- Are you sure?
Yes, move it!
Could you ask my children to come
and get me?
- We're almost there. Just a few meters.
- Tell them I won't be any trouble.
Let's go!
Now what?
Have you got nothing better to do
than piss me ofF?
Hey! What are you doing?
Help me!
I can't.
- Shoot it!
- I can't! I can't!
Get it off me!
What's that?
Let it go! Let it go!
What the hell's that?
Machine room, loss of oil pressure.
Just what we needed!
Get out! Let go!
Shit!
What was that?
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Where is she?
- She's gone.
- Fuck me!
What are we going to do?
You go up to the bridge.
I'll look for her.
Hey! Where the fuck are you going?
You're unarmed, she's got no chance.
It's suicide.
We can't leave her. Someone has to go.
I fucked up.
I owe you.
Let's go.
It's us! Open up!
- Wait!
- It's us! Open the door!
- We don't know if they're infected.
- Open up! Open the door!
Nic!
Come on! Close it! Close it now!
What the hell's going on out there?
The quacks have fucked us over, right?
The situation's changed.
From now on, you're back in charge.
- We're going home.
- I wish I could. The engine's leaking oil.
If it overheats, it could catch fire.
- I have to turn it off.
- No!
- Calm down!
- You don't know what that thing is!
Wait!
- We could try the backup engine.
- Start it up.
I can't from here.
It can only be started from the engine room.
Shit! Shit!
What the fuck is this?
You were in the building, you should know!
I don't know anything, but those doctors do.
If we're going to stand any chance,
we need to know what they know.
Oh, sure! How shall we do that?
Are you going to go out there
and take a survey?
Their computers.
Do you think you can access them?
They put me online to send them
the camera images.
They've handed it to us on a plate.
Okay, it's what I thought.
The system's encrypted and reinforced.
- What's that?
- Nothing serious. I hope.
I don't understand, everything's in order.
It should have worked.
Maybe the virus mutates
according to the host's DNA.
That would make each strain different.
We need the original strain,
free of mutations.
The girl. And obviously, we don't have her.
Gentlemen, it's game over.
No, wait. There must be another way.
I'm very sorry. You know the protocol.
- No!
- Twenty minutes. Make the most of them.
No, listen!
We could try to modify the DES1 enzyme,
then the membranes will become more rigid
and we could delay the virus
reaching the DNA.
That will just slow down the process.
It won't help.
Not without the original strain. I'm sorry.
Please. You can't.
There was no room for error.
You know the rules.
Wait! The boy's done it!
We've got the camera images.
Go, Nic! All yours.
How can I find the oldest files?
Let's see. Here.
What is all this?
- What the fuck?
- Wait, wait.
I saw that name in the building.
In the attic.
There were newspaper cuttings
with that name.
It's her! It's the same girl.
The place was full of her photos.
Information about a hospital admission,
ordered by the Diocese of Naples.
Priests?
Parascientific diagnosis,
what the fuck is this?
Wait.
The cuttings were about the girl
being possessed or something.
About the Church. The Devil.
- Stop fucking around, man!
- It makes sense.
They admitted her to get
medical confirmation.
The doctor in charge...
What a surprise.
What's that?
- It can't be.
- Yes, it can. It's the girl.
- What the hell was she doing there?
- Rewind.
What is this? God!
- A parasite.
- The source of the virus.
It was right in front of our noses!
This was the devil they were searching for?
A parasite?
That thing was controlling the girl's body
and mind and used her as a transmitter.
But it kept her immune to protect itself.
Clever.
It's been growing inside the girl
all these years.
Until it found a better host.
The original strain. We've got it!
Get everything ready. Surgical material.
We have to get that thing out of her.
We can still stop this!
Ma'am. Ma'am, come on.
We have to find the others.
You have to trust me.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
No, no, no.
Fuck you!
Don't move!
Drop your weapon and turn around slowly.
Where's the girl?
On a cruise!
Last chance.
Where is she?
What's wrong? No answer?
And there's not going to be.
Then we have to go down there
and do it ourselves.
We have to start that engine.
Easy.
Except I'm not planning on going out there.
And what do you suggest?
We just wait here for those things
to come get us?
Listen, this was my last voyage.
And no one wants to go home more than me.
But I want to make it alive.
Open up!
- Lucas.
- Open up, please!
- Hey, hey! What are you doing?
- Nobody touch her!
Get away from her. Stand aside!
- What's going on?
- It's a parasite.
It's inside her.
It's the source of the virus.
What?
- What are you talking about?
- We saw it on the video.
How it went inside her.
You can see for yourself...
What are you talking about?
You said she was clean.
She is. That thing keeps its host immune.
That's how it goes unnoticed.
Careful! We need her alive!
Tell them to let her go.
- You're making a mistake.
- Let her go.
That gun's not loaded.
But this one is.
Don't you understand?
This parasite's the original strain.
It's the only way to make the retroviral.
That's why it didn't work before.
There's no other way.
- I don't care.
- Please be reasonable.
We only have to extract it.
She doesn't need to get hurt.
- No, no, no! They're lying!
- You're a doctor.
You have experience controlling epidemics.
You know this is the only way.
We'll never get her to the lab like this.
On that table. We'll do it there.
- Hurry!
- Nic! Nic!
Be careful!
- On her back.
- Help me!
Grab her head.
Tie her down. Like that. Good.
- Wait a minute, and if it's a mistake?
- I told you, it's on video.
You can see it yourselves.
Time's running out.
Nic!
Hold her down.
- I can't find it.
- We saw it. It has to be there.
Doctor.
Don't move. Push her head back.
- I need towels!
- In the bathroom.
Quickly!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hurry! Hold her down!
What the hell's going on?
Help me!
I don't have a shot!
Shoot! Shoot!
What's going on?
Get her!
Don't let her escape!
It's superficial. It's nothing.
Wait. The DES1 will work.
You said so yourself.
We can still find the girl
and make the antidote.
You know there's no time.
You still need me.
Not any more.
- And now what?
- Now we find the girl!
No! This is over.
Stop fucking around and call for help.
- You're the only one who can use the radio.
- Not without an antidote.
You'll never do it. You're crazy.
Well if I don't,
I can assure you that very soon
there'll be nowhere to go back to.
Let's go! We're wasting time.
Walkie-talkies on frequency 9.
She can't have gone far.
Shit!
Okay, fuck this. Can you pilot the ship?
I can try, I've helped a couple of times,
but I don't know.
Okay, we'll go down and get the backup
engine started. Do you know how?
I think so.
But I can't go down there, I'm sorry.
He's right, all we have is four kitchen
knives, which won't take us very far.
- Are you fucking kidding?
- Any better ideas?
Wait, there's some fishing material
stored on the stern deck.
Fucking great! Now we're going fishing!
Okay, you stay here.
We'll go and grab whatever we find.
We'll come back
and then all go down to the engine room.
Lock the door. We need you alive,
you're the only one who can pilot this ship.
Stern, this way.
This is a fucking maze. We'll never find it!
Over there!
Got her! She's in the cabin corridor.
- Where?
- Cabin corridor.
Let's go! Let's go!
No! Shit! She's smashing the cameras!
We've lost her.
Where is she?
Shit!
Got her! Dining room corridor.
Go, go, go!
Quickly! Hurry!
Angela, no! Here!
It's Nic.
The walkie-talkie,
pick up the walkie-talkie.
Pick it up!
Come on, come on, pick it up. Do it!
Okay! Now, dial 7.
Dial 7, come on!
Dial 7, dial 7!
Nic?
Good. We're alone now.
I can see you.
But I can't help you
if you smash the cameras.
- Okay.
- Now get the hell out of there.
They're coming for you.
What the fuck are you doing?
You have to get out of there!
They're right behind you!
What are you doing?
They'll be there any minute!
Angela, listen to me.
You have to get out of there right now.
Go!
Why did you do that?
Come on!
- Go, go!
- Take this!
What the fuck are you doing, Lucas?
Come on! Let's go!
It's party time!
Where is she? How did you lose her?
She was here!
Careful!
Where the hell is she?
Help!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Fucking help me!
Get it off me!
The fire extinguisher!
Get the fire extinguisher!
Move!
Hurry!
Help!
- I don't know how it works.
- Its head! Hit it on the head!
You're wrong.
I don't know what you want from me,
but you're wrong.
Now check it.
Go back to your fucking lab and check it.
Then tell them to leave me alone.
I'm sorry.
- What now? We're unarmed.
- Go home.
Wait!
What happened to your hand?
You've been bitten.
Nic? Are you there?
Angela, fuck! I saw you!
Why did you do that?
You have to trust me.
I need the access code to the lab.
What?
Fuck! I have to prove to them
that they're wrong!
- But...
- Please!
But you bit him, Angela.
I saw it on the camera.
Trust me, Nic!
We can get out of this together.
But I need that code.
Please.
Nic!
Okay. I've got it.
Guzman showed me how to get it
from the camera above the door.
Here it is.
I hope you know what you're doing.
It can't be.
- It can't be.
- Yes, it can.
I saw it on the video.
- I saw it enter your body.
- I don't care what you saw.
I don't know what you're looking for,
but it's not me.
- Harpoons.
- Yes, harpoons
Is that all?
- Okay.
- Fine.
We'll go down there, you'll get
the engine started and we're done.
And then go home.
Hang on. Angela's okay.
There's nothing in her.
Ricarte checked, I saw it on the camera.
They're in the lab.
We have to go and get her.
Okay, I'll go.
You two go down to the engine room.
We'll meet back here.
Now tell them!
It's impossible. There must be a mistake.
There's no mistake.
Tell them right now to leave me alone
or I swear I'll kill you.
Tell them now!
Tell me what?
The parasite leaves its host
when it finds a better one.
She was the best way
to get it out of the building.
The video doesn't lie. We've all seen it.
I don't care what you saw
but your tests don't lie either.
That's true.
If it were inside her you'd be infected.
She bit you.
I know! But there must be an explanation.
She's lying.
Is that true, Angela? Are you lying?
And you? Are you lying?
Why did you want the lab access code?
You asked Nic for it. What for?
I wanted to know what they were
doing in there. Didn't you?
Last night in the corridor, you were coming
back from the lab, weren't you?
You used the power cut
to let the monkey out.
Really? And why would I do such a thing?
You rescued me from the building.
We were alone almost a minute.
If that thing was in me...
It leaves its host when
it finds a better one.
Wasn't that it?
Exactly.
So the old host is of no more use.
You're brave Angela, I love that...
Auto-destruct protocol activated.
Twenty minutes.
AII personnel evacuate immediately.
It's over.
Fuck you!
Where do you think you're going, Angela?
Careful with that, don't hurt yourself.
Evacuate immediately.
Now it's party time.
Detonation in 18 minutes.
Evacuate immediately.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Wait!
Get back! Get back!
Come on, Nic! Let's go!
This way.
- Is this it, Nic?
- Yes.
- Hurry, hurry! Shit!
- What? What's wrong?
Nic, what's wrong?
It won't start.
What do you mean?
You said you knew how to start it!
I said I could try and
that's what I'm doing!
Don't try! Do it!
Hurry, hurry, come on!
Quickly! Shit!
Fuck!
Give me that!
Quickly, Nic!
Holy shit! The motor! Start it!
Help, Nic!
- No, no! Not now!
- Nic!
Evacuate immediately.
Detonation in 13 minutes.
Detonation in 10 minutes.
Evacuate immediately.
No! No! I'm okay!
Where's Angela?
I don't know.
Listen, we can get out of here.
The ship's about to explode.
Look, it's an inflatable life raft.
We can use that motor.
Where's Angela?
Forget her! You can't help her now.
Look out for yourself.
You and I can get out of here.
We still have time.
Come on!
Fuck you!
Go, Nic!
Evacuate immediately.
Detonation in 8 minutes.
Shit!
Angela!
We have to get out of here.
This place is going to blow!
The dining room...
They're going.
Can you hear anything?
No.
Evacuate immediately.
Detonation in 6 minutes.
We have to get to the deck.
Time's running out.
The motor? Where's the motor?
- It got stuck. I left it in the corridor.
- Fuck!
It's okay. We'll go back,
grab it and run, okay?
Okay, one, two, three!
You're not leaving without me?
After all we've been through...
No, Angela. I'm going with you.
I still have a lot of work to do.
Come on! Go!
Detonation in 4 minutes.
Come on! Run!
Run, run!
Run!
The motor! Give me the motor!
- We have to jump!
- I can't! I can't!
If you don't jump, we're going to die.
Jump!
I can't! I can't!
Nic!
Jump, Angela!
Jump, damn it! Jump!
You have to Jump! Jump!
Angela!
Nic!
Here! Angela!
Grab my hand.
Take my hand, Angela.
Come on!
Shit! It won't start! It's jammed.
Any cars for the Plaza Hotel?
Car 5, I'll drop my passengers downtown
and head over there.
Some party, eh?