Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
This is where she did it.
Right here in this room.
The dorms were different
back then,
but the showers
have always been the same.
She ran a tap over her wrist,
and then sliced it open
with a razor.
Then she lay her head back
and drowned in her blood.
They say her heart
stopped beating
at exactly 3:13 a.m.
Yvonne, what time is it?
3:12, one minute till.
I don't believe any of this.
Nothing's gonna happen.
Well, Kerrie, we'll know
soon enough, won't we?
It's exactly 3:13...
now.
Are you ready?
Edelvine ghost,
rise up to us.
Edelvine ghost, rise up to us.
Aw, what's the matter, Kerrie?
Forget the words?
It doesn't matter anyway.
It should still work
for you all.
She's supposed to appear
behind you.
Do you see anyone else
in the mirror?
See? Told you it wasn't real.
It's just...
Did you guys hear that?
Hey.
Is somebody there?
Alice? Don't.
Now let's get out of here,
please.
Funny.
Which one of you guys did this?
Oh, my God!
You guys fell for it completely.
You guys are fucking assholes.
Oh, come on, Ros, even you can
admit that was a good one.
Oh, it was totally worth it.
You were in on this, too,
Bethany?
It was Bethany's whole idea.
Well, I mean, Alice came up with
all the good parts.
Well, partially I did, at least.
Hey, so, where did
Kerrie go anyway?
Who's there?
What now, Alice?
Another dumb prank?
No, that wasn't us.
Right. I'm going to bed.
You know what?
I bet you're half right.
Kerrie's screwing with us.
She figured it out,
and now she's just trying
to get back at us.
Come on.
Kerrie? Are you okay in there?
- Oh, my God.
- What?
Oh, my God.
Call... Call an ambulance.
Camille Meadows.
I see you've been at the top
of our wait list for some time.
You'll face a challenge
since our classes
are already underway.
As one of the higher-ranked
academies in the country,
our climate can be
quite competitive,
especially among seniors
like yourself.
Even girls who entered
as freshmen can sometimes
find the stress of their
last semester to be too much.
I've worked very hard to be
where I am right now,
Mrs. Landry.
That's good to hear.
It's fortunate that a space
has opened up for you
here at Edelvine.
Yes.
May I ask what happened?
A girl here died?
That's correct, I'm afraid.
A terrible accident.
Uh, one of our students slipped
and fell from her window.
The poor thing. Tragic.
Well, then, I'll have Helina,
our student aide,
show you to your room.
You sure you don't need
any help?
I got it.
Supper's in the dining hall
at 7:00.
You're gonna want to be on time.
The tables can be
a bit cliquish,
but I'm sure
you'll figure it out.
Curfew's every night by 10:00,
so make sure you're back
in your room,
in case Mrs. Landry
decides to check.
All that's in your
orientation pocket,
but it can be a lot to digest,
especially considering
I'm sure you already have a ton
of catch-up work to do.
This is your room.
The girl who died...
...this was her room?
Yeah. Kerrie Riley.
She lived here.
All the other rooms are full.
But, um, hey, why don't you
come find me
in the study lounge
once you've finished unpacking?
We could go over your
class schedule together.
I'd really appreciate that.
Perfect.
Hey, this is our table.
Scram.
- Your table?
- Uh, yeah.
This is where we sit every day,
not you, whoever you are.
My name's Camille Meadows.
I'm new here.
I didn't ask,
because I don't care.
This is our table,
and everybody knows that.
Move.
- No, I'm good here.
- You're really not.
Look, um, I get that
you're new here,
so you don't know us yet,
but you really don't want
to get on our bad side.
Why's that?
You guys seem so nice.
Um, Camille.
Let's go sit somewhere else.
Oh, Helina's already
made friends
with the retarded new girl.
Why am I not surprised?
Shut up, Yvonne. I'm just...
Hey. What's going on here?
The new girl wants
to sit at our table.
It's true.
It's good conversation.
Sure.
I mean, we do have
an extra chair now, don't we?
And you already took
Kerrie's spot in school,
so you might as well take
her study lounge seat, too.
Thanks, Alice, but it's fine.
We'll just go sit
somewhere else.
So...
What's your name?
Camille.
Well, I'm Alice.
And you've already
met Lenora and Yvonne.
This is Bethany.
And over here...
Oops. Oh, my God.
I am so sorry.
Looks like you're gonna
have to go get changed.
Go on, get the fuck out of here.
Stop!
Stop that immediately!
Ugh!
All of you to my office.
This instant.
Are you certain
you don't want to tell me
who started this fight?
It was just
a little misunderstanding.
I can't say you're off to the
best start here, Ms. Meadows.
I hope you don't make me regret
our decision to enroll you.
Now, unless one of you girls
tells me who was responsible
for this altercation,
I'm afraid I will have no choice
but to punish you all.
Fine, then. You're dismissed.
Tomorrow's a new day.
You fucking joking?
Hi. I got a maintenance
request for this room.
- Just one moment, please.
- That's okay. I'll, uh...
Sorry about that.
No problem.
So, you're the guy around here
who fixes stuff?
Yeah, I guess that's me.
Janitor, handyman, et cetera.
Uh, really just those two.
So, you put a request
in the maintenance box.
Yeah, that light
keeps flickering.
Or at least it was last night.
I'm new here.
Yeah, I heard.
Uh, nice to meet you.
My name's Trevor.
Camille.
Oh.
It must be the ghost again.
No, this building's supposed
to be haunted, you know?
Isn't every old school building
supposed to be haunted?
Yeah, each school probably does
have its own stories,
but this one especially
used to freak me out
when I was a kid.
You grew up around here?
I did. You've undoubtedly met
my mother, Mrs. Landry.
Your mom's the head mistress?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, she moved here to start
teaching when I was 5.
All my babysitters growing up
were students,
so I know all the best
Edelvine ghost stories.
I, um...
I've got to go to class.
So I'll just let you...
Yeah, no problem.
Is everything else okay?
Um, I think the window
might be loose.
I kind of felt a little draft
last night.
Okay. I'll take a look at it.
Uh, I meant...
Oh, that's just...
- It's just an accident.
- Well, be careful out there.
Let me know if you need
anything else.
In the Noh drama style,
women were barred
from participation onstage.
Their lead roles were acted out
by male performers
wearing masks,
not entirely unlike those
that you each designed
for yourselves.
Camille, I was hoping
you could tell us the name
of the first acknowledged female
performer in English theater.
I'm not sure.
Margaret Hughes, who took
the stage on December 8, 1660.
This was in your reading.
I understand it will take
some time for you to catch up
with the rest of the class,
but it might help
to keep your eyes forward
while I am speaking.
Now, before we finish today,
as you recall, last semester,
you each submitted essays to the
Ivy Gate Fellowship competition.
I am very proud to announce
that one of our own students,
Bethany, has won first place,
with a prize of a $250,000
college scholarship.
- You didn't tell me that.
- Her winning essay will be
featured in the next issue
of the Edelvine Gazette.
And I suggest you all read it
to learn from her example.
Class is dismissed.
As for those of you
with detention,
Mrs. Landry has asked that you
meet her in the library.
In order to make our entire
storage collection
searchable online, a good deal
of archiving and scanning
will have to be done.
And I have decided that you
will all have detention
each and every day until
this project is completed
to my satisfaction.
I know you girls are dealing
with a lot right now,
but we do not tolerate
any physical altercations
here at Edelvine.
If you can all manage
to work together as a team,
I'm sure you'll get through
this quickly.
This is gonna take forever.
- Thanks a bunch, new girl.
- Her name is Camille.
And also, how is
any of this her fault?
- You and Alice started it.
- I shouldn't even be here.
- I didn't do anything.
- Shut up, Bethany.
You just got a quarter-million-
dollar scholarship,
so you can stop freaking out
about your transcript.
Whereas I have
a recital next week
- I should be practicing for.
- Okay, well, you know what?
I think we all should've gotten
a pass this semester
'cause of Kerrie.
Okay, I don't mean to be harsh,
but aren't you supposed
to get an automatic 4.0
if your friend dives
out a window?
I think that's
only if you're roommates.
As much as I'd love
to spend my last semester
listening to our complain,
I suggest we put all our
differences aside for now,
and like Mrs. Landry said,
get to work.
Agreed?
I can start looking
for those books in storage.
If someone shows me
where that is.
Yeah, I'll come with you.
Um, okay, next one is 115.25.
Okay, I'm gonna go
take these up front.
Um, you happy to start
on the next shelf?
Yeah.
Helina?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Wow.
Well, if you can't have fun
in detention,
when can you have fun?
Hilarious.
Yeah, you like?
We made masks of our faces
in theater tech.
I did such a good job.
Can you even tell
I'm wearing it?
Oh.
Oh, hi, Helina.
We were just having fun
with your new girlfriend.
You know, one of these days,
you two are gonna mess
with the wrong person.
Maybe.
Not today, though.
Oh, no.
Are you mad at us, Helina?
Oh! Boo-hoo!
Sorry about them.
I'd say they're better
once you get to know them,
but they're not really.
If anything, they've gotten
worse since, um...
since Kerrie died.
Did you know her well?
Yeah, we used to be close.
My first year here, but, um...
we... we grew apart.
Kerrie started hanging out
with Alice and the others,
and then she just didn't have
time for me anymore.
I'm sorry.
Not your fault.
What happened, exactly?
I'm sorry. No one's told me.
Some people think
it was an accident.
I heard a rumor that
her parents want to reopen
the police investigation.
What do you think?
I think it's easier to believe
almost anything
other than that someone
we were close to
was in pain
and we didn't notice.
So, I-I don't know.
Guess we'll never
really know for sure.
What if I told you
there's a way we can find out?
What are you talking about?
Come, I'll show you.
So, we've been talking
about doing
something like this anyway,
and then Bethany found
this ritual online.
It's in Latin.
So, you're gonna do a seance.
In here.
To contact your friend.
This is really fucked up.
What is your problem, Helina?
If it doesn't work,
it doesn't work.
Worst-case scenario,
nothing happens, right?
And I mean,
don't you want to know
why Kerrie did what she did?
I'm in.
Why not? Sounds weird.
Besides, I'm not working in here
while you all take a break.
Okay, fine. I guess if you're
all really doing this...
Grab a chair, then.
Where's, uh... what's her name?
Oh, Lenora said
she wasn't feeling great,
so we shouldn't wait for her.
There's someone
hiding in that corner.
- How... How did you...
- They're trying to scare us.
Just play it cool.
So, is this what you all do
for fun here?
To be fair,
we don't have a ton of options.
Okay, then. Fine.
How does it work?
Well, first,
you need a planchette,
like a writing tool.
Alice had a great idea for that.
Neat, huh?
Okay, so, we've got to
concentrate our energy
and maintain contact
with the, um, planchette here.
You guys ready?
Is that it?
So, what happens now?
Wait, I guess.
- For how long?
- Wait.
Okay, I...
Who's doing that?
"Me."
Okay. Spirit, is there anything
you want to tell us?
Hold on. This is...
Shh! Ros.
"Ghost is real."
What... What
is it talking about?
Oh, come on.
You didn't seriously think
this would scare us, did you?
Quiet, Helina.
We're not doing this.
This is too weird.
No, wait.
We shouldn't break contact.
Seriously?
Yeah.
We should keep going, right?
Spirit, with whom am I speaking?
Kerrie.
Is it actually her?
- You all really are sick.
- What the fuck is going on?
I can't believe that even you
would sink this low for a joke.
Okay, what... what's
that supposed to mean?
W-Who is going to kill us?
"She is."
W-Who is she, Kerrie?
Who do you mean?
- "Her?"
- She's talking in circles.
Maybe being a ghost
is confusing.
"She is here."
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I...
So, what was that in there?
It seems like you
should tell us.
It was supposed to be a joke.
We were gonna move
the planchette around,
draw a pentagram
with the lipstick,
and then Lenora was gonna
jump out and scare you.
Would have been really funny.
Yeah, it would have.
But that wasn't us.
I honestly figured it was
one of you two
who was doing it at first.
What, you really expect me
to believe
that we just talked
to Kerrie's spirit?
I don't know.
I really did read
that incantation.
On the site where I got
the ritual, it said that
you could only contact
the spirits of people
who died somewhere nearby.
We really did
the summoning, too.
The Edelvine ghost,
that night with Kerrie...
we said the words
at the right time.
The Edelvine ghost?
It's just an old legend.
Some girl supposedly killed
herself in the dorms years ago.
Story goes, if you call to her,
she appears, and then...
- Then you die.
- Yeah, but it's not real.
And, I mean, no one's stupid
enough to actually try it.
Oh.
The night Kerrie died, it really
was supposed to be a joke.
Then she ran to her room,
and that was the last time
any of us saw her alive.
Hey, so, I honestly couldn't
hear or see anything
from over in the corner.
Can somebody tell me
what happened?
Are you okay?
I guess.
I mean, that had to just be
an awful fucking joke, right?
Maybe.
They seemed pretty sincere.
Yeah, they're good at that.
It's the same joke they played
the night that Kerrie died?
I just know I don't
trust any of them.
No idea how I meet these guys.
Last guy who messaged me just
wanted pictures of my feet.
Uh, I'll just
catch up with you guys in a bit.
- Okay?
- Are you sure?
Yeah, it's cool.
What the...?
Is somebody there?
Okay, come on, if this is
somebody playing a joke,
it's really not funny.
Fuck...
Camille?
Um, yeah? Come in.
Hey, um, I printed
those Renaissance notes
I was telling you about.
Oh, thank you.
That's really...
super helpful.
Thanks.
Helina?
Do you mind me asking,
the girl who lived here,
Kerrie...
what was she like?
Are you worried your room
is haunted now?
I don't know.
My grandmother used to say
that if someone dies
in a really horrible,
like, bad way,
the energy imprints
on the surroundings.
And if you're sensitive,
you can pick up on it,
like playing back a recording.
Look, even if Kerrie was here
in some way, she...
Kerrie was a good person.
Okay.
Thanks.
And a tendu, close.
Shape the arm, and in.
Dégagé, dégagé, piqué,
and close.
Pas de cheval, and in.
And side, and in.
And back, and in.
And seven, and eight.
And a-one, and a-two.
Balancé, and four.
And five and six,
and developpé.
Chassé, grand jeté.
Yes?
What?
No.
No, she isn't.
Hm.
That's all for today.
Good work, everyone.
Alice, Bethany, Yvonne,
Rosalind, Camille...
after you've changed,
please come see me in my office.
Camille, just one moment,
please.
Your transcripts say you
undertook ballet at Brighton.
Is that accurate?
Of course.
Huh.
I'm sorry. I... I didn't sleep
very well last night.
And I have cramps.
Ah.
I truly hope to see some
improvement from you shortly.
Now go get dressed
with your friends.
They're not my friends.
So, you're telling me that none
of you have seen or heard
from Lenora since supper
last evening?
No, she wasn't at lunch
or in class.
And she didn't say anything
about perhaps
traveling somewhere,
anything like that?
I've been texting her all day,
but I think her phone is off.
And I went to her room
before lunch,
but her door's locked.
Yes, a staff member checked
Lenora's room this morning
when she wasn't in class.
Almost all of her personal items
are missing.
We've spoken with her parents.
They're trying to locate
a young man
she's become acquainted with
online.
Wait, you think
Lenora ran away from school?
She would never do that,
Mrs. Landry.
I mean, definitely not
without telling us.
Which is exactly why
I've invited you all here.
I can assure you that
any information given to me
will be passed along
in confidence.
Her parents just want
to know she's okay.
- So do we.
- Yeah. This doesn't even...
Mrs. Landry, we honestly
don't know anything.
But I don't think Lenora
would just take off like that.
I can see that
we're getting nowhere.
But please, if any of you girls
should suddenly recall
anything at all
regarding this matter,
please let me know.
You're dismissed.
Why are old people so stupid?
Your brain cells die
after you turn 30.
I read that.
There's no way
Lenora just bailed on us.
Mrs. Landry said all her stuff
was packed and gone.
That's just not possible.
Mrs. Landry's son, Trevor,
he's like the handyman
around here, right?
Would he have a key to her room?
I guess so.
What are you doing?
Texting him.
How do you have his number?
- He gave it to me.
- Well, that's just impossible.
Because he doesn't talk
to us students, like, ever.
Great.
He's gonna meet me in the dorm.
What's got you playing
detective?
You don't even know Lenora.
Why do you care
what's happened to her?
I don't. But whatever it is,
I don't want it to happen to me.
Come with us. Or don't.
Up to you.
So, when you said
you wanted me to meet you here,
that was kind of like
a plural "you," huh?
Sorry. It's important.
Well, it better be.
Could get in trouble for this,
you know?
We won't tell anyone.
We just want to see in her room.
Her suitcase is gone.
Yeah, I assume that's the kind
of clue they'd look for.
Seems like she packed
in a hurry.
Her room's always
kind of like this.
There's a hidden space
behind the top drawer,
in case you get a room search.
You didn't see this.
I'm not even here.
I don't think she would leave
without this, would she?
Can I see that?
Well, we should probably
get out of here,
so if you're all finished...
Yeah, I guess.
Lenora made her bed?
The police are on their way.
They've told me that
they'll have the substance
on Lenora's bed analyzed
to determine if there's
any cause for real concern.
Cause for real concern?
Mrs. Landry,
our friend's disappeared,
and there's a cross
drawn in blood on her bed.
As I said, Bethany,
the police are on their way,
and I'm sure they'll take this
quite seriously.
I, for one, just hope this isn't
a waste of their time.
To me, this appears to be
exactly the sort of prank
Lenora and you girls
love to play.
- We wouldn't...
- We shall see.
As for you, Trevor,
we'll discuss this matter later.
Wait for me at home.
Whatever's going on here,
I'm sure there's no need
to impress upon you
how bad it would be
for rumors to circulate.
If I hear any gossip
regarding this matter,
I will know its source.
The police will be here shortly,
and I will apprise
you of their findings,
but if this turns out to be
one of your jokes...
To that point, shouldn't you all
currently be in detention?
This is it.
I think I found her.
Alicia Kane, daughter of
Noah and Ethel Kane.
Born February 24, 1982,
Gridley, Illinois.
Died October 13, 1998,
at Edelvine Girls Academy.
Funeral service will be held...
Is that it?
They won't say suicide
in obituaries.
I wouldn't expect
any more details.
How do we know it's her?
We don't.
But, um, I did
an obituary search online,
and this was the only listing
I could find
for a student who died here
at Edelvine.
I mean, aside from Kerrie.
1998, right?
- So, that's the Edelvine ghost?
- Wait, look at her necklace.
It's the same cross.
That's her, but...
now what do we do?
Better hurry, Ros. Past 10:00.
Hey, someone's still in here!
Assholes.
Shit.
Excuse me, please, everyone.
As some of you may have heard,
I have tragic news.
One of your classmates,
Rosalind Carlisle,
passed away tonight.
I've just spoken to the coroner,
and it would seem
that she somehow fell
in the shower.
For now, I'll ask you all
to please return to your rooms.
Hey, Camille,
are you in there?
Hey, um, I-I just heard
the awful news about Rosalind,
and I wanted to, um...
j-just check and make sure
you're okay.
Thanks.
Yeah, I'll be fine.
Are you sure?
I... I have some Xanax,
if you need anything.
I-I've just been taking them
to sleep since...
Lately.
No. Thanks.
Okay. Um...
Good night, then.
Hey, um, do you want
to hang out here for a while?
Rosalind.
It doesn't make any sense.
How so?
For her to fall in the shower.
I mean, I know
stuff like that happens,
but, like, only
to really old people, right?
Maybe I do believe in ghosts.
There have been times in here
when I felt like someone
was watching me,
but there was no one there.
You know?
You're kind of freaking me out.
Sorry.
Me too.
I think I'm pretty high.
Hang on.
I want to give you something.
Camille, you didn't have to.
Okay. What is it?
Keep it.
If anything scares you,
hit it in the skull.
Don't you need it?
No, I've got other stuff.
Okay. Um...
Thank you, Camille.
No, Mom, I'm fine.
I'm just...
We're all just really upset.
Ros was...
No, no, I don't... I don't
need you and Dad to come here.
I just wanted
to hear your voice.
No, it won't affect my grades.
I'll study, Mom, I promise.
Yes.
I need to go to bed now, okay?
I'm really tired.
You too.
Okay, good night, Mom.
Good night, Mr. Bear.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Wait, what?
She was in my room.
Check the closet.
O-Okay.
What's going on in here?
We don't know.
We just got here.
She... She was right over there.
Tell me exactly
what happened, Bethany.
I... I heard a voice in my room,
and it was the Edelvine ghost
looking right at me.
And I threw my lamp at her...
The Edelvine ghost.
Not that nonsense again.
Think logically, Bethany.
Where were you
when you saw this ghost?
You were asleep in bed.
I wasn't asleep.
I'd just turned out the light.
Bethany, you've had a bad dream.
It's entirely understandable
under the circumstances.
I-I was wide awake. I swear.
Everyone return to your rooms.
I know this has been
a terrible evening,
but you need to get some rest.
You can stay in my room tonight,
Bethany.
That's okay, right, Mrs. Landry?
Yes, fine. Just for tonight.
Helina, what are you doing
on this hall after curfew?
I-I was just making sure
that Camille was okay.
What are you doing here,
Mrs. Landry?
Rosalind's mother asked me
to pack up some of her things.
Her family will be here
tomorrow,
and I've offered to help.
Now, all of you,
back to your rooms.
I just need to pack a bag,
Yvonne.
I really think we need to tell
someone what's going on.
Tell them what? That we conjured
a ghost and now it's killing us?
No one will believe it.
Well, I'm not sure I believe it.
Whatever was in Bethany's room,
she scared it off.
I just... don't understand that.
I guess it's difficult to say
why ghosts do what they do.
Are you two high?
Where's Alice?
I haven't seen her tonight.
I don't know. I guess
she slept through everything.
Um, we shouldn't
wake her up now.
I'll tell her in the morning.
Okay.
Be careful.
You too, I guess.
Great, you're finally here.
We're gonna try
and contact Rosalind.
What, right now?
We should do it when
her spirit might be near.
She could have a message for us.
If you don't want to, fine.
Okay, so should we should all
focus our thoughts on Rosalind.
Fuck off.
Rosalind? Is that you?
Do you have a question for her?
Rosalind, hey.
We miss you.
Rosalind, how did you die?
What happened?
"Murder."
Did the Edelvine ghost kill you?
What does she mean?
Rosalind, who killed you?
Was it...
Camille?
What the fuck?
This is fucking bullshit.
One of you is doing
something to...
Camille!
Wait. Wait! Maybe Ros was saying
something else!
Seemed pretty fucking clear.
Are you fucking nuts?
Stay away from me.
Get the fuck away from us.
- We should tell someone.
- Tell them what?
Look, I'm sorry, Camille.
I admit, I don't know
what's going on here.
And if I'm wrong,
then I'll apologize.
But in the meantime,
I'm texting my friend back home
and I'm telling her that
if anything bad happens to me,
Camille Meadows did it.
Yeah, good idea.
I'm gonna text my brother.
Text the FBI for all I care.
I didn't touch Rosalind.
Why would I kill her?
You got into a fight with her.
I got into a fight with you.
Is that a threat?
You should text someone,
too, Yvonne.
Maybe we should call the police,
leave an anonymous tip.
That way, we don't have to
explain, just in case.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
W-Where are you going?
- I need to go to practice.
- Right now?
Yeah, I-I just want to think
about some things.
I'll catch up
with you guys later.
Who's in here?
You?
Go away.
You're not supposed to be
here anymore.
You're not alive.
You're not supposed to be here.
My room is definitely haunted.
Can I sleep with you tonight?
Um, yeah, sure.
Thanks.
Yeah. No problem.
I took a couple pills, so I'm
probably gonna pass out soon.
Cool?
What?
What the fuck, Yvonne?
Yvonne?
Where the hell are you?
Lenora?
What the...?
Yvonne, what the fuck?
She'll scream.
No one can hear us
back here.
Scream all you want.
Fine. Suit yourself.
There's not much need
for masks anymore.
I like wearing it.
You two...
killed Kerrie?
Kerrie?
Yeah.
Yeah, and Rosalind.
And Yvonne.
And Lenora.
Fuck this.
Oh, yeah. She's dead, too.
Technically, uh,
I killed them.
I-It's true.
Kerrie?
Are you okay in there?
Trevor knows how to make
crawl spaces in these buildings.
He's been at it for years.
Oh, my God.
Call an... call an ambulance!
Why?
Did you hate them all that much?
Yes, I did.
But no, I only did it
because I had to.
I honestly never expected
that scholarship essay to win.
I didn't have time
to write my own,
so I just copied one of Kerrie's
depressing stories,
just retyped it.
When I found out it actually
won, I thought I was fucked.
Not only would I lose
the scholarship,
but I'd be expelled
for plagiarism.
My whole life gone.
Unless...
The problem was,
once Kerrie was dead,
I realized I had to kill
the others, too,
because if they
actually bothered to read it
once it was published,
they'd know it was Kerrie's.
They could put it all together.
So I just had to keep them
distracted.
Enter the Edelvine ghost.
The funny thing about
those pranks we used to play
is that the girls were actually
very superstitious.
So I moved the planchette.
I put a magnet in my phone case
for the big stuff.
And if I had been caught,
I would have laughed it off.
But no one did.
And after that, no one was
thinking clearly about anything.
Trevor had already helped me
there before we even met.
Didn't you, babe?
Alicia Kane.
She used to babysit me
when I was a kid.
She was a real bitch.
When I was 12, I snuck
into her room just to scare her.
She really freaked out.
So I hit her with my hammer.
Then it wasn't too hard
to drag her to the bathroom,
cut her wrists.
I think my mom might've guessed.
I've been more careful
since then.
It was just a dream.
When we found that
picture of her wearing
that necklace,
Trevor had the idea
to put the blood
on Lenora's bed.
Not many girls would appreciate
someone with a unique mentality
like Trevor.
We've had to keep our love
secret since my freshman year.
But not much longer.
Freshman year?
So you were 14.
Gross.
Can I kill her now?
Not just yet.
It's for the medical examiner.
While I'm here,
I might as well take this.
Do you think I didn't see
your shoulders moving?
Come on, it's amateur hour.
Use this to kill Alice.
More evidence.
God must truly be on my side.
Right when I was trying
to figure out how I was gonna
pull this off,
the weird new girl shows up,
picks a fight publicly
with all the victims.
With Alice and Yvonne's
text messages about you,
plus the evidence
we'll plant in your room,
I don't think the police
are gonna look
too closely at this.
I mean, Helina might not buy it.
But when she commits suicide
in a day or two,
everyone will understand.
It's just more tragedy.
If you touch Helina...
You'll what?
Be dead?
This has been
tremendously satisfying,
but it's time to wrap it up.
Go ahead, babe. Alice first.
What?
Oh, you're so fucked.
Hey, since you decided to frame
me for a series of murders,
did you bother
to look me up at all?
I did.
And you're not on social media,
which is weird...
But I bet you did find a
Camille Meadows, though, right?
Lives in Florida,
gets good grades.
Went to Brighton for ballet.
You're not you.
Hey, I'm a little lost here.
Can somebody loop me in?
I don't get it. Why?
I came to this school...
to pay off a debt.
And how's that going?
Could be worse.
Where's the breaker?
By the back door.
Stay here.
Hey, Trevor.
Last chance.
Untie me, and maybe you can go
to hospital instead of prison.
Yeah, you know, my mother
sent me to therapy a few times.
I always got along fine
with the therapists.
Good listeners.
No, thanks.
I like it out here.
I'm supposed to kill her first.
Some forensics thing
Bethany's got figured out.
But...
you know, I bet
if I cut you now,
she'd make it work.
She always does.
Hold on.
Please don't do this.
Hit him again.
Good.
Untie me.
Are you okay?
I am now.
How'd you find us?
I-I'll tell you later.
You're hurt.
I'm fine.
Did you call the police?
No, I left my phone in my room.
Is she... Is she dead?
No, she's just knocked out.
Help me untie her.
Okay.
We're gonna have to carry her.
Through the library.
Hey, wait.
Where you girls going?
Fucking useless.
You can't run from me.
You shouldn't have killed
my friend.
Kerrie.
Hi, Alice.
What happened?
Bethany and Trevor
killed everyone.
So, there...
there wasn't a ghost?
No, I think there is a ghost.
The ghost just didn't kill
your friends.
You're... You're alive?
Careful.
You have a concussion.
You know, I think we all do.
But can you walk?
Is... Is Bethany...
She's dead.
I'm gonna need you both
to go back to the dorm
and call the police.
Wait, you're not coming with us?
Trevor's still back there.
I'll tie him up and wait here
for the cops to come.
I'll see you
when they get here, okay?
You had to kill Bethany, huh?
Literally the only girl
I ever got along with.
There's nowhere to escape to.
I already locked the back door.
Doesn't matter
if your friends bring help.
No one will get here...
...in time.
Hey. You under there?
Aah! Aah!
My leg. It's broken.
Should've killed you earlier.
Guess I'll be going
to that loony bin, after all.
Maybe my mom can pull
a few strings,
get me out in a couple years.
How many friends did you have
growing up, Trevor?
I don't know.
I just had one.
Whoa!
I thought you might try
something like this.
You killed him, didn't you?
Of course.
Alice told me what she heard.
You... You did this
all for Kerrie.
Kerrie and I grew up together.
I owed her a lot.
She killed herself.
I wanted to know why.
I called the police.
They're gonna want
to talk to you.
Well, I might be hard to find.
I'm not Camille Meadows, Helina.
I just used that name
to get in here.
Now I'm done.
Gonna find another name
for a while.
So, I'm sorry, but...
I'm afraid you'll have to
explain things for me.
What, so that's just it?
You're leaving?
I mean, w-what am I supposed
to tell everyone?
Tell them whatever
you want, Helina.
I don't care.
Then how will I be able
to reach you?
I mean...
if I wanted to.
I'll find you.
But I really have to go now.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull