Hi, there!
Oh, God. Not again.
We are best friends
because, well,
first of all we have
so much in common
and you tell
a lot of better reasons.
Well, 'cause
whenever I first met you,
which was so long ago
I can't even remember...
When we were like first born.
In our mums' bellies!
Our mums knew each other and
went through our mums' bellies.
We were like, "Hi, there!"
Yeah, so we were talking
and literally
I just can't, like,
picture myself without her.
So, yeah, you're my best friend.
I am loved.
I am special.
I am enough.
I am doing my best.
We all are.
And now we take our ropes
and we lay them around us,
just like so.
And, you know, when we form
a circle around ourselves
we're actually reminded
that we carry with us
an invisible boundary.
It goes with us wherever we go
and no-one enters this boundary
but us.
It's our very own safe space.
And now we breathe in short,
rapid breaths,
just like we practised
in my last video,
and for those new friends
joining us today
that's Episode 253,
Making Friends
With Hyperventilation.
Mm.
And before we seal off
our practice
with 20 minutes
of blissful meditation
I just want to take a moment
to tell you all about Elon Mask,
the amazing, deep-cleansing,
paraben-free rubber mask.
It's highly absorbent,
perfect for combination skin
and I mean, look,
I use them all the time,
especially before meditating.
I just find that having
a fresh face,
it really helps me
to connect with my body,
my inner essence, my core self.
And to celebrate
SincerelyCecilia reaching
200,000 followers...
Ooh, wow!
It's still so amazing.
Thank you.
I'm giving all of my friends
50% off
all Elon Mask
deep-cleansing masks.
All you gotta do
is just swipe up
and enter the code 'SINCERE' to
reap your hard-earned reward.
Alright! I love you all
so much.
Sincerely, Cecilia.
I am loved @SincerelyCecilia.
I needed this today.
The world needs more people
like you.
SincerelyCecilia, I think
you just saved my life.
Good evening, Jane. Things have
certainly escalated in the...
mobilising troops
as international tensions rise.
Sea levels are rising
at the fastest rate in three...
I just... I thought
I was his pick, you know?
Like, I've given
everything to him
and he just goes with Shazza.
Like...
Prayer, sparkle, angel face.
I... I don't get it.
Like I'm such a good person.
I don't want to cry.
I'm sorry.
I just feel stupid, you know?
Welcome to Pharm Animals!
Udderly cheap, udderly friendly.
- What are you looking at?
- Nothing.
Hi.
So my mum gets these, like,
really big headaches
and, um, I don't know
if you have it here?
Like, I talked to the cashier
and they said that like
they don't know
so like they, um...
Basically I just... I need to
help her with that headache.
Do you sell it
over the counter here?
That is... That is available,
but you'd need a prescription.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
In the States they just
kind of... They sell it.
So I need to go to a GP?
You're gonna have to
get to a GP.
- What the actual fuck!
- I just...
Yeah, I'm just pregnant.
It's fine.
Here.
- Ah, we don't take cash.
- Excuse me.
Sissy?
- Oh, my God, it's you!
- Oh, my God.
What's it been,
like 10, 15 years?
It's... It's me, Emma.
Emma Quinn?
- You remember me, right?
- Yeah.
I was thinking about you
the other day,
and now here you are,
right in front of me.
Isn't the universe just crazy?
- So crazy.
- Oh, yeah, I know.
It's a little embarrassing,
right?
But I'm just crazy about Fran,
my fiancée.
You should come to
our engagement party.
- We're doing karaoke.
- Oh, I don't...
Nuh, you have to come.
You have to come.
Give me your handle.
I'll send you the deets.
Um, it's...@SincerelyCecilia.
Holy shit.
200,000 followers?
What... Are you...
Are you an influencer?
Influencer?
Sissy, you're doing really well!
Ah... Cecilia.
What?
Ah, it's just, um...
It's actually just...
Cecilia now.
Oh! Yeah! Cool! I love that.
Cecilia. Très profesh.
It was so good to see you,
Sissy.
Sorry. Sorry. Cecilia.
Ohhh.
Let's make a pact.
No matter what happens,
we end up in the nursing home
together.
You're the only person
I want to poop my pants with.
Now let's do this.
Sorry!
- I'm walking here!
- Sorry!
- Fuck!
- I'm sorry.
Seriously, though,
I love you, Em, and I love you
for loving my Franny.
Sorry. Our Franny.
To Fremma! We stan you forever!
Oh, raise!
♪ Here's to Emma
She's true blue
♪ She's a pisspot
through and through
♪ She's a bastard
so they say
♪ She tried to go to heaven
but she went the other way!
♪ She went down!
Down! Down! Down! Down!
♪ Down! Down! Down!
Down! Down! Down! Down! ♪
Let's sing some fucking karaoke!
♪ Yeah
Start a campaign
♪ Sip some champagne
♪ Go get on a call and make
yourself a bad name
♪ On some big bad
Pull up in the fast lane
♪ We're hittin' rock bottom
With some top models
With some top models... ♪
Whooo! Cecilia!
- You came!
- Of course I did!
You came!
- Hey, congratulations!
- Ohh! Ooh!
Thank you!
Come with me.
Excuse me!
We're going over here.
- Hey!
Right, you here.
You stand there.
Drink here.
Emma! Emma!
Emma!
Emma! Emma! Emma!
Emma! Emma!
This is my friend Sissy.
Oh, sorry, Cecilia.
This is Cecilia.
Um, we used to have baths
together. I've seen her naked!
Whooo!
- Should I be worried?
- No. No.
♪ Won't get off
the phone
♪ She won't leave me alone...
No, you're singing with me.
Sing with me.
Um...
♪ She can be a real nightmare
Gets me to do her hair
♪ And says it never
turns out right
♪ But then I put on a face
♪ She can tell
♪ 'Cause she knows me so well
♪ Closer than my closest friend
♪ Someone who will be there
till the end
♪ My sister, sister
Deeper than the deepest sea
♪ No-one loves you
like your family
♪ My sister, sister...
Oh, babe, your hair.
Babe, just give me some space.
OK, OK.
I'm Fran, by the way.
- Oh, ah, yeah. Cecilia.
- I know.
Emma literally hasn't stopped
talking about you all day.
Oh, shit! What did she say?
She's just...
She's really happy you're here.
Well, I'm sorry
if it's weird that I came.
I know that we haven't seen
each other in a long time
and like we've never met and...
Oh, babe.
I'm gonna call you an Uber
and get you some water, OK?
- No. No!
- Wait, close your eyes.
- What?
- Just do it. Trust me.
- It'll be worth it, I promise.
- OK.
Don't open until I say so, OK?
I think that real friends
are like stars.
You can't always see them
but you know that
they're always there.
- OK, like now or...
- No, just a sec, just a sec.
OK. Open.
Don't laugh at me.
Remember when we were little,
when you used to always say,
"You know, not everything's
about you."
Hey, I'm so sorry.
Oh, nah. It's no worries.
Remember Fantagate?
That was way worse.
- Oh, my God.
- Gross.
- Hey.
- Mmm?
What are you doing this weekend?
Ah, I don't know.
You should come
to my hens' weekend.
Oh, nah, you don't have to...
Yes, yes, you have to come.
Why don't we just get a coffee
when you're back...
- yeah?
- Sissy. Sissy.
- What?
- Look at moieee.
- Listen.
- Emma.
Sissy!
I mean Cecilia. Sorry.
Oh, my God.
Hey, so I, um...
I drove past
this like nursing home today
and there were
these like old bats
having like the best
fucking time
and I remembered our pact.
And then I ran into you.
Like... Like what are
the fucking odds?
Right? Right?
So like let's just like...
Let's cut the bullshit.
You're coming to my hens'.
You're coming to my hens'
and I'm gonna make you
'cause I'm gonna send
the address.
I'm gonna send the address.
It's gonna take me a second.
Be there or die.
Dead face emoji.
Alex?!
Oh, my God, Alex,
these are so expensive!
Thank you!
Um, hey, do you mind
if we change the address?
Oh!
♪ But then I put on a face
♪ She can tell
♪ 'Cause she knows me
so well
♪ Closer than my closest friend
♪ Someone who will be there
till the end
♪ My sister, sister
♪ Deeper than the deepest sea
♪ No-one loves you
like your family
♪ My sister...
Hi, guys.
Welcome to my channel.
My name's Sissy and this
is my best friend, Emma,
and today's her 13th birthday.
Oh, my God,
is this a time capsule?
Your favourite nail polish.
And a poster of the hottest
man on the earth - Jakey.
Who do you want to be
when you grow up?
Tell all the fans at home.
They're dying to know.
I don't know.
I don't really want to grow up.
I don't want anything to change.
I want to stay
like this forever.
Boring!
I'm sorry.
Let's make a pact.
No matter what happens,
we end up in the nursing home
together, OK?
You're the only person
I wanna poop my pants with.
I am not a sissy.
- I am not a sissy.
- Hey.
I'm not a sissy.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- I'm not a sissy.
- Who are you?
I'm not a sissy.
It's not my fault.
Oh!
Ahh! Shit!
I am loved.
I am special.
I am enough.
I am trying my best.
We all are.
- Hey!
- Oh, Cecilia!
Do you know how to drive stick?
Oh, yeah. Yeah, I can.
- Of course.
- Keys.
Thank you.
- Right.
- Hurry up, Franny!
OK, well, if y'all helped me
I would have been in the car
five minutes ago.
I'm so sorry for being disabled
and not be able to help you.
It's such a hard life for you,
isn't it?
- Hey.
I'm really glad you came.
Shhh!
Ooh!
- Shut the fuck up.
- What?
Shut up!
What, what? What -
Oh, Alex just sent me
a photo of where we're staying
and it's like,
"This is your vacation home."
Like, what is her life?
Um, Alex?
Yeah, ah, Alex Kutis.
Didn't y'all go to school
together?
Come on, Sissy,
don't be a sissy.
Sissy, the sissy.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Sissy, the sissy.
- I'm not a sissy.
Sissy, the sissy.
- Sissy...
- Watch out!
What the fuck was that?
I think it was a roo!
Get out the car.
Get out front. Is anyone hurt?
I'm a vegan, guys.
- This is really not cool.
- Oh, shit, my neck!
Come on.
Oh.
This is so fucked.
Will someone please
finish it off?
I... I don't suppose anyone
has a gun?
We're in Australia, babe.
We drive back over shit here.
Where's the keys?
Cecilia?
Cecilia. Keys.
- But it... it's still alive.
- Barely.
Look, it's the humane thing
to do.
My dad is selling
this car next week.
- He's gonna be so pissed!
- It's a shitty Tarago.
Couldn't be worth
more than $200 anyway.
Oh, my God, this is gorgeous!
Wow!
My God, it's so beautiful!
I wanna fuck this house.
- Bitch, we're here!
- We're here!
Alex, can I please have
intercourse with your house?
Yeah, if you don't mind.
I wanna come inside.
Oh!
Yeah, let's do it! OK.
This is so beautiful!
Let us in!
Hey.
Um...
Pussy!
G... G'day.
Sissy?
Um... Ah, yeah, you know,
it's actually Cecilia now.
Yeah, how crazy is this?
I ran into Cecilia yesterday,
right, at the pharmacy,
and then I invited...
Alex.
Alex!
Um, Alex? Ow, my hand.
Um, she, um...
What just happened?
Awkward!
Oh, this is cute.
Shut up!
I'm so sorry.
I didn't, honestly...
- She's crazy.
- I know.
I fucking hate her.
I didn't think she'd actually
come. I forgot I invited her.
She's a psycho.
Oh, fuck! That was
great. They're gonna love it.
She has the weirdest crap, hey?
She? Why do you have to
gender her?
Sorry, Cecilia.
Emma neglected to inform me
that you'd be joining us.
Oh.
Unfortunately all
the beds are taken
but you are welcome to sleep
on the couch.
Oh, thanks.
The couch is totally fine.
Sorry, I didn't
know about the beds.
That's OK.
Ooh, bitches!
Paradise Lost!
Are you guys serious?
This is the most...
THE most commercial,
white, privileged bullshit -
- Oh, shut it, Saint Frances!
- It's an example
of how much we've slipped
as a society.
It is.
- Oh, my God, she's so dumb.
- Her bikini.
OK, I'm just going
to the toilet.
Do we just like objectify women?
- Are they real, though?
- They're not real!
- Is it, um...
- None of these are real.
- OK, but I guarantee you...
- Is it round that way or...?
Half of these girls are
sleeping with each other.
Sorry, I'm busting,
so I'm just gonna...
Don't judge him.
He's a loser.
He's disgusting!
You know this is all scripted.
Have you guys never done that
before?
I am loved.
I am special.
I am enough.
I am trying my best.
We all are.
Yeah, we all are.
I'm sure
it's like a two-point deal.
Like one boob job, the other
boob job, you know what I mean?
You still gonna do that for me?
- No. Stop it.
- I'm joking. It was a joke.
- "I'm joking."
- No, it's not.
- You can't make up this shit.
- It's trash.
Ah, excuse me?
Thank you. Thank you.
And the gaslighting this season
is like the crème de la crme.
Hey, so I just wanted to make
a little speech.
- It's artistry.
- Of course it is.
It's so good.
It's just like...
Emma?
- It's not!
- It's beautifully scripted.
- It's the best writing ever!
- Hey, Emma!
- Sorry.
- Hey.
Sorry.
Um, I, ah, I got you this.
Well, I... I mean it's, ah...
I guess it's an early
wedding present.
Something old.
Is this our time capsule?
Oh, my God,
I totally forgot about this!
Oh, Cecilia!
This is amazing.
This is like that
Britney Spears movie
where they bury their dreams
in a box
before they get their period
but by prom
they hate each other
and one of them gets knocked up
and wants to paddle in the
Pacific 'cause her life's over.
- J.G.
- J.G.!
He's too hot.
Do you know how many times
I made out with this poster?
Hold on, this is the best part.
How many times did that
make out with your vagina lips?
Yeah, that's yours! Fuck it.
Hey, guys.
Ah, but what about Paradise?
I promise it'll be so worth it.
Alright?
Just... fuckin' wait.
Babe!
- Oh, my God!
- Yeah.
I totally forgot about this!
- I know!
- Look at us! We're so little.
Literally I just can't, like,
picture myself without her.
So, yeah, you're my best -
Dinner's ready.
But Remy's gonna bitch slap
Chloe!
But I'm gonna bitch slap you
if you don't get your ass
to that table
because I am really hungry.
Yes, Mum.
I'm gonna get changed.
I smell like rotten cum.
Not mine!
- Your CEO's maybe?
- Don't you fucking dare!
Alex!
Sissy, don't be a sissy.
Oh, my God, Alex,
these are so expensive!
Happy birthday, biatch!
And to Alex, my maid of honour,
thank you for hosting us all
this weekend. I love you.
I am loved.
It's the least I could do after
missing your engagement party.
I am special.
I am enough.
And your beautiful
lives together.
I am doing
my best. We all are.
I'll get down on one knee.
I am confident.
I am special. I am enough.
His married CEO!
I'm doing my best.
What about you, Cecilia?
Are you dating anybody?
Oh, nah.
Nah, I don't really have time,
you know?
I'm just like busy and focused
but guess that sounds kinda...
kinda stupid, right?
Not at all. Not when you're as
successful as you are.
- Really? What do you do?
- Oh, I'm... I'm a -
- She's an influencer.
- An influencer?
- Well, um...
- That's your fulltime job?
Pretty much.
She has like 200,000 followers.
Fuck off.
That's more than Alex.
Oh, are you an influencer too?
Ew. No.
Fuck off!
You know Chris Hemsworth?
No. No.
I wouldn't say I know him,
I just promoted his app
for a little bit.
- And you got paid to do that?
- Mm-hm. Yeah.
Fucking hell. I'm the least
cool person at this table.
I've been telling you
that for years, babe.
So what's your thing?
Are you like a model, or...
Nuh. No, definitely not.
You're like a therapist, right?
I'm more like a mental health
advocate.
You know, basically
I just try to
help people with their issues.
Like what?
You know, like confidence,
self-worth, self-acceptance,
anxiety, depression, OCD.
That's really cool. Do you need
a degree for that, or...
Oh, I'm...
I'm not a psychologist.
I'm just, ah... well,
just a fellow human
trying to, you know,
share some things that I've
learned along the way.
How much money do you make?
- Tracey!
- What?
- That's none of our business.
- Yes, it is.
If she's a public figure
and she's profiting
from people's pain
then that should be
public knowledge.
I'm not profiting from -
Actually, Alex has a point.
You're getting paid, maybe not
by your followers directly
but you're influencing them to
buy whatever you're advertising
and you're not qualified.
Which, legally, is very murky.
I mean, what if someone
killed themselves
because you didn't
check your DMs?
- Jamie!
- I'm serious.
Cecilia could
get into a lot of trouble.
No, I've always been
very clear with my followers,
you know, from the beginning,
that I'm not a professional.
Sometimes people want to feel
seen, you know?
They wanna feel like, um...
somebody sees their value
and they want to feel loved.
So, um... I just try to remind
people that they're special.
It's kind of like
what you do, babe.
- Oh.
- Oh, what do you do?
She's a psychologist.
Oh, like an actual psychologist.
- No. No, no, no, no.
- Wow.
I'm not a psychologist.
I... have a few years left
on my doctorate
- so I'm studying to be.
- Whoa.
- That's really cool.
- Thanks.
Fran helps real people
with real problems
- whereas in Sissy's case...
- Cecilia...
you could argue that those
people aren't even like real.
Alex, of course Cecilia's
followers are real people.
- Are they, though?
- Alex.
No, no, no, I mean,
Alex is right.
What I'm doing is nothing
compared to what Fran's doing.
That's incredible.
Well, to Fran and Cecilia.
The world needs more
people like you. Cheers.
Cheers.
I just... I'm sorry,
but I can't help but find it
all a little bit ironic.
- Ironic?
- Yeah, that of all people
Sissy is preaching
about mental health.
Cecilia.
- What are you, rebranding?
- Alex.
Guys!
OK.
I am enough.
I... I am...
trying my best. Fuck.
The world needs more
people like you.
I hate myself. Please help.
I'm #trying.
- Knock, knock!
- Hi.
Hey. Do you mind if I join you?
Whoo!
Come on in.
The water's great!
Are you OK?
- Yes. Fuck.
- Oh, don't cry.
Please don't cry.
Fuck.
- Cecilia.
- I'm sorry.
I just feel like I...
I've just tried so hard to...
to like... to heal
and to move on and...
Whatever. I'm always gonna be
Sissy, the sissy to her.
Well, you know what?
Fuck Alex.
Seriously. Seriously!
- Fuck Alex?
- Yeah.
Do you know how much
fucked-up shit
she's done over the years?
But like this is what I think,
OK?
All of that stuff that happened
between the two of you
was a lifetime ago.
It was an accident.
You were a child.
Like you didn't know
what you were doing.
You are a really good person,
Cecilia.
Mm.
And I'm really glad you came.
So I would like for you
to stop punishing yourself
and just have some fun with me,
OK?
Yeah, righto, OK.
- Do you think it's expired?
- Oh my God.
Come on.
Righto.
- Ohhh.
- Ahhh!
Ohhh. Ooh, still good.
You know, you're exactly
how you said you'd turn out.
Oh, God, really?
What did I say?
God!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Bad dream?
I didn't mean to scare you.
I just came to get some water.
Do you mind if I sit?
Go ahead, yep.
I can't sleep either.
I feel really bad about before.
I'm sorry.
- Oh, look, that's OK.
- Truce?
Um...
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Truce.
You have the softest hands.
Thanks.
Do you moisturise?
Yeah. Um, I use this...
this...
stuff. Um.. Do...
Do you want...
Maybe...
Maybe you can help me with this.
Oh!
Thanks, Trace.
Look, I'm just trying to change
the ionic composition of the air
so we can all reduce our stress
levels after last night's vibe.
Speaking of.
Where is Sissy?
Her name is Su-sil-ee-ah.
Guys. Not today, please?
Please? Please?
This saviour complex you've
got going is so boring, Em.
- Saviour complex?
- The chick's a total killjoy.
Weren't you the one who was
gushing about how cool she was?
I mean, you've literally
never mentioned her
and she's invited to our hens'.
Babe!
I don't have a problem with it.
It's just a little weird,
don't you think?
Actually, Fran,
it's textbook Emma.
I couldn't stand her
when we were kids
'cause she clung to you
like a fucking koala.
But you were too chickenshit
to tell her, so I had to.
And we both know how that ended.
- How?
- Fuck off!
Yep. Deadset.
- Are you serious?
- Hell, no, that was her?
She's not your best friend.
I'm her best friend.
Really? Well, you're not even
invited to her birthday party.
Alex!
What birthday party?
Well, it's just...
I didn't think you would come.
All the girls are there
and you don't really
get along with them.
So you didn't invite me
to your birthday party?
- I knew it! I knew it!
- Why did you invite her?
She's a psycho!
Oh, my God!
Alex, it's not like you're a
victim. You were bullying her.
Fuck you.
OK, OK, OK, let's just chill,
team, yeah? Just chill?
No, if she's gonna defend
that psycho over me,
then fuck her.
Alex, we were 12 years
old. It is time to get over it.
You're not the one
who has to look in the mirror
every morning
- and be reminded of her.
- Sissy's cancelled!
I knew there was
something off about her.
All that self-help stuff
that she spouts?
I mean, this is exactly
what's wrong with social media.
It's a breeding ground
for con artists.
Like Belle Gibson.
Exactly!
Sissy's cancelled!
Jamie, stop.
Can't argue with the clicks,
bitch!
Baby, where are you going?
I'm cold.
I'm going back to the bridge.
Yeah, me too.
OK, well, can you just
give me a second?
- Are you OK?
- Yeah.
- I should probably...
- That's OK. Go.
We need to crack that brie ASAP!
I love you.
You're lactose intolerant.
No, I'm not!
Your farts were
so rank last night,
I literally couldn't breathe.
- You're homophobic.
- No, dude, she's right.
It's like on another level,
and I think you should really
see a doctor.
I don't need to see a
doctor, OK? I want my cheese.
Just leave me alone!
You guys are bullying me.
Stop bullying me!
Well, you're not even
invited to her birthday party.
Come on, Sissy,
don't be a sissy.
Sissy, the sissy.
Sissy, the sissy
Sissy, the...
Sissy!
I know you're there.
Hey!
Ooh! It's cold.
Why are you here?
Um, Emma left me a map.
No, why are you here
at Emma's hens'?
I get that you didn't
expect me to be here
so you're probably feeling
really triggered.
And I'm sorry for that.
Like I really am.
I hate knowing that my presence
is resurfacing old trauma
for you
but wouldn't it be better
- if we just put this -
- Stop it! Ugh. Stop it, OK?
- What?
- No-one's around.
- So you can just drop the act.
- It's not an act.
I'm just trying to connect
with you.
You can't
connect with anyone, Sissy.
You're a psychopath.
Um...
I'm not a psychopath.
- Say that to my face.
- I'm not.
Or better yet your followers.
W... What, is that my phone?
Did you...
Did you take my phone?
Go on.
Tell them what you did to me.
Tell them.
Fine.
- Alex...
- Hey, friends!
I have something to tell you
about your beloved guru.
Cecilia is not as sincere
as you think she is.
How do I know this?
Well, see this scar?
Once upon a time,
she lost her fucking mind
and she tried to murder me.
OK, that's enough.
Come on, come on,
come on, come on!
I'm not a sissy!
It's not my fault.
- Help!
- It's not my fault.
It's not my fault.
Help! Help!
Help!
Fuck! Fuck!
Alex!
Oh, wow.
Look at these beautiful trees.
And can you hear that?
Silence.
It's so rare, especially
these days, and you know what?
Now would be a great time
to meditate
but first I just wanted
to remind us all
about the power of kindness.
I found this little
uprooted plant
and I thought
why not repropagate it?
I mean, it's the least I can do
to offset the erosion
I'm causing by hiking today.
Pay it forward.
And, you know,
simple acts of kindness
are actually known to activate
the area of the brain
that is linked to improved mood.
So keep that in mind.
And, hey, don't worry
if you don't have a shovel.
I mean,
that's what our hands are for.
Plus, if we get a little dirt
under our nails,
maybe we'll get
a bonus boost of B12.
Alright, everyone.
I love you.
Sincerely, Cecilia.
Fuck!
♪ We're hittin' rock bottom
with some top models. ♪
Wow.
So beautiful.
Hello?
Don't fuck with me, Trace.
My cock's out
and I'm not afraid to use it!
Hey! Jamie.
Were you watching me pee?
No.
Gross.
Nah, I just couldn't find
you guys.
- What happened to you?
- Hmm?
Oh, ah... I tripped
back there. I stacked it.
I went flying.
You should have seen it.
- OK.
- Yeah.
I'm really high right now.
Right, should we go?
Let's go. Let's just...
Should we just head that way,
or...
- Oh!
- Argh!
Fuckin' piss!
Fuck. Sorry.
- Here you go.
- You're pretty.
- Shut up.
Shall we go?
- What the fuck?
- Oh!
Oh, my God! Is that Alex?
Hey, Jamie!
Jamie, come back!
Jamie! Jamie! Hold on!
Just... If you just wait
one second!
Just wait a second! Jamie!
You have picked this card
today to help you remember
the importance
of spending time in nature
and connecting with Mother
Nature's healing energies.
Ha. I'll see you guys
back at the house, yeah?
What? You don't have to leave.
Oh, no, no,
I really need some me time.
OK, well, can you check
on Jamie, please?
Yes, Mum!
Look, the thing that I love
most about you
is that you always see
the good in people.
But it's also
one of your biggest flaws.
Which is why...
you always end up
feeling this way.
You just...
You just need to relax.
I'm sorry. I can't.
I just...
I should probably go apologise.
Cool.
Great.
Jamie!
Hey.
Wait! Wait!
- Wait.
- Just let me explain!
Stay the fuck away from me!
It was an accident!
Look, I'm not gonna hurt you,
I promise!
Alex had it out for me
for years, alright.
And she attacked me and
I didn't have any other choice.
I had to defend myself.
If it was self-defence, then
why hide it? Why not tell us?
I mean, I'm cancelled, aren't I?
Aren't I cancelled?
So why would any of you
believe me, even if I told you?
Just...
Please, Jamie.
Please help me.
I feel really scared.
Um, it's OK, OK? It's OK.
I'm here, OK?
I've got you. You're safe.
- I see you.
- Jamie!
Hey!
Trace-
Jamie!
Jamie! Jamie!
Oh! Oh! Ugh!
Bitch, Paradise Lost is on soon
and I'm not waiting for you!
- Jamie!
- Alex!
Hey, this is Alex.
Just text a message.
Don't leave me a voicemail
because I'm never gonna
listen to it, OK? Bye!
I'm not a sissy.
All hail, queen.
SincerelyCecilia,
love your vibe, babe.
DM us for a collab.
You know more guys
are coming in here
and they're gonna
throw their dicks at you.
They better. They better fully
throw their dicks at me,
otherwise I'm actually done.
I'm gonna walk out of the house.
I can't believe
he didn't pick me.
- His loss, babe.
- Yes. Absolutely.
- In your face. That's it.
- Fuck, yeah, babe!
You got a snack,
I got a snack...
I mean, I him one time -
- Wait, you him?
- No, it was before this even -
Help.
- Holy shit, are you OK?
- Help me, please.
OK, the magnesium
will soothe your body
and this should help
soothe your face.
Oh, my God, I can't believe
you're sponsored by Elon Mask.
Like, that's amazing.
Oh, are you...
Are you crying?
It's OK. Um... I can't
believe she did this to you.
When the others get back
we'll just hash it all out,
yeah?
Maybe Alex just needed
to get back at you
to feel better or something.
Get back at me for what?
Ah, I don't know. Um...
That wasn't my fault.
Yeah, I'm not saying it was.
So why are you looking at me
like that then?
- Stop staring at me!
- Sorry.
Sorry.
- Hey, um...
- It's OK.
Just having
a really weird day.
Um... I'm just going to...
going to get my phone.
Wait, wait, wait,
hold on, hold on.
Please can you... Sissy.
Ah, Cecilia.
Um... You're hurting me.
- I'm not who she says I am...
- You're really...
- OK?
- OK. Just... you're hurting me.
- Why don't you believe me?
- Please let me go.
Please let go.
- I'm a good person, OK?
- OK.
- OK, look.
Trace, hey, I'm sorry, OK?
I just feel like -
Cecilia! Just...
Sorry.
That's OK.
- I didn't mean -
- It's OK.
- I'm sorry.
- Let's just, um...
- I really didn't mean it.
- Let's just step outside.
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Let's get some fresh air.
- And...
- OK, I...
Let's just talk.
Let's just talk outside.
- Alright.
- We'll figure this out, yeah?
- Yeah.
- OK?
Sissy!
Time to destination,
four hours and twenty minutes.
Hey! Hey!
Stop.
Oh, my God.
Cecilia, thank you so much
for finding me.
Dude, I thought that
I was gonna die out here.
No-one's answering their phones.
Why is no-one answering?
Whoa! Hold on a sec.
I can't get this seatbelt
to work.
In four kilometres, turn right.
Hey, I think the house is
back that way, you know?
Where's Emma?
- What, she's not at the house?
- Mm-mm.
- Where is she?
- I don't know.
- Isn't that your job?
- Excuse me?
Well, if you love her so much
then why don't you know
where she is?
Hey, are you OK?
Wait, Cecilia, calm down.
Don't fucking tell me
to calm down, alright?
Calm down?
After the fucking day I've had?
OK, I think you should
pull over and let me drive.
Do you have any idea
what I've been through?
No, I... I don't
but if you could just slow down
because my seatbelt -
I can't get my seatbelt on.
OK, but can you just slow down?
Cecilia, what's happening?
Where are we going?
Everything's fucked, OK?
That's what's happening.
Cecilia, stop the car.
It was supposed to be
me and Emma,
like, that was supposed
to be us.
That was our pact.
Stop the car.
And we were gonna
make our kids fall in love.
I don't know what's going on
but could you just slow down -
And we were gonna like move
into the same nursing home
when we were too old to pretend
that we cared
about anyone else
but each other.
Cecilia, what's going on?
Slow down. I'm here for you.
We can...
It was gonna be really cute
and like...
- Like we promised each other.
- Cecilia.
I just need you to slow down
and we're gonna solve this -
And we promised each other
that we were gonna do that.
OK.
Just... I really...
Stop the car.
I'm gonna drive, OK?
I'm gonna drive.
But I guess none of that's
gonna happen now, isn't it?
- None of that's gonna happen.
- Cecilia, slow down.
'Cause you're gonna
fuck off to America
and I'm never gonna
see her again.
- How the fuck is that fair?
- Stop the car!
I mean, why do you get
that kind of life
and I'm still so fucking lonely
and you don't even know
where she is right now!
- Fiancée of the fucking year!
- Stop the car!
STOP!
In three kilometres, turn right.
Why'd you do that, Fran?
Hey! Hey! Hey, it's OK.
It's OK, it's OK.
It's the...
Huh? Huh?
It's the humane thing to do.
What?
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Phone!
Senior Constable Martindale.
Is that you, Gaz?
I told you to stop calling here
when you're
fucked off your head. Huh?
Yeah, yeah, boo-hoo.
Just sober up, alright,
ya bloody drunk.
And, mate, I'm not kidding.
I'm this close to kicking
you off the netball team.
Ahem!
What the fuck are you doing
out in the sticks?
Ah, this is
the Police Department.
Is this, ah, an emergency?
We've got your location here,
mate.
Shit.
Emma!
Hey, Emma.
Now would be
a great time to meditate
but first I just wanted
to remind us all
about the power of kindness.
Sissy, the sissy!
Come on, Sissy.
Don't be a sissy.
Get it done.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Please... Please help me.
Alexandra Kutis has killed
three of my friends,
maybe more.
And she's coming for me too.
Please, send help.
Please. Please.
Sissy?
Sissy.
Cecilia.
Cecilia?
Cecilia!
What happened?
OK, don't move. Don't.
Don't move.
Don't move. Just stay there.
- Stay there.
- OK.
Fuck!
Alex?
Babe?
What the fuck!
Towels?
What the...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh, my God! Oh!
Oh, my God! Oh, fuck!
What the fuck?
No! No!
Fuck!
Fuck! Tracey!
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Oh, shit. Shit.
Emma, please, I'm really scared.
She went crazy.
- She... She tried to kill me.
- Who?
Alex.
I'm so sorry.
Fuck, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have come here.
I mean, if I wasn't here,
none of this would have
happened.
Fuck.
Um...
where's Fran?
I don't know.
Cecilia, um...
I think it might be time
to call the police.
No, no, no.
Nuh. Mm-mm.
There's no time.
We have to go.
Come on.
Emma, come on. Come on.
Just come with me.
Come...
It was an accident.
You were a child.
You didn't know
what you were doing.
You are a really good person,
Cecilia.
And I'm really glad you came.
So I would like for you
to stop punishing yourself
and just have some fun
with me...
We are best friends...
OK?
Because, well,
first of all
we are absolutely the same
and we have so much in common.
Oh, my gosh.
We were so young.
Doesn't it feel like it was
yesterday?
So crazy.
But you know,
the more I think about it,
the more I realise, like,
time is just a construct.
Ooh, ooh, hold on.
I'm gonna show you something.
Get ready, bitch.
It's gonna blow your mind.
Do you love it?
Matching! Sisters!
Pink really is your colour.
Hold on, hold on, hold on,
shut up!
Deep blue sea, baby!
♪ My sister,
sister... ♪
What?
Oh! You're fuckin' right.
Let's get you some nail polish,
babe.
- Mm!
- One second!
Just hold on one minute, OK?
Did you put it in your bag
or something?
It kinda just grew legs
and walked off!
Hey, um, give me a second.
Emma?
Found it.
Great! Still some left.
Emma, what -
Where's Fran?
It... It was an accident.
I just...
I really didn't mean
to hurt her.
Everything just kind of
spiralled out of control.
Please don't hate me!
No! No!
No!
No, no.
- Oh, gosh.
- Hey.
OK, look.
I think we can get through this.
You're a fucking monster.
You're a fucking, psychotic,
little, fucked-up monster.
You always have been
and you always fucking will be.
I'm a good person.
You said that!
You fucking said that!
Shit, Emma.
What are you doing?
Emma, no! No!
You're the fucking monster!
I mean, did you ever
even really like me?
Or did you just get some
kind of like sick pleasure
out of pitying me?
You just care so much
what people think about you.
Can't stand the thought
that maybe someone might
think you're weird.
They might know the real you.
Might find out you
have a heartbeat
or feelings or a fucking soul.
I'm real.
And if that makes me a sissy,
then so what?
Great.
- I'm proud of that.
- Help. I need help.
My friends are missing.
My address is...
Please, I need help.
You know, it's people like you
that make the rest of us
feel like shit.
Emergency.
Police, fire or ambulance?
Police.
- Are you in a safe location?
- No. No, I'm not safe.
Please help, please help.
Please come.
Thank you.
Em!
Hey!
Hey.
Are... Are you...
Are you alright, love?
Mm-hm.
Alright, is there anyone else
in the house?
Alright, you just...
You stay there, alright?
You... You...
You're safe there.
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna secure the house, OK?
And I'll be back.
Yep.
Oh, my God.
Fuck me.
You got this.
Yeah, you're a weapon.
And this is Sissy,
my best friend
in the whole wide world.
This is you
when you were a baby!
Hi, guys, welcome to my channel.
My name's Sissy and this
is my best friend, Emma,
and today is her 13th birthday.
You're officially old enough
to be a child bride.
Speak for yourself. I'm gonna
be so cool when I'm older.
- Oh, really?
- Yep.
I'm gonna have pink hair
and drive an old yellow car.
Your turn.
Who do you want to be
when you grow up?
Tell all the fans at home.
They're dying to know.
I don't know.
I don't really want to grow up.
I don't want anything to change.
I want to stay like this
forever.
Boring!
I am loved.
I am special.
I am enough.
I am doing my best.
We all are.
And now we take our rope
and we lay it around us like so.
And as always when we form
a circle around ourselves
we are reminded that we carry
with us an invisible boundary.
No-one enters that boundary
but us.
It's our very own safe space
and we never, ever
have to leave it.
When I was the lone survivor
of the Alexandra Kutis
massacre...
my boundary was all I had.
When I hid in that bathroom
as Alex murdered my friends...
honestly, I...
I wanted to give up.
I wanted it to be over.
But then I thought of all of you
and I realised
I had to be strong.
I had to practise
what I preach, you know?
So I did The Steps.
I came back into my body,
regained control of my mind
and refused to be a victim.
And now you can too.
Order my new book,
Don't Survive, Thrive: Simple
Steps to Living Your Best Life.
And, even better,
all of my friends,
all ten million of you,
will receive one of my new,
bespoke,
non-allergenic therapy ropes.
Just swipe on up
and enter the code 'SINCERE'.
Sincerely, Cecilia.
♪ Sister
♪ She won't get off the phone
♪ She won't leave me alone
♪ When I'm talking to that guy
♪ She can be a real nightmare
♪ Gets me to do her hair
♪ And says it never
turns out right
♪ But when I put on a face
she can tell
♪ 'Cause she knows me so well
♪ Closer than my closest friend
♪ Someone who will be there
till the end
♪ My sister, my sister
♪ Deeper than the deepest sea
♪ No-one likes you
like your family
♪ My sister, sister
♪ To celebrate the good times
♪ To help me through
the hard times
♪ To bring me down to earth
Remind me what's important
♪ And who comes first
Who comes first
♪ Gotta tell me
who I'm talking about
♪ My sister, sister
♪ Oh, yeah
♪ And who comes first?
♪ Ain't no doubt about it
♪ Who am I talkin' about?
My sister, sister. ♪
♪ Hello?
Remember me?
♪ Narcisa?
♪ Your frenemy
♪ Project, deflect and blame
♪ I'll shame, wane and shirk
♪ To keep your mouth
♪ Sans my name
♪ Baby, I'm a widdle baby
♪ Won't you please
♪ Spit my dummy out
♪ For me?
♪ I don't care
♪ What you think
♪ Or feel or say or do
♪ You keep this up
♪ I swear to God
♪ I'll bury you
♪ Joking?
♪ No, I'm not joking
♪ I'd rather see
♪ You rot in hell
♪ Than let you have
♪ This one over me
♪ Hush, now
♪ Our world still spins around
♪ None the wiser
♪ While I burn it all
♪ Especially you down
♪ Hello?
♪ Remember me?
♪ I'm the end
♪ Of your dreams.
Captions produced by
Access Media Pty Ltd