(tape recorder sounds)
(TV Din)
(Kaylee) Ya?
(tape player whirs with no sound)
Dad?
(tape plays succesfully)
(tape version of “Babar”)
(silence)
(small footsteps)
(Kevin) One.
Two.
Three
(falling down stairs)
(child sobbing down the hall)
(adults footsteps)
(child sobs louder)
(car leaves driveway)
(silence)
(muffled cartoon music plays)
(music ends abruptly)
(door opens)
(families footsteps enter)
(dads quiet footsteps)
(whisper) Kaylee?
(footsteps continue)
(dial tone)
(dialing)
(ringing)
(Dad) So... he's fine
(Dad)
But Kevin, fell down the stairs
(Dad) and hit his head
(Dad) Mhmm..
(Dad)
No. They didn't even need to do stiches
(Dad) Mhmm..
(toilet flushes)
(Kaylee) Dad?
(silence)
(Kaylee) Kevin.
(bed sheets rustle)
(eerie tone)
(blinds being pulled)
(Kaylee) Dad?
(kids footsteps on stairs)
(eerie tone)
(Kaylee) Dad?
(blinds being pulled)
(eerie tone)
(Kaylee) Dad?
(clumsy dialing)
(disconnected tone)
(dialing)
(abruptly hangs up)
(Videotape machine whirs)
(Kevin)
I cant sleep with the lights on.
(cartoons play quietly)
(Kaylee) Kevin?
(Kevin) Ya?
(Kaylee whispers) Love you.
(Kevin) Love you too.
(Kaylee) Kevin.
(Kaylee)
I think it's time to get up.
(cereal box rattles)
(Kaylee)
I'm gonna go upstairs to get some stuff.
(Kaylees footsteps)
(rumaging through toy bin)
(footsteps stop abruptly)
(Kaylee) Dad?
(silence)
(footsteps fade)
(click)
(crayons on paper)
(drawing ceases)
(light switch is flicked on and off)
(drawing resumes)
(gentle snoring)
(movement on couch)
(little footsteps)
(Kaylee Whispers)
(Kevin)
How come no ones come yet?
(Kaylee) I don't know.
(Kaylee) Maybe we should just..
(rapid thumping from upstairs)
(Kevin) What was that?
(Loud scrape)
(Kaylee whispers)
We should be quiet.
(cartoons play quietly)
(Kevin whispers)
(Kaylee whispers)
(Kevin)
(Kaylee)
(snoring)
(Kevins footsteps)
(Kevin) Kaylee.
(rustling on couch)
(Kevin)
You have to come see this.
(two sets of footsteps)
(footsteps stop)
(eerie tone)
(Kevin) Where did it go?
(Kaylee) Just hurry...
(bathroom door closes)
(Kaylees slow footsteps)
(Kaylee gasps)
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
(Scream)
(Kaylee out of breath)
(Kevin) Sorry.
(Kaylee) What?!
(Kevin)
(Kevin) Gross!
(Kaylee) Did you see anything..
(Kaylee) weird up... stairs?
(Kevin) Like what?
(rumaging through toys)
(Triumphant cartoon music)
(clicking of plastic blocks)
(cartoon volume quiet)
(snoring)
(strange voice) Kaylee.
(strange voice)
(cartoon music fades to nothing)
(Kaylee) Dad?
(Dad whispers)
(Kaylee whispers)
I can't see anything.
(Kaylee gasps)
(Mom) Kaylee?
Your..
Your father and me
(door slams)
Kaylee.
(mom whispers)
(creaking)
(quiet struggle)
(stange voice whispers)
(Mom) Someones here.
(creak)
(Mom moans)
(stange voice whispers)
(Mom) Kaylee.
(Mom)
(bone crack)
(moaning quietly)
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
(inhuman squeal)
(Tone)
(Kevin)
(Kaylee)
Help me move the couch, okay?
(clicking light switch)
(rustling through kitchen cabinets)
(Kevin)
(cartoons play quietly)
(TV muted)
(Kaylee breaths heavily)
(strange voice)
(silence)
(Kevin) Kaylee?
(Kevin) Hello?
(Kevins little footsteps)
(VCR winds up)
(Cartoon sounds resume)
(Kaylee breaths heavily)
(cartoons play loudly)
(Kevin clicks flashlight)
(urinating)
(cartoons play quiet)
(Kevin snores)
(toys click and rustle)
(Triumphant cartoon music)
(Strange voice) Kevin.
(Strange voice whispers)
Come to the basement.
(cartoon music fades away)
(silence)
(Kaylee muffled)
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
(deafening tone)
(cartoons play quietly)
(running steps come closer)
(running stops)
(Kevin out of breath)
(TV din from downstairs)
(rumaging through cabinets)
(strange voice)
(Kevin) Hello?
(strange voice) Kevin.
(strange voice)
(body falls)
(cartoons play loudly)
(cartoons stop)
♪♪ Presto-Change-O♪♪
(silence)
(cartoons play normally)
(Kevin rustles on carpet)
(clicking of plastic toys)
(Strange voice)
(Kevin stops playing)
(playing resumes)
(Strange voice) Kevin.
(playing stops)
(Strange voice)
I want to... play!
(playing resumes)
(drawer slams open)
(playing stops)
♪♪ Presto-Change-O♪♪
(music stops)
(Kevin breaths heavily)
(Strange voice) Kevin.
♪♪ Presto-Change-O♪♪
(rummaging cutlery)
(Kevin whimpers)
(saftey knife cranks)
(Strange voice)
(pained moaning from downstairs)
(sobbing and screaming)
(Strange voice) Wake up.
(Kevins pained breathing)
(slow/clumsy footsteps)
(blankets rustle)
(cartoon music resumes)
(cartoon music distorts)
(audio stops)
(Kevin breaths heavily)
(silence)
(ominous tone)
(slow footsteps through toys)
(unidentified beeping)
(clumsy bumping)
(flashlight click)
(off-hook tone)
(dial beep)
(dialing)
(ringing)
(operator heard faintly)
(Kevin whispers) I hurt...
(Kevin whispers)
..myself and I feel sick.
(Kevin whispers) Ya.
(Kevin whispers) No.
(Kevin whispers) Umm...I
(Kevins continues faintly)
(Kevin whispers) Ya.
(Kevin) Ya.
(Kevin whispers) No.
(Kevin whispers)
I'm downstairs but the doors is gone.
(thud)
(blankets rustle)
(flashlight click)
(Kevin) You did that.
(strange voice laughs uncannily)
(silence)
(Strange Voice) Kevin.
(Kevin breaths shakily)
(sound static slowly grows)
(silence)
(Kevin) How did you do that?
(strange voice whispers)
(flashlight click)
(Kevin whimpers)
(Strange Voice) It's okay.
(Strange Voice)
I will pro-tect you.
(unidentified banging)
(Kevin breathes shakily)
(Strange Voice) Keep going.
(Kevins breathing echos)
(Kevin) Can I go back now?
(faint echos in distance)
(Kevin whimpers)
(uncanny animal call echos)
(monster growls in distance)
(growls grow louder)
(quiet)
(flashlight click)
(cartoon music fades in)
(Cartoon boy sings)
♪♪I don't have to worry♪♪
♪♪I don't have to care♪♪
(Cartoon boy sings)
♪♪My coat is very furry♪♪
♪♪I'm a furry grizzly bear♪♪
(cartoon melody continues)
(cartoon music grows chaotic)
♪♪
(innocent melody plays)
(silence)
(uncanny gasp)
(crawling echos)
(inhuman cries)
(VCR winds up)
(machine quietly whirs)
(machine loudly whirs)
(silence)
(eerie melody echos)
(music ceases)
(crawling echos)
(flashlight click)
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
(Loud Ring)
(silence)
(child whispers unclear)
(whisper grows deeper)
(audio dead)
(tape player whirs with no sound)
(clicks off)
(clicks)
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
(child cries)
(uncanny murmer)
(child screams)
(monster screams chaotically)
♪♪ Presto-Change-O♪♪
(older child cries)
(uncanny murmer)
(older child screams)
(monster screams chaotically)
(Tone)
(monster growls chaotically)
♪♪ Presto-Change-O♪♪
(Strange Voice laughs)
(tortured scream)
(monster screams chaotically)
♪♪ Presto-Change-O♪♪
(Strange voice cackles)
(silence)
(flashlight click)
(Kevin) Kaylee.
(Kevin)
♪♪Heavenly melody♪♪
♪♪
(Music slowly fades)
(Strange Voice)
(child)