Whippoorwill flies about
27 miles an hour.
That what you thought
it would have been?
I'd have thought more like
31 or something.
32.
Goddamn, that's a pisser.
Normally, I could
look at anything,
tell you exactly
how fast it's going
within 2 miles per hour.
That's fascinating.
I'm gonna...
Get the fuck out of the way,
cocksucker!
Morning, Mayor.
Hi. How you all doing?
Easy come, easy go.
When Darwin said "fittest,"
he didn't necessarily mean
the strongest,
or the most intelligent,
or any one trait.
He merely meant those
organisms most well-suited
to their environments.
Now, we humans,
we think we're more fit,
more evolved,
because we're smarter.
But we're neophytes.
We've only been on this Earth
two million years,
give or take.
The cockroach, that fellow's
been around 350 million years.
So, based on that,
which of us is
the more successful species?
A lot of folks build houses
on unsafe ground.
The erosion in Cambodia
is some of the worst.
My friends wanted to
buy a house there, but...
Hey. Come on.
Hey, Grant.
Okay.
Later, Hank.
He's teaching
environmental studies.
He's gonna borrow
one of my lesson plans.
Oh, I know what he
wants to borrow,
and I ain't lending.
Come on, you little varmint.
Cassidy, come.
That's it.
Hey, can Cassie come over?
Did she say she was
gonna be here?
Quit your lollygagging.
Hi, sweetie.
See you guys later.
Come on!
That's it.
Here, sweetie.
You have
a good day today?
Very nice.
Hop on in there, baby.
Baby, when did you
go to Jack in the Box?
That's one match
I'll never get.
Ain't no mystery.
Starla's raised in them
shanties off St. Luc.
Dirt poor.
All she ever wanted was
to be a lady.
Old Grant Grant, he's
always been made of green.
Gold digger, huh?
Oh, hell, Margaret.
Starla's mother left her.
Her daddy's a drunk.
She's 17 years old.
Old Grant pulls up,
big old Cadillac. House on
the hill and college tuition.
What would you do?
Blow.
Hell, if he had a 'gina,
you'd have married him, too.
What's a 'gina?
It's a country.
You know,
where Ginese people come from.
Learn to eavesdrop better.
Zach. Hell, your mother's
waiting over there.
What the hell you doing here?
Scoot, scoot.
Sugarplum,
you coming to bed?
...why the crocodile has
survived for millennia,
when so many similar species
have gone extinct.
Oh, yeah.
You know what, baby?
I'm just not
really in the mood.
Come on, baby doll.
It's been a long time.
We both need it.
I know. I'm just...
Baby, come on now.
I don't just have some switch.
Sure you do.
Flick, flick.
That's disrespectful.
Come on now.
I'm just playing with you.
Come on, honey.
No, come on, baby.
Why don't you just,
you know, work one out for
yourself there, darling?
Come on.
Honey, I'm just not
in the mood. Can't you tell?
When the hell are you
in the mood anyway?
Dang.
Where you going?
Out. For a walk.
Grant. Baby.
I...
Yeah.
Hit me again there, killer.
Megan Montgomery's
little sister.
You're kidding me.
Nope.
Brenda.
My sister, Megan,
she was a big fat old cow,
and I'd be thinking,
"What does he see in her
that ain't in me?"
Shit, come on now.
You couldn't have been
more than 10 or 11.
Hell, I was game.
I'll give you
a ride, then.
All right, come on.
Yee-haw! Giddyup.
Come on.
Where we going, girl?
Come on, you.
Where we going?
Get over here.
What'd I tell you?
I had a crush on you.
Will you look at that?
Your initials, "B.M."
Like a piece of shit.
Oh, shut up.
At least I don't got
the same last name
as the first.
Oh, you're nothing
but a little turd, girl.
Oh, stop!
Stop, yourself.
Stop.
Wait. Wait, wait.
Oh, Grant.
Oh, God. You gotta stop.
I can't.
Starla.
She gets real worried about me
if I'm out too late.
I'm sorry. I gotta go. I...
Starla.
Yeah, shit. Go.
What is it?
I don't know.
There's a trail.
Oh. Oh, that's gross.
Come on.
Oh...
Come on. Grant.
Come on.
Wait, wait, wait.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What the fuck?
God dog it!
Oh, God.
Grant.
Grant?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Grant.
Grant, are you okay?
You okay?
Meat.
Good morning, baby.
We haven't heard
this song for a while.
I was hoping it could be
a peace pipe.
I'm sorry about last night.
I don't mean
to push you away.
Or make you feel rejected.
I do want to be a good wife.
You're crying.
Baby.
Baby, what's this?
It's just a little bug bite.
What are you so smiley about?
Nothing.
Grant and I had
a good morning.
And it's been a while.
Oh, you slut.
Janene.
Quiet.
You're a married woman.
It's Grant.
I don't know, he's like...
It was like he was discovering
all these different parts
of my body.
You know,
like a little boy
or something.
I'm telling you, this morning
I sensed a real change
in Grant.
Meat.
Meat. Meat.
Howdy, Mr. Grant.
Oh, hey there, killer.
What can I do you for?
Give me
a couple of your rib eyes.
How many you need?
Eight.
Know what? 10.
No, no, no. You know what?
Give me 14.
Having a party?
Yeah, yeah,
something like that. Yeah.
It's a little surprise
for the wife.
Grant. What's this lock
doing on the door?
Baby, you drilled right into
the frame. It's all busted up.
Sugarplum, you really think
you should be asking
so many questions
when it's so close
to your birthday?
My birthday's
not for two months.
That's close.
Not really.
Matter of opinion.
Grant, I'm jumping in
the shower. Baby, we need to
leave in 40 minutes.
What are you doing?
Nothing. I gotta...
I gotta go to work.
I left something at work.
What? Grant, Deer Cheer starts
in about an hour,
and you promised me.
Gotta go! Gotta go to work.
I'll meet you there!
I will never understand
what joy a grown man gets
using a $1,000 weapon
to blow the face off
a cute little deer.
Yeah.
Surprised you're able to lift
a mug, you've been carrying
that torch for so long.
Oh, that reminds me
of something I want to
tell you.
What's that?
Fuck you, fat ass.
Melvin,
clean up the toilets.
It stinks over here.
Okay, I'll be right there.
Look what you did,
you fucking asshole!
Grant.
Damn, girl.
You are chocolate
for the eyes.
I thought maybe you was dead
after the other night.
I am dead. Don't I look it?
The old half-Mexican around?
At his mama's for the weekend.
I'm all alone.
Besides this one.
Hey.
Hi.
Scared you?
Hey, Bill.
What you doing?
Oh, nothing. Just...
I'm trying to get a buzz on,
but I can't.
I'm too buff.
Got too much muscle mass.
I don't know what it is.
Oh, really?
Congratulations, by the way.
Thank you.
Yeah, on the promotion,
that's...
Thank you.
Chief.
Yeah.
Sounds weird, doesn't it?
No, it sounds nice.
So where's old Grant?
I don't know.
He was supposed to
meet me here, but...
It's kind of chilly tonight.
Yeah.
It sure is pretty.
You know...
It's probably time
for the countdown, almost.
Right.
Yeah, I think Jack's gonna
make a speech or something.
Well,
that will be interesting.
Thank you.
I would like to introduce
Mayor Jack MacReady.
Thank you.
Cheese and crackers.
Ladies and gentlemen,
right after God invented
this world of ours,
he came unto Adam
and he said that man
should have dominion
over the fish of the sea,
and over the birds of the air,
and over every living thing
that moveth upon the Earth.
Amen! All right! Yeah!
Now, I believe
when God said that,
he was thinking of
deer season in Wheelsy
and how much damn fun it is
to shoot a buck or two!
Huh? Am I right?
Are you ready?
Yes!
Ten, nine, eight,
seven, six, five,
four, three, two,
one!
Oh, God, Grant!
Let the hunt begin!
Grant, what is it? No!
Grant?
Grant,
you know about this fuse?
Grant, why didn't you
answer your phone?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Grant?
Oh, my God, baby,
what happened to your face?
It's just a bee sting.
I'll be all right.
I have a little reaction,
that's all.
Oh, we gotta get you
to the hospital.
No.
No, no, no, no.
I already saw Dr. Karl.
Gave me a prescription,
said it should clear up soon.
Said things like this happen.
Happens to people
all the time.
Come on, baby, don't...
Don't look at me like that.
Yes, hi, Dr. Karl.
This is Starla Grant.
O£, Starla. How are you?
I'm fine, thank you.
I was calling about...
About Grant's condition.
I think that it may be
getting worse.
What condition is that, dear?
The one you just
saw him about.
Starla, I haven't
seen your husband
in over a year.
What's the matter?
Come on now, don't cry.
Now, look here.
You're doing a good job.
I'm so hungry,
I think I'm gonna die.
No, no, no, no. Here.
I got something here,
help you feel better.
Brought you munchies.
Come on now. Treat yourself.
Yeah, that's my girl.
Everything's
gonna be all right.
Hey, Starla.
Hey.
Bill. Wally.
Howdy.
Grant around, by any chance?
Oh, no. He's not
home from work yet.
Mr. Grant!
He's not home yet, Wally.
I just said.
What's going on?
Do you know
a Brenda Gutierrez?
Maybe she
called the house, or...
No.
What's...
Girl disappeared Friday night.
Signs of a struggle
in the house.
Here in town?
Yeah.
The thing is,
people saw Grant
going into her house,
and that's the last
anyone's seen of her.
It must've been someone
that looks like Grant.
Yeah. Maybe.
But have him give me a call
as soon as he gets in.
All right.
Well, thanks.
Night.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
...116·.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
You've reached Chief Pardy.
No, no, no, no, no.
Please leave a message
and your call will be
returned promptly.
Bill! It's Starla.
You were just here.
And you need to get back here
right now. I think...
Grant is sick or something.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Why are you running from me,
baby? I wasn't gonna hurt you!
I love you, baby.
I tried not to change.
No!
I'll get it.
I'm too ugly for you now,
is that it?
You don't wanna hurt me.
You betrayed me.
I can't trust you no more.
Let me go.
Here, I got a little surprise
for you. Huh, sugarplum?
Starla?
Starla, you in there?
Starla, you all right?
Stop!
What the fuck was that?
Whole damn Council's
a bunch of fucking morons.
I don't know how any of them
got elected. They blame me
for it, like it's...
Bill. Bill, we need to talk.
Shit. Morning, Jack.
We need to find this Grant,
I mean yesterday.
Town Council lit
a Roman candle,
stuck it up my ass.
Jack, your leisure activities
ain't my business.
Hey, don't you fuck with me,
Bill. Your post here
as Chief is in dire straits.
Nobody wants to go
hunting in a town
with a pet-murdering
kidnapper in it.
We'll find him, Jack.
Ain't many places he can hide.
Looks like a damn squid.
Sea World, maybe.
See? She heard you say squid.
She's going to go out
and create a goddamn hysteria.
Shelby,
you gonna create a hysteria?
Not today, Bill.
What's this?
I thought we could
use that like a police sketch,
Chief.
You know,
take it door to door,
see if anybody recognizes him.
Y'all show
some respect right now!
And you! You don't know
what was in there.
You said it was dark!
You don't know
what the hell you saw.
His arm was all bendy, Mayor.
Well, it's obvious
the bastard's got
Lyme disease.
What?
You touch some deer feces
and then you eat a sandwich
without washing your hands,
you got your Lyme disease.
And that makes you
look like a squid?
Well, fuck you all
for laughing.
Chief, another attack.
Over at the Castavets'.
What?
Grant's been stealing animals
off farms, edge of town.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
All right, folks, let's go.
Don't forget your guns.
We don't want any Lyme disease
popping out at us.
Oh, ho, ho, ho.
Ha, ha, fucking ha.
I reckon Grant ain't
got one of them
puppy calendars on his desk.
He just don't strike me
as a real dog lover, is all.
Hey, look!
Knocked this one's head
clear on over here.
Put that down, numb nuts.
He drug the cow through here.
How can one man do that?
Slay all them dogs by hisself?
Well, he's gotta be
in the forest. All three
ranches run alongside it.
You think we should
get up a posse?
Head in there?
It's 100,000 acres.
Be finding a needle
in a fuckstack.
Gather some folks together.
I think I know where
Dr. Dolittle's gonna
strike next.
Right after
Grant ran off,
a calf went missing from here,
Raglan's ranch.
Two nights ago,
a mare was stolen from this
property owned by Fitzgibbon.
That rancher with
the cleft palate?
Yeah. I know that guy.
He looks like a chipmunk.
Your mama weren't too proud
when you came out neither,
Wally.
And then we got
the Castavets right here.
That's where last night's
shit storm took place.
And if he keeps to that
pattern, next he's gonna
end up here,
owned by a family
called the Strutemyers.
I know you're all tired.
You've barely seen
your families.
But we're gonna have to
go there tonight,
lie low and wait.
Well, let's go and get
that son of a bitch, Chief!
Yeah.
All right, boys.
Where's my little darling?
There she is.
Hey, Bill, we got this
grenade we confiscated
from them jokers
who wanted to use it
to fish for trout.
No. We should be
all right with what we got.
All right.
I didn't know the Russkis
were invading.
You seen this guy,
you'd have wished they was.
Give me...
Just give me one second.
Bill, I heard you're
going to get Grant.
Yeah. We...
I think I should go with you.
What? Go... Honey, no. No.
Bill, you need to let me help.
Look, I ain't well-read
on police procedure,
but I'm sure there's
a heap of regulations
No, this is my fault.
against taking
a civilian on a stakeout.
I should've seen it coming.
This is my fault.
It ain't your fault!
He tried to kill you.
He had all those
physical symptoms.
He was acting peculiar...
Starla. Thank you.
I was just trying to
pretend that it wasn't
happening, Bill.
Thank you, Starla.
I appreciate the offer,
but I can't.
If that girl's
still out there,
how are you gonna find her?
How, unless you bring
Grant back alive?
Your best...
Your only chance of
doing that is with me.
She's got a point.
Hey, hey, hey. Come on.
You all done, honey?
Thank you.
Hey, come on now.
Kylie, what did you
do to your fingers?
Kiri Goshimi done them.
She's Japanese.
Yeah?
Looks more like that
Pokeyman's done them, to me.
Foreign stuff is classy,
if you knew something.
There's Jack.
Now, I want you all to
stay inside tonight. You hear?
Hey, Otis!
This turns out to be
a mountain lion,
we're gonna look like
a bunch of damn idiots.
Oh, yeah?
Thanks.
Be a good night to
chase some pussy, wouldn't it?
How about that
Deputy Margaret?
You have a little
deputy thing going on,
you two?
Margaret packs a box lunch.
No shit.
Hey, Starla.
You remember that time
we were kids
and you came knocking
on my window in the middle
of the night?
So Starla here, 12.
I guess I was 14.
I said, "Starla, what the hell
are you doing out there?"
She says that she's gonna
run away to Hollywood
and be a big star.
And she knew I was
in the ROTC, so she says
she needs a bodyguard
and invites me to come along.
And I said, "Starla,
if there's anyone who can
take care of herself,
"I think it's you.
I'm gonna have to decline. "
How far did you get?
About the bus stop.
Because Ranger Rick here
called my dad.
Damn. A cop from the get-go.
You son of a bitch!
You fucked up our fame
and fortune there, Bill Pardy.
Yeah.
Yeah, I guess maybe I did.
You said squid.
It got worse.
He looks like something
that fell off my dick
during the war.
Hey. Hey.
Grant?
Holy shit.
What are we
gonna do now, Bill?
Cuffs won't even
fit on him.
Starla, where are you...
Go, go.
Come on.
Grant.
It's okay, Grant.
You're
just sick, is all.
You're just sick.
We're just here
to take you to get some help.
Right now.
And I'm gonna stay by you.
Just like I swore I would.
For better or worse.
Much fucking worse.
Grant.
Marriage is a sacred bond.
Right, baby?
It's gonna be all right,
Grant.
Just come with us.
You stop right there,
you son of a bitch.
Now, I don't care
what kind of
leprosy you got.
We need to find that girl.
Now you can make this peaceful
or you can make it hard.
No!
Fire!
Move!
Grant!
Get him!
Wally, on my tail!
Do not lose him in the woods!
That fucking...
Get the fuck
out of the way!
I don't want to
lose anybody! Stay together!
Wait for me. Wait for me.
Come on out, you cocksucker!
What are you,
some little pussy?
You afraid?
Psychology.
Over there!
Where did he go?
Now we ain't never
gonna find that girl.
Starla,
get the hell out of here.
What's that smell?
Something dead.
It's coming
from in there, ain't it?
Do you think he's inside?
One, two, three.
You suck.
Margaret, get over here.
Oh, God.
Something's wrong with me.
Yeah.
Oh, Jesus! God!
Brenda.
Oh, I didn't want
no one seeing me like this.
Shit.
How's my boy, Bill?
Is he all right?
Boy's fine, Brenda.
So what's
going on here exactly?
I'm so fucking hungry, Bill.
I'm so hungry.
I never knew anyone
could be so hungry.
Do you mind handing me
a piece of that possum
over there?
Just a little bit.
I think we best get you
to a hospital right quick.
What the fuck they gonna do
with her in a hospital, Bill?
Shut up.
Jesus!
Why is she doing that?
Her tumors is moving.
Relax.
Somebody get her
to stop doing that shit!
It hurts, bitch!
Jesus.
Please help me!
Bill.
Oh, the little fuckers
are tearing me apart!
Oh, the bastard led us here.
Christ,
look out, everybody!
Fuck!
Wally!
Margaret, cover your mouth!
Don't let them in your mouth!
God dang.
Tried to get in my mouth.
What kind of thing
wants you to eat it?
Kylie, honey,
you're gonna turn into
a plum in there.
Prune, Mama.
Plums turn into prunes.
I know what turns into what.
So I want you to finish up
in there and get yourself
into bed, you hear?
Time to turn in, ladies.
Just a couple more pages, Mom.
No.
Besides, you know
what day tomorrow is.
Family fun day.
That is correct.
So good night.
Sleep tight.
Don't let the bedbugs bite.
Night, night.
Night, Mom.
Night.
What the fuck?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Mom!
Help!
Emily! Jenna!
Jenna, open the door!
Shelby, come in.
11-41. I need paramedics
out here right away.
I got four men down.
Shelby, are you there?
Shelby, we got
an emergency here.
This is Bill.
Oh, crud.
Shelby.
This is no time for a break,
Shelby. I mean it.
Shelby?
They alive?
Shelby, I need your help now.
Praise Jesus.
Praise Jesus?
That's fucking pushing it.
This shit's about as far
from God as shit can get.
Either of you ever seen
anything like that?
You ever heard
of anything like that?
Me neither.
And I watch Animal Planet
all the fucking time.
I got no reception out here.
I'm gonna run back to the car,
try to call the paramedics
from there.
That's a long way
with those worms out there.
Yeah, well,
nice change of pace
from shooting them deer.
All right, you three,
get these folks
out of the barn.
All the rot and stench
can't be doing them any good.
You take this. I got my Colt.
Be careful.
Yeah, there's a thought.
You know what this is?
It's goddamn
biological weapons,
that's what it is.
Government's testing them
on Wheelsy. You know why?
Because I don't take
no shit from nobody
at those State hearings.
They wanna put a cock
in Jack MacReady,
they can kiss my ass.
If this shit is contagious,
I turn into a fucking mollusk,
I'm gonna sue those bastards,
I swear to God!
And you can sue right
alongside of me. I don't care
if you're a lesbo.
You don't deserve this shit.
It's like...
Oh, man, it smells like
rotten mayonnaise in here.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hi, sugarplum.
Marriage.
It's a sacred bond.
Just like you said.
What?
I'm sorry for trying to
strangle you and all.
I lost my head.
I didn't mean to do
none of them things I done.
Not
kill them
pets.
Not make Brenda a worm.
But it's my nature,
ain't it?
How can you blame
someone for acting
according to his own nature?
I wanted to tell you
what was going on,
but I was afraid
you wouldn't love me no more.
I never knew love, Starla...
Wally?
You all right?
Maybe you better
set back down.
You don't look so good.
Hey.
Kylie, honey, you okay?
Hi, Kylie, it's me.
Kylie, open the door,
jellybean.
Come on, Kylie.
Open the door.
We love you, sweetheart.
Come on out now.
Open the door.
Get away!
You all get away.
Kylie. Kylie, there's
no excuse. No excuse
not to be with your family.
This is family fun day,
isn't it, Kylie?
Y'all better just
set back down.
You need to get some rest.
You're sick!
Meat.
Hey!
Let her go!
Y'all just take
a step back now, all right?
There you go, sugarplum.
Why you choosing camps
before you hear
both sides of the story?
Both sides of the story.
Why are you talking
like Grant?
'Cause I am Grant.
I'm your husband.
You swore to honor
and obey me.
Obey me.
So put that goddamn gun down.
Oh, shit.
Get away from her!
It burns. What the...
Meat.
Get away from her!
I am gonna shoot you,
I swear to God!
You ain't
gonna shoot me, Starla.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I told you, you always
needed me to protect you!
You for damn sure
ain't got the balls to...
Christ on a cross.
Go. Go, go, go.
Uncle Grant's gonna
show you a good time, girlie.
Get out!
Open this door,
you little whore!
Don't mess with me,
you little slut.
Kylie.
This is your last chance.
Open this door now!
Come on,
you spoiled brat!
No!
You little bitch!
Hey!
What's going on?
What the hell are you doing?
Hey, hey, easy, easy, easy.
What the hell
happened to you, Otis?
Poison ivy out back, maybe?
We're itchy.
No, they're not my parents.
They're trying to trick you.
Hey.
The worms are in their brains.
All right, look,
y'all stay right there
on the spot.
I'm gonna call the paramedics
to come help you.
And Kylie's gonna
come with me.
Hey there, killer.
Starla's my woman, you prick.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Come on.
Damn it!
Come on, Kylie.
Hey, come on, come on.
Don't mess with me,
little girl!
Hear me, girl?
What's with the spitting?
Margaret, come in.
Margaret? Margaret,
are you there?
Chief, go!
They're gonna get in. Go!
My friends
are still out there... Trevor?
What the heck is going on?
My easygoing nature is getting
sorely fucking tested.
Bitch is hard-core.
Get in the car.
Get in the car!
All right, yeah.
Go, go.
Go! Go! Go!
Starla!
Starla! Starla!
So,
how's everybody's evening?
Good?
Good.
Thanks.
Shelby?
Shelby, you there?
Hey, Chief,
how you doing?
Did you find that...
There's a skeeter in here
driving me bonkers.
Shelby,
you seen any of these...
I don't know
what to call them.
They're like big slugs,
only they're fast.
No slugs.
But your mama called.
She said, "The toilet's
all backed up again.
"Why don't you come over
soon as you're
finished there?"
All right, sweetheart, listen.
I need you to listen to me
just for a second, okay?
She said it's what you done
in there on Sunday
what caused the backup.
All right, listen.
I need you to...
I need you to get the CDC
on the horn for me, okay?
Shelby, are you nodding?
Oh, yeah, sorry.
I'll get you right back.
There's a big tree
in her front yard and
the roots got in the pipes
and it messes with
the whole system
on the way to the main.
She uses lots of paper.
Where is the Mr. Pibb?
I told your secretary
to pack Mr. Pibb.
It's the only Coke I like.
Goddamn Brenda exploding
like a water balloon
and worms driving
my friends around like
they're goddamn skin-cars.
People are spitting acid
at me, turning you into
cottage cheese,
and now there's no fucking
goddamn Mr. Pibb!
Jesus Christ, Jack.
Let me get right on it.
It was me.
I became it... Him.
Part of him.
Who?
Mrs. Grant's husband.
But it wasn't always him.
He came from...
He's a goddamn Martian?
Martians is from Mars, Jack.
Or it's a general term meaning
"outer space fucker. "
No, it isn't.
Look it up, cocksucker.
Enough.
Kylie.
Honey.
Honey, what do you mean?
His real face
looks like a needle.
But he's always got another.
He goes from place to place,
worlds, planets, killing them.
Some he gets pregnant,
others he just takes over
with his worms.
And the rest he eats
till they're gone.
Now he's here.
Are you saying
these worms...
These worms in their brains,
you saying
they're all connected?
It's like
they're all one deal?
An animal
that doesn't procreate.
It spreads, grows,
absorbing the minds and bodies
of the organisms around it.
It's a conscious disease.
If I weren't about
to shit my pants,
I'd be fucking fascinated.
We're back.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Shelby,
did you get the CDC for me?
We're at the city limits.
Welcome back,
killer.
Got a little surprise
for the lot of you,
just right around the corner.
Starla!
Starla. Starla! Let her go!
Jesus.
Meat.
Chief!
Come on, come here.
Stay here. Stay here.
Jack, wake up.
Wake up!
Hurry!
Jack!
Meat.
Stay here.
Worms beat us here.
Okay. All right.
There's a grenade
in that station.
Now, if I use that to destroy
Grant... He's the center of
the whole system, right?
Does that mean
the whole thing
will be destroyed?
Maybe.
Okay.
You wait here.
All right? Stay hid.
I'll be back.
Okay. All right.
Easy.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
This is Chief Pardy.
I can't...
Fuck me.
No!
Get... Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
Hey. Motherfucker.
Thank you. Come on, come on.
We gotta go.
Once one sees us,
they all see us.
Okay. Take this. Here.
Starla.
Oh, God!
Sweetie, don't look.
Don't look.
What are we gonna do now?
Probably turn into a couple
of these fucked-up things.
That's kind of negative.
Well,
it's been that sort of day.
Thank you for saving
my ass back there.
You're welcome.
Of course, when I tell
that story, it's gonna be
the other way around.
What do you mean?
Like I saved you.
Yeah, if we live.
Right.
Now, they're dragging
these bodies due north.
Do you think that will
lead us to Ms. Grant?
You like her, don't you?
Come on.
Starla,
don't you be fooling, girl.
Come on down!
Who's there?
Bill?
Starla?
Hello?
Don't you look
at me like that!
Don't you judge me!
You got no idea
what it's like
to be this hungry!
I just ate pig
and I still want more.
Oh, God damn!
Don't you dare judge me!
Are you trying to judge me?
Damn Republican.
We'll run all
you Republicans out of town.
Starla,
I hear you in there.
Come on down and fulfill
your wifely duties,
you hear me?
Starla. Starla.
You said for better or worse!
You lied!
Bitch!
Slut!
Whore!
There's the worm heads.
That's where
they're bringing the bodies.
Probably new breeders
feeding inside.
Oh, my God, that's Grant.
That's where
they're joining together.
Well, now,
that is some fucked-up shit.
There's Starla.
Okay. Okay.
All right. All right.
You stay here.
No, I ain't
staying here by myself.
All right, come on.
You tried to kill me
and run off with Pardy.
You just wanna fuck him now,
cause he's so good-looking.
It's all over, Starla.
And I'll keep growing
till I'm everywhere.
Till I'm all that is!
Then you'll know
what it feels like
to be betrayed.
Won't you, sugarplum?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I just thought
you were trying to kill me.
And you can't expect me
not to go through
some adjustments
after all these changes.
You did a real nice job
decorating, baby.
You like these memories?
Yeah.
I know you don't wanna
hurt me, Grant.
Yeah.
You like being called Grant,
don't you?
I can do that.
I can call you that.
'Cause you're lonely. Right?
You've been alone so long
I can't even imagine, I bet.
You don't have to
be alone anymore.
'Cause you and I,
we could be together.
I never had much use
for this world, anyway.
And I can stay with you
while you do
what you need to do.
'Cause it's your nature,
and I see that now.
I'm here for you.
Pardy!
Kill me, Pardy, please!
You Podunk whore!
I've been around
a billion years.
You think you can
fuck with me?
Yep.
Shit!
Shoot him.
Shoot him!
Bill.
Oh, that...
That really hurt.
Are you all right?
You need both of them things
in you to get all wormy.
Oh, that's awesome. Yeah.
Bet you regret not running off
with me to Hollywood now,
hey, Bill?
Oh, hell, Starla,
I always regretted that.
Now, Bishopville's just
a few miles down the 10.
They got that hospital there
with the big green
steeple thingy up top.
Hey, Kylie, why don't you tell
Ms. Grant that story about how
I saved you from that deer?
Oh, yeah.
Bill saved me from a deer.
Oh, yeah?