Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Dr. Cotter.
He's gonna die.
She's gonna die.
Mom's gonna die. I'm
gonna die. Everybody dies.
I don't wanna... I'm gonna...
I haven't been able
to get him to talk...
respond to me, nothing.
Just this.
Yeah.
I got it.
Thanks, Dan.
She's gonna die.
Mom's gonna die.
I'm gonna die.
Everyone dies.
Nobody matters.
She doesn't matter.
He doesn't matter. She doesn't
matter. Mom doesn't matter.
I don't matter.
Nothing ever matters.
I don't matter. I don't
matter. I don't matter.
He's gonna die.
She's gonna die.
He's gonna die. I'm
gonna die. Everyone dies.
Nobody matters.
She doesn't matter.
He doesn't matter. She
doesn't matter. Everyone dies.
I'm gonna die.
Nobody matters.
She doesn't matter.
He doesn't matter.
Mom doesn't matter.
Nothing ever matters.
I don't matter.
I don't ma...
I'm gonna... I'm gonna...
She's gonna... She's gonna...
Everyone... I'm gonna...
I don't matter.
I'm gonna... I'm gonna...
Hi, Carl.
What's going on today?
I'm dying.
No.
I don't think so.
I think you're having
another manic episode.
Don't...
Don't you tell me.
You don't know.
I feel it all around me,
squeezing.
I'm scared.
Carl, I know that what
you're experiencing feels real,
but it can't hurt you.
I promise.
He's gonna die.
She's gonna die.
Mom's gonna die.
I'm gonna die.
Everyone dies.
Nobody matters.
Hey, Wanda. I'm gonna put Carl
Renken into observation for a few days.
He's harmless. Just make
sure someone checks on him
every couple hours.
You got it.
Thanks.
Hey, Dr. Desai
was looking for you.
Thank you.
No! No! Please!
Please! You don't understand!
I can't go in there! No!
No! No! Please!
No!
Come in.
Hey, did you send
a patient named, uh,
Sarah Marquet
over to residency yesterday?
Yes. She has a history
with drug abuse and mania,
and she's been in and out
of our unit a few times.
Rose, she has no insurance.
Okay, but she needs treatment.
The board is down my throat
about paying out of pocket
for another bed
in the residency program.
Maybe the board should try
giving a shit
about the point of our
job here once in a while.
I'm not questioning
your judgment.
I just need you to
come to me first
so I can get ahead of
it next time. All right?
Yes.
Okay. I'm sorry.
Hey, you haven't been here since
the late shift last night, have you?
Dr. Cotter.
Laura Weaver, 26.
She's a grad student.
Police were called on her
for public disturbance.
EMS brought her in.
Got any psych history?
Nothing on file, but the
police sent over a report
for a different incident she
was involved in last week.
And what was that one about?
A professor at her school bludgeoned
himself to death with a hammer.
She was interviewed
as the only witness.
A hammer?
Hi.
Laura?
My name is Dr. Cotter.
I'm a therapist.
Do you wanna sit down?
Okay.
I know you're nervous.
That's okay.
I just wanna have a chat.
I promise this is a safe place.
Not for me.
Why do you say that?
Come on. Let's sit.
Please.
Okay. I'm gonna have to ask you a couple
of questions that might sound stupid.
What day of the week is it?
Thursday.
And the month?
October.
I'm not crazy.
Nobody's saying that.
But I need you to understand.
I'm a PhD candidate. I'm
not some lunatic. Okay?
Let's just take a breath,
and you can just
tell me what's going on.
I'm seeing something.
Something no one else
can see except for me.
I know how insane that sounds.
I do.
But it's... This thing,
I can't explain it.
What is it you're seeing?
It looks like people,
but it's... it's not a person.
I'm not sure I understand.
It looks like people.
It looks like different people.
Sometimes it pretends
to be someone that I know.
Sometimes it's a random
stranger. Sometimes...
Sometimes it looks like
my grandfather
who died in front of me
when I was seven.
But it's all the same thing.
It...
It's... It's like...
It's... It's like it wears
people's faces like... like masks.
Okay.
Do you see it right now, here?
What happens when you do see it?
It's smiling at me.
But not a friendly smile.
It's the worst smile
I've ever seen in my life.
And whenever I see it,
I just get this
god-awful feeling like something
really terrible is gonna happen.
I've never felt scared
like I do when I see it.
Laura, have you
or anyone else in your family
ever experienced hallucinations?
It's not a hallucination, no.
It's real.
You don't get it.
It does things to me.
It causes shit
to happen around me.
It's taken over my whole life
and my mind and...
it tells me things.
It told me that to...
today... Today's the...
Today's the day that I'm...
I'm gonna...
Okay. That's okay.
That's okay.
I know that what you're
experiencing feels incredibly real.
Sometimes, when we get
emotionally overwhelmed,
or experience an intense trauma,
our minds tend to...
You're not listening to me.
Oh, my God.
I'm gonna fucking die,
and no one will listen to me.
Okay. Laura, it's okay.
Oh, God.
Hey, it's okay. Laura.
Hey, c-can you look at me,
please?
It's okay.
Look at me.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I...
Oh, my God. No!
No! It's here!
Please!
Laura. It's okay.
It's just us.
Get away! Please!
There's nobody else here.
No!
Oh, my God.
I... I have a patient
emergency in eval 2.
I need staff here now.
Hurry.
Laura?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Had Ms. Weaver
ever been a patient here before?
No. Would you say she was
typical of the patients you see here?
This is an emergency
psychiatric unit.
Typical is not really
a thing here.
Right. But she was
a head case, yeah?
I'm sorry, a head case?
I think we're just trying
to get your opinion
of her mental state.
She could've been suffering from
acute post-trauma psychosis.
She was having
paranoid delusions.
What kind of delusions?
She was convinced that some
sort of evil presence
was haunting her.
Yikes.
It's just, we're gonna have to
contact Ms. Weaver's family
and attempt to explain
what happened.
So we're looking for anything that
might make some sense of all this.
If there's anything else you
can tell us that... that might help.
Uh, before she died...
she was... smiling.
Yeah, she sounds
fucking crazy to me.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Rose.
Whoa.
My bad. Did I scare you?
I didn't hear you come in.
Shit.
Hi.
What's up?
Nothing. Sorry.
Something's wrong.
A patient died today.
My patient.
Oh.
Hey, come here.
I'm sorry.
It happened
right in front of me.
It was awful.
I'm so sorry.
What can I do?
This is a nice start.
Maybe we should
bail on dinner tonight.
We can't.
Holly hired a sitter,
and it's just gonna be a
bigger headache if we don't go.
No way. Holly turning
into a headache?
Hey.
I'm sorry, you wanna
talk about being tired?
Now that Jackson's
in the first grade,
I'm literally up
at 6:00 a.m. every day
to make him breakfast
and pack him lunch.
God knows what kind of non organic
garbage that cafeteria is even serving.
Then I have to drive him
to school,
barely have any time
to run my own errands.
Like, I haven't been to Pilates in
weeks. Okay, my body is so fucked.
Not true. I have to go
back to school, pick him up,
then I have to take him to either soccer
practice, swim lessons, karate, theater...
Oh, and he just started
taking Spanish.
I mean, my weekdays
are literally impossible.
Mmm. You are coming
Saturday, right?
What?
Uh, sorry, what's Saturday?
I'm sorry, is that a joke? Wow.
Rose, Jackson's seventh
birthday party. Wow.
I've told you, like, five times.
I can't. I have work.
What do you mean work?
It's Saturday.
I work Saturday.
See, this is exactly why
you have to
get out of that gross hospital
and into a private practice...
Gross?
It is not gross.
...working normal-people hours.
Rose, there have to be
plenty of crazies out there
who will actually
pay you for your time.
Thank you so much
for your input, Greg.
That's very sweet.
I'm just saying,
why become a doctor
if you can't get
disgustingly rich?
You're kidding, right?
Rose loves being a doctor.
She'd do it for free.
What...
Well, on the subject
of wasted earning potentials,
we could always sell the fucking
house. Can we not right now?
I don't understand you.
It's just sitting there.
We grew up in that house.
Rose, it's a total teardown. Why
not just get the money for the land?
Can you guys just
shut the fuck up?
Wow.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Sure.
I've been
looking forward to this.
You okay?
Yeah.
Morning, Doc.
Morning.
Hey. Yesterday,
that patient, Laura Weaver...
The police had sent a report about a
different incident that she was involved in.
Can you get that
forwarded to me?
You got it, Doc.
Also, I was supposed to have
a session with Jane Park.
Oh, yeah. She pulled out a bunch of
her hair overnight and swallowed it all.
They took her down to medicine
to have her stomach pumped.
Shit.
Uh, Rose.
What... What are you... I was
on a... I was on a call nearby,
and I just thought I would...
Um...
You know, we didn't really
get to talk yesterday,
other than the whole...
Whole thing.
And I just wanted you to know
that when the call came in,
I had no idea
it was gonna be you.
So, I'm sorry if that was weird.
It's your job. I get it.
How you been?
Joel, why are you here?
You know, like I said, I was
on a call nearby, and I just,
you know, thought I would...
come check on you.
After everything that happened yesterday,
that's... that's not an easy thing.
Okay. I appreciate it, but I
don't need you to check on me.
Right.
No, yeah, I mean... Sorry.
I have to get back to work.
Yeah.
See you around.
You do know
she's engaged, right?
Yeah.
I'm single.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Um, look, I just wanted to say
sorry about last night, okay?
I shouldn't have
kept going at you like that.
Uh, no, I...
I should apologize.
I've been just dealing
with some stuff.
I wasn't being
very good company.
Okay. If you can't make it to
your nephew's party tomorrow,
you could at least
get him a present.
If you need an idea, he's
really into electric model trains.
Uh-huh.
You sound weird.
Are you okay?
Yeah, no, I'm fine.
Hey, Carl.
How you feeling today?
Carl.
Carl?
She's gonna die.
I'm gonna die.
Everybody dies.
Carl, look at me.
You're going to die.
Help!
Help! This patient is 5150!
He needs to be restrained!
Go, go, go!
No! No!
No!
No! No! No! No!
No! No!
No!
He was aggressive.
Acting psychotic.
Carl Renken has been in
and out of here a dozen times
and has never exhibited behavior
even remotely aggressive.
Do you think I'm making
it up? Of course not.
But yesterday,
a patient in your care
killed herself brutally
in front of you.
Is it possible,
when you presumed
that Carl Renken
was a danger to himself,
that that's what your mind
was reacting to?
I suppose I could've misinterpreted
the situation and overreacted.
Okay.
So, here's what's gonna happen.
You're gonna take
a paid week off.
Morgan,
that's really not necessary.
You've been working
80-hour weeks for months.
I'm concerned
that you haven't been sleeping.
We can't help these patients unless
we have our own mental health in check.
And it's in
the unit's best interest
if you just take a week
and clear your head.
Just do what you gotta do
and come back focused, okay?
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Fuck!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hello?
This is First Line Security.
May I have your name
and the pass code?
Uh, Rose Cotter.
Um, "Acapulco."
Ma'am, we've detected
a door alarm.
Yeah, uh, the... the back
door of my house is open.
Are you alone
in the house, ma'am?
Yes.
Are you sure?
What? Are you sure you haven't
let something inside, Rose?
Look behind you.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Shit.
Hello?
This is First Line Security.
May I have your name
and the pass code?
We did a full sweep
inside and out. It's all clear.
Um, what about the back door?
Is it possible it wasn't fully
latched last time it was closed?
I... I don't know.
Maybe.
Hey, I wouldn't worry about it.
These false alarms
happen all the time.
If anything else comes up,
you can give us a call.
Okay.
Evening, sir.
Um, evening.
What happened?
Mustache?
Mustache.
So, is there a reason
you set the alarm?
Uh...
I literally
don't remember doing it.
I must have just, like,
set it by accident or something.
By accident?
Sorry. Sorry.
My head has just been
in this, like,
foggy, creepy,
spacey place all day.
And there was this weird
incident at work and then...
And then my boss
is making me take a...
Sorry.
Everything is okay.
Are you sure?
No, no, I'm fine.
I was just venting.
Okay.
Can you see
if you can find Mustache?
I haven't seen him
anywhere at all.
Yeah.
Rose, did you
break another glass?
Mustache?
Come on, kitty.
Please. Please.
Mustache.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
It looks like people.
It looks like different people.
Sometimes it pretends
to be someone that I know.
Sometimes it's a random
stranger. Sometimes...
Sometimes it looks like
my grandfather
who died in front of me
when I was seven.
- But it's all the same thing.
- It...
It's smiling at me,
but not a friendly smile.
It's the worst smile
I've ever seen in my life.
And whenever I see it, I
just get this god-awful feeling
like something really terrible
is gonna happen.
Oh, my God! No! No!
No! It's here! Please!
Get away! Please! No!
I... I have
a patient emergency in eval 2.
I need staff here now. Hurry.
Laura?
Rose.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Rose!
Rose?
Whoa! Oh, my God! Rose!
Rose! Whoa, whoa!
What the fuck?
Rose, put the knife down!
Rose!
Hi.
Rose?
This is a surprise.
It wasn't so much the blood.
It was, um...
her face.
The look that she had.
How did it make you feel?
Uh...
Terrified, obviously.
Um...
Vulnerable.
Guilty.
Guilty?
Well, she was my patient.
She was a disturbed young woman
you only met for ten minutes.
Yeah. I just...
I just feel like
I've gotten stuck on it.
I can't, you know,
get it out of my head.
Have you considered
the reason you feel stuck
could actually be more about
your mother's suicide?
Do you still blame yourself?
That...
I'm really not trying
to relitigate
that part of my life
right now. So...
What would you like
to talk about?
I was hoping that I could get
a script for Risperdal.
Ever since that...
patient, I've been, um...
seeing things
and hearing things.
I'm sure it's just a symptom
of post-trauma.
Let's avoid any self-diagnosis.
What is it you've been seeing
and hearing?
Echoes of what happened
with my patient.
You know, just fleeting moments
of stress-induced
hallucinations.
But when they're happening,
they feel so...
corporeal and unsettling.
Rose, from where I'm sitting, you don't
seem delusional or disordered to me.
And certainly not psychotic.
It's my impression this
experience with your patient
triggered old anxieties
compounded with too much
stress, not enough sleep.
You have wounds
that have never fully healed.
And it is possible they never will
completely. That's the nature of trauma.
But you can learn
to get control over it.
Have you been continuing
to see patients
while you've been coping
with all this?
No. I'm just taking
a short hiatus. Good.
If you want my advice,
use this time
to do something different.
Anything that will
take your mind off
the triggers
that are causing you stress.
I also think it would be helpful
if we resumed
our regular sessions again.
Sure.
And what about the Risperdal?
Just... You know.
Let's talk again next week
before we consider any medication.
In the meantime,
you can always call me.
Sure.
No, I asked you for
a white wine spritzer. Jesus.
Oh, my God. You made it.
Hi. Surprise.
Come on in. Come on in.
Oh.
I thought you had to work?
Oh, I decided to take the
afternoon... I'll take that.
Hey, Greg.
What are you doing?
I told you not to take
those out yet. Mmm, mmm.
Geez.
Uh, ladies, I have to go
corral my dipshit husband.
Would one of you please show
my sister to the adult refreshments?
Sure. We have a stash
in the kitchen. Come on.
Wait.
You're that therapist, right?
Yes, I... I am.
Oh! Fantastic.
Can I ask for advice?
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday... ♪
So cool.
Gracias, Harper.
Gracias, Harper's mom.
Ooh, that one's from Aunt Rose.
Open it!
Rip it open!
What'd you get, sweetheart?
No. No.
Oh, my God.
No, no. Mustache.
What the hell is wrong with you?
This can't be happening.
No. No, no. No, I promise
you, this wasn't me.
It wasn't.
It wasn't me, I swear.
You have to... You guys
have to believe me, please.
Somebody
please fucking believe me.
What the fuck are you?
Leave me the fuck alone!
You see her.
You have to see her.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Please, Holly,
tell me that you see somebody.
Please.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, God.
Hey, Rose.
Fuck.
I heard you were brought
into the ER.
I wanted to come check on you.
How're you doing?
Fine.
It was just an accident.
Thank you.
Yeah. They... They said that
you had had a anxiety attack.
Rose, I'll be honest with you,
I'm... I'm concerned.
And I... I mean this
as your friend,
but I really think you
should speak to someone.
Are you seeing anybody
professionally right now?
Rose, are you listening?
Wait.
I need to tell you something,
and I need you to know
that I'm not crazy, okay?
Okay.
Um...
Something is happening to me.
And it's gonna be really hard
for you to believe.
Maybe we should just go inside.
No, wait. Just listen to me!
Sorry. Sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Okay, um...
Something is threatening me.
Some kind of a evil spirit,
or energy.
I... I don't really know
what it is, but...
But I think that it...
It killed my patient.
Because she described experiencing
the same thing before she died.
And now it's somehow
attached itself to me.
And...
I'm just really scared
that something bad
is going to happen.
I really need you
to say something.
What do you want me to say?
I want you to believe me.
Rose, you're talking about
a fucking ghost.
No, no, no. It's not...
It's not a ghost.
It's something else.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I can't.
I cannot fucking do this
right now.
No. Trevor.
Whoa, whoa, wait. No,
no, no. Don't walk away.
I need you...
You're not listening
to what I am saying.
Okay, Rose.
What the fuck am I supposed to
say to respond to this right now?
Do you hear yourself? I mean,
Jesus Christ. You sound crazy.
I am not crazy!
Sorry. Sorry.
But it's genetic, isn't it?
What?
Mental illness.
You can inherit it
from a parent.
I looked it up.
Why would you look that up?
Because...
I wanted to know
what I was potentially
hitching my entire life to.
Is that so fucking unfair?
I'm going in the house.
No, no, no. Please,
Trevor. I'm in danger!
Rose.
Did you kill Mustache?
N... No!
No! That was not...
That was not me.
Then tell me,
what happened to him?
It was the thing.
Trevor, please.
Please. Please.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Rose.
Come here.
Baby...
Please. Help me.
- Mommy made a mistake.
- No, no, no.
No, no, no.
Rose!
Look where you're going!
Are you crazy?
Sorry. I'm sorry.
Mrs. Muñoz?
At first,
I noticed small changes in him.
Then it all happened so fast.
He was on edge.
Paranoid.
He would wake up in the
middle of the night, screaming.
I'd never heard him
scream before.
Then he just
stopped sleeping altogether.
I would catch him having
these conversations with himself.
He was seeing things.
Doing strange things
that he didn't even
seem to remember.
Then one morning he was gone.
That night, the police called
and told me he was dead.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
They asked me
to identify his body.
His face.
Twenty-five years of marriage,
and that's what I have left
to remember him.
I'm so sorry.
Did Gabriel ever describe
the things that he was seeing?
I'll show you.
I should take it all down,
but I can't stand being in here.
This is what Gabriel said
he saw.
He kept saying it was trying
to get inside of him.
That is Gabriel's brother.
He died in an accident
20 years ago.
Gabriel never got over it.
How long had this been going on?
Ever since he got back from that damn
conference he would go to every year.
It was because he saw
that awful woman kill herself.
But no one reports on that.
He watched someone
die by suicide?
Yes.
I assumed you knew this.
What was her name?
I don't remember.
I'd have to find it.
Um...
Did... Did he ever, um...
say why
all of this was happening?
Did he find any explanation
in all of this?
What kind of reporter are you?
Mrs. Muñoz,
your husband was not insane.
The things that he was seeing,
they're real. I've seen them.
What are you, a fucking nutcase?
What? Some kind
of morbid fanatic?
How fucking dare you?
No, please. Please.
What happened to your
husband is happening to me.
Out of my house. I want
you out of my house, now.
Just please give me the name.
Please, just give me the name!
Get the fuck out of my house!
Oh, fuck. Shit.
Yeah?
Hey.
Come on in.
Finally got rid of
that ugly yellow couch.
Uh-huh.
So, uh, what's up?
I assume you're not here
to catch up
considering the cold shoulder
the other day.
I need a favor.
I need you to not ask
any questions about it.
Terrific.
Yeah, let's hear that.
Uh, so, nine days ago,
a man named Gabriel Muñoz
killed himself.
I need to know if he had been involved
in any other recent police reports.
Can you find that out?
Here, for me.
Come on. Are you serious?
This is my one day off.
Go to the station.
Joel, please?
Fine.
Goddamn it.
All right,
what was his name again?
Gabriel Muñoz.
All right.
I see the report on his death.
Yeah. There's another
incident report here
from a week earlier,
from a precinct upstate.
What was it for?
He gave a witness statement.
He was staying at a hotel where
a woman committed suicide.
Okay, um... And what was
her name? The woman?
Um,
Angela Powell.
She's a real estate agent.
What is this?
Fuck.
What? What is it?
It's a picture from the scene.
Let me see it.
No.
No, no.
Look, you don't wanna see this.
This is, like, evidence.
Or, just, you know, have at it.
Holy shit.
Told you it was gross.
Okay, um...
Okay, uh, I need you to do the same
search again, but this time on her.
The woman, Angela.
Can you please tell me
what this is all about?
Joel, you said you weren't
gonna ask me any questions.
No. You said I wouldn't
ask you any questions.
Joel, I need your help.
Okay?
Please?
Hmm.
There was a previous report
filed four days
before her death.
That's a weird coincidence.
She was also interviewed
about a suicide.
What is this?
Is that a video file?
It's, um,
security camera footage.
Put it... Put it on.
Just... It's... It's loading.
What the fuck is this?
You know,
my day was going just fine.
Can you rewind it?
Really?
Rewind it, Joel.
Okay, stop.
Is he smiling?
Rose, who are these people?
I have to go.
Where are you going?
Rose, where are you going?
What is going on here?
I'm so confused right now.
Can you do me one more favor?
Do you have a printer?
Trevor. Trevor, you here?
Hey.
Hi, Rose.
What is this?
What is she doing here?
I wanted to see
how you were doing.
I was talking to my fiancé.
I called her.
Why?
Because you've been acting
completely unhinged.
I... I don't...
And I... I didn't know
what else to do.
Are you fucking kidding me?
I came to you, the person I'm
supposed to trust most in the world,
and I... I confided
that I was scared to death.
That I needed you.
And you didn't listen
to a word I was saying.
No. Why do you think
I even called her?
All I'm trying to do here
is help you.
No! All you're trying to do is make
it so you don't have to deal with it.
You're fine as long as
everything is easy and agreeable,
but God forbid
anything become real,
or even a tiny bit difficult.
And... And you just...
You just think about how it's gonna fuck
up your whole little perfect life plan.
Are you serious right now?
Yeah.
If that's how you feel,
then why are we even together?
Maybe I just don't know.
Why don't we all
just take a breath...
Why don't you just
fucking make yourself at home!
Rose, are you
actually leaving right now?
Greg. Rose, what
are you doing here?
Is Holly here?
I need to talk to her.
I don't think
that's a good idea.
Greg, let me talk
to my fucking sister. Holly!
You're gonna come
and talk to me like that?
Holly, can I talk to you,
just for one sec?
No, I don't think...
Can I please talk to you?
I don't think this is a
good idea. Honestly.
Yeah, it's fine.
It's fine. Holly.
Just go the fuck inside.
I don't... All right. Fine.
Jesus.
Okay, okay, okay.
How are you?
My eyes are open now.
I have been cursed.
Okay, uh...
Or somehow wrapped up
in a curse.
I... I got it from my patient.
She was cursed, and then when
she died, she... she transferred it to me.
And now I'm being threatened
by this... this entity.
By an entity?
No, no.
It... It's what killed Mustache.
It was at the party yesterday,
but you couldn't see it.
Nobody else can see it,
except for me.
Jesus Christ.
No, look, Holly,
I know it's so hard to believe,
and it was difficult for me
to believe it at first either.
But look... look at this. Look.
Oh, my God. Rose. Why
the fuck do you have that?
Because this has happened
to other people.
And they're all dead.
Rose.
And I...
Holly, I'm gonna be next!
Rose, curses are not real.
Okay? You are
having some sort of a...
A breakdown.
What? No, no. Holly.
You're not hearing me.
You are not hearing me.
Rose.
This is exactly
what happened to Mom.
You sound just like her.
How the fuck
would you know that?
I'm sorry, what?
You were never around
when Mom got bad.
Where the fuck were you
when she died?
You have no idea
what you're talking about.
Okay? Because I was older, I
got the worst of Mom's insanity.
I had to fucking
leave the house.
That was the only way
I... I could survive.
And I'm... I'm sorry
that I left you alone and that
you had to be the one to find her.
I know that
that fucked you up, and...
And I know that that's not fair.
I wish I could do
something about it,
but, Rose, I have tried so
hard to move on with my life,
to leave all of that shit
behind me, okay?
You, it's like
you can't accept the fact
that Mom lost her mind
and fucking killed herself.
And you let it
define your entire life,
and you punish me
because I don't want to.
Well, I'm sorry that I'm
actually trying to help people
instead of being some fucking
stay-at-home PTA housewife,
who lives in her own
self-centered, smug little bubble!
Okay. I don't know
why I said that.
You know what, I'm... I'm not
doing this. I'm not doing this with you.
You've completely
traumatized Jackson, okay?
I can't have you around
when you're like this.
Fuck.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Holly?
Fuck! Fuck!
Fuck!
Motherfucker!
Joel?
Why didn't you tell me
about your patient's
connection to the others?
Wha... After you
left, I kept digging.
These cases?
This same pattern.
It goes back further.
So far, I've found 20 cases
involving 19 suicide victims
with a direct line
linking them all together.
And the things these people
are doing to themselves, Rose.
Holy shit.
Wait, you said, um, 20 cases,
but only 19 suicides.
One of the cases
mixes up the pattern.
Some accountant, Robert Talley.
His business partner commits
suicide right in front of him,
and four days later, Talley goes
and fucking murders a woman
he's never met before,
completely out of the blue.
But get this, a week later,
the key eyewitness to the murder
also commits suicide.
Pattern resumes.
So, he's alive?
Yeah.
He's sitting in holding
in Al to on a.
Joel, I gotta talk to him.
I'm gonna need you
to say something.
Yeah, I... I will.
Just... Just...
Give me a second.
I mean, Jesus...
I thought you were gonna say
this was some kind of, like,
crazy suicide cult,
or blackmail scheme.
I mean, this? This is...
This? This is... Hey, Joel.
Okay.
Let's just put aside
the possibility
that some sort of evil,
extraordinary force
could even exist.
What you're saying
is that this thing
is jumping around
from person to person,
and it is causing them
to kill themselves?
Okay,
but maybe it's not suicide.
What do you mean?
Okay. So, my patient,
she was terrified,
but she was not suicidal.
And then at... at the end,
everything about her changed.
It was like the person I had
been talking to was gone.
And something else
had taken over.
So, it's kind of like the guy...
Yes... on the security
camera footage?
Yes. Yes. Exactly like that.
Oh, my God. What the fuck?
In the cases that you found,
um...
how long was it
between each victim's death?
None of them survived
longer than a week.
Some of them didn't even
make it past four days.
Today was my fourth day.
Hey.
Whatever happened
to those people,
it's not gonna happen to you.
I promise.
Transfer guard to gate three.
Thank you.
Give them a buzz through.
They're clear.
I owe you one for this, Doug.
You're just lucky
that he fired every lawyer
he was assigned.
You do know
what this guy did, right?
Well, Dr. Cotter's building
a psychological profile
on a similar case for us.
Oh. Well, Talley's
a whole box of fruit loops.
So, good luck.
Look, you only got
ten minutes with him, okay?
It's the best I could do
without a court order.
Well, I appreciate it.
Mr. Talley, my name
is Dr. Rose Cotter,
and, um, I was hoping
you'd be willing to
answer some questions about...
I'm done answering questions.
I confessed.
I actually don't care about
what you were accused of.
What I need to know is what you
experienced in the days leading up to it.
I have a patient,
a young woman.
Four days ago,
a man killed himself
right in front of her.
And ever since then,
she has been seeing something.
Something that pretends
to be other people.
The man that
she saw kill himself,
he claimed that he was seeing
the exact same thing.
What the fuck
do you want from me, huh?
What is it?
I don't know.
Why is it that everybody else
who's seen it is dead
and you're alive?
Why? Please.
Mr. Talley, you
can help her. Okay?
Please.
Make the cop leave.
Not gonna happen, pal.
Make him leave,
and I'll tell you what I know.
Joel, please.
I'll be outside, all right?
I tried to research anything and
everything I could about this thing.
There's been other chains
in the past.
Found one that was in Brazil
a few years ago.
A man there escaped that chain
by killing his neighbor and
passing it to his neighbor's wife.
Your patient is going to die
unless she kills someone.
That's the only way
you can get rid of it.
The only way.
She has to make sure there's
a witness for it to pass to,
'cause this thing needs trauma
to spread.
That's what gives it power.
Trauma.
Your patient has to
make it count.
Tell her to use
some kind of weapon.
Make the biggest mess she can...
I can't kill someone!
You?
You have it?
No, no, no.
Why the fuck did you come here?
You're not giving it back to me.
Get out of here!
I'm sorry.
Get her away from me!
Hey.
Hey! Wait.
What happened in there?
Nothing.
What'd he say?
Nothing?
He's out of his fucking mind,
Joel.
Ah, fuck.
What are you doing here?
I apologize
if you felt ambushed yesterday.
That was the wrong approach.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
I think you should go.
Rose.
We both know I have a
responsibility to notify the authorities
if you're a danger
to yourself or others.
I need you to help convince me
you're not a danger.
Trevor mentioned there
had been talk of ghosts.
I never used the word
"ghosts."
Evil beings, then.
Paranormal.
I admitted to him that I was seeing
things, the same thing that I told you.
That's not happening anymore.
Okay?
It was stress and lack of sleep.
I confided in him, and that
was obviously a mistake.
But that's it.
Okay? Are we good?
How are you feeling today?
Let me think, um...
I'm pretty sure my fiancé
thinks I'm crazy.
My sister has just
totally shut me out.
And now
my former therapist
is making unannounced
house calls
to ensure that
I am not a danger.
So, other than that,
I'm really good.
Should you get that?
What?
Rose, it's Madeline.
I've been trying your mobile
all morning.
I'm very concerned about
how we left things yesterday.
Rose? Are you there?
No.
Hello?
Rose?
No. No.
Almost time, Rose.
What the fuck are you?
Ple... Please.
No, no.
No. No, no.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
No.
Hey, Dr. Cotter.
Aren't you supposed to be
on leave?
Just grabbing something
from my office.
Carl. Hi.
No. No.
It's okay.
No, no, no.
Oh, God.
No, no. Oh, no, no, no.
Shh. Shh. Just calm down.
No! No, no!
No! No!
Shh! Shut the fuck up.
Just calm down, okay? Okay.
Rose.
What are you doing here?
I don't know.
Rose, you can't
be around patients.
Fuck! Rose!
Fuck!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Rose, what are you doing here?
Nothing.
I don't... I don't know.
I don't know why. I, uh...
Why don't we go inside together
and we can just talk?
No! It's...
It's not safe.
Rose, I don't think you should
be alone right now.
I need... I need to be alone.
I need to be...
I need to be alone.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I have to go.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Rose, I don't think you should
go anywhere, okay?
You just relax, I'm gonna make
a phone call, all right?
Rose. Rose, don't go anywhere.
Wait. Rose, please.
Please don't go anywhere, okay?
Just hang...
Rose. Rose, wait! Rose!
- Joel.
- Rose, I saw a police APB go out for you
that says you're dangerous.
What the fuck happened?
I know what I need to do.
What?
This thing, it needs
all of its victims
to pass it on
in order to survive,
but if there's no one else
around, it has no way to pass.
As long as I'm alone,
I can deprive it
of what it needs.
That doesn't make any sense.
Your plan is just to
avoid people forever?
I am not gonna
keep running, okay?
I've got to face it.
Okay, Rose, I'm coming to you.
Just tell me where...
Rose.
Baby...
Help me, please.
Mommy made a mistake.
Get the phone.
Call for help.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Rose!
Rose.
It's okay, baby.
Come here.
I am so sorry.
I... I haven't been a good mom.
I want to be.
I really try to be.
But sometimes
everything is just too much.
There is something terrible
inside of me.
I hate myself.
Stop. Stop. Stop.
Are you ashamed of me?
No.
Then why did you let me die?
Why didn't you save me?
It's not my fault.
You could have called for help.
Stop. Stop it.
But you didn't.
Stop it.
You wished that I would die.
Because I was afraid of you!
I was ten years old
and you were a monster.
And I know that it's not fair.
You... You needed help.
But I couldn't.
And I have carried that guilt
for my entire life.
And I... I have to let it go.
I ha... I have to let it go.
This is not real.
But Rose,
your mind makes it real.
What are you?
Why are you doing this to me?
Because your mind...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
...is so inviting.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
You can't escape
your mind, Rose.
It's...
It's my mind.
You can't escape it either.
Rose!
Holy shit.
Are you okay?
Can I just come in for a
sec? Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
Where have you been?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for dragging you into
my whole fucked-up mess.
For most of my life,
I've been afraid of
letting people get too close,
because I was afraid of...
what they might see
if they really looked.
And so I... I put walls up,
and I kept people at a distance.
And then...
I met you,
and I could feel
those walls coming down.
And it scared the shit
out of me.
And so...
I was selfish,
and that was not fair to you.
And I am so, so sorry.
And I'm... I'm being selfish
again by even asking,
but do you think that...
That I could stay here
and just...
just sleep?
Could you...
stay with me while I sleep?
Please.
Yeah, of course
I'll stay with you.
I'll stay with you forever.
No.
No, no, no, no.
No, no.
No.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Rose.
No, no, no!
Rose!
No.
Rose, open the door!
Open the door.
Rose!
No!
Fuck. Uh...
Hold on. I'm coming!
No!
Rose!
Rose.
Rose?