♪♪
Kayla, are you seeing this?
Whatever.
It's pretty spectacular.
Wow.
Those mountains are gorgeous.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
They converted this
massive old church off of 20th Street
into this, like, insane,
just, dreamland.
There was dancers hanging
from the rafters and glitter
just like exploding
from the ceilings.
There was boys and girls
and club kids and queens
and everything in between,
you name it.
And so it's my first night
there, and I see this guy
and he's like this, like,
perfect Adonis,
just like flowing blonde hair
and sculpted abs,
and just, like, a
total Greek statue.
Wait, so you were in your 20s?
Uh-huh.
And I was terrified.
He turned out to be
a total prick,
but your first one usually is.
Actually, most of them are.
Everyone except your dad.
- Aaron, what's up?
- Do you guys hear that?
No, what?
♪♪
I don't hear anything.
Exactly.
No traffic, no sirens,
no shouting.
I think it's the most
beautiful sound I've ever heard.
Well, you know what they
say about silence right, Dad?
- What?
- It's deafening.
How original.
I think she means it's peaceful.
So what about you, Dad?
What?
How'd you lose your virginity,
was it with Mom?
It was.
I was about 100 years old,
which is how old you'll be
when you lose yours.
How do you know
I haven't lost it already?
Ok, booger.
Dinners over, you're done.
No.
You know, it's just
because of her mom, right?
She's feeling abandoned.
Let's just give her some time.
She'll stop blaming you
soon enough
and when school starts up again,
she'll be busy like
totally being a senior.
Yeah.
Yeah, maybe you're right.
She'll be like the cool new kid.
Yeah, exactly, she'll be fine.
She'll be better then fine,
she'll be too legit to quit,
that's what all the cool kids
are saying, right?
I-I don't know.
I'm the old man, remember?
You're the New York
party monster.
Come on, baby, you know I burned
all those brain cells years ago.
Don't burn anymore.
You really have
to start tomorrow?
Mm-hmm.
You know I do.
Can't afford to take
another day off.
♪♪
Yo.
Rise and shine, booger.
It's your first day in paradise.
Screw off.
Come on, your dad's
already left to work.
Let's surprise him and get
this palace put together.
- No.
- Come on, kid, get up.
No.
♪♪
I look good though, right?
Oh, my God.
Yeah, that's hilarious.
What'd you use for your tits?
Um, socks, obviously,
stuffed with rice, duh.
You think that ones good,
check that out.
Wait, oh, my God!
Is that my dad?
Ah.
She's such a pretty girl.
Oh, my...
No, no.
- She's hideous.
- What?
Unh-unh, honey, this is not
hideous. This is punk rock.
Oh, my God. It's my dad
in a dress.
- It's not punk rock.
- Oh, booger.
Believe me, choosing to live
your life loud and proud
is about the bravest thing
you can do in this world.
♪♪
Hey, how's it going?
- This sucks, Kayla.
- Yeah, I know.
You might as well be
in another country.
Don't say that.
You know I don't want
to be here.
- Hey.
- Learn to knock, Dad.
I did knock.
Well, you have to wait
for an answer.
Hey, Mr. Miller.
How you liking
the small town life?
Hey, Derek.
How's it going?
Doing my best.
City's not the same
without your daughter, though.
Oh, well, you guys will be
together soon enough.
I'm sure of that.
Hey, Derek.
I'm going to get murdered
if I stay in this room
any longer so um, we'll catch up
later, okay, dude?
Sounds good,
Mr. Miller.
Alright, I'm going.
-How's your other dad doing?
He's fine, I guess.
Just do me a favor, Kayla, and
I don't mean anything by this,
but just, don't share
any drinks with them, okay?
All men are created equal.
They are endowed
by their creator
with certain unalienable rights,
that among these
are life, liberty,
and the pursuit of happiness.
Hey, how's it coming?
Slow.
This guy's the worst.
Honestly, I just can't believe
I'm still taking on spec work.
It won't be for long.
I've seen enough of your writing
to know how brilliant you are.
Get to work.
I need some help paying off
this damn house.
Okay.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
♪♪
- Good morning.
- Hi there.
Hi, I'm Tiffany
you're new neighbor.
Oh, oh, hi.
I'm Aaron.
Sorry to come by so early,
I just, I saw your gardener
working so I figured
I'd come say hi.
My gardener?
Uh, I... Oh, oh, no,
that, he's not.
He's my um, my partner.
- Malik.
- Oh.
Come say hi.
This is Tiffany,
our next door neighbor.
- Hi.
- Wow.
That's so exciting.
We don't have any
of you in town.
Really, none, huh?
Maybe they're just all
in hiding.
Anyway, I brought
over a housewarming gift.
When it blooms, it's just...
It's stunning.
Okay. Thank you. That's,
that's really, we didn't...
Oh, don't worry about it.
I'm just so happy we have some
fresh faces in the neighborhood.
Nothing ever changes
around here.
Well, that's sounds like
just the kind of change
we're looking for.
I better get going, I just...
Yeah, it was so good
to meet you.
Bye bye.
She seems nice.
Mm.
She's something.
This is, uh...
Okay.
Well, I gotta go.
What you doing, booger?
Printing resumes.
I'm gonna go crazy if I'm stuck
inside with you every day.
So sweet of you, Kayla.
Thank you.
And here I was kinda hoping
you'd stick around
and be my assistant.
Oh, yeah, what you going to
pay me with, my dad's money?
Excuse you, I have
my own money, thank you.
Yeah, right.
Let's hope I don't end up
on a milk carton.
Okay, your dad and I
won't miss you if you do.
♪♪
It was through
my wife and loving children
I realized what
American values really were.
It's not our personal pride
or what we achieve
as individuals
that makes this country great.
It's our ability as a family to
maintain and uphold our values.
The traditional family unit.
It's everything.
♪♪
The traditional family unit.
It's everything.
Kayla?
♪♪
I did not realize
we were painting.
Yeah, figured it could
use a fresh coat.
Look's great.
What'd you get up to today?
Oh, my God. What did
you get up to today?
Oh, you know, I hung out.
Unpacked a few things.
Got a job.
Shut up!
Yeah, for real, all by herself.
- What?
- Whoo.
You're looking at
the new hostess
at Bill and Pete's
Bar and Grill.
Oh, my God, totally
celebrating that.
You're getting up.
♪♪
♪ Why you look so blue ♪
♪ Boy, I know it's true ♪
♪ You do
You do ♪
♪ Come on to the floor ♪
♪ There's room for one more ♪
- ♪ And that's you ♪
- No.
♪ Yeah, you ♪
♪ Yeah, we got all the kids who
got nothing to lose ♪
Malik, you're missing out,
get up here.
Malik, get over here.
♪♪
Oh!
♪ Here's looking at you ♪
♪♪
Do you remember
when we were kids?
That summer we stayed up
at your aunt's cottage
and you thought it was a
good idea to tell your friend
Erica about us?
And you remember how I said
I had a really bad
feeling about it.
Except the world's
a different place, Malik.
It's not like it was back then.
Oh, my God, how can you say that
and actually even believe
yourself?
Someone just broke into my house
and spray painted the word...
Okay, don't... don't say it.
I hate that world.
Well, my point is the world
is exactly
the same place
as it was back then.
People don't change, Liam,
they just get better
at hiding how they feel.
I know you don't mean
that Malik.
What does Aaron
think about it all?
He thinks the same as me.
You haven't told him
yet, have you?
You just had a security
system installed,
Malik, what's he going
to say about that?
I don't know.
Okay. Whatever.
It's your life.
You do what you want.
Shit, I gotta go.
- Oh, hi.
- Hey.
What are you doing in here?
Just putting away some boxes.
How was your day?
- So long.
- Mhm.
Can you please hurry up
and get famous already
so I can retire?
Maybe in a million years.
Confidence, that's great.
I knew there was a reason
I fell so hard for you.
I'm so glad you guys
could make it.
Well, thanks so much
for inviting us.
Marshall.
These are our neighbors
I told you about.
- Hi, there.
- Hey.
- Hi, I'm Aaron.
- Aaron, welcome.
- This is Malik.
- Malik, welcome.
Thank you.
Hi.
So, Malik, it seems
that you and I have
a little something in common.
Oh, yeah.
What's that?
Well, we both stay
at home all day
while our significant others
venture out into the real world.
I run an IT company
from the house.
I work alone. I'm a one-man
show, but I love it.
♪♪
Oh, yeah, I bumped into
Tiffany on my way home
from work the other day.
I mentioned you're a writer.
A writer.
That's so exciting,
So what are you working on?
I mean, it's just a bio piece.
Just ghost writing.
- Well, to new neighbors.
- New neighbors.
New neighbors.
- Cheers.
♪♪
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hey!
Stop!
Don't hurt me!
What the hell are you doing
on my property?
Take this.
Please take it.
Take it.
Don't tell anyone.
♪♪
What the fuck?
What's going on?
Is everything all right?
Do you know where I put my keys?
I get so confused lately.
I, uh, my sense of time
is, uh, mixed up these days.
A security system.
We didn't
even have one in Chicago.
Jesus fucking.
I said I'm sorry, okay.
I should have asked.
- I'm sorry.
- How much did this thing cost?
- Like a few thousand.
- Oh, my God.
You know what people do
in the suburbs,
they leave their doors unlocked.
♪♪
Don't tell anyone.
Please take it.
♪♪
Everything all right?
Yeah.
Well, it's nice to see you, too.
♪♪
You call the alarm
company today?
- For what?
- A refund.
We're not keeping that thing.
So is this what you do
in this town?
Pretty much.
So you're the new girl
with the two dads, right?
Here we go again.
No, I didn't mean it like that.
I think it's pretty cool.
So where's your mom?
You're nosey.
Just want to get to know
you is all.
She's probably partying
in Costa Rica
with her new family
and my inheritance.
Ouch.
You really want
to get to know me?
Get to know this.
Shit.
No way!
- I just crushed you.
- Okay, rematch.
We're doing this again.
♪♪
Hi.
Good God.
Is he?
Aaron, last night I... I think
I saw something over there,
there was...
Tragic, isn't it?
Yeah, do you know what happened?
Well, his grandson found him
in the middle of the night.
Called a few of us
over to say our goodbyes.
Turned into a bit
of a celebration.
It's just so sad for him.
They were really close.
♪♪
Need a lift?
Are you stalking me now?
Pretty much.
Where you going?
I'm heading to work.
Call in sick.
No way.
Come on.
Please?
♪♪
You just don't give up do you?
You ever think about leaving?
I don't think so.
I mean, everything's here.
My friends, my family.
You.
I have a boyfriend
back in the city.
I mean, at least I think
I still do.
You should probably
figure that out.
♪♪
Hey, do you see that?
What is he doing?
♪♪
Come on, let's get out of here.
What is it?
Nothing.
What?
What is it?
Just look... I just really
don't want to go over there,
those people creep me out.
Oh, my God.
You always do this.
Do what?
Every time we try to make
friends that are bit more,
like, normal, you create drama.
What does normal mean?
You know what it means.
Okay, what's the world
for an "Uncle Tom,"
but for gay people?
Really?
Well, I don't care
what anybody says
it doesn't matter
if you're a single mother
or a married couple like us,
or... or even, you know.
Love is all that matters.
I mean, that's a really nice
thought and everything,
but I'm not sure most people
would actually agree with that.
Well, people who don't
are assholes.
Honey.
Well, come on, honey, they are.
No, he's right.
Even my ex-wife showed
her true colors.
You wouldn't believe
how many times I had to hear
her lawyers try and educate me
on how being gay meant
I was fit to parent
my own daughter.
Hm, Yeah, I believe
the official term
they used to describe our
relationship was "illegitimate."
That's right. High risk, that
was one of my favorites.
You know what high risk means.
What?
Oh, Jesus.
I-I find it disgusting
how easy it is
for false stereotypes
to shape public opinion.
People don't think anymore,
they follow.
Tyler, is that you?
Yeah, sorry I missed dinner.
It's in the fridge, honey.
- So, where were you, son?
- Just out, with a new friend.
How did it go?
Very well, thanks, Mom.
I'll be in my room.
Seems like a good kid.
Well, he's a teenager,
does that count?
Did you say the second door
or the third?
Alright, who's ready
for apple crumble?
♪♪
1792.
I see you found Richard.
He was my great,
great something or other.
Apparently quite a ship's mate.
He fought for the blue coats.
I could have sworn you said it
was the third door on the right.
Second, but who's counting?
You can really see
the family resemblance.
Well, a long blood line.
I started gathering info on our
lineage over a decade ago
and I've got a solid
collection of photos now.
Come on, let me point you
in the right direction.
♪♪
It became my duty to help them.
To lead them back to
a wholesome existence
where they can find happiness
and reclaim their identity.
These young men and women,
they're suffering inside.
♪♪
During a time of racism
and homophobia
my father was a maverick.
An American hero.
♪♪
I thought your ass got a job.
It's part time, duh.
Make sure not to
strain yourself too hard.
I'm not stupid, thanks.
♪♪
I got you.
Hey, you look freezing.
♪♪
Thank you.
Come on, let's go smoke a bowl.
Yeah.
Hi, it's Malik, right?
Listen, I...
I need to talk to you.
It's about my grandpa.
Please.
I'm sorry if he startled you
in your back yard.
His mind, it wasn't well.
But did he say what he was
doing out there?
Honestly, your guess
is as good as mine.
Did he give you anything?
No.
♪♪
Why?
They're calling it a suicide,
saying that he took
all his medication at once.
I miss him.
It's okay.
♪♪
I miss him so much.
Uh, I didn't realize
we had company.
Uh, Aaron, this is uh...
I'm Matthew. Hi, it's nice
to finally meet you.
You're Aaron, right?
That's right.
Uh, well, I should probably go.
Thank you for listening.
♪♪
So, you obviously like him.
Who?
Matthew.
It's been a while since
we played with someone.
- Could be fun.
- Are you serious?
Do you remember
when you dragged me
to that party at
your friends Jason's?
Could be like that.
It's never gonna happen.
I only want you.
Come here.
Oh, my God.
- Kayla.
- Oh, my God.
- I'm bleeding.
- Kayla, honey what is it?
- Ah!
- Look at me!
- What happened, from where?
- I don't know.
Where's it coming from?
What is it?
- I don't know.
- Malik, get towels!
♪♪
Oh, my God.
Do you think someone
put those up there?
What?
No.
Why would anyone do that?
Probably just living up there
and they ate poison
or something and died.
♪♪
God, that's so much blood.
That's why I founded
the Ernie Darrylson clinic,
in my father's name.
The clinic, you see, it offers
a path back
towards righteousness,
away from sin and temptation.
These young men and woman,
they're suffering inside.
It became my...
♪♪
That's why I founded
the Ernie Darrylson clinic,
in my father's name.
♪♪
Gay conversion therapy works.
Jesus Christ.
Have you guys
seen my Polaroid blanks?
I swear I had a bunch of them.
Maybe if you cleaned
your room once in a while.
Nice try.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
♪♪
Don't tell anyone.
Please take it.
♪♪
I need to tell you something.
- What?
- I can't do it.
What are you talking about?
The book.
My hard drive failed.
It's totally fried,
last night it started smoking.
I just...
Well, did you back it up?
Oh, my God.
Malik, you've been in there
for almost an hour.
You're using up
all the hot water.
I have to go.
♪♪
Sorry, booger, I'll be out
in just a...
♪♪
Police are calling it
a murder suicide.
♪♪
Oh, my God.
Is everything all right?
♪♪
- We need to move.
- Oh, God, here we go.
We need to get out
of this town, Aaron,
there's something
not right about this place.
What are you talking about?
The night the alarm went
of Mr. Reinhart,
he gave me a piece of paper.
There's a series of dates on it.
It goes back for decades.
Will you just listen to me.
He was trying to warn us.
I saw them in his house, Aaron,
Marshall and Matthew
and a bunch of them
and they were doing
something in there,
and the next day Reinhart,
he just turns up dead?
I just...
There was another couple, Aaron.
There was a gay couple
that lived in town
and they were killed
10 years ago.
Why the fuck wouldn't
Marshall and Tiffany
have mentioned this?
They knew and they
didn't say anything.
They've been lying to us.
Nobody's lying to us, Mal.
If you engaged with them.
If you literally spent any time
at all being social with them,
you would know this.
They were close with them.
They told me all of this.
Marshall and Tiffany
are good people, Mal,
and you know what,
I happen to like this town.
Jesus Christ, Aaron.
You need to stop thinking that
everyone's trying to get you
all the time.
I thought we were past this.
What happened to you,
was tragic, I know, but...
Oh, God, please.
It's not going to happen
again, I promise.
♪♪
You can't make
that kind of promise.
♪♪
Malik, calm down, you're
just seeing what you want to see.
The numbers are just noise,
they're meaningless.
Every 10 years,
you don't think that's even like
a little bit strange?
Do you think maybe,
the reason you keep calling me
is because you're looking
for permission?
Permission for what?
To move on.
I have moved on, okay?
I've clearly moved on.
We can't keep doing this, Malik.
I'm hanging up.
What? No, Liam, come on,
I need your help with this.
Liam?
Shit.
♪♪
This happened to us
our first week living there.
♪♪
Hello?
Who's there?
♪♪
What the fuck?
Aaron!
Why was my hard drive removed?
What is this?
This isn't me.
Aaron, I swear
this didn't happen.
They look pretty real to me.
Don't you see what's going on?
They're doing this to us.
Why didn't you tell me
that this is what you wanted?
I would have let you.
It didn't happen.
It's not.
Aaron, don't go.
Stop.
I don't.
I don't want to see you here
when I get back.
Where am I supposed to go?
Figure it out.
Aaron!
♪♪
Fuck.
Aaron, you have
to let me explain.
What?
Wait, what did she do?
She deserved it.
Jessica's a total bitch.
Kayla, seriously, I do
not want to hear it.
She said I was going
to give Tyler AIDs
because, well, you know.
People see your dad and I
as different than them,
and different scares people.
Well, people are idiots.
Plus, Tyler likes me way better.
I am fucking serious
right now, Kayla.
In this town
and in this country,
it is not safe for people
that stand out, okay?
You need to forget
everything that I said
about loud and proud,
do not draw attention
to yourself.
Don't speak out,
don't speak up, it is not safe.
♪♪
Besides, that Tyler kid
is a little creep.
He only wants one thing
from you anyway.
I don't want you hanging
out with him.
Do you hear me?
Kayla, do you hear me?
Yeah, I hear you.
Promise.
♪♪
Don't worry about Jessica.
We're done.
I want to be with you.
♪♪
Wait.
Hold on a second.
♪♪
I've never gone
all the way before.
Thanks for telling me.
I'm ready though.
No, that's okay.
I think we should wait.
♪♪
What's wrong?
You don't want me?
No, no I do.
I really do.
Just, I want it to be special.
♪♪
This, my friends,
this is radical feminism.
The agenda that Clinton
and Clinton
would impose on America.
Abortion on demand, a litmus
test for the Supreme Court.
Discrimination against
religious schools,
women in combat units,
homosexual rights,
but that's not the kind
of change America needs.
It's not the kind of change
America wants,
and its not the kind of change
we can abide in a nation
we still call God's country.
♪♪
Malik.
Can I help you with something?
- I could use a drink.
- Cheer up.
I'm sure Aaron will come around.
Just doesn't make any sense.
So it's not true then?
I'm not judging.
No, it isn't true.
At least I don't think it is.
You don't think it is.
Things have just been...
They've just been
a bit foggy lately.
So, your hard drive.
It's funny, Aaron
seemed so worry about it
when I swung by the house
to pick it up
but there was
nothing wrong with it.
- Nothing.
- No.
Nothing.
There was something else though.
Malik, I, I saw the folder.
What folder?
Well, I think
you know which one.
If people were to catch wind
of that stuff,
I mean, it just...
It wouldn't look good,
especially someone
in your standing.
I have no clue
what you're talking...
We're friends, Malik.
Your secret is safe with me.
But if I were you, I really
would consider getting some help
because you obviously
have a problem.
I made you a back-up hard
drive over there
I'll come by later
and install it.
♪♪
It's an exciting time
to be alive, Malik.
So much change happening
in the world, yet so much
seems to just stay the same,
do you know what I mean?
Excuse me.
I have to go.
♪♪
Liam, are you there?
Your call cannot be
completed as dialed.
Check the number and dial again.
♪♪
Did you find your keys?
Okay, yeah.
Oh, I found them.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- They're right here.
- Oh, thank God.
♪♪
And here we are in
our first day in our new house.
Let's get a shot of Sam's
new bike.
- We're going to be happy here.
- Yeah.
Hannah documented everything
that happened to her family.
Well, at least they told us
how they really felt.
Fuck you, whoever did this.
It's all the same things.
Look at this,
he's giving camera tips.
It's part of some
kind of ritual.
Every 10 years, they make a
selection, that's...
Please, please do not
say what I think you're about to say.
-We're the selection.
-Okay, don't, don't.
We've been chosen.
- Chosen for what?
- Once the selection's been made,
there's nothing anyone
can do to stop it.
♪♪
Malik?
Malik? You need help.
Fuck.
♪♪
Oh, motherfuck.
They switched my fucking meds.
This number has been
disconnected or is
- no longer in service.
- Liam, are you here?
If you feel you have reached
this recording in error,
please check the number and try
again.
Mom, please stop recording me.
I suck.
Oh, come on, you're
getting really good.
♪♪
I'm terrible.
Oh, you're great
what are you talking about?
I love you, Mom.
Thank you.
Kayla.
♪♪
What the fuck?
Kayla!
Aaron!
♪♪
Malik, oh, my God.
I'm so glad you made it.
It's such a special night.
What the fuck
is this? Where is she?
She's fine. After all,
this is all for her.
Aaron?
Aaron.
Where have you been?
What do you mean,
"Where have I been?"
You kicked me out.
That was almost a week ago.
Malik.
Hey, welcome. I didn't know
you were going to be here.
- Where have you been?
- Malik what are you doing?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, Malik, no.
Stop.
Malik, Malik.
What are you doing?
- I'm protecting her.
- From who?
You!
♪♪
Malik.
I'm putting the house
up for sale.
Kayla and I...
...we're going to move back to
the city
- and stay with my mother.
- Oh, my God, thank God.
Oh, my God.
Aaron, you have to run as far
away from this town as possible.
It's not the town we're
running from, Malik.
I know you don't understand it,
but I did what I had to do.
Liam knows why I had to do it.
Liam?
Who's Liam, Malik?
My ex-boyfriend,
who do you think?
Jesus Christ.
Maybe if you just... maybe
if you just go talk to him.
Maybe If you talk to him, then
he can tell you everything
and you'll know...
You'll know why I did it.
I can't do that, Malik.
Why?
Why can't you?
♪♪
- I have to go.
- No.
No, Aaron, please.
Aaron, don't go...
Just talk to him.
Just talk to him, please.
Aaron, just talk to him.
I was just protecting her.
I had no choice.
♪♪
Can I come in?
We're in this together.
You know that, right?
We're gonna get through this.
♪♪
Is this thing even working?
Mom, seriously, the red light
is blinking,
that means it's recording.
What, it's a party.
Come on, I want to go see Ty.
You're too young
for a boyfriend.
You got broken into
in this town?
That's what we thought,
my wife is, she's really upset about it.
Well, obviously it
must have been teenagers.
Well, speaking of which,
ours seem to be
getting along just fine.
Why don't you and Ty
come get a plate of food?
Jesus Christ.
♪♪
What the fuck are you?
I'm someone who's been around
for a very long time.
Kayla?
Kayla.
I don't like this
any more then you.
But this is how it works.
And this, well, this,
is how we make it work.
You can take me, okay?
You can take me.
I'll do anything you want,
just don't hurt her.
You know I can't do that.
It's too late.
Stay the fuck away from her!
Kayla, open the door.
Kayla, open the door, wake up.
♪♪
You broke out of jail
tonight, Malik.
You had drugs in your system,
another relapse.
You killed her, you killed your
husband, and then yourself.
♪♪
No.
- Why!?
- Isn't it beautiful?
That's what everybody's
going to say,
and not one soul will question
it because of who you are.
People won't care, Malik,
they've already
got their minds made up.
They're afraid of you,
and when the tides change,
there will be someone
else to be afraid of.
There always is,
there always will be.
It's human nature... fear.
We just exploit it.
♪♪
They choose someone vulnerable,
and they vilify them.
♪♪
They do this so no one bats
an eye.
♪♪
This happened to us
our first night living there.
Everything I know
about this town
and what the people here have
been doing,
is in this document.
♪♪
I'm making this for you
so that you have a chance.
♪♪
I don't know who will find this,
or what kind of person you are.
♪♪
But my hope is that
you might be the one
to finally break this cycle.
♪♪
Now that I've told you all this,
what you do with the
information is up to you.
Just remember, hope is never
silent.
♪♪