Happy birthday to me!
Happy birthday!
- Oh, my God!
- Anybody want this?
That's what happens when
you do a mercy invite.
I believed you wanted
to invite everyone.
Dad, I can't invite everyone in
my art class except for one person
without social networking evidence
inflicting more pain on that
person than was intended.
And I'm not a monster.
I'm proud of you. I think.
She gets detention a lot and she yells
at teachers sometimes.
There was that rumor that went around
that she just kept
running away from home.
Um, maybe she can Uber.
I seriously believe that
we can go home now.
Um, did I mistakenly convey
this was a democracy?
We are not going
till she gets picked up.
Uh, the car broke down.
I'm just gonna take the bus.
You're not taking a bus.
I'll drive you home.
Claire has almost saved her half of
the money she needs for a car.
Isn't that right?
This'll be one of the few times left
I can drive you guys around. Huh?
Uh, I...
You won't be able to hear
my dad tell jokes
that only he thinks are funny
for an entire car ride unless you come.
You don't really wanna miss that.
Wow! I got more gifts
than I thought I did.
Can I put this in here?
Yeah, I'll get it.
Thank you, Marcia.
Maybe he just is into...
Maybe he's just content where he is.
Hey. Can I help you?
What?
This is the one.
He's really funny.
He does these weekly videos.
See? It's so random.
That is so weird.
Yeah, you have a crush on him.
- I don't get it.
- Pause it.
Yeah, go back.
Why don't you get it?
I just don't get it.
He's blond and he's cute.
No, his eyebrows are just like...
Shut up. His eyebrows?
That's the one thing you couldn't get?
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Oh. You see what he does, though?
How does he even do that?
That's the whole point
why I'm showing you.
Genius!
So bad.
Hey!
Pardon me, sir. I think
you have the wrong car.
We woke up in here.
What the hell is going on?
What are we doing here?
What happened to my dad?
He's out there.
Do you know what happened to my dad?
I choose you first.
It's only gonna be a minute.
Pee on yourself.
No!
No.
Open the door!
Hey, are you okay?
He wanted me to dance for him.
The outside door is locked.
Everything's okay.
We're okay.
I hear the tiniest little splash
and here it comes.
A freak of nature, like this.
So, he comes across the stream
and he's so tall
that the water doesn't even
get to his belly.
Then he stops.
And my heart's coming out of my chest.
You got buck fever.
Uncle John's got buck fever.
That's not true, Casey.
Your daddy's a liar.
How big was the rack?
It was huge.
Where are you supposed to
look when you shoot, Casey?
At the body.
Then why was he looking at the rack?
'Cause he had buck fever.
She'll say anything you say.
You gonna do that when you get your
mentored hunting license in three years?
No, sir.
Make sure you put your
gloves on after you finish.
Your feet and your hands
get cold first out there.
Three students abducted.
The father of one of the students
woke up dazed in King of Prussia,
reportedly drugged.
He found the kids and the car missing.
Neighbors are in disbelief.
A normally quiet community
is reeling after this abduction.
If you have any information concerning
the whereabouts of these girls,
you are urged to contact the police.
It doesn't matter
if you open that door, Claire.
There's a second locked door.
He's gonna come in
here again, any second,
and we're not letting him
take one of us out again.
We just cried and screamed
and we didn't hurt him
because we were afraid to get him upset.
God, that's victim shit. Jesus!
We should fight him.
We should drop a crazy-ass bomb on him.
I saw him carry one of you
and lay you on the bed
like you weighed nothing.
One punch from him
would knock one of us out.
I took six months of Kenpo karate class.
And you distract
the assailant with pain.
Everything is so easy for you guys.
You do one thing, you can
predict the next thing.
It's not the way it's gonna be
in this situation.
We're not getting out of here.
You're saying that you're not gonna
fight with everything in you?
You know the only chance...
The only chance we have is if
all three of us go crazy on this guy.
We have to hurry.
We need you, Casey.
Claire's smart. Let's listen to her.
I'll do it if you're gonna do it, too.
We can win.
He'll hurt us.
No. Shut up.
Both of you.
You're gonna pick your miserable
self up and help us get out of here.
Blow me.
And your six months of karate at the
King of Prussia Mall can blow me, too.
No! No, no, you can't do this today!
You can't do this right now.
Why do you do this?
Why do you act like this?
Why do you act like
you're not one of us?
When you're aiming, Casey,
always keep both eyes open.
Cover your target with the barrel
then move with it to get its pace.
I'm warning you, it's gonna be
frustrating the first times.
You're gonna shoot
under it or behind it.
You'll learn to stay with it.
Females are smarter than the males.
But you know that, it's like humans.
Females use their nose to stay alive.
They make sure they have cover.
They always remember they're
trying to stay alive.
Bucks go off by themselves.
Bucks get dumb during mating season.
Boys make too much noise.
Yes, they do.
I'm better than a boy, right?
Yes, you are.
Hey
I'll let you know when I hear
something that makes sense.
We don't even know what this is yet.
Hey! I was inspired.
No, no, no, that one.
That one, before the pink
frock coat with the thorns.
That's supposed to be
like a tailored jacket,
but I'm gonna hand-print it
with newspaper headlines.
I'm a simple blouse and
skirt person, but these...
These are very artistic, Barry.
Just the kind of thing Hamptons
ladies would spend $15,000 on
to wear once at a charity ball.
Shut up!
You know, I can't stay too long.
This is just a visit.
Well, tell me what's going on.
What, you mean the email?
No, just the usual things.
Just feelings of being overwhelmed.
The terseness of your email made it
sound specific and time-related.
Are you looking for something?
- No.
- No?
I'm just admiring. I'm better now.
How's work?
It's great.
When I last spoke to them,
they believed you were a model employee.
They found you meticulous
and conscientious.
- You know this, right?
- I do.
You've managed there for 10 years.
You're functioning very well, Barry.
And it's a rare and wonderful
place for you to work.
Yes, it is.
You know, of all my other
clients with your disorder,
you've been the most
consistent at your job.
Did something happen, Barry?
How old are you?
Just... The Internet is
inconsistent on this point.
Why is that on your mind?
Who's gonna look after us
when you retire or pass on?
You know, we're gonna have
to take care of ourselves
and nobody even believes that we exist.
If ever something were to happen to me,
I've made arrangements with a colleague
from Baltimore to take over.
Hmm.
Hey, do you, uh...
You live alone?
You know this.
I'm sorry, I just meant how long?
Always.
That must be so lonely.
Uh, you know what?
I'm doing much better. I shouldn't
have emailed you. I'm just...
Look at me. I'm too impulsive.
By the way,
is anybody listening?
Does anybody care about us?
Yes.
The University of Paris has asked
me to do a lecture, in fact.
I'm going to be doing it
via Skype from right here.
People are believing more.
Let's meet at our usual time next week.
I would rather you didn't leave, Barry.
Did something happen?
Don't worry.
This was just a visit.
I'm doing much better, I actually...
Don't you want your sketches, Barry?
You're usually very protective of them.
Yeah.
Thanks.
I'll see you next week
at our usual time.
Thanks for fighting
for us, Dr. Fletcher.
Thanks, Dr. Fletcher.
Welcome.
I just think I'm gonna blow it.
No, you'll be great.
I'll see you next week.
Okay, thank you.
...DJ's exclusive million dollar
Holiday Bucks Bonanza.
I don't know how you work
with those people.
What people?
Your patients.
You can't use your thumbs
to spin the wheel, dumbasses.
They always use their thumbs. Oh.
Well, we look at people who've been
shattered and different as less than.
What if
they're more than us?
What?
Do you believe them?
Your patients.
Just between you and me.
- Yes, I do.
- Hmm.
Flick it! Flick it!
...coming up next, right after this.
I don't believe it.
- No offense.
- No.
...but when you call, we'll send you
a second easy-feet absolutely free!
Just pay separate processing.
So that's two easy feet...
Now, that, I need to buy that.
He's back.
There's a lady outside.
Dennis, admit what you've done.
Don't get upset.
Don't tell me.
I'm getting frightened.
I thought that you had
this under control.
Please tell me it's not too late.
The food is waiting.
Is she in that room?
- We're here!
- Help us!
We're in here!
What is this? How many are there?
No, don't go in there!
Don't go in there!
Don't worry.
I'll talk to him.
He listens to me.
He's not well.
He knows what you're here for.
He's not allowed to touch you.
He knows that.
Mmm-mmm.
Hmm?
Karen. Joe.
They said you can't have your
own panel at the national conference.
They conceded, however,
that you can be part of
the mood disorder panel.
It's not a mood disorder.
Oh, I'm aware of your beliefs, Karen.
Well, were they open this time
with the new evidence?
One of your arguments is a dog?
You submitted video of
a dog acting differently
to one of your patients
at different times?
It is more dramatic than that.
They are what they believe they are.
The brain has learned to defend itself.
You speak of them like
they're supernaturally gifted.
Like they have powers or something.
Karen, these are patients.
They have been through trauma.
And perhaps now they are
capable of something we're not.
We have brain scans now.
DID patients have changed their
body chemistry with their thoughts.
He's just trying to scare us.
He was having a full
conversation with himself.
What was that line about?
"The food is waiting."
Does everyone get how wacked this is
and that we need to get out of here now?
No.
Please, keep your area neat.
The bathroom, it's unacceptable.
To make it easy, I've color-coded these.
Use the blue bottle for the floor
and the pink bottle
for the ceramic surfaces.
Uh...
Patricia has reminded me that
I was sent to get you for a reason.
That you are sacred food.
And I promise not to bother you again.
Maybe he has a dog or something.
You think he's gonna
feed us to his dogs?
Casey.
Casey!
My name's Hedwig.
I have red socks.
He's on the move.
What?
He's...
on...
the...
move.
Who?
Someone's coming for you
and you're not gonna like it.
You guys make noises in your sleep.
Tell us.
I'm not supposed to say.
But he's done awful things to people
and he'll do awful things to you.
I have blue socks, too.
We're his food?
How old are you?
Nine.
So you're not the guy that took us?
No.
You're not the lady?
What are you, blind?
You don't know how they think?
No, they don't tell me much.
I just ate a hot dog.
Could you help us, Hedwig?
No, I'm not even supposed to be here.
I stole the light from Mr. Dennis,
but he'll be back real soon.
I can't steal the light for too
long or he'll know and get angry.
Etcetera.
See you!
Wait.
We heard something.
We didn't understand it,
but now we do.
Do you know what we heard?
What did you hear?
Come here.
I'll whisper it to you.
Okay.
This guy
is coming for you.
You're a big fibber.
I never lie, Hedwig.
But Mr. Dennis,
he said that he followed
those two girls for four days
and that he knew
that they were the ones
that he would want.
When you're not around,
Dennis and the lady talk about it.
They talk about how
he wants a boy this time.
They're going to give him you.
No, Miss Patricia, she said...
She said she's not mad at me anymore.
She sings to me sometimes.
I think Miss Patricia is
still a little mad at you.
Miss Patricia thinks I'm...
She thinks I'm stupid.
She thinks I make silly mistakes.
Look at me.
We're like your babysitters.
We'll let you watch TV
and make you a fun dinner.
We all need to get out of here.
You could show us the way out.
We could be gone
before anybody gets back,
but we have to hurry, Hedwig.
We have to hurry and get out of here.
Wait a minute.
It took forever to get this place safe
without the nosey bodies
that work here finding out.
You can't get out of here!
I have to blow my nose.
No, wait! Please don't go!
Who's coming?
This is seriously scary.
No one's coming.
He said something.
He said something
about making the room safe.
This is all new drywall.
What was unsafe?
Wait.
Wait, are we sure about this?
Casey, you were right.
There's something here.
He was covering up a way out.
Tell me if you see him.
Casey, tell us what you see.
He's here.
You can't let him in!
This is our one chance.
We're not gonna make it.
Yes, we are!
What?
Hey, what are you guys doing?
Hey.
Okay, quit it.
Okay, guys?
Let me in.
Give us a second. We're changing.
What are you guys doing?
Let me in.
Guys, you're not being funny.
You're being bitches!
Now, I'm gonna slap you!
I'm gonna slap you in your face.
Just give me as much time as you can.
You're gonna get me into trouble.
Guys...
All right, push up.
Hey!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I thought I lost you.
Would you, uh...
Would you step outside, please?
You like to make fun of us.
But we're more powerful than you think.
Step outside.
Please.
You shouldn't trick children.
That shows who you are.
Look at your sweater. It's ruined.
It's dirty.
Remove it.
I'm trying to be good.
You will not see your friend again.
She will be kept separate.
You take off your skirt.
You take off your shirt.
Clothes you got all dirty from the dust.
One identity in an individual with
Dissociative Identity Disorder
can have high cholesterol.
One.
There have been cases where one
identity is allergic to bee stings.
The others are not.
Are there moments where two identities
can coexist at the same time?
There are times when two identities
can take the "light" or "the spot"
or consciousness at the same time.
This happened with a student
that I was working with.
And her left and right hand
were taking notes
in different hand-writings about
separate things at the same time.
The differences in the
identities can be dramatic.
As much as the difference
between you and me
and every person in that auditorium.
The identities have different IQ’s.
They have different physical strengths.
One personality is
a Russian weightlifter
and can lift three times
his body weight.
Their ability to hyper-focus
and have different
experiences is astounding.
Have these individuals,
through their suffering,
unlocked the potential of the brain?
Is this the ultimate doorway
to all things we call unknown?
Is this where our sense of
the supernatural comes from?
It's about depth
and curves...
Hey, you see that one?
It's kind of like
a chenille sweater-dress.
Who are you?
Barry.
I don't think you are.
I've developed a nose for sensing
whom I'm talking to and whom I'm not.
Have I done something?
You've emailed for
an unscheduled appointment
two days in a row.
We're just feeling overwhelmed.
Garden-variety issues.
I think Orwell or Jade
or Samuel or Heinrich
had the light for a moment
and emailed me.
And you're here to
tell me everything's okay.
I emailed you.
May I talk to one of them, please?
That can't happen.
I...
I told them that I wanted to
spend the session with you today.
I'm gonna ask again.
To whom am I speaking with now?
Dr. Fletcher, it's Barry.
It doesn't seem like Barry.
Barry is an extroverted leader.
Yes, I am.
I'm gonna take a professional guess
based on the description
of all 23 identities
that live in Kevin's body,
that I've gotten from Barry.
I think I'm talking to Dennis.
But he's been banned from the light
because, among other reasons,
he has a proclivity to watch
young girls dance naked,
which he himself knows is wrong
and has fought against
with little success.
I'm encouraged we can finally meet.
And I've guessed this
because you've adjusted the chocolate
dish twice since you came in here
and I understand you have OCD.
I see. Now, I see. That's clever.
That's clever, but I'm not Dennis.
And you and Patricia have
been banned from the light
for quite a while now.
Primarily, shall we say,
because of your beliefs.
Patricia and Dennis are very unstable.
I'm not Dennis.
Have you both taken charge now?
Please believe me, I'm Barry.
You must forgive me.
My job is to challenge you.
And, as you must know by now,
I have plenty of opinions about
how everyone should live their lives.
Ask me something about fashion.
I'll prove it.
Look, look, look. Lindt.
Yeah, look.
You see? I'm not Dennis.
You want me to do something else?
You got ice cream?
Oh, this shirt's a cotton blend anyway
and the collar is from
three seasons ago.
Snood? I mean, come on.
Jai, what health-conscious
fast food purveyor
did you originally solicit
to buy these chicken wings
you've so lovingly reheated
in a minor suicidal gesture?
Hooters. And you can't just
throw them out, Dr. Fletcher.
Oh, this is wrong on so many levels.
We finished about 3:15,
so look around 3:18.
You're getting a little soft
around the middle, Jai.
Mmm-hmm.
The authors of Hooters play
on our incessant need for fat
and man's incessant need to be in
the proximity of augmented breasts.
It's like Henry V ran
a fast food franchise.
It's a good place, Dr. Fletcher.
Right.
How'd you know
the trash would be spilled?
How can I say this, Jai?
You're not the most
meticulous of people.
This guy isn't very neat, is he?
He walked right through the trash.
No, Jai.
Any normal person
would have walked around it.
That was an act.
What are you up to, Dennis?
Or is it Patricia who's deciding things?
We're not gonna die.
Bad things happen.
But not like this.
Casey...
Talk to me.
We need to get to a window
or a door, or something.
Don't you think?
The thrill, Casey,
is about whether you can
or can't outsmart this animal.
See, you didn't used to
like to come out here.
This is like our
family tradition, right?
Good shot, big brother.
Thank you, John.
I have your meal, sleepyhead.
Eat.
It's good?
It's got paprika in it.
I'm sorry.
I think I'll put a pretty
flower in your hair.
There we are.
That's to show how important you are.
Come along.
We'll have a proper meal.
I understand.
This must all seem
so unsatisfactory for you.
But we are doing the best we can.
Good?
Hmm?
Can Claire come eat with us?
No.
No, I'm afraid that can't happen.
She almost ruined our big reception.
Mmm...
I've heard that Asian people's
music aids digestion.
I'll make you a second sandwich.
Do you know,
a family of lions can eat
35 pounds a day?
A buck can lose 30% of its
weight during mating season,
chasing does around.
They're crepuscular, right?
It means they travel around
during dusk and dawn.
Good for you.
It's crooked.
Forgive me.
I don't know if you know,
but tigers have only 30 teeth.
That's 12 less than a dog.
I thought that was a fun fact.
No.
Marcia.
Marcia, listen to me.
Go to your room. Shut the door.
Do it now.
"In the sun, we will find our passion.
"In the sun, we will find our purpose."
You've always been protected.
You've never truly suffered.
And that's why we chose you.
You've always been asleep.
You never had a chance.
The dark-haired girl,
she's gonna be kept in another closet.
You might as well know at this point.
The Beast,
he's coming for you.
All three of you, you're
gonna be kept separate.
You've got...
You've got a crumb on your shirt.
Please take it off.
Just...
Just take it off.
Hey.
Ah.
It wasn't nice, what you
said about Miss Patricia.
You lied.
I'm sorry about that, Hedwig.
You guys lied to me,
made me scared, etcetera.
Mr. Dennis, he says
you wear a lot of shirts.
I like this shirt.
Thank you.
Do you know who Dennis
and Miss Patricia are?
No.
Every one of us has to wait in a chair,
and Barry, he decides
who stands in the light.
But Barry lost that power because of me.
I can wish myself into
the light anytime I want.
It's a special power.
Barry just has to keep sitting
in his chair if I want him to.
That's why Dennis and Miss Patricia
said I could be with them.
Dennis and Miss Patricia,
they believe in The Beast
and what he can do.
Have you seen him?
The Beast?
No. Can I kiss you?
I wanted to kiss the other
girl with the dark hair,
but she's in trouble.
So, do you want to?
I mean, I don't know
much about kissing, though.
Yeah.
Okay.
Uh...
Okay, here we go.
One...
Two...
Three.
You might be pregnant now.
Am I a good kisser?
Yeah.
I like dancing.
Do you like dancing?
I like dancing to
my CD player in my room.
Kanye West is my main man.
We got my CD player set up in my room,
right next to my window.
I'm like...
We gots the moves.
Wow.
Maybe I could watch you dance
and listen to music with you.
No, my music's in my room.
Oh. Right.
Maybe
you could sneak me there.
Are you trying to trick me?
Etcetera?
I'll tell on you.
I'm telling on you.
I'll tell you something.
And you can tell me
if I'm lying or not, okay?
- Mmm-hmm.
- Like a test. Okay?
I get into trouble
at school, on purpose.
So I can get sent to detention.
To get away from everyone.
So that I can be alone.
Okay, I'll show you
something cool in my room.
Okay.
But after Mr. Dennis has finished
his getting-ready ritual.
I have to go.
He's got an appointment.
When I fall asleep,
one of the others keeps trying
to reach the doctor lady
to tell on us.
That pant, it's got a red lining.
You can see it in
the long slit down the side.
We have been talking about
silk-and-wool blend for 20 minutes.
Can I guess that you emailed
me in the middle of the night
for an emergency session
due to garden-variety issues?
I was down and I emailed you and
I woke up and I feel better.
I feel better.
I had a thought.
Mmm-mmm.
I want to talk about
the incident at work.
It's okay, Barry.
You're safe.
I just want to bring the details back.
We'll just talk about the details.
A high school from Camden, New Jersey
was on a field trip
at your place of work
and two young ladies came up to you.
And one took your hand
and put it under her shirt on her breast
and the second one did the same
and then they just ran off
laughing to their friends.
You surmised that it might be on a dare.
You said they were 17 or 18.
You said it upset you for days.
It was just a teenage prank.
I get that now.
And see, that's my mistake.
I believe that I went over this
incident with you too fast.
Although you said you were fine,
and the other identities
I met with said it was fine,
I believe that this brought up issues
from when you were a child and abused.
Sometimes another incident of abuse
can cause suppressed
personalities to take the light.
Dennis, if this is you,
I completely understand
why you felt the need to take
over and protect the others.
Please!
Doctor, not this again.
The others told me
that you and Patricia told
the group about this Beast.
And I told them that these
are just scary stories
that Dennis and Patricia tell
the others to scare them.
How this Beast can crawl on walls,
like the best rock climbers using
the slightest friction and imperfections
to hold his body close
to seemingly sheer surfaces.
How his skin is thick and tough
like the hide of a rhinoceros.
Do you really believe
the stories about The Beast?
Hmm.
If this is you, Dennis,
I understand why Kevin needs you.
You are strong and disciplined.
You are precise
and you will not be taken advantage of.
You can trust me.
For example,
I do have the ability to use Kevin's
full name and bring him forward
as he has in the past.
But I wouldn't do that.
I know that that would
be chaos for all of you.
Everyone would grab the light.
I don't want to hurt
any of you that way.
You don't have to hide.
I know you are someone
who cares for Kevin.
You are not evil to me.
You were necessary.
Dennis.
Is that you?
They keep calling us The Horde.
The others, you know?
Miss Patricia and I, we are ridiculed.
Now, we're not perfect, but we
don't deserve to be ridiculed.
We're all struggling.
They have to admit that.
I am pleased to meet you, Dennis.
You, too.
I assume you don't know who emailed
me for the emergency sessions?
One of the others.
Are you in charge?
Yeah, we've taken charge.
We're the only ones
that can protect Kevin.
We're all here to protect Kevin.
He's very weak.
He doesn't know how powerful we can be.
Would you mind telling me when
you first came into existence?
And how you and Patricia,
the other undesirable identity,
became aligned?
That's okay.
Do you still have strong beliefs?
That depends on what.
This story of The Beast.
One thing, Dennis, that may
comfort you if you are confused
is that you've met the other alters.
You're all in a room in chairs, right?
Yeah.
But you never met The Beast.
Because he doesn't reside
with the rest of you.
Because he resides in the
train yard, as the story goes,
because Kevin's dad left on a train.
But the fact is,
you and Patricia have
never met The Beast.
Have you?
No.
That's because he's not an alter.
He's not the 24th identity.
He's a fantasy.
Hurry up! Let's go!
Come on, it's time.
Wow.
I know.
This is your CD player?
Yeah.
You don't like it?
- It's not new...
- No!
No, I'm just, uh...
I'm confused.
You said it was near a window.
Oh, that's here!
Watch.
Now, it's closed.
Now, it's open.
Did you think it was a real window?
So you could leave, etcetera?
Help me get out of here, Hedwig.
Just get me the keys
and let me out the door.
Please.
Miss Patricia says that nobody
will make fun of me anymore
when The Beast comes!
She says that everyone
will see how amazing I am
and then all of the silly mistakes,
they won't matter anymore.
I think you should go
back to your room. No!
Wait, please,
I wanna hear your Kanye West albums.
Show me your room.
Let's stay here.
I'm sorry I asked to leave.
I can't.
You said you wanted to show
me something cool, right?
No.
- Show me something. Please!
- I don't want to.
This!
Wow.
It's nice.
It's not a toy.
This is real?
Yes!
It's Mr. Dennis'.
He doesn't even know I stole it.
Pretty cool, right?
You can listen to people talking
and they don't even
know you're listening.
Who does this talk to?
Don't touch that.
I just wanna see if it works.
Hey, what are you doing?
Don't touch those buttons.
You're gonna get us found out.
- Yeah, East gate here.
- What up?
Don't talk.
- Don't talk.
Hello?
I'm gonna slap you!
Who's this?
Hello. Hello, my name is Casey Cooke.
I'm being held in a basement.
I've been abducted with two other girls.
Who the hell is this?
Hello?
Casey Cooke.
I've been abducted.
You need to find me.
Betty, is that you?
This isn't funny.
Call the police. I must be near you.
I'm being held in a
basement or something.
Okay, Betty, listen.
Tell Larry and Fish I said hi.
Tell him I still got his
orange headphones.
I don't know where I am.
There's a man here.
He abducted us and
he's going to kill me.
I only have a few hours left.
Please.
I'm begging you.
Somebody save us.
Wait, who is this?
And how did you get one of our walkies?
Put your hands together in contrition.
"In the sun, we will find our passion.
"In the sun,
"we will find our purpose."
I read that on a sympathy
card in a supermarket.
It was for funerals, but
I thought it was beautiful.
Dennis will explain the
meaning of this evening.
The Beast is a sentient creature
who represents the highest
form of humans' evolution.
He believes the time of
ordinary humanity is over.
I hope this makes you feel calm.
You will be in the presence
of something greater.
I was gonna ask for your last shirt,
but I won't.
Because tonight is a sacred night.
It's almost over.
Casey. Come on.
Let's pretend we're animals again.
Come on.
Casey, come on. This is our game.
I'll tell your dad
you're not being nice.
Come on, take off your stuff.
Animals don't wear clothes.
Come on.
Yeah, yeah.
Hey, Casey bear.
This isn't funny.
Is it loaded?
Casey.
I'm your uncle.
Stop it, Casey.
Put that gun down.
I'm getting upset.
I'm about to get very angry.
Give me the gun!
Could have killed me.
This place is closed.
You can't get in.
No, it's okay.
Hello, Dennis.
One of the others emailed me just now.
Is everything okay?
We're fine.
Dennis,
Kevin is really lucky to have you.
You are quite extraordinary.
I just don't want you guys to get hurt.
You think we're extraordinary?
I like you, Dennis.
May I come in?
And can we talk?
I know you wanna tell me something.
Why don't you just tell me?
We're very similar, you and I.
Both on the outside, looking in.
Please, sit.
I don't get many visitors.
Uh, I'll get you some water.
They got a proper quarters for me
in a building on the south side,
but we prefer it here.
When they promoted me
to head of maintenance,
they said I could have it.
Who are you going to meet?
I wanna talk about
Kevin
and what his mother did to him.
I remember it all.
I'm happy you're suddenly so open.
Kevin's mother had
rather malevolent ways
of punishing a three-year-old.
Is that when you arrived in the light?
Yeah.
The one way to avoid her attention
was to keep everything spotless,
everything perfect.
I know you're coming from
good intentions, Dennis,
but there are other ways
to help Kevin now.
I've lost so many patients
into the system.
I want you to know, Dennis,
I will never stop fighting for you.
My patients have become my family.
They are what I've chosen instead
of a more traditional path.
I hope you feel you can
be truly honest with me.
I actually wanna be honest with you.
I lied before.
When you asked if
I'd ever met The Beast,
I said no.
That really isn't true.
You wrote about a woman in Germany
who'd been blind for 10 years.
And then, it was discovered
that she had DID.
Then three of her identities
developed sight.
And you speculated that her
optical nerves regenerated
because of her beliefs.
What are you trying to say?
There are things, Dr. Fletcher,
that all of us would
find hard to believe.
Are you trying to tell me
there's a 24th identity?
You protect the broken.
When you said that you thought
this situation was extraordinary,
I knew you can maybe understand.
Understand what?
The Beast
is real.
He's just emerged.
You were right about everything.
What does he look like?
He's much bigger than I am
and I'm the biggest of all of us.
He's tall.
He's very muscular.
And he's got a long mane of hair
and his fingers are
twice the length of ours.
He believes we are extraordinary.
That we don't represent
a mistake, but our potential.
You say the same things.
He's on the move.
What does that mean?
I don't understand.
He can't be real.
There must be limits to what
a human being can become.
And there's another whole part
of the story, isn't there?
About the eating of the impure young?
What does impure even mean?
Well...
We should discuss that
so that you can understand fully.
Understand what?
Sometimes,
there's just no other way.
Who are you going to meet?
Him.
You know what?
I would love to take notes
on all of this.
We should probably discuss this
in a proper session tomorrow.
Really?
You're okay with this?
This has been so wonderful,
you being so open.
I can see that you feel very empowered
by the philosophies of The Beast.
I'm going to go now.
I knew you would understand.
I'll see you.
Would you mind
if I used your bathroom?
No.
It's down the hall, near
the stairs, on your left.
How we doing?
I'm okay.
Are you real?
Who is it?
Help me.
Is someone there?
Please help me.
They will never reach their potential.
They don't really matter.
Listen to me, Dennis.
I should've listened better.
I should've understood
what you're capable of,
how powerful you are.
Patricia says your way isn't working.
The world will understand now.
Dennis, this is an egregious wrong.
These young women are suffering.
This is a crime.
I can't let you keep them here.
We've gotta stop this.
This identity is monstrous.
I'm really sad you feel this way.
Can't you see?
He is formed because of
your time in this place.
There's a lady.
Someone's here.
We need to get out of these rooms.
Is there anything in your room?
Anything that we could use?
There's nothing in here.
There's a hanger.
Thank you, Dennis.
Here you go, sir.
It sounded like there were slide
bolts on the outside of our doors.
See if you can move the lock
through the crack in the door.
Stay calm.
We're getting out of here.
We're gonna get Casey.
You can do this, Marcia.
With regard to Chahamana's defeat
and Muhammad of Ghor's conquests
between 1192 and 1200,
I would liken it to
Muhammad's brazen ultimatum
that Prithviraj
either apostatize or fight.
Like Prithviraj's defiance,
we should stand up
to The Horde's advances.
In the face of their scare
tactics, we should show...
I hate my insulin shots.
No one else around here
has to take them.
Why do I have to have diabetes?
All the doctors, besides Dr. Fletcher,
say that we're the same person.
Just personalities, huh?
How do you explain I'm the only one
that needs these, you motherfuck...
I'm wearing cargo pants from the '90s.
And a scarf.
If it wasn't for the
Varvatos T-shirt underneath,
I'd be a mess.
I got no taste for things right now.
I'm worried sick.
I have a very bad feeling
that I'm losing time.
I decide who gets the light, right?
I think
someone is stealing the light
from me when I'm not aware.
The Horde keeps obsessing about
the ones who haven't suffered.
I don't know where they're going
with this, but it scares me.
Picture yourself
in a couple hours at home.
On the couch,
in that ugly-ass sweatshirt
that you love.
It's an animal!
He goes like this if there's
a coyote or something.
Kevin, Kevin.
Thank you
for helping us till now.
I guess I should tell
Dr. Fletcher about this,
but she'll worry.
She's such a sweet woman.
I believe I will go for a nice walk
and think this through organizationally.
Thus ends my journal for Monday.
Ciao.
Claire.
Marcia.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Claire.
Claire, let's go.
"Kevin Wendell Crumb."
Kevin Wendell Crumb?
Kevin Wendell Crumb.
Kevin Wendell Crumb!
You made a mess.
Come out here.
Kevin Wendell Crumb!
You made a mess!
Get out here!
Who are you?
What's happening?
Something horrible.
What'd I do?
Did I hurt you?
Dr. Fletcher.
Who did that?
You did.
I swear, I was on a bus.
I don't remember
anything after that. I...
This is still September 18, 2014, right?
There's a shotgun I bought.
It's in the bottom cabinet,
hidden behind things.
The shells are in my uniform
closet out in the service hall.
Kill me.
Then kill me.
[AS JADE] Wait, no!
Don't do that!
He can't handle reality.
My name is Jade.
Has Dr. Fletcher been
getting our emails?
This is what we have to do.
[AS ORWELL] As in 1008,
when Anandapala suffered
the Shahis' most crushing defeat
and Mahmud overran the entirety
of the Punjab region,
taking the famed temple of Kangra,
we have been wronged by this alliance,
this horde of Patricia,
Dennis and the boy.
Their actions do not represent us.
They are every...
[AS BARRY]
Everybody, just take a minute!
Oh, baby girl.
They've been stealing control
of the light from me.
But the group are gonna
work through this.
Honey, my name is Barry.
[AS HEDWIG] You shouldn't
have used the walkie-talkie.
They almost caught us.
Stop it, Hedwig!
They were right. Look at you.
You're so frightened of us.
Dennis and Miss Patricia
are in charge because of me.
I'm gonna give the light to them now.
No one's allowed to
make fun of me anymore.
[AS PATRICIA] Thank you, Hedwig.
Everything's fine now.
Kevin Wendell Crumb.
Kevin is asleep.
We've made him sleep far away.
You can call his name
all you like, dear,
but he's not going to hear you.
The Beast has shared with us his dream
of a larger group to sustain him.
No.
Ten to 12 unworthy young next time.
This is just
the start.
Let go!
Help!
No! No!
No.
It runs in our family.
My daddy died, too.
Same way.
Heart attack.
But you don't need to worry.
I'm going to take care of you.
Now,
you won't be giving me
any trouble, will you?
I know you won't, sweetie.
We are glorious!
We will no longer be afraid.
Only through pain
can you achieve your greatness!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
The impure are the untouched,
the unburned, the unslain.
Those who have not been torn
have no value in themselves
and no place in this world!
They are asleep!
Fuck!
Your gun cannot hurt me.
Can't you see I am not human?
Kevin is a man. I am much more.
You are different from the rest.
Your heart is pure!
Rejoice!
The broken are the more evolved.
Rejoice.
What in the name of Mary and Joseph?
What are you doing in this area?
Just keep walking, honey.
They won't do nothing.
Vince, call the police.
She said some people got hurt
in the area below maintenance.
Okay.
Now, I'm just gonna check you.
Third deceased name
of Dr. Karen Fletcher.
Still trying to locate the family.
Casey Cooke's guardian's here.
Your uncle's here.
You ready to go?
[AS DENNIS] It didn't go through.
[AS PATRICIA] We are
what we believe we are.
Holy shit!
This is so cool!
They're gonna believe
we exist now, right?
[AS DENNIS] They're gonna have to.
[AS HEDWIG] So what do we do now?
[AS PATRICIA] We trust in him.
He'll protect us.
Look at what he can do.
Let him show the world
how powerful we can be.
The suspected murderer Kevin Crumb
suffers from the controversial
psychological disorder DID.
The rumors coming out of the scene
are almost unbelievable.
There are conflicting stories
if the suspect is alive or dead
after sustaining
two point-blank gunshots.
Reports even indicate
one of his personalities
is an amalgam of the various animals
in the Philadelphia Zoo where he worked.
The press is already referring
to the alleged attacker
by a dark name leaked by
a source close to the case.
Because of his many personalities,
he is being called...
The Horde.
This is like that crazy guy
in the wheelchair
that they put away 15 years ago.
And they gave him a funny name, too.
What was it?
Mr. Glass.
Oh, yeah.