Subtitles by explosiveskull
Hello?
Anybody?
Please.
Hey.
Did you hear that?
What is that?
Pass it over here.
Hello?
Oh my god.
Oh my god, can you hear me?
But keep this
woman, oh King of kings,
beneath thy almighty wings.
Oh God, the spirit
of all our joys,
the cause of our delights, the
glory of our darkest nights,
and the comfort of
times like these.
Strange, isn't it?
Everybody's always smiling.
I keep just waiting
for her to walk in
and stop all this nonsense.
It's Aubrey, isn't it?
Aubrey Parker, right?
From Spirit 105 AM.
- I remember you.
I didn't know you knew Grace.
Hey.
I don't know how he does it.
Mark, I mean.
I don't know how he puts
up with all the consoling.
I couldn't handle it.
I didn't know
what to say to him.
I just left.
He looked right at me.
I'm Alice, once of Grace's
English cousins, obviously.
I'm Aubrey.
You're Aubrey?
God, I don't think I ever
had a conversation with Grace
where you weren't mentioned.
You escaping?
Yeah.
I have a flight in the
morning that I gotta catch.
Your speech was
really beautiful.
I love hearing about
grown ups as kids.
Well, you should go.
Yeah.
I'm sorry to ask,
did you get her letter?
She was obsessed with this song.
She kept playing it
over and over again.
It seemed to be
something that helped.
She'd take her
walks, and the music,
she kept saying, "Aubrey
would understand.
"Aubrey would get it."
I still don't know
how you drank this shit.
Oh, fuck.
Hungry?
Hey, Bellini.
No bitey bitey, okay?
Perv.
Hello?
My name is Aubrey Parker.
And I broke into my
dead friend's apartment.
Who the fuck are you?
Who are you talking to?
Hey, mom.
Aubrey, I didn't
recognize the number.
Yeah.
Honey.
How's your night?
Are you okay?
How did it go?
It went.
Was Edward there?
Did you get to speak with him?
No.
Oh, honey, I'm sorry.
Look, I think...
Do you remember...
We're the ones...
are going to...
Okay?
I think
you're cracking up, mom.
Honey.
Baby, I wish you were here.
I wish you could just fly...
For the holidays...
It's so...
Yeah.
Time zone.
Sweetie?
Well, I just
wanted to hear your voice.
Wait a minute.
I'm...
Honey, I can't hear you...
Mom,
I can't hear you.
Listen,
make sure you get...
Okay?
Happy New...
Baby.
Happy New Year.
Now, let's take
a little trip back in time,
just you and me, Nate Fowles,
on this beautiful
crispy New Year's Eve
right here in the
mountains on Sparrow 103.
Edward.
What the...
Hello?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hey!
Aubrey.
Aubrey, can you hear me?
Can you hear me, Aubrey?
Aubrey?
Can you hear me?
Yes.
Yes, yes, I can hear you.
Listen to me carefully
and do exactly as I say.
I don't know what
the fuck is going on.
Close your eyes.
Take the walkie and
face it toward the door.
What?
Face
it toward the door.
Okay.
Fuck.
Stand up.
Walk toward the door.
Aubrey, keep your eyes closed.
Well, that's encouraging.
What is?
You want to live.
What?
What the fuck is going on?
You're
going to want to go
back upstairs now,
and lock the door.
It's going to be okay, Aubrey.
How do you know my name?
I knew Grace.
Now, I need you not
to be scared, Aubrey.
I need you not to panic.
I know exactly
how you're feeling
but we can help each
other, I promise you.
I think there's a way
out of this, Aubrey.
Hey, stop saying my name.
How did you do that?
Do what?
Before, in the diner.
It was like a
signal or something.
You did some kind of signal
and you made it leave.
It was the signal.
It caused all of this.
Would you just tell me
what the fuck is going on?
Do
you have to understand
everything to accept it?
You're not
answering my question!
That's because
you're not listening yet.
Okay, well, what did you mean
when you said that we
could help each other?
The
final part of the signal
was transmitted last night.
It caused all of this,
the snow, the monoliths.
Look, Grace found something.
It's in the apartment with you.
What do you mean?
What did she find?
She left
it for you, the first part.
Hey, there are people out there,
and I think that
they need our help.
You
can't help them, Aubrey.
- But they need our help!
- Stop, Aubrey.
What the fuck is happening?
What the fuck is happening?!
I need to go.
Please don't go.
Please don't go, please
don't go, please don't go.
Please don't go.
Maybe I'm dead.
This makes me
cringe talking into this,
listening to my stupid voice.
You were always so much
better at this than me.
Anyways, I'm not sure when
I'm sending this to you,
if I send this to you.
But, I figure you'll
be the only one
to take this remotely seriously.
I trust you to help me, or to
tell me I'm being an idiot.
Someone found
something, this group.
They uncovered some signal.
It was buried in a
radio transmission
and there have been
others, I mean before.
We started to find them in
all sorts of transmissions.
It's what I've been working on.
I'm trying to help them.
It started as just fun,
conspiracy bullshit, you know.
Oh, Aubrey, there's
a correlation
between events, disasters,
natural disasters.
The patterns repeat.
They seem to form a chain of
signals that link together
in a loop, but we're
missing one: seven.
We have the rest, or
I have the rest and ..
I mean, we think the signal
is only dangerous fragmented,
like computer code,
in pieces it corrupts,
but put it all together...
There are people after it.
It's all fucked up, Aubrey,
and I'm a little scared...
and excited.
I'm hiding the rest
of the tapes, okay?
Where we used to go.
You'll figure it out.
I hope.
I buried each signal in songs.
It seemed apt.
I hope you enjoy them at least.
It's been a while since we made
each other mix tapes, hasn't it?
I miss it.
If nothing else, it'll
make a great mix tape
for the next road trip we take.
I feel stupid talking to
you like this right now.
Where are you?
You should ring me
more often, stupid.
I have to go back
to the hospital
tomorrow for some more tests.
It's the strangest thing,
not being able to
trust your own body.
I need to get out.
But it feels good, you know?
To have a secret.
Aubrey, pick up.
You left me.
I had to.
You had to see for yourself.
You played the signal, right?
You have to be careful.
The signal is very powerful.
It opens doorways.
I think the creatures...
I think they came through
one of these doorways,
but they also seem scared of it.
Is everyone gone?
Or hiding.
I don't know.
My mom?
My dad?
How come you're alive?
I told you.
I knew Grace.
We were helping each other.
But she's dead now, isn't she?
Tell me what you think it is.
I don't know
exactly, but we have ideas.
The signal might be
a natural pattern,
something older than us,
something necessary, repeating.
It could be manmade,
a new kind of warfare,
something we don't
know about yet.
It could be...
just coincidental, a pattern
simply because we
want to see one.
Tell me what you
really think it is.
What if
it isn't random, the signal?
Transmitting for decades
buried in our transmissions,
repeating, looping,
echoing the same pieces,
waiting to transmit
in the right order
to make a chain of code.
Maybe all science doesn't need
to be based on the same systems.
Maybe there is something,
something out there,
that uses sound waves as the
foundation of its science,
sound waves used not
just for communication,
but for interaction,
for warfare,
for exploration, for travel,
for opening doorways.
What if the signal...
is them trying to
come across to us?
When I first came
here I didn't know
what I was looking for
or what I was hoping for,
but you know what
used to be my dream?
My absolute favorite fantasy...
was for everyone
to just disappear,
for the world to just be
devoid of distraction,
empty shells of empty lives,
empty cities,
empty streets,
just trees...
and brick.
Grace said that she trusted
me to decide what to do.
Aubrey.
Aubrey?
Aubrey, you have to help.
We have to stop it.
Aubrey!
Aubrey, listen to me!
You might think that being in
this forced close proximity
means that we're going
to become great friends.
Don't count on it.
The home for everyone is to
him his castle and fortress,
as well for his defense
against injury and violence,
as for his repose.
I wonder if the world still
exists if I choose to ignore it.
Whenever I find myself
growing grim about the mouth;
whenever it is a damp,
drizzly November in my soul;
whenever I find
myself involuntarily
pausing before
coffin warehouses,
and bringing up the rear
of every funeral I meet;
I account it is high time to
get to sea as soon as I can.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
It's official.
We're out of food.
We're almost out of water,
and sooner or later we're
going to run out of batteries.
I'm open to any suggestions.
Yeah.
Maybe I don't want to.
Oh, fuck you.
I'm allowed to be scared.
Yeah.
Yeah, I know.
This makes me
cringe talking into this,
listening to my stupid voice.
You were always so much
better at this than me.
Anyways, I'm not sure when
I'm sending this to you,
if I send this to you.
But I figure you'll
be the only one
to take this remotely seriously.
I trust...
The patterns repeat.
They seem to form
a chain of signals
that link together in a loop,
but we're missing one: seven.
We have the rest, or I
have the rest and...
I mean, we think the
signal is only dangerous...
And excited.
So, I'm hiding the rest
of the tapes, okay?
Where we used to go.
You'll figure it out.
I hope.
I've buried each
signal in songs.
It seemed apt.
I hope you enjoy them at least.
She kept listening to
it over and over again.
On her walks.
Around town.
You built something.
You built something, didn't you?
Something that could recognize
the signal, and it did,
the night that I arrived.
Seven tapes, one you gave me,
seven you hadn't finished yet.
That was the final piece.
Okay, Grace.
You get one chance.
Let's try it your way.
So we can protect ourselves,
only if we have to.
Wake up!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Want to know the saddest thing
about everybody being gone?
Everybody being dead I mean.
All the lost stories.
People are going to die anyways,
but their stories don't have to.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hey.
How have you been?
I have these dreams...
where you talk to me,
like you're still here.
I'm here.
How have you been?
I can't feel my
fingers sometimes.
It's called disassociation.
You're pulling away
from the world.
Why?
Because I can't
forgive myself.
What for?
Is this real?
I'm dead, stupid.
I mean all this, everything
that's happening, is it real?
Do you
want it to be real?
I didn't want to
leave the apartment.
Why?
Because I didn't
want you to be gone.
But I am gone.
I can't do that.
I don't think I can do that.
You have to do
what makes you happy.
If you're not happy, you
can't make anybody else happy.
- I told you that before.
- I don't believe that.
I think that you're wrong.
Well, you're
not dead, are you?
So what do you know?
What if making someone else
happy is what makes you happy?
Why haven't
you taken it off?
I can't.
Why?
Because it's a reminder
of everything bad I've done,
of how much that I
have to make up for.
But you can't
make up for it, can you?
No.
So what
are you going to do?
I don't know.
Can you tell me?
Can you please tell me?
Be happy.
I can't.
I'm suffocated.
You cheated.
I cheated.
You have
to live with that.
You have to confront it.
Stop...
hiding.
I can still remember
the sound of the waves
and the sand on my palm.
We're just people,
wandering around,
bumping into each other.
No.
No, we aren't.
So what are you going to do?
I'm going to stay here.
And I'm going to never leave.
Sounds like a plan.
I'm so sorry.
For what?
For not being there for you.
When you...
When you needed me.
You were always there for me.
I wasn't fucking
there for you,
and I should have been
there for you and I wasn't.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't know.
Yes, you did.
Please forgive me.
I just want to go home.
Yeah, no, that's
actually true though.
Yeah, that's a very accurate
drawing right there.
Let's go on a walk, Bellini.
This is ridiculous,
that you're here.
You know that right?
It's ridiculous.
Just ash, dirt, fucking ash.
If you can hear me I'm
guessing that you already know
everything that's happened,
so I'm not going to bore you.
I got the message.
Don't worry.
Okay.
Welcome back
to Sparrow 103, your local...
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Hello?
My name is Aubrey Parker,
and...
I think I might be
the last person left.
I don't know...
I don't know if I
did anything to fix
what's going to happen, but...
I really hope that I did.
So...
If there's anybody
else out there,
now's the time to say something.
Hello?
Anybody?
Please.
Hello?
Oh my god!
Oh my god, can you hear me?
Yes.
- We can hear you.
- Holy shit!
Are you okay?
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, no, I'm safe.
I'm safe, I'm at
the radio station.
Did you say we?
There's a few of us.
Why would you think
you were alone?
Well, I just, I
thought that I'd been
alone this entire time.
I didn't realize.
Why are
you at the radio station?
Wait, how do I know
that you're real?
We're real.
I figured it
out, I stopped it.
Figured what out?
The signal?
You know about the signal?
We know about it.
Well, yeah.
I found all the pieces
and I put them together.
I sent the reply
so it's okay now.
I closed all the doors.
So you
took the message they sent,
the one that caused all of this,
you put it back
together for them,
not knowing what it was,
what it did,
and you...
and you sent it back?
You shouldn't have done that.
You didn't close the doors.
You opened them.
Aubrey.
Pick up!
Aubrey!
She's at the radio station!
Subtitles by explosiveskull