Well, I was...
I just wanted to see
how it ends.
So, you're the brave one.
- I guess.
- It's good.
It'll carry well down there.
A little help here, Francis.
Come on.
Not quite it, Francis.
Just not quite it.
Francis! Look what you did!
Bad turtles
don't get smoothies.
Come on...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Stop!
It's not funny.
Stop it!
This is good,
if I do say so myself.
Ow.
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
The end is kind of sad.
Are you sure
you wanna hear this?
Okay.
"Once upon a time,
there was a unicorn
named Eleanor.
She wasn't like
the other unicorns
because she had two horns.
There's the wizard,
he says he can help her,
but only if she finds
someone else like her.
So she wanders around
until she finds a knight
who's stuck in a tree.
He's lonely, too,
and his name is Francis.
And they go back to the wizard
so he can make her normal.
But then the wizard says
that she's better than normal,
she's special.
And now that
she has another friend,
she's not lonely."
And that's it. The end.
But it doesn't make sense.
That's not even what she wanted.
See?
Told you it was sad.
I want Mommy and Daddy.
No peeking, okay?
One alligator,
two alligator,
three alligator,
four alligator,
five alligator,
six alligator,
seven alligator,
eight alligator,
nine alligator,
ten alligator,
eleven alligator,
twelve alligator,
thirteen alligator,
fourteen alligator,
fifteen alligator,
sixteen alligator,
seventeen alligator,
eighteen alligator,
nineteen alligator...
twenty alligator...
twenty-one alligator,
twenty-two alligator.
Okay, Francis, I'm here.
Come find me!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Go away. Please, go away!
Go away.
It came back.
See that?
That's where it lives.
Out past the trees.
When the monster comes,
you have to stay calm.
You can't even think
bad thoughts.
If it hears you,
it gets super angry.
Don't worry,
I won't let him get you.
You have to do what I say,
because I'm your mommy.
That means I'll always
take care of you,
and never go away
and leave you.
Come on, Francis,
kick it back.
Don't be a loser.
Oh, Mr. Hopper!
I'll be right back.
Shoot!
Shit!
Shit-ass! Shit!
Shit-ass, shit-ass,
shit-ass, shit!
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit!
Shit!
Shit-ass!
Ass!
Shit-ass, shit,
shit, shit, shit.
Mr. Hopper...
I made you lunch.
Why don't you come back home?
We miss you.
Me and Francis.
Aw.
You just enjoy
the nice cup of tomato sauce.
No! Wait!
Wait, stop.
Come to Mommy.
Stop.
Stay.
Now, come back.
Come here, Mr. Hopper.
Wait!
Don't go in there!
Please come back.
Don't leave me.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Ugh.
Sorry, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have brought
you a pumpkin.
It was stupid, it's just...
they get rotten so fast
and you never got to finish it.
So, don't be mad.
Okay?
Paul?
The monster's back.
Your fingers are cold.
Let me sleep here.
Those outside
the hot-zones are required
to remain in their homes
while quarantine is in effect.
Airports are closed.
No unauthorized travel
is allowed to...
Containment
facilities are being
constructed around the country
and authorities are cautioning
that citizens
should not approach
this new...
There you are, Francis.
The guests will arrive shortly.
Well, you look marvelous.
You're marvelous, Ma...
I must compliment you
on your taste
of horn decorations.
Have you met Sir Francis?
He's a very famous explorer,
you know.
And he's not even afraid
of the dark.
At all.
If only we had Mr. Hopper.
Stay there.
Francis, did you do that?
Francis?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
You were supposed
to take care of me!
That's your job!
Dad says you're the big brother
and you take care
of Stephanie.
It's your fault.
They left because of you!
They'd still be here
if you hadn't died!
It's your fault!
Okay, you stay there.
You can do this.
Keep a lookout
for anything weird.
I believe in you.
I'll only take a minute.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Did you hear that?
Shh...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh, my God.
Stephanie.
Daddy!
- Come here, baby.
I got you.
Yeah.
I got you, princess.
We're here.
Let me see your face.
Let me see you.
You okay?
Yeah?
Look at you.
You're okay.
My princess.
That's my girl.
I'm sorry.
I got ya.
Come on, baby.
Paul?
How are you gonna find
your way home?
Stephanie.
Sweetheart! Stephanie!
- Steph!
- Stephanie!
Stephanie!
Steph!
Stephanie! You are not to leave
our sight, young lady!
Don't.
- She needs to listen.
- I said, don't.
Stay calm.
Both of you.
Baby, it's really dangerous
for you to be out there, okay?
Why did you take Paul away?
I want him to come home.
Hi, princess.
Hi, Daddy.
- I'm gonna make us breakfast.
- Okay.
Did you sleep well?
Mm-hmm.
The lights are back on.
Yeah. Your, um,
your father messed
with the breaker.
More?
Mm-hmm.
What's he building?
Oh, you know your dad.
He would rebuild
the Panama Canal if he could.
Why did you leave me?
Stephanie,
you have to understand
that your dad and me,
we never would have left you
here alone if...
We thought that...
You thought
that the monster got me, too.
Yeah.
It still comes
sniffing around.
It's in the woods.
But if we get upset,
it comes into the house.
What do you do then,
when it comes in the house?
We get totally quiet.
Me and Francis are aces
at hiding from it.
Aces.
Mm-hmm.
Steph, you're one tough kid,
you know that?
Not really.
Really, I'm pretty scared.
What do you think?
For the monster?
Yes.
Do you think it's strong
enough to keep it out?
Well,
it's pretty good anyway.
Thanks.
I think so, too.
I like it
when you build stuff.
Is that so?
Mm-hmm.
Can I ask you a question?
Sure.
What happened to Mr. Hopper?
Well, he...
Honey!
Can you come inside
for a minute?
Yeah.
You stay here.
Clear.
Clear?
Crystal.
You stay here.
Clear?
Clear? Okay.
So what's Atlanta
saying about the new protocols?
The CDC
has no comment at this time.
You've seen the news.
The president...
is weighing all options.
There are rumors online
that they've had some success
at the containment facility
in Mumbai.
Yeah, rumors but...
what's going on?
Jane, I've never seen you
like this.
Are Paul and Stephanie okay?
It's cool.
It's impossible not to worry
about all of our kids.
Look, can you talk me through
the isolation protocol?
Three!
Two! One! Popcorn!
Done! Bam!
Eh-eh-eh!
Eh-eh-eh.
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot.
Ah, shit.
- Dad!
- Oh! Sorry.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean that.
Fantastic.
Salt!
Good. Taste.
Good.
Give me some love.
You almost done
with that fence?
Probably tomorrow.
Good.
Ah, so they tell me.
Steph, what's Francis doing?
Dancing.
Oh baby, turtles can't dance.
Don't listen to her, Francis.
Show her your special dance.
His special... Oh!
Oh!
That is not a special dance!
That is tickle!
Oh, Francis,
you're Fran-tastic.
I don't get it.
I do!
- Francis is Fran-tastic.
- Francis into fantastic.
But the word is fantastic.
Fantastic. It's not Fran-tastic.
It's Fran-tastic.
Be right back.
Okay.
Why, baby. Why?
It's okay, it's okay.
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
I know.
Take your time.
- Shh, shh, shh, shh.
- I got you.
I got you.
Come on. Come on.
How did Paul come back?
Did the monster bring him?
Yes.
Why?
We don't really know why it does
any of the things it does.
Maybe we should leave.
I think it would just
come after us, princess.
After me?
Yes.
It wants me, right?
That's why
it keeps coming back.
Yes.
You used to say there's
no such thing as monsters.
I know.
I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
May I be excused?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hey, princess.
Hey, Dad.
Can we talk?
Your mother's sorry
for losing her temper.
- No big deal.
- Mmm, no, it is a big deal.
All of us have to watch
what we do, how we feel.
You included.
Because that will make
the monster come.
Mm-hmm.
We didn't mean to upset you.
And that's why
we didn't wake you up
when we took Paul away.
And maybe that was wrong,
I don't know.
Parents aren't perfect.
That's the sad truth.
Why did you leave me here?
We were afraid, how's that?
I was afraid.
Of what?
Don't lie.
I was afraid of myself, maybe?
That I wouldn't be strong enough
to take care of the things
that I need to take care of.
What do you need to do?
Well, that's the scary part,
I'm not quite sure.
Can I help?
Maybe, princess.
You're strong, Stephanie.
I'm talking about
strength up here.
Strength on the inside.
Your mommy and me,
we made you.
We made your eyes that color
and we made your hair
straight and blonde.
That's what we did.
We made everything out here.
But up here, on the inside,
that's all you.
All the way.
The good and the bad,
that's for you to control.
That's for you to change,
if you want to.
The fear and the anger
and the doubt,
they're what call the monster.
And when you get those feelings,
the bad feelings,
all you have to do
is make them small.
That's how you beat it.
That's the number one rule.
Don't let
the bad things get big,
everything will be fine.
You get it?
Mm-hmm.
Now, I'm betting locked up
inside that head of yours,
you have enough strength
to stop that monster cold.
Dunk.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
You all right?
Mm-hmm.
I love you, Daddy.
She's lived longer
than any of them, right?
Yeah.
Do you really believe
that she isn't gonna end up
like the rest of them?
I talked to her,
she can keep herself calm.
- She's a tough kid.
- You talked to her.
Maybe it is,
I don't know, we don't know.
We have to protect her.
This procedure, I can do it,
- I can keep her safe.
- You're not
that kind of doctor,
it's too dangerous,
the procedure could kill her.
The best thing to do
right now is we just wait.
That's all I'm asking you
to do is wait.
- Wait for what?
- What if she can't?
You've seen
what those things can do.
Yeah. I've seen it,
in my house.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Mom?
Dad?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Mom?
Dad?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Daddy?
Daddy!
Hi, princess.
Mom?
Dad?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
No!
Steph!
All right, take it easy,
she's fine, she's fine.
Look at me,
you got to stay calm. Okay?
The monster killed you.
Nobody killed me.
Listen to me, baby,
you got to stay calm.
No, Daddy, the basement.
Run!
- Daddy! Dad!
- Shh! Shh, shh...
Daddy!
All right, it's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
Shh! We have to be quiet.
The monster might hear us.
We did it.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Come on, it's clear.
Mom!
Ow. Ow.
Francis.
Stephanie! Wait!
Stephanie!
The monster!
The monster! The monster!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, it's you.
It's you.
The monster is you.
Baby, how'd you sleep?
I had a weird dream.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Your mom will be back
in a little while, she had
a meeting at the hospital.
Sure.
Hey, Paul.
Hey, Steph.
I don't wanna remember.
I don't want to remember.
It's okay.
You're all right.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
But what are you sorry for?
I won't run away again.
You're sick.
You have something inside you.
It's making you see things.
It's making you do things.
Part of what it's making you do
is hurting your memory.
We think if you can remember,
it'll help you fight it.
Your mother and I
have been talking
and there's something
we'd like to try with you.
Like an experiment.
More like a game.
Mm-hmm.
I need you
to close your eyes.
Go on.
I want you to listen
to these clicks.
Let your body relax.
Good. Let your mind wander.
That's it.
Let it go.
Tell me what happened
the day Paul died.
that morning.
We're carving pumpkins.
That's right.
That's, that's good, princess.
He's being mean.
Teasing me.
I think he was just playing
with you.
What happened next?
Cut it out!
- I got mad.
- Sure, you did.
Of course, you did.
And that's okay.
What happened after you got mad?
I went for him.
How?
With my arms.
All of them.
What happened after that?
I hit Mommy.
Okay, stop. Stop.
- Just stop.
- You ran!
You left me.
Okay, Eric, stop it, now!
What happened next?
Stephanie!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Yes. I'm Stephanie.
I am Stephanie.
You happy?
You think she can control that?
- We do it your way.
- Thank you.
That's still
our little girl in there.
Stephanie?
Princess?
What's next?
If you take the razor,
and just...
just shave
this section right here.
Yeah.
You okay?
Jesus Christ.
Actually,
it's relatively simple.
As soon as we get
through the bone,
we feed the endoscope through.
There's a natural pathway
for it to follow.
If this doesn't work?
It's going to work.
Tragedy unfolding in Mumbai.
We are now expecting
confirmation
from the White House.
There has been
an incident in the lab,
where the rumored
surgical trials
are being conducted.
The death toll is unconfirmed,
but there were at least
200 physicians
and researchers gathered
by the coalition of nations,
at the facility.
With all the therapeutic
containment efforts failing,
this surgery was viewed,
by many researchers,
as our last best hope
to finding a cure,
a hope that is now fading.
The nation and the world
are reckoning
with what some fringe elements
of the scientific community
have been saying
since the initial outbreak
in April,
that euthanasia may be
the only cure.
"Once upon a time,
in a place
just beyond our sight,
there lived a magical kingdom
called Anywhere.
In Anywhere,
anything was possible."
Hey, Steph.
Do you wanna come for a walk
in the orchard with me?
Come on.
Okay.
I made you
some hot chocolate.
We haven't been out
to the orchard in a while.
Mm-hmm.
Do you think we can make
some orange juice?
For all three of us?
I don't see why not.
Okay.
I did that.
- No, baby.
- Yes, I did.
But you don't remember doing it.
Well, then it wasn't you.
What's wrong with me?
Imagine you're a door,
and there's something
that's trying
to come through.
What is it?
We don't know.
Something we don't understand.
Something,
from another place.
I don't even think
it has a body.
That's why it uses yours.
It changes you.
And you're not alone,
there's kids like you
all over the world.
Can they stop it?
There's one more thing
we're gonna try.
I'm sorry.
No, stop apologizing...
- But I'm sorry.
- Don't be!
Don't be sorry.
You didn't do anything wrong.
Not one day in your life.
Do you understand me?
I think it's getting cold.
It's getting cold.
We should drink up.
Wait.
Don't forget cheers, Dad.
Cheers.
Dad, wait. I, I can stop it.
Dad. No, don't.
See? I can stay calm.
I love you, Daddy.
You are my baby girl.
You're my princess.
I love you so much.
Stephanie...
Steph
You should've killed me
when you had the chance.
Ah.
Oh, what did I do?
Oh, it's over,
I loved her. Oh.
My God.
- Upstairs.
- No, no!
- Go! Go upstairs.
- Go!
- No!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Princess... oh.
Stop! St... Stop!
You tried to kill me.
You're not my daughter.
What the hell are you?
Big.
Stay there. Clear?
Good.
No! I'm so... I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
We should have never left you.
You shouldn't have come back.