Brad!
Hello?!
Lucas?!
Okay.
Hey.
Brad. Brad.
Hey, it's Jenn. Hey.
Hi. I-I'm gonna help you, okay?
Shit.
Okay. Okay, just...
Oh, f...
Help!
Somebody help!
Okay.
- Jenn.
- Hey.
Did you see it?
What?
I need to find you water.
Water...
Here.
Brad.
Oh, my God.
Hello?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Shit.
Ugh.
Oh, my God.
Jesus.
Come back!
Hey, come back!
Please, please.
No, no...
No!
Oh, shit!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Oh, shit.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
It's okay. It's okay.
We're here now.
Oh, it's gonna be okay.
It's gonna be okay.
God, this place is beautiful.
- It's a miracle.
- It's incredible.
Mmm. How is there soda here?
There was a family here
a long time ago,
and they left a bunch of stuff.
Mmm.
So, whenever you guys are ready,
we should get out of here.
Uh... back on the raft?
It isn't safe here.
There's...
...an animal...
Sweetheart, I'm sure
there's a lot of animals.
It's a monster.
Okay, I saw it.
It crawled out of the ocean
and it walks on land,
and it drags its food
back out to this...
There's a, there's a black hole
out there.
Okay? Zack washed up.
He was already dead,
and I saw it
drag him out there.
Okay. The family that-that
I was telling you about...
Look at this.
- What is this?
- Do you see that?
Th... Those are,
those are his eyes.
- It killed them.
- How could you know that?
Because I found their graves.
They were buried here.
Well, then what happened to
the person who dug the graves?
Now... Okay.
Well, there's clearly a current
pulling things
towards the island.
All right?
We all washed up here.
I say we wait, we'll see
if anyone else arrives.
Same. What if Brad shows up?
Brad's dead.
Brad's dead?
Yeah.
Oh, fuck...
I'm sorry, I...
What happened to him?
Okay, I buried him.
I buried him deep into the
ground and this creature came
and dug him up.
What does this thing look like?
It's massive.
It-it has two sets of eyes,
and it smells.
Look, I-I got it last night.
Okay? That's black blood.
Was he, was he in pain?
Mia, he knew
that he wasn't alone.
He knew that
I was there with him.
You still love that sound?
I guess everyone does.
Don't think I'll be coming
to the beach much after this.
You know, out on the raft,
for the first time in my life,
I thought I was gonna die.
I really thought that...
that that was it.
A-And it's funny because
all I was thinking about
is how embarrassing it would be.
Everyone back home's
just waiting for me to fail.
Out on the raft,
you don't hear waves.
You don't hear anything.
I'd rather die on the raft
than this place.
You don't know
what it's like out there.
So, we're gonna head west.
I saw a bunch of planes
go that way.
I'm pretty sure they'll see us.
Okay, hey.
- I know this all sounds crazy.
- Yeah.
I really need you to believe me.
I do.
It's just a lot
to process, all right?
I mean, we just need
a little bit of time, okay?
I'm gonna get more food.
We should bring
as much as we can.
Can I borrow this?
Thanks.
Hey, make sure she gets ready.
Okay, there's enough for a week.
We got to be smart
with what we have.
All right,
let's load up the raft.
Jenn.
We're not leaving.
- What?
- Not right now.
- Not in our condition.
- We can't do it.
I understand that you're tired.
Guys, I'm tired, too.
I'm exhausted, but...
We're not just tired.
We're weak.
All right, we've barely eaten.
- Just need to rest up, all right?
- No, you don't rest here.
Jenn, you've been alone
and you're scared,
and I get that.
But whatever you've been seeing,
this animal...
- It's not an animal! I told you that!
- Hey, okay, listen to me,
there's nothing for miles, Jenn.
Okay? I-I say
we light a huge fire.
Y-You said there
are planes, right?
We'll-we'll light a fire
and they'll see us.
It's getting dark.
Get ready to leave.
Sweetheart, are you even
listening to me?
We are not getting
on that fucking raft!
Just not tonight, all right?
We'll figure this out.
Okay.
Lucas.
Hey! Jenn!
Hey!
Stop it!
Stop! Jenn! Wait!
Hey! Stop!
- Get off me!
- Calm down.
- Let go of me! I'm leaving!
- Stop! Stop!
Stop. Just stop.
No!
Hey!
Hey.
- I'm leaving, I don't care!
- Calm down!
I don't care! No!
Stop!
Hey.
Shh. It's okay.
Where is Lucas?
He's just taking a look around.
Don't worry, it's been dark
for a few hours,
and we haven't seen anything.
You had to tie me up?
I think just for now.
I'm sorry.
Really, I... I shouldn't have
hit you like that.
I just... I didn't know
what else to do.
Yeah, I don't care.
Just...
untie me.
I think we've all been
through something traumatic,
and we're all just trying
to cope with it in our own
different ways.
I'm just as guilty, I am.
Guilty? Who's guilty?
I didn't make this up.
I'm not lying to you.
Right.
Like when you got mugged
before we left.
Jenn, it's not that
I don't believe you.
It's just that, over the years,
you've made it pretty hard
for me to believe you.
This is a little different.
I just want what's best
for everyone.
I really don't need you
to tell me what's best for me.
I didn't see anything.
There's nothing out there.
'Cause it doesn't come
from the trees.
I just want you to feel safe.
We're all just trying
to figure this out.
Figure it out?
- Yes, figure it out.
- We need to
get away from this place
as soon as possible.
Do you want me to give
you guys a second?
- Okay.
- Thank you.
She's really sorry
about what happened...
Yeah, she mentioned it.
Lucas, untie me.
Not until you promise me
you'll relax.
You all right?
I just want to make sure
that you're okay.
You're fine.
There's always a black cloud
hanging over your head.
You know that, right?
This whole thing, Jenn.
It's so crazy.
I was having a great time
all week.
On a boat with my friends,
weather was perfect.
Brought you
on this incredible trip.
Everyone's having a great time,
except you, right?
And the night you come up
to tell me
that you might not be happy,
that you maybe don't want
to be in this...
...storm clouds roll in.
How perfect is that?
No matter where you go,
there's always a storm
right behind you.
Lucas, you know I love you,
but this is not the time
to talk about this.
Let me go.
So, what were you gonna do?
- What was your plan, exactly?
- I told you.
- Head west.
- No, I get that.
But you head west, you get found
and brought back home.
And then what?
You've got no one else.
Where you gonna live?
You gonna go back to school?
And afford it how?
I pay for your life.
And you pay me back
by taking the raft
and leaving me here
to starve to death?
You don't starve here.
That's not what happens.
You get torn into pieces
and dragged into a hole
in the middle of the ocean.
That's what happens here.
Mia thinks you're starting
to sound a lot like Zack.
What happened to Zack?
Lucas.
Shit.
Lucas!
Run. Now.
Are you sure?
I've never seen it
during the day.
There's nothing
you could have done.
Give me a hand?
I'm gonna see
if there's anything else
we might need
from the old campsite.
All right.
Climb in.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Shit!
It grabbed me.
Help me!
Shit!
Aah!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
You said it wouldn't come out
during the...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I'm writing this letter
hoping it serves
as some sort of proof.
A little more than a week ago,
my boat went down in a storm,
and I've been surviving
on this island since.
Zack and Brad from our group
are both dead.
Brad washed ashore
with me already injured
and died shortly after.
Days later,
Zack washed ashore,
already dead.
I never knew their last names.
Shit.
Mia Reed and my boyfriend,
Lucas Griffin,
arrived on a raft
a few days after.
And they were both killed
by a monster
that lives
just off this island.
And there's nothing I can do
to prove that.
For a lot of my life, I've
struggled with being believed.
The truth doesn't always come
with a receipt.
Sometimes all we have
is our word.
There's no way for me
to show you
the things that I can tell you.
That there's a monster here
taller than any man
I've ever seen,
twice as fast in water
as it is on land,
and it bleeds black blood.
For a week I've run from it
and hid from it,
but not anymore.
If you find this note, what's
left of my body will either
be on this island or deep
in a hole off the west shore.
I hope this letter is enough
for you to believe my story.
Jennifer Remming.
♪ I've been here before ♪
♪ Demons knockin',
knockin' at my door ♪
♪ Hangin' from a wire,
one step at a time ♪
♪ Losin' my mind ♪
♪ I'm in heaven ♪
♪ Everything has changed ♪
♪ Colors runnin',
meltin' into rain ♪
♪ Focus on the life
drippin' from the knife ♪
♪ Give me a sign ♪
♪ I'm in heaven ♪
♪ Ooh... ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Careful what you wish for ♪
♪ And do it all over again ♪
♪ Ooh... ♪
♪ Do it all over again ♪
♪ Do it
all over again ♪
♪ All over again ♪
♪ All over again. ♪
♪ Oh, all my life
been a black sheep ♪
♪ All my life been
the black keys ♪
♪ True, I never really
was a bad breed ♪
♪ Daddy probably rather me
an athlete ♪
♪ Man, that nigga move
like a taxi ♪
♪ All my life in the backseat ♪
♪ You talk about life,
is it that sweet? ♪
♪ All these eyes starin' at me ♪
- ♪ I've been feelin' real low, nigga, low-key ♪
- ♪ Low-key ♪
- ♪ How a brave heart feelin' so weak? ♪
- ♪ So weak ♪
- ♪ Tattoos on my passport, no sleep ♪
- ♪ No sleep ♪
♪ This is what you asked for,
don't weep ♪
♪ Don't whinge, man,
I'm here and I won't leave ♪
♪ All I wanna do...
make songs, blow trees ♪
♪ Wouldn't be honest with myself
if I don't speak ♪
♪ So I make the point to address
'em, man, you know me ♪
- ♪ Got me believin' in Buddha the more I proceed ♪
- ♪ Yo ♪
- ♪ Oh, this life isn't guaranteed ♪
♪ All my life felt
a cold breeze, in and out ♪
♪ We stayin' up and never down,
you hearin' me now? ♪
♪ Give me some time and a little
space, I'll figure it out ♪
♪ They wanna know my whereabouts
and who I'm around ♪
♪ Been in Wonderland for time,
tryin' to find our way out ♪
♪ You can hear it my rhymes,
I'll be thinkin' aloud ♪
♪ I'm-a be ghost for a minute,
don't get in your feelings ♪
♪ I ain't even wrote for
a minute, not a single lyric ♪
♪ Man, I got a life that is
crazy, most cannot live it ♪
♪ See 'em tryin' to sabotage me,
got me livid ♪
- ♪ All my life been a black sheep ♪
- ♪ Black sheep ♪
- ♪ All my life been the black keys ♪
- ♪ Black keys ♪
♪ True, I never really
was a bad breed ♪
♪ Daddy probably rather me
an athlete ♪
♪ Man, that nigga move
like a taxi, yo ♪
♪ All my life
in the backseat, yo ♪
♪ You talk about life,
is it that sweet, yo ♪
♪ All these eyes starin'
at me, yo ♪
♪ Oh, phone rings
and I missed-called everyone ♪
♪ All I hear 'em sayin' is,
look what you've become ♪
♪ This is what you signed up
for, you forget ♪
♪ This is what you get,
this is what you get ♪
- ♪ All these eyes in the front row ♪
- ♪ Front row ♪
♪ Hella pure souls
in the front row ♪
♪ Remember seein' J. Cole,
I was in the front row ♪
♪ Couldn't move, was in awe
if you must know ♪
♪ Still strugglin' to find
who I trust, though ♪
- ♪ All my life in the cut, though ♪
- ♪ Yo ♪
♪ All my life caught the bus
home, through the north side ♪
♪ Then I got a pedal bike,
Mommy flipped when I got home ♪
♪ Like, "People get killed
out here" ♪
♪ But, Mummy,
I'm a rider and a fighter ♪
♪ Never been a dickhead in life,
don't ever try me ♪
♪ Don't get it confused 'cause
I'm humble and I'm quiet ♪
♪ Loud niggas steppin' to Simz,
they get silenced ♪
♪ I ain't gotta say how
and it don't involve violence ♪
♪ Though I got Gs that are ready
and are here for it ♪
♪ But there's no need,
I just want peace ♪
♪ Take me higher, get an eighth
from the supplier ♪
♪ Make your mind up,
what you mean what you desire? ♪
♪ Niggas hatin', but it's cool,
man, it's a minor ♪
♪ I just do me and my own,
and I'm the driver ♪
♪ 23, feelin' older
and I'm wiser ♪
♪ All my life been searchin'
what I'd die for ♪
♪ Guess I am the one,
the people I'm-a fight for ♪
♪ Surely you should know who
you rep, know who you ride for ♪
- ♪ All my life been a black sheep ♪
- ♪ Black sheep ♪
- ♪ All my life been the black keys ♪
- ♪ Black keys ♪
- ♪ True, I never really was a bad breed ♪
- ♪Bad breed ♪
♪ Daddy probably
rather me an athlete ♪
♪ Man, that nigga move
like a taxi, yo ♪
♪ All my life
in the backseat, yo ♪
♪ You talk about life,
is it that sweet, yo ♪
♪ All these eyes starin'
at me, yo, all these... ♪
♪ Phone rings
and I missed-called everyone ♪
♪ All I hear 'em sayin' is,
look what you've become, yo ♪
♪ This is what you signed up
for, you forget, yo ♪
♪ This is what you get, yo,
this is what you get. ♪