(SALLY SOBBING)
SALLY: They're trying to kill me!
They are crazy!
MAN: Just calm down, Sally. You're safe now.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Can you tell me what happened?
SALLY: We ran out of gas.
Kirk went for help.
(SOBS)
KIRK: Hello?
Hello?
Anybody home?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Kirk!
(SCREAMING)
(CRYING OUT IN PAIN)
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Kirk?
(YELLING)
FRANKLIN: Jerry!
SALLY: Jerry!
Sally, I hear something. Stop! Stop!
(SCREAMING)
(SCREAMS CONTINUE)
No! Please! Please!
Please! Please stop!
(SCREAMING)
Give me that hammer!
(CHAINSAW WHIRRING)
(HORN HONKING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(SCREAMING)
(SIREN BLARING)
RADIO DISPATCH: Sheriff, we've got
the victim's statement.
She's en route to the hospital.
What's your 20?
SHERIFF: On Quick Hill Road.
Headed out there now.
Call for an ambulance,
in case there's any others still alive.
Hey, Sheriff. This is Marvin.
I'm only two minutes
behind you and I'm closing.
SHERIFF: All right, step on it, Marvin.
RADIO DISPATCH:
Sheriff, that family is likely armed.
You gonna wait for backup?
SHERIFF: I can't wait. I'm going in now.
- I swear to God.
- Come on, let's go.
Shit.
RADIO DISPATCH: Sheriff wants
an ambulance to 647 Quick Hill Road.
You copy?
- Drayton?
(GUN COCKING)
You know why I'm here!
Come out and bring your son, Jed.
Hands high above your heads.
I ain't leavin', Drayton.
I have a girl says you butchered her friends.
No one's turning a blind eye to this.
He's protecting the house and the family.
Yeah, well that ain't the way I heard it.
(GUN CLICKING)
Oh, damn it. Come on out here!
Look, I ain't waiting out here all day.
I'll call in the Staties,
if that's what you want.
Send the boy out, Drayton!
Look, this don't have to
get no uglier than it already is.
Fuckers ain't getting anybody in this family.
SHERIFF: You don't wanna make it worse.
I ain't leaving without the boy, Drayton.
We're Sawyers!
MAN: Hell, yeah!
SHERIFF: What's it gonna be?
You do what you have to do, Sheriff!
Send the boy out!
Give him the boy. He's simple anyway.
He's family.
(SIRENS WAILING)
We're gonna send out Jed.
All right. Send him.
Hold it up, Marvin.
And he gets a good lawyer!
SHERIFF: Agreed.
You did it now, boy!
You let that bitch meat get away.
- Oh, shit.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
- Come on out, Sawyer!
- Give us that retard!
There's more! Them ain't cops.
Get back here, Drayton!
We got trouble!
All right, just stay back now, Burt. I got this.
- We're here to back you up.
- Yeah, you can start
by getting everybody back in their cars
and high-tailing it outta here.
Yeah, that ain't gonna happen.
BURT: Let's go, boys!
Lynch these son of a bitches.
SHERIFF: I've got control of this.
He's bringing the boy out, okay?
What are we doing there, Sheriff?
Kick his ass out!
Look, he's bringing his son out here.
Bring him out!
- Light 'em up, Ollie!
- Special delivery!
- No!
- Motherfuckers!
(SCREAMS)
(GROANS)
(BABY CRYING)
BURT: Hell, yeah. Sawyer bonfire.
This is on you, Burt.
Eye for an eye, Sheriff.
Can't get around the Good Book.
Helluva job, boys!
Whoo!
Keep looking.
When they're charred, they're hard to find.
Ah, hell. Hey, Burt!
(COUGHS)
- Yeah?
- Looky here.
I'm hanging this bad boy over the bar.
- This baby's coming home with me.
- We gonna be heroes.
- Son of a bitch.
(BABY CRYING)
Help us.
Yeah. Yeah. Come here.
Come on. Come here. Come on.
Come on. Let her go. Let her go.
Come on. Yeah. Yeah.
I got her. Everything's okay.
(GROANS)
Shh! Shh!
It's okay.
Hey, Gavin, where've you been? What is...
Oh, my God. It's a baby.
Found her.
Brought her out through the woods.
MAN: Gavin! Come on, man,
we're gonna be in the paper.
Yeah, man, I'll be right there.
Yeah, yeah.
MAN: Come on now, you're gonna miss it!
ARLENE: - Gavin...
- Come on!
She's been burned.
Okay. Yeah, yeah, brother!
Be right there, my man!
We're gonna keep her, right?
I got her for you, Arlene.
You never know how you look
till you get that picture took.
(CAMERA CLICKING)
(ALARM RINGING)
I'll be right back.
NIKKI: Come on, what were you thinking?
Hey. He was Ryan's idea. I warned you.
Well, next time your raunchy-ass boyfriend
tries to stick me with one of his
high school band buddies,
- kiss him for me.
- What?
I like him. He was pretty cool.
We started talking
and he made these incredible crepes.
Amazing.
He's got this thing about becoming a chef.
And there's actually a lot more to him
than meets the eye.
So, do you think you can handle this
four-day road trip with him to New Orleans?
I am way ahead of you, girl.
He even volunteered to drive.
- Seriously? Wow.
- Hell, yeah!
- I was talking to...
GIRL: - Hey, Nikki!
Bobby wants you back at your register.
All right. I'm gonna go work
on my Halloween costume.
And I don't mean scary.
(MEWS)
(CHUCKLES)
Nikki digs your old high school friend.
- Something about crepes?
- That's Kenny's signature move.
Nikki had no chance.
I thought we weren't gonna
bring our work home with us.
You think I'm cracked?
No. But you might
wanna broaden your extracurriculars.
Get over here and tear this up.
I'm not up for a bruising.
I wasn't talking about the bag.
Neither was I.
I love your crazy little birthmark.
(DOORBELL BUZZING)
Fuck.
Who is that?
Shit. That, it might be my contract.
(BUZZING CONTINUES)
I'm coming!
(EXHALES)
(DOOR OPENS)
(SIGHS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
- It's for you.
- Me?
Some law office in Dallas, yeah.
My grandmother died three weeks ago.
I thought all your grandparents were dead.
So did I.
I just wanted to have a child.
GAVIN: Enough.
- I wanted to have a child so bad...
- Enough!
- ...and I couldn't!
- Enough, Arlene. Enough!
Why couldn't you tell me?
Tell you what?
Your mother has a defective uterus?
She wanted a kid. End of story.
So what? We're not
good enough for you now?
I didn't say that.
I just wanna know where I came from
and who I came from.
Well, we're the ones that raised you.
And you were damn lucky, I'd say.
Those people were...
I can't even put that into words.
- There are no words...
GAVIN: - Shut up, Arlene.
- ...for that, Heather.
- Shut up!
You came from a shit heap.
There. Now you know.
If I'd had half a mind, I'd've left you there.
(SCOFFS)
I'm out! I'm done.
Don't even think about going down there!
Heather!
Heather.
Heather. You go down there
you're gonna bring trouble on us.
What are you talking about?
Trust me.
Newt, Texas is the last place you wanna be.
(DOOR CLOSES)
RYAN: - How'd it go?
- Like shit.
It sucks when you find out
your parents have been
lying to you your whole life.
Baby, I'm sorry.
I was adopted.
I never felt right about them.
I'm gonna go pack.
- For Texas, not New Orleans.
- Wait.
- Hold on.
- No, Ryan. I have to go.
- Forget Halloween.
- Wait. Wait, just listen to me, please.
Hey.
Oh. Ryan called us.
RYAN: - Kenny!
- That's really cool art.
See, I kinda figured you'd wanna deal with
your grandmother's stuff so...
So, knowing how hard-headed you are,
we have decided to come with you.
Really? You guys would do that?
Are you kidding me?
Come here. Of course!
Come on. You're our girl.
Listen, I wasn't gonna send you to some
cousin-fuck town all alone.
(LAUGHS)
I don't mind driving to Texas.
I hear they got great barbecue.
So, maybe so, maybe no?
All right. Sounds like a plan.
- Let's do this.
- Oh, yeah.
What! What!
Texas here we come!
(THUNDER CRASHING)
Oh, my God. Are you kidding me?
Jesus Christ.
Go, go!
(PANTING)
Fuck.
- What'd you get?
- All this.
You like? 'Cause it was, like, 25 bucks.
Get out. That's a rip-off.
Don't worry about it, honey.
It's on your credit card.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh, yeah? Well, that's okay. You know why?
Because...
- Kenny paid for the gas.
- What?
What the... Give me that.
- How'd you get that, man?
- Oh, Kenny.
RYAN: Don't cry.
NIKKI: It's okay. Let's go, baby.
- Ready?
NIKKI: - Baby, let's go.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
What was that?
(GROANS)
Jesus, dude, you all right?
Oh, my God.
- Yeah, it's all right.
- You hit him, Kenny.
Sorry, I didn't see you, man.
It's all right.
I should probably sue.
But I'll settle for a stick of that jerky.
Say, where y'all headed?
New Orleans.
You're kiddin'! That's great!
- That where you goin'?
- No, no.
Shreveport? It's on the way.
Did your car break? Where's your car?
Uh, that's a bit of a long story.
Short of it is
my lady dumped my butt and I've been
thumbing my way back from Tulsa.
I sure could use a ride.
Ain't got no problem paying my way.
60 bucks.
You'll be doing a guy a favor.
Help a fella out.
Rain?
- Okay. Come on.
- Yeah?
We have to stop in Texas on the way.
Well, sure beats walking.
All right.
You Okay?
Yeah. I'm good.
- You scared at all?
- No.
I'm just wondering where I fit, you know?
Yeah.
So, what's in Newt?
One-sided family reunion.
My grandmother died.
I gotta sign some papers.
My condolences. Were you two close?
I just learned about her yesterday.
But family's family.
Amen, sister.
Family is a messy business.
Ain't nothin' thicker than blood.
(HORN HONKING)
So, do you know anything about this place?
Just the address.
KENNY: We're just in and out, right?
That's the deal.
KENNY: We'd never find this at night.
NIKKI: What the hell?
We wouldn't be able to see anything.
Hey, this is it.
This is Homestead Road. Make a left.
RYAN: This can't be it, right?
He said a big gate.
RYAN: Wow.
- Wow.
(EXHALES)
Well, there's gotta be
something behind there.
Like a castle or somethin'.
All right.
(CAR APPROACHING)
Mr. Farnsworth? I'm Heather.
I could tell from the car. Dead ringer.
Thank you for coming
all the way from Dallas.
Anything for Verna.
She was a good woman. Salt of the earth.
Though not the most popular in these parts.
I didn't know you were bringing friends.
Is that okay?
Well, it's your house, if you want it.
Just so you know...
Verna's trust forbids you from selling it.
It's all described in these papers.
Okay. Thanks.
You can't quite see the house from here.
But it's just up beyond those trees.
These keys, they open
everything inside and out.
Verna was big on security.
0-8-19.
Best to remember it as a date.
August 19th.
Right. And the gates work automatically
from the other side.
- I have a house.
- And a whole list of assets
that I'll be forwarding to you
as soon as the accountants sign off.
Oh. I almost forgot.
The most important thing.
It's from Verna. Make sure you read it.
Okay. I will.
And call me if you have any questions.
HEATHER: You're not coming in?
Uh...
No. I promised some other folks I'd stop by.
Don't forget to read Verna's letter.
Hey.
How did you find me?
Find you? Honey, you were never lost.
NIKKI: It's a mansion! Oh, my God!
(LAUGHS)
- Wow.
- Sweet.
NIKKI: No way. Oh, my God, girl!
KENNY: - Wow.
- Are you kidding?
This is nicer than the outside.
- I don't know where to start.
- How about here?
What is going on here?
(CHUCKLES) Wow.
Some fine dining.
- Heather, can I open this one?
- Yeah.
NIKKI: Wow.
KENNY: Wow.
This is definitely worth coming home to.
NIKKI: Want some tea?
KENNY: It's all set up.
So, Heather.
What exactly did Granny do for a living?
I have no idea.
Hey! Check this out!
Look like Granny liked to play a little pool.
- Who wanna play?
- I do.
NIKKI: Got money, bitch?
RYAN: Okay, I'm a bitch now.
Yeah, you're my bitch.
Okay, rack 'em up.
- What'd you say about my rack?
- Rack 'em up.
- Oh!
- Whoo.
Now it's a party!
NIKKI: Nice.
RYAN: Oh, I scratched.
Oh, too bad.
Ouch!
All right. You wanna see me?
I'm gonna dominate you.
Where's the white one?
(SIGHS)
Thank you.
Hey! What's going on?
NIKKI: This house is insane!
God, we gotta stay the night. It's too cool.
KENNY: That kitchen is so amazing.
Y'all have to let me cook for you tonight.
RYAN: Yeah. And you can thank Darryl.
He's the one
splurging on the steaks, ain't that right?
Hey, Shreveport can wait.
I needed something like this for a long time.
Thanks, you guys.
God, is he a Boy Scout or what?
- Come on.
DARRYL: - No, I'm overkill on this mission.
I'm gonna get the bags, clean up a little.
(ENGINE STARTING)
Yeah, I'm a regular Boy Scout.
(LAUGHS)
All right. So let's, uh, divide and conquer.
Will you take care of that for me?
We'll see you in a few weeks, Mr. Mayor.
Burt. Wish I had a swing
like that in my backyard.
Yeah, that's something all right.
Hello, precious.
Whoo.
Come on, baby.
Where's your mama? Where's your mama?
Where's your mama?
I'm gonna get, like,
one more thing and then I'm done.
- All right. I'll meet you outside.
- Cool.
There's, like, a carnival
or something going on?
(MEOWS) Price check.
- Fuck are you doing?
Nobody's looking.
Listen, it was one time.
One time. And I had,
like, 18 kamikazes. Come on.
Come on. You begged for it.
And now I'm begging you to
keep your hands off my shit.
- Okay.
- All right.
Beautiful big door for a beautiful big key.
Oh, I got your stash now, you old cunt.
What am I gonna do with a bunch of wine?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
What the hell is this?
(GRUNTS)
Here we go. Come on.
Come on!
I've dealt with stubborn bitches before.
You just need some kicking.
Now, honey.
(SNAPPING)
(PANTING)
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
I'm coming back here. I don't quit easy!
(GROANS)
You're asking for trouble.
That wouldn't burn
if you doused it with a fuel tanker.
This here will give you some good flavor.
But if you wanna unleash some hellfire,
this here's the stuff.
Good to know.
In town for the carnival?
Just a little housewarming.
Well, you best keep it down.
I'd hate to have to haul you in.
I'll try to behave.
- How much is this?
- That'll be $9.
So, whereabouts is this shindig?
Homestead Road.
Ain't nothing out there
but the old Carson place.
That's the one.
I thought that place was empty.
Not anymore.
This officer bothering you?
Say the word and I'll shoot him.
He will, too.
BURT: Go read some meters.
Burt Hartman, proud mayor
of this little slice of paradise.
How're you doin'?
- Heather.
- Nice to meet you, Heather.
Now, my ears aren't what they used to be,
but I swear I coulda heard you say
something about the Carson place.
I inherited it.
- You're a Carson?
- No.
- You're not a Sawyer.
- Yep.
Yeah, you've got her eyes.
- You knew her?
- Yeah.
Me and your family go way back.
And I know they wouldn't want you
to be burdened with that beat-up old trap.
Tell you what.
I'll take the whole place off your hands.
No, thanks.
Gonna hardball me, huh?
Hell, I like you already.
Come on, let's go.
Come on. Give me a number.
KENNY: Yo!
Oh.
HEATHER: Oh, shit.
NIKKI: What?
Fucking thief.
He took my keys.
- Wow, he played that smooth.
- Yeah, he did.
We should've never picked that guy up.
RYAN: Yo!
- Whoo!
- Let's do this right.
- What's wrong?
- Darryl ripped us off.
So he heisted some ashtrays
and candlesticks.
That shouldn't keep you
from having a good time. Come on.
- Cheers, you guys.
- Yeah.
To happiness.
- To the queen.
- Yeah.
- To the Sawyers.
Sawyers. All right.
(KENNY WHISTLING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(CREAKING)
(CHUCKLES)
Hey, there's a butler's pantry in here!
Darryl?
Yo, Darryl!
Darryl!
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
(METAL CLAN KING)
(SCREAMS)
(PANTING)
(SCREAMING)
Oh, my God, you've gotta see this!
RYAN: What?
- It's so fucked up! Come on!
- Whoa, what's wrong?
Come on!
NIKKI: It's right down there.
RYAN: Where?
- It's right down there.
- Where?
It's in that stall, right there.
RYAN: In here?
NIKKI: Oh, God!
Nikki, I don't see shit.
It's right under that bucket.
It's under that bucket right there.
Okay.
What the hell, Nikki?
What are you doing?
I told you it was fucked up.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Ryan!
You guys!
(PANTING)
(CLATTERING)
Kenny?
(GASPS)
(SCREAMS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(CHAINSAW WHIRRING)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMING IN AGONY)
(CONTINUES SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
(CHAINSAW WHIRRING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GRUNTS)
(WHIRRING STOPS)
(SOBS)
(SOBBING)
(CHAINSAW WHIRRING)
(SCREAMING)
Dude, what the...
What is that? What the... What is he doing?
Who is that?
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
- Go.
- What?
- Oh, my God!
- Go!
- Move. Move!
- Close the door!
Welcome to Texas, motherfucker!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
RYAN: Did you hit him?
I don't know.
- Did you hit him?
- I don't know!
(CAR APPROACHING)
Something's coming. Back up.
Back up! Back up, Nikki!
- Get in the van!
- It's Heather!
Move over, move over!
Let me in! Hurry and get us out of here! Go!
Go, go, go, go!
Go!
Go! Go!
Go, go, go!
What the hell was that?
Where's Kenny?
He's dead. They're fucking dead!
HEATHER: Ryan, slow down. Slow down.
The gate, the gate needs to open!
- Give it time to open!
- We got to go.
Fuck the gate! Buckle up!
(ENGINE REVS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
- What happened?
- The car stopped.
NIKKI: Why?
HEATHER: Okay, back it up. Back...
- Ryan!
HEATHER: - Back it up, back it up, back it up!
- Back up the car!
- What's wrong with it?
- Ryan, go!
- I'm fucking trying!
- Back up the car!
- It won't start!
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck!
- Back up!
- Here we go. Here we go.
Wait for the gate to open.
- Fuck!
NIKKI: - Ryan!
Ryan! Start it!
(CHAINSAW WHIRRING)
- Go Ryan, go!
- It won't start!
Now, go, go, go!
- Ryan, go!
- Come on!
- Go, go!
- Please, go!
Come on!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
NIKKI: Here he comes!
Ryan. Ryan.
(HEATHER SCREAMING)
(HEATHER SOBBING)
Heather, what happened?
(CHAINSAW WHIRRING)
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What?
(SHUSHING) Quiet. Quiet.
We gotta get outta here now.
We gotta get outta here right now!
(SHUSHING)
(SCREAMING)
Get away, get away, he's coming over here!
My leg.
No, Nikki!
(SCREAMING)
(WHIRRING STOPS)
(RUMBLING)
(SCREAMING)
(CHAINSAW WHIRRING)
Hey! Hey, you country fuck!
(PANTING)
(SCREAMING)
Run, run!
Hey, Wanna play a game?
(SCREAMS)
Call the police!
Get out of the way! Call the police!
- Go! Get out of the way!
- What the hell?
What is going on?
Hey! Hey!
Drop the fucking saw!
I said, drop it!
Put it down!
(PANTING)
SHERIFF: Where's the girl?
WOMAN: Carl is tending to her in the back.
SHERIFF: All right.
Sheriff? This is Marvin. I'm at the crash site.
- You copy?
- Go ahead, Marvin.
MARVIN: Approaching the vehicle now.
Late model VW bus on its side.
It's a real mess.
- Do you need an ambulance?
- Checking now.
That's a negative.
No one. No victims on the scene.
Sheriff? There's blood everywhere.
Seat's all sawed up.
Somebody died out here.
All right, stay where you are, Marvin.
I'll get back at ya.
Roger that.
(SNIFFS)
(KNOCKS)
- Hey.
- They find her?
We Will.
- Got you a shirt here.
- Thanks.
At least it's clean.
I should've never brought them here.
Look, this town ain't much,
but we take care of our own here.
He'll be a sack of meat scraps by dawn.
You can count on it.
SHERIFF: Carl!
- Take your time.
- Okay.
Sheriff Hooper? This is Heather.
Hi.
You the girl that guy was chasing?
Yeah.
He killed my friends, but Nikki...
She was still alive after the crash.
Yeah, we're on it,
but there was no one at the site.
No, she was there. I left her there.
He must have moved them.
Do you know who he is?
No. He was in the house, he was...
- What house?
- The Carson Estate.
My grandmother left it to me. Verna Carson.
We just got here a few hours ago.
I'm a Sawyer, if that's your next question.
Sheriff, I dug through the evidence room.
Pulled out what we had on Verna Carson.
Also pulled a big file on the Sawyers.
You get a good look at him?
He was wearing a face.
A mask?
A human face.
Carl, we're a little short-handed.
I'm gonna need you out on the street.
Get going.
(INTERCOM BEEPING)
WOMAN: Sheriff, the mayor just got here.
He's looking for you.
Thanks.
Take a seat. I'll be back in a minute.
Some fucking crazy just tore up the carnival!
I need to know
what the police are gonna do about it!
My office.
I think it may be Jed.
Jed Sawyer?
No way.
We burned that place
to the ground years ago, Hooper.
You were there. No one escaped.
Well, maybe he crawled out
through the back. I don't know.
You telling me he's been
holed up all these years
and now he's running around on the loose?
I'm telling you a 6'5" man
came out of Verna Carson's house
wearing a skin mask and wielding that.
MARVIN: (ON RADIO) Sheriff?
I'm at the Carson place.
Gate's busted open.
There's a broken side mirror that looks like
it matches the van.
Marvin, I told you to stay at the van.
Now, that's an order. Do you copy?
Hell, no! That's not how we play this!
There's a blood trail on the pavement.
Sheriff, no disrespect,
but I think I need to move on this.
SHERIFF: That's not your call, Officer.
BURT: Marvin! This is Mayor Hartman.
You got your Eagle?
You know it, with an extended clip.
Just looking for a reason, sir.
Then what the hell are you waiting for?
Marvin, stand down.
Now, we believe Jed Sawyer may be alive.
And he may be in that house.
Copy that, sir,
but a chainsaw don't make you bulletproof.
MARVIN: Door's wide open.
This is a mistake.
Now, stop it now before you get him hurt.
- It's hot pursuit, Hooper.
- I'm going in.
(GUN CLICKING)
Police!
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Yeah.
- Give me a visual.
- You got it.
Movin'.
This is on you, Burt.
Eye for an eye, Sheriff.
Can't get around the Good Book.
MARVIN: Entering the kitchen.
Proceed.
What the hell?
Following the blood.
Jesus!
You seeing this?
Shit.
Looks like it leads to this door.
BURT: Push it open.
What the hell is this?
BURT: Proceed, Officer.
I don't know about this, Burt.
God damn it. Do I gotta come down there
and hold your hand?
(EXHALES)
SHERIFF: So, where are you now?
I'm in the wine cellar.
There's an opening to some kind of...
I don't know.
Going through.
Looks like some kind of crazy catacomb.
Still following the blood.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Getting a bad feeling here.
(CLATTERING)
Jesus Christ. What is this?
It's a haven?
Dresses.
High heels.
Little farm toys.
Bones.
Man.
Ladies makeup? What a fruitcake.
This is the most disturbing place
that I have ever been.
What's that to your left?
It's a door.
SHERIFF: Marvin, keep your hands
on that gun!
My fucking God.
BURT: How many?
MARVIN: You tell me.
What fucking human does that?
(TREMBLING) Shit, this is fucked up.
What's in there?
What's in the freezer?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
SHERIFF: Be careful, Marvin.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
(SCREAMS)
Oh!
Shit!
It's okay! It's okay. Didn't happen!
Marvin! You get the hell
out of there right now!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
That sick fuck'll be back out there tonight.
We rally the boys,
we torch that place to the ground!
End this! Finish what we started years ago.
Not this time. Not on my watch!
(SCREAMS)
(GRUNTS)
(CRYING OUT IN PAIN)
(GRUNTING)
(CRYING OUT)
(SIGHS)
- What happened that day was a travesty.
- It was justice!
I wanna see the Sawyer girl.
She's a victim, Burt!
She hasn't done anything!
She's breathing, ain't she?
Yeah, I know what you're thinking, Burt.
You have no idea!
Nothing better happen to that girl, Burt!
(CELL PHONE BEEPING)
- Hello, Farnsworth here.
- Hi. This is Heather Miller.
My friends have all been killed.
I just found out about August 19th.
How could you leave us
alone in that house?
Okay. Where are you?
I'm at the bank on Main Street.
Uh, meet me at Johnny B. Red's.
It's a bar about a quarter mile
east on Fifth and Main.
I'll be there in 20 minutes.
(WOLF-WHISTLING)
(CARS HONKING)
I want your Halloween candy!
Come on and party with us!
(FOLK MUSIC PLAYING)
(GROANS)
(COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING)
Why didn't you warn me?
All my friends are dead.
My family was wiped out by this crazy town.
- Did you read Verna's letter?
- No.
Well, I asked you to, right?
Verna was very particular.
I'm sure she laid it all out.
But you knew about him.
You knew about this town.
You knew everything.
Oh, okay.
Okay, so who is he?
Well, the person in the basement
is Jedidiah Sawyer.
Goes by Jed.
He's your cousin.
For years I suspected something,
but I never knew for sure about Jed
until about four months ago when Verna,
who was very sick, presented him to me.
A grown man, huge, but mentally stunted.
With emotions of an eight-year-old.
Frankly, he scared the shit out of me.
Why'd she keep him?
Nobody loves you like your family, I guess.
She preserved you, too.
She investigated everyone
who was involved with the...
August 19th.
Found you right away.
And she let me live with those people?
You were safer there.
And she knew
there would always come a day.
Jed knows about you, too.
That was some welcome.
He doesn't know who you are.
And the last time a girl got away,
Jed lost his whole family.
So, he'll stay after you.
He doesn't know any better.
Burt Hartman, too.
After reading that police file,
you know this town's dirty little secret.
- Burt. Burt!
- Yeah!
Let me through.
Let's go. I'm getting you out of here.
- Move!
- Hey!
- Out of my way!
- What's your problem?
Use the back door. Yeah, take it!
Burt.
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
OLLIE: I got her, Burt!
She's right here.
You going somewhere, precious?
Huh?
Oh.
She cut me. Burt!
That little bitch.
She won't get far, that's for sure.
Come on. Get up now!
Stop! Stop! Stop!
What's going on?
Burt Hartman and his guys,
they beat up my lawyer at the bar.
And they're after me.
Okay, come on. Let's give you a ride.
We have to stop at the bar.
We have to go back.
Okay.
There he is. That's Farnsworth.
That's the place! Stop the car!
Stop the car!
That's the bar! Stop!
Let me out! What are you doing?
Stop the fucking car!
What are you doing?
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Yep?
Sawyer girl's loose.
She's headed towards town.
Yeah, yeah. I got her. She's in the back.
What do you want me to do with her?
Tell you what,
take her up to
the slaughterhouse and hold her.
I'm dealing with Ollie. She sliced him good.
Just give me a few minutes.
Okay.
You got it, Dad.
That's your fucking dad?
Fucking stop the car!
Let me out!
Open the door, you liar!
BURT: Okay, Marvin, do you copy?
We have the girl from the Carson house.
Come on, Marvin, pick up.
Are you there? Come on, Marvin.
That you, Marvin? If you can hear me,
then meet us out at the slaughterhouse.
Sheriff, I represent Verna Carson's estate
and her granddaughter, Heather.
I know who she is.
Well, at this very moment,
she's in the back of
one of your police cars against her will
heading out of town,
out past Johnny B. Red's.
All right, come with me.
She's headed out Highway 28.
There's nothing out there.
Oh, shit. I know where he's headed.
You know,
I thought you were pretty cute.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
So you're a Hartman, huh?
Yep.
Whoa!
I'm a Sawyer.
(GRUNTS)
(HEATHER SCREAMS)
Please stop!
CARLI Quit it!
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
Don't tempt me.
You should feel
right at home in this nasty place.
Your family used to work this shithole.
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
We'll take it from here.
No place for a cop, son.
(CHAINSAW WHIRRING)
It's me!
It's Heather!
It's your cousin!
It's me! I'm Heather!
Please, it's Heather!
(CHAINSAW WHIRRING)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
Come here. You remember me?
BURT: Come on, Ollie.
Let's feed his ass to the shark.
- Move!
- Hit him, Burt.
Come here! Move your big ass!
Get up there!
You about to die, motherfucker.
Just like your gammy, your sick cousins
and your damn horrible brother.
- Get down! Move!
(WAILING)
BURT: I'm gonna end the whole
Sawyer bloodline tonight.
You and your pretty bitch cousin.
OLLIE: Atta boy, Burt. Hit him again.
Motherfucker, you're about to die, boy.
Son of a bitch!
- Go get that chain, Ollie.
- All right. I'll get it, Burt.
Grotesque excuse for a man.
You're not gonna get off that easy, boy.
I'm gonna enjoy this shit, you hear me?
- Hurry up, Ollie.
- I got it.
Give me that.
You're about to
get chewed up like a fucking cow!
OLLIE: Fit for a pig meal, is what you'll be.
(IMITATES PIG)
Turn it on, Ollie and fire it up. Let's go.
All right, Burt. I'm on it!
Bet your ass, boy.
I'm gonna enjoy
watching you get chewed up.
You son of a bitch.
This is my town, you fucking cockroach.
She rolling, Burt!
Out of all you Sawyers, all you sick fucks,
the only one that gets out of the fire
is a fucking retard?
How the fuck did that happen?
You remember me?
(GROANS)
(GROANING)
BURT: You got nine lives? Are you a cat?
You came back. But you're gonna die today,
you motherfucker, just like your daddy.
Your day has come!
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
HEATHER: Hey!
BURT: - Fucker!
- Hey!
Hey!
Oh-ho.
Look who's back.
That's right.
Do your thing, coz.
- You cockroach.
(GROANS)
Bitch, you're dead now.
I will fuck you up, you hear me?
You piece of fucking trash.
(CHAINSAW WHIRRING)
(GROANS)
BURT: Oh, thank God, Hooper!
Shoot him!
Come on, shoot him! Shoot him!
Don't shoot!
BURT: Hooper! Take him out!
Shoot the fuck. Kill him!
Pull the trigger, you weak son of a bitch!
He's gonna kill me!
- Oh, God!
- Don't shoot him!
Hooper! Finish what we started!
Can't get around the Good Book, Burt.
Clean this shit up.
(WHIRRING STOPS)
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
VERNA: Dearest Granddaughter.
This home and all it
comes with, is now yours.
Just know that these gifts
come with certain burdens.
Your real name is Edith Rose Sawyer.
Farnsworth was instructed to give you
a set of keys to the manor.
The large key opens the fortified door
to the wine cellar.
There you will discover a metal door.
Behind it lives your cousin,
Jedidiah Sawyer,
your only remaining blood relative.
He's family-bound and will protect you.
He simply requires your care in return.
Edith, you are the last of my line of Sawyer.
(COUGHS)
My blood runs through you.
The decision to stay is yours.
Just remember, you're a Sawyer
and this is home.
Now, it's your time.
(DOOR BELL RINGING)
Now remember, you tell her
that you love her.
(CHUCKLES)
For this kind of money, I almost do.
(CLATTERING FROM INSIDE)
(CHAINSAW WHIRRING)
(SCREAMING)