Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh, I'm so hungry.
If only there was some juicy,
delectable, tasty humans.
But wait. I see one, two.
But which one will I eat first?
Her.
Her? You think her?
Well, maybe I'm gonna eat
her anyway. Ahhh!
Oh, I've got you.
Oh, I'm gonna miss you girls.
I hate it when you're away.
When will you be back?
It's just a couple of days
this time, alright?
Enough scary stories. Bed time.
No.
Come on. Bed time
Okay. Why don't you guys go
and brush your teeth
and I'll come upstairs, and we'll
read that book that you love, okay?
Okay. Go. Go. Quickly. Race.
I could get used to this.
Yeah. This...
this conference is...
It's the most important thing
ever. I know. You already said that.
Yeah. It's a big one.
It's a game changer.
Yeah, same as the last one,
and the next one after that.
Because I don't wanna, I don't wanna
bring the girls up in my Mom's old house
and I want them to have
their own bedrooms.
They love sharing, you know? Almost as
much as they love their Dad coming home.
Yeah, well, this is it and then
I am all theirs, and I'm all ours.
If that's okay, huh?
Bye.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Jess, you seen the book the
girls love?
Babe. I'm gonna check
if it's in the car.
Jess, you seen the keys?
What the fuck?
What's wrong with Mommy?
Baby, you stay here with Mommy.
Don't move. Don't move.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Daddy!
Baby?
Oh, baby. Baby, give me your
hand.
Baby, it's okay.
It's okay. Give me your hand.
Baby, come on. It's okay.
Baby.
Welcome to paradise.
See anything on your way in?
Aah!
It's no use.
Oh fuck!
Oh, God. Jess. The kids.
No. No. No. Fuck, no.
He doesn't want them.
Only you.
What's your name?
Jay.
Adam.
Kat.
What is this place?
As bad as it looks, man.
I gotta get the fuck outta here.
You behave, you stay here.
You don't, you go back.
Understand?
Eat.
I said eat, boy.
This is your home now.
It's for the market.
What do we do when we're upset?
Remember.
Remember what?
Who saved me.
Yeah. Good boy. Hmm?
I just want my Mom.
Your mother and father are scum.
They abandoned you.
If they cared about you, they'd have
come looking for you, now, wouldn't they?
I'm your father now.
And if you upset me,
I swear to fucking God...
Who's doing this?
He was there when I got here.
Kat calls him Paul.
After my cat.
Paul doesn't say much.
Where were you when
you were taken?
Parking lot after a night out.
Working the graveyard shift.
It's his playground.
Whose?
See, this must have been a
mistake
'cause I'm a good person.
I didn't do anything wrong.
You see, I do charity. I...
I gave blood once.
Oh, get used to that shit.
A big fan of the red stuff.
I take it you've tried
to talk to this prick?
Oh, yeah. I've tried to hug
it out, bought him flowers.
One guy did all this? I mean,
you're a fucking cop!
Security guard.
Well, you are.
Good to know.
Dominic!
Are you trying to test me?
Hey, don't start with me, son.
Dominic?
Father, I'm sorry!
Are ya?
Yes!
Say it again.
I'm sorry!
Ssh.
That's it. Let the evil out.
What was that?
Feeding time.
What's with the lights?
Well, it ain't fucking
Christmas.
What, so he warns you
before he tortures you?
Yep.
Only it's not him that
does the torturing.
Who does?
You're his pets.
It's not even cooked.
No thanks. I'm vegan.
Of course, by vegan
you mean fucked.
Well don't waste it.
Throw it back.
Quite the summer camp, ain't it?
It's a big mistake, not eating.
Not exactly Mother Theresa.
What about Paul?
He gets injections.
They keep him alive.
That's your future, right there.
You two can do what you want
but I'm getting outta
here if it kills me.
A very poor choice of words.
Come on!
Any loose?
Not yet.
Nothing your side?
Found this.
Not been very lucky for me.
What?
It's a waste of time.
Like your police application?
Like your mom's labor.
Not got any keys?
Nope.
Do you have any?
Shit!
A hundred years, and nails like
Freddy fucking Krueger
wouldn't get through it.
Or you could learn the hard way.
Adam's right.
The only way out is
through that door.
Hey.
Seriously. If he sees you doing
that, he'll go fucking insane.
I had an ex just like you.
He wouldn't give up either.
I had to get his Dad arrested for
raping me, just to get rid of him.
So he deserved it.
Oh, he didn't touch me.
When I was 15, I'd set up
dates with married guys.
Take pictures
send them to their wives.
Fucking perverts.
I'd give a nut right now
to be back at home.
Guess which one's
gonna happen first?
Gives the old ball and chain
a whole new meaning, huh?
You guys are fucking
insane, you know that?
Don't.
If Frankenstein comes back
in, we'll all lose our fuckin' balls.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Dominic
Playing it safe, huh?
Why did you do that?
I don't know.
You don't know.
But you chose to do it.
You see, every maneuver is a
promise.
A promise to your next maneuver
and your next one.
'Cause life's all about choices.
When you got no choice
you got nothing.
You chose to be here
with me, didn't you?
Dominic.
I'm asking you a question.
Ugh!
Your mother and father are scum.
They abandoned you.
If they cared about you, they'd have
come looking for you now, wouldn't they?
I'm your father now.
I need to tell you a secret.
This is the world that
left you for dead.
But ours isn't a strange
world, is it, son?
I'll never let anyone
hurt you again.
Promise you'll never leave me.
Yes, father.
And you'll grow big and strong?
I promise.
Show me.
Grow big and strong,
just like him.
It's beautiful.
We're just like each other
one and the same.
Not all of us are kind.
Some of us need to have
the evil taken out of us.
Does that mean you're evil too?
Yeah.
See, sometimes, we do bad things and the
only way to take the bad out is through pain.
I want you to stab it.
Remove the evil.
It's what's gonna make you a
man, Dominic.
Healing through pain.
I promise. I'm not
gonna punish you.
Oh, that's it.
That's it.
Oh, good boy. Huh? That
wasn't so bad, was it?
Huh?
Watch the evil, huh?
Watch it leave me.
Oh, you...
You motherfucker.
What? What is it?
Oh, come on, then,
you fucking pussy.
You enjoy watching...
Have you never noticed this?
Shut the fuck up for our sakes.
What are you hiding from?
I'm married, you prick.
I have a fucking life.
Jay, please, Adam's right.
Great.
Great, thank you.
Thank you so much!
Come on.
My wife, my daughters.
Hey!
My wife and my daughters.
Are they alright?
Does that mean they're okay?
Don't.
You gotta let him, man.
Or he'll go for our families.
Oh.
Jay, you have to do what he
says.
It'll be worse if you don't.
Don't do anything stupid.
It's either Paul or you.
No, no. No, no.
No, no. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Please.
Sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's... what the fuck?
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Oh my god, no.
She's fucking choking, man.
She's fucking choking!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
I do like a birthday.
You can talk to me, you know.
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
Bring it here.
Who did that?
Doesn't matter.
Why?
I said it doesn't matter.
Sit down.
How come it doesn't matter?
Come here.
It's alright.
Whatever you're doing, don't.
Fuck you, man. How many
times I gotta tell you?
Paul tried that. You
wanna be like him?
Oh, fuck.
Grass greener on the other side
of the door, asshole?
Is there a way out?
Oh, so we didn't suffer for
nothing. Great.
We can escape.
We just need to be clever.
What's he doing?
He's just pissed you're back.
Why is everything a
fucking joke to you?
The joke's on us, my friend!
What's he doing?
Why doesn't he just kill us?
No one throw away
their favorite toys.
I have to.
Adam, please don't!
It's either you or me.
I can't fucking take
this anymore.
Never leave me.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I can't feel my arms!
God!
Come on! Get up!
Huh?
Come on!
You promised you were
gonna spent more time with us...
Jay!
Hey.
Jay! You've gotta
stay with us.
You guys ever seen his face?
Oh yeah, he's gorgeous.
No. We haven't.
So what's the freak hiding?
I don't know. Probably
just ugly. Never kissed a girl.
No, specifics.
Come on, you guys have clapped
eyes on him more than me.
He stinks.
Yeah. We all stink.
More.
He doesn't speak.
Right. More.
Paul, shut the fuck up.
What was that?
Just leave him be.
Schh!
He's trying to speak.
Paul, what?
Horse, what?
What are you trying to say?
Paul?
Horseshoe.
He has a
a horseshoe burn on his hand.
I saw it when you
tore his glove off.
Oh my god.
Paul was trying to tell us.
There's spiders. Worms next?
I know you.
I fucking know you.
After the farmer's wife died
he went crazy.
Started wearing a pig skin mask.
Locked his kid in the old
farmhouse.
Didn't let him out of his sight.
Made him eat the pigs alive
and then one night,
when the sky was at its blackest
the old man sharpened his axe
until it was ripe for scalping.
The kid was hiding.
All he could hear were his
footsteps.
Louder and louder, closer and
closer.
Police found what was left of
the kid
in the scalding chamber.
Skinless.
And they say the farmer
still stalks these woods
looking for his next victim...
It's not true.
Is so. Creepy farmer.
Stuff of legend.
I'd kill that crazy freak.
I don't think I could.
Think about it.
Actually ending a dude's life.
Let's go find the farmhouse.
What's that?
Kat, Kat, come on. Kat.
Dominic, the boy.
What the fuck are
you talking about?
The traveller, Kat.
The one with the horseshoe
burned on the back of his hand.
It was my family summer
vacation.
Holy shit.
Hey. He's still following us.
Hey, what's that scar?
Whoa.
Looks like a wiener.
Wiener fingers doesn't
say much, does he?
Say Adam's a fucking asshole.
Adam's a fucking asshole.
So. Horseshoe.
You wanna hang with us?
You could replace.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What's your name?
Dominic.
Well, you can be in our gang.
Just needs to pass the dare.
Stop.
Oh shit! Did you swallow that?
Ugh.
You do wanna be in
our gang, right?
Don't let them get in your eye.
They'll eat your brain.
Actually, let's leave him.
Leave him?
Oh, fuck.
We left him in that
creepy farmhouse.
He's done all this 'cause he was in
some house for a moment? Come on.
It was more than a moment.
I don't wanna him back here,
okay, he can stay out for ever!
Get, boy. You get
before I beat you!
Stop it! No, don't say
that! Stop it! No!
What you say to me?
Someone's in trouble.
I did it after they
shot my horse.
He was my best friend.
I've got something really
cool to show you.
Don't worry, it's just us.
I'm sorry but...
this really is the final dare.
Look, all you have to
do is just go inside.
I'll kiss if you do it.
Show us how brave you
travel kids really are.
You wanna kiss me, right?
Then go inside.
20 minutes.
Make it 20 years.
No wait!
Shit!
I went home that afternoon.
I never thought I'd
see you guys again.
Did anyone see
him after? The kid?
My mom. She said ..
Don't go into that farmhouse.
She'd known I was there.
What month were we at the camp?
My thirteenth birthday.
August 25th.
I had that big meeting tomorrow.
It was the 24th.
That's 20 years.
We were kids, we didn't
know any better.
Neither does he.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Why aren't you working?
I heard a noise.
Bullshit.
No!
Ahh!
Oh sorry.
Get back to work.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
How dare you?
Okay.
Ahh!
Ahh! I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Ah!
No, don't! You, you had a son.
Henry. Are you gonna kill me
just like you killed him?
I didn't kill him.
It was an accident in the scalding
chamber, he wasn't strong enough.
You took me to replace him.
Didn't you?
I just wanted you to
be stronger, huh?
I hate you.
You wouldn't last five minutes
out there without me.
No one loves you like I do.
How do you love me?
That scum outside?
They're burning marks in
your skin. Leaving you to rot.
Well, surely they're a
better scum than you.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean
what I said before.
No wonder no one
came looking for you.
What are you doing?
Wait! Wait! No, stop! Stop!
How can I let you live?
A fraud in Henry's home.
Please, please don't,
please don't!
Ahh! Ahh!
Oh god, oh, stop!
Tried to remove the evil ..
To make you strong!
No! Oh god, please!
Please, please no!
Father, I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
But it doesn't leave everyone.
Sorry, please! Let me go!
No, no, no!
Agh! Please no, stop!
Ah! Oh god! Ah!
Henry.
It's Dominic.
My parents were looking for me.
You burned them alive.
I love you, son.
You already killed your son.
Ah! Oh, oh!
I need to tell ya a secret.
The only way you'll ever truly
be free is if you find them.
Those that abandoned you.
When you're big and strong,
no matter how long it takes
no matter how hard you look,
bring them back here
and let the evil out.
We need to apologize.
For what?
We only knew each other
two fucking days.
At most.
Think about it.
When kids get bullied, who do they
want to like 'em more than anyone else?
What a nicer place to make
friends.
Ah, think about it.
If we can tap into even just a
chink of humanity in that fucked
up head of his.
And do what? Just let us go?
Better the devil you know.
Exactly.
Jesus Christ.
Fuck you, I'm getting outta
here.
Alright. Huh. Dominic.
No.
Dominic.
Now we know who you are.
And we know what we did.
It was wrong to leave you.
Now, I can't claim to know or...
or where to understand
I can't.
What you've been going
through in the past
the past 20 years.
What I do know
is that each one of us
is sorry.
We're so sorry.
We wanna get out of here, we do,
man. We wanna get out of here with you.
No, no.
No!
Oh come on, man.
Spiders.
Come on, poor souls, ah.
Please no more. No more. No.
I'm sorry!
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
In her ear.
No!
Yah! Grab the hose!
Adam, come on!
Ugh! Ugh!
No, no, no, no!
No! No! Oh!
Ugh! No! No!
Oh please! Oh.
His eye.
Oh god, no!
Cut it.
No, no!
Hey asshole!
That's right.
No wonder we left you to rot.
Look at you. A girl wouldn't
kiss you to save her life.
You're nothing but
a waste of skin.
Leaving you was the best thing we
ever fucking did, you fucking freak!
I'll kiss you then.
No one will ever love you.
All you have to do
is just go inside.
Your mother and father are scum.
They abandoned you...
I'm your father now.
No one...
Get it out!
Cut me loose.
Has it gone inside?
Oh shit, you gotta pull it out!
What?
Pull it out! Don't let me die.
I'm not gonna let you die, I'm not
gonna let you die. Wait, bite down.
Right down. Hold him down.
Ahh!
Alright this it okay, he's
gonna come for us.
We've got nothing to lose.
Just one other fucking eye.
Oh, he's gonna kill me.
Oh god, it's fine, you're
gonna fucking kill me.
It's best you hand over the
knife. I need it more than you.
I gotta protect myself!
You're braver than me.
No one's gonna get hurt anymore.
That's easy for you to say,
you got the fucking knife!
Give it!
No, Adam. Adam, come on.
Don't. Don't.
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop!
Adam.
Kat, it's not your fault.
Kat, repeat after me,
"It wasn't my fault."
Maybe it was my fault.
All of it.
I never went back.
I never checked to
see if he was okay.
After you left, the police came.
Asking all kinds of shit
about a missing boy.
And you know what I told them?
Fucking zero.
All this time you knew?
20 years.
20 fucking years I held onto
this shit and for what?
You left him too.
You could have saved him.
You could have told someone.
You could have stopped this.
Let her go.
We just wanna go home.
I returned to your world after.
Still no family.
You're a good kid, Dominic.
No. I was still unwanted.
An orphan.
Came back here.
The farmer was right.
You are all scum!
You were my friend.
No.
You abandoned me.
Left me for dead.
Why don't you let
me see that face?
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Let me see, my friend.
See that wasn't so hard.
I would have come and rescued you if
I'd known what you were going through.
Ahh!
I failed.
The evil never left you.
Kill me.
Look at you. You're pathetic.
Come on!
Yaah! Ah, oh.
Urgh!
Dah!
Ahh-ah!
Ugh.
Uugh!
Ah, god!
Arrh!
Ur-ah! Ya!
Raah!
Ru-aah!
Uahh! Uah! Uah! Uah! Ugh!
I could have had a family.
If I could fix it,
I would, I swear.
Well then, fix it now.
Now end it.
Kill me.
No.
No, I can't.
Aah!
Your wife. I'll take her.
She'll suffer worse than you.
Look at me.
Ahh!
Your daughters will live with
me.
I will make them love me.
Huah!
Gah!
Jay!
Oh my god!
I'll live.
Daddy?
Molly. Poppy.
What's wrong with your face?
Daddy's gonna be okay.
Alright?
Dad would kill us if
he knew we were here.
Dude...
Dad will never know.
Besides, the freak's long gone.
D-E-A-D. Fucked.
I hate dares.
Well then, you should
have chosen truth instead.
And you and Isaac could have stayed
at home like little virgin snowflakes.
Is it really the same forest?
Yeah. Not far from here.
Your dad kicked his ass, right?
Hells, yeah. Ten years ago
tonight.
No, I get it.
Freak fed him cockroaches.
Made them slice each other.
Nailed them to the wall.
He even kept their skin.
But that's not all.
Dude, pinned one of the
prisoners down and...
Got him with the worms!
Poppy! Oh.
So.
Who's coming with me to find the
farmhouse?
Yeah, I'm game.
Yeah?
No, no way.
You know they never found a
body.
What?
Oh shit.
Yo.
I'm gonna go grab my
gloves from the car.
It's freezing out here, man.
Yo. Fuck this, come on guys.
Come on, I'll, I'll bring
the car around.
We should go.
Pussies.
Poppy, come on!
Upcoming jump scare (Major)