Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[wind rustling]
[wood creaking]
[eerie music]
[woman] I can't possibly run
from there all the way back
to my home,
so I move quickly.
I walk as fast
as I possibly can.
You can sense it
when someone's following you.
Even though
I never hear any footsteps,
I just have the feeling
someone's watching.
[ominous music]
[woman 2] She was found in
the section of the map here
between the village
and the clinic.
As you can see, the clinic
is quite far from the village
she started from and
they found her right over here
sitting on the ground.
Naked, completely in the nude.
Clothes folded beside her.
So then after that,
that was when
they sent in all the police,
all of the investigators,
they did their tests,
and in the end they admitted
that they had no idea
how she had died.
[light dramatic music]
[woman 3] They tried to tell me
he took off his clothes
and just died in the forest.
[interviewer] Mm-hm.
The local guys who found him
told me that he was actually
found naked,
but that there were some kind of
markings all over his skin
like he was tortured
or something like that.
- Who would do that?
- [interviewer] Yeah.
They put it on the news and
nothing ever came of it.
[light dramatic music]
[woman 4] I try not to run
by there, but I do walk fast,
- really, really fast.
- [interviewer] Mm-hm.
[woman 4] You know,
I... I always feel like
there's someone
right behind me,
[interviewer]
And you said you hear nothing?
[woman 4] I hear nothing,
but I'm afraid to turn around.
- [interviewer] Why is that?
- [woman 4] I'm afraid
- I'd terrify myself and fall.
- [interviewer] Mm.
[woman 4]
It... what it feels like
is that someone
is always around
15 or 20 steps behind me.
- It's hard to describe.
- [interviewer] Mm. Mm-hm.
- [woman 4] I can't.
- [interviewer] Mm-hm. Mm-hm.
- So, like, following you.
- [woman 4] That's right.
And I bet you
they're watching me.
[dramatic music]
[woman 2]
There is one, this woman,
my village says
she takes people this way.
She took a child, a boy.
They found him.
He was just like the other ones.
- [light dramatic music]
- [metal rattling]
Now they stay away from her.
That whole area,
farmers won't even run
their cattle by there anymore.
She hung herself.
The only thing
people said about it
is that she sure had it coming.
[light dramatic music]
[heavy breathing]
Can you feel your legs?
Are you able to move?
Sit tight, we're gonna
get you out of here.
[reporter] Viktoria.
Mind if I ask you a question?
You guys,
why do you rescue people?
We each have our own reasons.
Someone has to do it, right?
Go talk to Andre.
It's my first call of the day.
- [dramatic music]
- [man screaming]
[Viktoria] Hold him.
- [man 2] Have to hold...
- Tuck in tighter, please.
[screaming continues]
Brace his leg.
Try to keep him still.
- I need a bandage.
- [screaming continues]
Ah, shit.
Lacerated artery.
[birds chirping]
[sighs]
[reporter] I have a mirror.
Viktoria, you weren't able
to save this man's life today.
How does that feel?
- [man screaming]
- I need a strap.
Don't have a strap,
only a bandage.
[Viktoria] Damn it!
Take off your belt, quickly.
I'd rather not answer
that question.
[reporter] Oh, come on,
it wasn't real this time.
[Viktoria] Mm-hm.
- [door thuds]
- [man screaming]
Try not to move.
- Everything's going to be fine.
- Time's up.
Time's up, guys.
Sorry, it's too late.
That's it, we lost the victim
due to significant blood loss.
[sighs] Damn it.
You can get up,
I didn't save you again.
[man] Give me a minute.
It's hard dying five times
in one day.
Does anyone see my cigarettes?
You can smoke later.
Right now
get the stretcher ready.
We still need to evacuate
your dead body.
Our visibility in the forest
is only about 30 meters,
however audibly, we can hear
about 200 meters.
That's assuming they're
still alert and can respond
and call out loud enough
for us to hear.
Actually as rescuers,
we have a rule.
We always secure
the first person we find.
If it's more than one person,
hand off the first to
the medics before going back,
no gambling with lives.
At least
that's how we're trained.
[man 2] Our role is to
fully secure each individual.
- [Viktoria] This one's done.
- [man 2] As you can see here,
some of the environments
we find ourselves working in
are extremely dangerous
and cave rescues
are among the most
difficult jobs we have.
It's important
that we get this type
of hands-on training in.
The thing I hate most
about my job
is working with
the dead bodies.
When you know
there's no one to rescue,
all you can do is
bring the body to the station
and onto the relatives
to deal with.
All right, we're good.
Ready to move.
- [Viktoria] All right.
- Let's get him up.
- Are you ready?
- [man] Let's go.
[grunting]
- Careful, careful.
- Keep holding tight.
- Careful!
- [heavy breathing]
[Viktoria]
Careful, it's slippery in here.
We're taught it's a sin
to get a slow start.
24 hours is a long time
in these elements,
every minute
could cost someone their life.
Go, go, go, go.
Careful.
[water sloshing]
Should I stand
closer to the water here
- or not?
- [reporter] No, you're good.
- No, you're right.
- [reporter] Unless you want to.
I guess you would know best.
Well, our team conducts searches
for people
who go missing in the wilds.
So in this area,
the forests, the swamps,
and the caves like here.
Watch your head.
Watch where you're going.
Look, it caved in here.
- Watch yourself here.
- [Viktoria] Careful, careful.
Hey, guys. Hang on.
Stop, stop.
What's going on?
What do you see?
This was also caved in.
There was a passage,
but it's blocked now.
If you choose to go
into the woods,
it makes sense to wear something
brightly colored like this,
for example,
red or orange or yellow.
I wouldn't advise
wearing camouflage.
And don't forget
to charge your phone.
There are things
people can do to, you know,
give us a chance to find you.
[Viktoria panting]
It's blocked.
Just wait.
Stop, stop.
I'll check ahead.
[man] Where are you going?
Viktoria!
Then, so,
look at the camera?
[reporter] No, just relax.
Pretend it's not there.
No, heroism is usually
life-threatening
to the hero himself, you know?
So we're taught
to avoid heroic actions.
Our rescuers' main...
almost our guiding principle,
is not to increase
the number of injured.
Recently, our ratings
and efficiency
have improved so much
that we're at the point
where now the guard
redirects some of
the emergency calls they
get to our team.
- [heavy breathing]
- Here this way.
No need to rush anything.
You can take your time.
Here, take my hand.
Are you all right?
It's okay,
just a little crawlway.
Stay calm.
- I'm stuck here.
- I'm telling you, easy.
This guy here is called Yukon.
I rescued him
from his first owner
who unfortunately
died in a fire.
He's been trained
to search for people,
specifically living people.
Cadaver dogs are trained
differently than him.
So he doesn't do that.
He specializes in
finding the living.
Hang on, stop.
Your harness is stuck.
Go back just a bit.
Just a little bit.
That's right.
- That's it, good.
- Nice.
Now take a few breaths
and exhale.
You're good.
Breathe, out.
Strong exhales now.
Deep.
- Come on, here we go.
- Come on, come on.
- You're almost there.
- You got it.
- Just a bit more.
- Yeah.
- Just a bit, great.
- That's it.
Good job.
Congrats on
your very first climb.
You did it.
[reporter]
Can you talk about the beacon?
Okay.
Ah, the beacon.
He wears this light-up beacon.
Uh, this is so we can track him
at dusk, in the dark, or fog,
anywhere there's low visibility
like in these caves.
All right, you got this.
Careful.
- Gripping it tight?
- [Viktoria] Mm-hm.
[reporter 2] Time for a good
morning with some good news.
[reporter 3] Number one talk.
[reporter 2] Ex-president Trump
was indicted today...
- I'm coming through.
- Sure, come on.
That's quite a lot of gear
you have.
Yeah, I'm doing a check
of the filming equipment.
[reporter 2] ...prostitution,
bribery, extortion,
- and the list goes on and on.
- A little action cam?
[reporter] Mm-hm.
have a few of them.
You can wear them on your head.
- They're handy.
- Right.
This is the main camera,
I can record in total darkness.
Why are you by yourself?
I thought you had a cameraman.
He was assigned to another
project at the last minute.
What can I do?
I'm not gonna back out now,
am I? [chuckles]
Well, if you need something,
I'm around.
[door thuds]
I'll see you.
Would you help me?
Is the red light on?
- [Viktoria] Mm-hm.
- [man] Ready.
I'm Christina Arrifeva.
We're now watching the search
and rescue team ISCRA
train a new volunteer
on how to provide
first aid to injured persons
when they're found in
extreme environments,
and very soon,
many kilometers from here,
they'll hold their annual um...
I think I'll start with
the second part first, okay?
And, and, and let's turn around
to face the cave opening.
Come on.
We've been fortunate
to see in action
their new state-of-the-art
training system
that simulates lifelike wounds
such as the bleeding
and fractures
they will actually see
on the job.
Their goal here
is to practice in the field
for situations
that they'll be expected
to respond to in
alive emergency.
With support from their sponsors
as well as the...
- [rumbling]
- [dramatic music]
[man] Hey, are you okay?
[Christina]
Yes, we're coming out.
[man over radio]
Andre, do you copy?
[Andre over radio]
Andre here.
[man] We have a missing boy
near your location.
14 years old.
He and his little brother
wandered into the forest.
The little brother
returned alone. Shocked.
Won't say a word.
If you guys could
wrap up your training,
you're our closest unit.
We're sending another group
but they're hours away.
Do you copy?
- Andre?
- [Andre] Copy, we got it.
I confirm,
we're taking your call.
We await the location.
Thanks. Over and out.
- [dramatic music]
- [engine rumbling]
[engine rumbling]
[crow cawing]
[man] That's where the kids
crossed the road
and went into the forest.
They were last seen by loggers.
It's swamp land
with woods beyond that.
That's where we'll start.
It's such a huge search area,
how will we find him?
Where did he even come from?
There's no villages nearby.
[man] Look here.
Their village is
about 15 kilometers
to the south along the river.
A little further up here
is an old saw mill.
- Right.
- [man] If we zoom out,
we see this area here
is nothing but swamp.
That's really treacherous land
out there.
So they're looking at the map
and it seems the area
we're going into is going to be
difficult terrain.
- [engine rumbling]
- [dramatic music]
[dog whimpers]
Hey, Andre, drive safely,
- come on.
- You nearly killed the dog.
[Andre] There's no way to drive
safe, we're in a Russian car.
[dark dramatic music]
[engine rumbling]
[man] Right, that's the spot.
We'll set off
in about five minutes.
[birds calling]
Can you turn towards me?
Uh-huh.
Perfect. Beautiful.
[static buzzing]
- [Christina] Ilya.
- [Ilya] Huh?
[Christina] Where's the tablet?
[Ilya] It's here in the car.
[Christina] Listen, can you
turn it on for me please?
I need to check and see if
Viktoria has a working camera.
[Ilya] What do you need
that for?
Viktoria,
take a step towards me.
See, the red light's on.
It must be working.
[Christina] Come on, Ilya,
I'm not asking for much here.
- [Ilya] Fine.
- It just takes a second.
[Ilya] Just a moment.
Do you know what
the connection code is?
- [Christina] Um...
- [Ilya] Four zeros?
Damn, how many useless things
are in this van anyway?
Why do you have a gun?
A flare gun.
German made in the last century.
They knew how
to make some things. Heh.
- [Christina] Alexey.
- [Alexey] Huh?
What's this thing here?
Oh, that.
That's our searching siren.
We mount it
on the roof of the van
and it lets the lost person know
that we're looking for them.
[siren wailing]
[dramatic music]
[music continues]
[ominous music]
[Ilya] You guys, we're entering
the search zone now.
We're going to spread out
and call out his name, Nikita.
Listen for his response.
Nikita!
[Christina] Viktoria,
face the camera.
Shh.
[Christina whispers]
Is Yukon on the scent?
[Ilya] Not yet.
[Andre] Nikita!
[Ilya] Keep your eyes peeled.
Stay alert, people.
Pay attention.
[Christina] So, right now,
the search team is calling out
the missing boy's name.
[Andre] Nikita!
[Christina]
They're looking for signs
and listening
as we make our way through
the overgrown brush.
Nikita, hey!
The saw mill where the boy
was seen is north of here
and there's a path just ahead.
Let's go ahead
and split up here.
Why don't you give me Yukon
and we'll follow the trail.
- And you two, you and Viktoria.
- Mm-hm, okay.
Go check that path
right over there,
but make sure you stay
within sight of each other.
- Uh-huh.
- Make sure to stay
in each other's field of vision
- at all times, okay?
- Careful,
everyone watch their step.
Let's disperse now.
Remember to stay
close to each other.
Yukon.
[ominous music]
[Viktoria] Nikita!
[Alexey] Nikita!
The sun is setting.
It'll be dark soon.
[Viktoria] Nikita!
Listen, it's useless.
We're never going to
find anyone.
Why's that?
I'll tell you why.
Over the last three years
I've had over 100 missions
and I haven't found anyone yet.
I'm unlucky.
I'll be your good luck charm.
Beginner's luck, you know?
You think so?
- Yeah.
- I don't know.
Nikita!
[ominous music]
Alexey.
- Huh?
- You smell that?
What?
Something's burning.
I can't smell it.
I can't smell anything.
[suspenseful music]
[voice] Will you play with me?
[eerie music]
[Alexey] Viktoria.
[dark ominous music]
[rustling]
[dramatic music]
[suspenseful music]
Is it ready?
Keep her head above her legs.
We found an old woman
in the forest completely naked
- and apparently in shock.
- [Andre] Keep it steady.
- So far she hasn't...
- [Ilya] I got it.
[Christina] ...been able to
explain what happened to her.
She has no visible injuries
or wounds of any kind
and we were unable
to locate her clothes
- anywhere in the area.
- [Andre] Watch out.
[Christina] We also have
no explanation of why
there was a child's toy
found near her.
Here behind me here
you will see the rescuers
urgently transporting the woman
back to their vehicle.
And from there she will be taken
to the nearest hospital
as soon as possible.
As of now,
we still know nothing
about the boy's whereabouts.
- [thudding]
- [Christina gasping]
[Andre] Watch for the stones.
Mm-hm.
- [Christina] Hang on guys.
- [man] You need to be careful.
- [ominous music]
- [Christina whimpering]
- [dramatic music]
- Oh, God.
Come on, stand up.
[dramatic music]
- [woman groaning]
- Stop. She's convulsing.
[Andre] Put her down,
put her down now.
- [Alexey] Okay.
- Here, hold her head.
- [Alexey] Holding.
- [Andre] She's not breathing.
Hold her head. Hold it still.
Let's open her mouth
and have a look.
Christina, out of the way!
[Andre] Give me a second.
Let's see what's in her mouth.
There's something.
Ilya, light.
I'll try and pull it out.
- [dramatic music]
- [Andre groans]
[Alexey] The hell?
[Andre] Give me a knife.
- I need a knife.
- [Ilya] A knife?
You'll break her teeth.
- [Andre] Open her mouth.
- [Ilya] I can't stop her.
- [Alexey] Mind her chin.
- [Andre groans]
[Ilya] Come on.
What the hell is that?
[woman coughing]
It looks like she's breathing.
- Looks like it.
- Wow.
[static buzzing]
This crazy lady
nearly bit my fingers off.
Come on, tighter.
I have another bandage
just in case.
She really did a number on me.
How is she?
I'll go check.
Ma'am, can you hear us?
[Andre] I hope she'll make it
to the hospital.
[Ilya] She'll be fine.
[Viktoria] Maybe we can give her
some medicine.
[Ilya] Seriously? We can't.
[Viktoria] Why not?
[Ilya] Because
you give her a pill,
or any kind of injection,
she might have an allergic
reaction or even overdose.
Then we end up in court.
[Andre] We're only allowed
to give them medication
if they have it on them.
Unfortunately,
the risk is just too great.
- Wrap it here.
- Mm-hm.
Alexey, what's up? Anything?
No, it's all bad out here.
The elevation's too low.
- [muffled yelling]
- [light dramatic music]
[ominous music]
You hear that?
[Andre] All right, guys,
it came from this direction.
Let's take the stretcher and
go see what's going on.
- [Ilya] Uh-huh.
- [Andre] Ilya, that way.
Watch out for these trees.
Careful, don't drop her.
- [muffled yelling]
- [Christina gasps]
Nikita!
Alexey, what the hell? Hang on.
- Alexey, Alexey!
- [Ilya] All right, let's move.
[ominous music]
- [Christina panting]
- [branches snapping]
[Viktoria] Alexey.
[tree creaking]
There's nothing here.
Probably the trees
creaking in the wind.
So, now the team went off
on a dead end lead
at a time when every minute
that passes is critical.
- Ilya.
- [Ilya] Huh?
Come see.
Hm, interesting.
[ominous music]
[Viktoria] It looks like a frog.
Well, yeah,
but actually it's not a frog.
Back in the day,
villagers would leave symbols
on old dead tree trunks to
mark the way to a sacred place.
This one indicates
an evil place.
Here we have a pointed head.
This would typically indicate
some type of evil spirit.
However, this one's strange,
at least from what I'm seeing.
It looks like it has...
maybe deformed or crippled legs.
Villagers would tell you
it's not a good sign.
[Christina] That's bullshit.
[Andre] All right, team, enough.
Let's go, there's not much time.
Ready?
One, two, lift her up.
[Alexey] Done.
[Andre] Watch your step,
be careful.
[Alexey] Got it.
[tree creaking]
[gasps]
[Ilya] Are we going
the right way?
[Andre] It's easy to get lost
in place like this.
[Viktoria] Yeah, does anyone
have the feeling
we're going in circles?
For more than three hours
we've been on a rescue mission
to save a woman
we found in the forest.
The team's getting tired,
- but we continue moving.
- Please don't block us.
You've filmed enough.
Sometimes we walk for eight
hours before we do our jobs.
We're nearly there.
Easy, not so fast.
Higher.
- Uh-huh.
- Right, you got it.
Careful now.
Easy.
Down.
- Ilya.
- [Viktoria] Let's go
one at a time.
- Pull it toward me.
- It's stuck here.
- Damn it.
- [men grunting]
- Come on down.
- [Andre] Put it here.
- Here.
- Let's get her up in the van.
- Come on, lift.
- [men grunting]
Let's put something warm on her.
Push more, more.
She's breathing.
[light dramatic music]
So, guys,
I know it's not my business,
uh, but what are you gonna do
about the kid?
Are we not looking for him?
- [bear] I'll be your friend.
- [Ilya] Remember our rule?
We always secure
the first one we find.
Let's go.
[engine rumbling]
[dramatic music]
- [engine rumbling]
- [keys jingling]
[engine revving]
Shit.
[door thuds]
Oh, come on. We're stuck.
What is it?
We're sitting in the mud.
Give me some light.
Yeah, the rear axle's stuck.
Let's wedge
something against it.
I'll tell you when to push
and you'll lean into it,
- all right?
- Uh-huh, yeah.
[Viktoria]
Andre, should I also get out?
[Andre] No, stay with the woman.
- You're light as a bird.
- [door thuds]
Are you guys ready?
- Gas it.
- [engine rumbling]
[rattling]
Keep pushing, keep pushing!
- [engine revving]
- [mud sloshing]
How heavy is this thing?
Three tons at least.
[ominous music]
[Alexey] Did it move?
I'll get the towing strap.
We'll use the winch.
[shovel scraping]
Ilya, can you hit
the bright lights?
- Can't see shit.
- Sure.
Ready.
Will it hold?
Of course, we only have
one tow strap. It has to hold.
- [Alexey] We're hooked up.
- [whirring]
[tense music]
[Ilya] Get rid of those twigs,
we need something substantial.
Alexey, move.
You, two,
wedge it under the wheel.
We need some traction.
- You get it?
- [Alexey] Yeah.
- [Ilya] All right, step aside.
- [Alexey] Uh-huh.
[Ilya] We're towing, so step
back in case a strap snaps.
- We're out.
- [whirring]
We're moving.
Think we're good.
[engine rumbling]
[dramatic music]
[music continues]
[engine rumbling]
[Andre] What fresh hell is this?
Let's go have a look.
- [light clicks]
- [tense music]
[door thuds]
[engine rumbling]
[Ilya]
Damn, road's completely blocked.
[Andre] This is shit.
I'll get the chainsaw.
[Christina] What's happening?
[Alexey] Don't worry.
We'll figure it out.
Just a detour.
[Andre] Wait in the van.
We'll saw it up.
No problem.
[woman coughing]
Don't worry.
Can you tell us
how you're feeling?
We're a rescue team.
We found you in the forest.
Don't worry, you're safe now.
You're in our rescue van.
I'm Viktoria,
and what is your name?
[woman]
Zoya. Give me some water.
- [saw sputtering]
- [Andre] Damn it.
[grunting]
[groaning]
[coughing]
None of you
will get out of here.
No one is allowed
to leave this place.
[groans]
Zoya, what do you mean?
[ominous music]
The lame widow,
she'll lead you around
in circles.
- [saw sputtering]
- [Andre grunting]
[Zoya] It was a long time ago,
before the war.
She was
Red Sophia Zurumokov's daughter.
She choked her husband to death,
they said.
The people would scream at her,
"Why did you murder
your husband?"
The mob came for her
and caught her.
They beat her and
broke both of her legs
with a metal rod.
[saw sputtering]
They stripped her and
rode her out in a wagon
and threw her naked
into a dark pit.
[lights clicking]
[ominous music]
- [Andre panting]
- [owl hooting]
What's that?
Everything's fine, don't worry.
Faulty wiring.
They let her drown
in that black ooze.
It was just before
Holy Virgins Day.
The old-timers say
that evil's lived
in that dark pit ever since.
[ominous music]
[birds calling]
[ground rustling]
Ilya?
[light dramatic music]
We all heard the stories
growing up
about a dead woman
wandering around at night
on her broken legs
and killing people,
always taking their clothes.
That's why people were always
afraid to go into these woods.
Where are those guys?
I tell you, that the lame widow
from rotten earth
will get her revenge.
She will get what she wants.
Get what?
They threw her
into that pit naked
eternally freezing.
[ominous music]
The widow won't allow anyone
to leave this forest alive.
[dramatic music]
[Andre grunts] It's no use.
[Alexey]
That's one hell of a story.
Hey lady, how about
you get some sleep, huh?
[doors thudding]
All right,
the situation's pretty bad.
I haven't been in something
like this.
The road is completely blocked.
Not sure what to do.
Chainsaw's dead.
Can we take a detour?
- Ilya?
- [Ilya] Yeah.
There's an option. A side road.
This logging path
leads to the forest highway.
We should end up approximately
back where we started.
And if we get lost again?
Can't we just start driving?
Anywhere?
- Come on.
- We won't get lost again.
As long as we find the path,
we're good.
[engine sputtering]
The car's not starting.
- [keys jingling]
- [engine sputtering]
[engine rumbling]
All right, here we go.
Ilya, the tablet.
[engine rumbling]
[dramatic music]
There's no fork here on the map,
God damn it.
[door thuds]
Now will you admit
that we're lost?
You might be right.
[Viktoria]
I'll go check this way.
We never go alone.
- Alexey.
- [Alexey] Huh?
- Go with Viktoria.
- [Alexey] Uh-huh.
I'll check this path.
Ilya, will you help me?
- Hold the camera.
- Okay.
Let's go. Be careful.
It on? We good?
- Yeah, we're good.
- All right.
Let's go.
It's less than an hour
before October the 14th.
In folklore, that day is also
known as the Holy Virgins Day.
It's a day that
our ancestors believed
to be the scariest night
of the year.
It's the last chance for
evil spirits to commit horrors
before they hibernate
until spring.
Of course now we understand
a lot of the things
that inspired legends
in the past.
However, I have to say,
when you're deep in the forest
like this
you feel inclined to take
the tales more seriously.
[Alexey sighs]
Can you believe this shit?
[ominous music]
What are we doing here?
[Viktoria] We're saving a person
who was in distress.
[Alexey] Yeah, you're right.
Let's hope we're not the ones
that need saving.
[Viktoria] What's that?
[Alexey] I don't know,
it looks like a haystack.
[Viktoria] It's pretty weird.
[ominous music]
Look, there's another one.
[Alexey]
Where did they come from?
It's creepy out here,
do you wanna go back?
Yeah, let's go.
[Viktoria sighs]
[horn honking]
[Andre] Ilya, Alexey, come back!
Found the right road!
[light dramatic music]
[engine rumbling]
[ominous music]
[engine idling]
[door thuds]
[Andre] Well, how deep is it?
It should be fine.
Just make sure to drive slowly.
What do you mean drive slowly?
We're gonna speed
right through it.
[engine rumbling]
[water splashing]
[beeping]
[Christina] Is she breathing?
[Alexey] I think so.
Andre, that's too fast.
The road's a mess.
I don't know about you, but
I can't be out here all night.
I have a wife waiting for me.
- Andre!
- Andre, stop!
[grunting]
[Andre] Everyone all right?
[Ilya] My door is stuck.
[Alexey] The heck was that?
[Andre] Yeah, well I thought
it was a bear.
[Viktoria] You're kidding me.
[Andre] I'll check it out.
[Yukon whining]
[barking]
[Alexey] Yukon, stop.
Stop!
[Yukon barks]
- Yukon!
- [barking]
Yukon!
What is it?
[sighs] Maybe he found the boy.
Let's go.
[barking continues in distance]
[Andre] Christina, stop!
What now?
[Andre] Stay here.
But why?
Because I need your help.
How exactly am I gonna help?
I'm going to show you.
Zoya, how are you?
I'm alive.
[Alexey] Yukon!
[Ilya] So why didn't Yukon
smell Zoya back there?
Sorry?
Well, you said he sniffs out
people who are alive.
Yeah, hell if I know.
[Yukon whining]
- Uh-huh.
- [whining continues]
[ominous music]
Oh, Lord.
What do you want?
I wanted to join you.
But Andre asked you to stay.
- He let me go.
- Mm-hm.
Better stay close.
[Alexey] Yukon!
[Ilya] Careful,
watch out for branches.
[Alexey] Yukon!
[Ilya] Don't poke an eye out.
- [Alexey] Move faster.
- [Christina] This isn't
- my first time walking here.
- How slow are you?
[Christina] This woman,
all naked, the lost boy.
And... and why was a haystack
in the middle of the road?
[Ilya] Some kind of witchcraft.
Well, naked people
have been found here before.
I've been involved in
two cases of it.
Are you serious?
Yeah, in one of the cases...
Hang on, wait.
I'll switch this on.
All right, it's working.
[rattling]
[panting]
[light dramatic music]
Hey, Christina,
can you pass me the wrench?
[rattling]
Damn it.
Christina?
Here you go.
Uh-huh.
[dramatic music]
[Andre grunts]
And where's Christina?
She joined the guys
like five minutes ago.
So, several years ago they
found a logger's body out here.
He was completely naked.
After he was back
to his village, his home,
he ended up choking to death.
Actually, it's more like
he drowned in mud.
He had mud everywhere.
In his mouth, his nose.
It looked as if
he was digging the ground
with both of his hands.
We could see where he was
shoveling it and even eating it.
And when was the second case?
Today.
[Alexey] Hey, guys!
Enough chit chat.
I found a trace.
- Come on, start.
- [engine sputtering]
Come on, start.
Do you think they're
going for the missing boy?
They're not gonna find shit
out there.
We just need to get outta here.
Andre, look.
Andre.
Look, Yukon's back.
[ominous music]
[door thuds]
[music continues]
Yukon?
[dog panting]
Where's your collar?
[dog growls]
Yukon, come here.
Yukon.
Yukon?
[music continues]
- [Alexey] Yukon.
- [Christina] Yukon!
- [Ilya] Yukon.
- [Christina] Yukon.
[dog whining]
[Alexey] Maybe his collar
got caught on something.
[Ilya]
Yukon, how did you get in there?
[Christina]
Are you going in there?
[Alexey] I have to.
- [dog whines]
- Here, hold this.
Alexey, wait just a second.
- What?
- Will you hold the camera?
I'll put a GoPro on you.
[Alexey]
Okay, but do it quickly.
[dog whining]
Come on, come on!
- Is the light on?
- [Ilya] Uh-huh.
[Christina] Yes, it's on.
- [ground rustling]
- [dog whining]
[man over radio] Over, over,
can you hear me?
[Viktoria] Yes, I can hear you.
Do you copy? It's Viktoria.
[man]
The second rescue team's close.
Tell me your coordinates.
Do you copy?
Our team leader has,
uh, has left.
[man] Okay, well,
we need your coordinates
or any information that
can help us find you.
If you'd like,
we can reconvene...
Do you copy? Can you hear me?
Over.
- [man] No, I'm having trouble...
- [dramatic music]
- Over, can you hear me?
- ...with our connection.
You should've just left me.
You don't know
what you've done.
No one's getting out.
Not alive, anyway.
[ground rustling]
[Alexey] Yukon?
Yukon!
Yuk...
- [ground rustling]
- [Alexey grunting]
Yukon.
[dramatic music]
[ground rustling]
Yukon.
Are you here?
- Alexey.
What do you see?
[music continues]
The widow will enter you
and you'll be no more.
[Viktoria] Andre, can you help
with the radio?
[door thuds]
[dog growls]
- [Zoya groans]
- [door thuds]
Red sunrise and brightest day.
Come and keep the evil away.
- Come and keep the evil away.
- [dog growls]
- Red sunrise and brightest day.
- [Viktoria] Andre?
[Zoya]
Come and keep the evil away.
- [dog growling]
- Red sunrise and brightest day.
Come and keep the evil away.
[growling continues]
Red sunrise and brightest day.
Come and keep the evil away.
- Red sunrise and brightest day.
- [growling continues]
Come and keep the evil away.
- Red sunrise and brightest day.
- [gear grinding]
Keep the evil away.
The widow
will not let you escape.
[dramatic music]
[engine rumbling]
- Stop!
- [thudding]
[ground rustling]
[Alexey] Yukon.
Yukon.
[Alexey panting]
[suspenseful music]
Yukon?
[ominous music]
Yukon.
[panting]
[Christina] Alexey.
Alexey.
Alexey, are you okay?
[Ilya] Alexey?
[Christina] Can you hear us?
[Ilya] Alexey, come back.
Do you hear me?
[dark dramatic music]
[tense music]
[Viktoria]
Andre, please slow down!
Andre!
Andre, damn it!
- [engine rumbling]
- [dramatic music]
[grunting]
[panting]
[grunts]
[Christina] Where's Yukon?
[Alexey]
Maybe there's another entrance.
[Christina] What happened?
I never saw him.
Why not?
But I did find someone's phone.
[siren wailing]
[groaning]
[water bubbling]
Andre!
No, please. No.
No.
Andre.
[water bubbling]
[Viktoria panting]
[sobbing]
[Christina] Why do you think
they turned the siren on?
I don't know.
Something might've happened.
Yukon's back.
[Viktoria shrieks]
[ominous music]
Follow me.
[Viktoria cries]
[water trickling]
[ominous music]
Andre!
[static buzzing]
Ilya, do you copy?
We have an emergency.
Ilya.
[Ilya]
The scream came from over here.
Viktoria!
Andre!
- Stop!
- [Christina] Wait.
- Ilya, grab him.
- What's wrong with you?
You don't know what's in
that water.
- [Christina] Alexey, stop it.
- [Alexey] Let me go!
- Listen, calm down.
- He might still be alive.
I'll go check it out.
You're not listening.
Stop it, chill out.
Take a deep breath.
Just stop it.
[water trickling]
[dramatic music]
[gasps]
Andre?
[ominous music]
Andre!
Here we go.
- Turn him over.
- Uh-huh.
[dramatic music]
[heavy breathing]
[ominous music]
[water trickling]
Andre!
[Alexey panting]
Enough.
Alex.
That's enough, do you hear me?
Alex, he's dead.
[dramatic music]
[ominous music]
[woman coughing]
Guys, did you hear that?
Over there.
Let's go.
[suspenseful music]
[Viktoria] Will you please stop?
[light dramatic music]
[water rushing]
Andre, what's uh...
What's wrong with you?
Andre!
[water rushing]
[eerie music]
[suspenseful music]
Andre.
- [thudding]
- [tense music]
- [Ilya] Viktoria!
- [Christina] Viktoria.
[Ilya] Zoya!
- [Ilya and Alexey] Viktoria!
- [Ilya] Wait.
[Christina] Viktoria?
- [wood creaking]
- [water trickling]
[light dramatic music]
Zoya.
Zoya's here.
Zoya, where's Viktoria?
What happened?
- [water rushing]
- [ominous music]
[music continues]
- [wood creaking]
[music, creaking continue]
Zoya.
[eerie music]
This is her husband.
Is she the widow?
[radio beeps]
[static buzzing]
Do you copy?
Hello?
- [wood creaking]
- [ominous music]
Do you copy?
Ilya, can you hear me?
Zoya's dangerous.
Think she killed her husband.
Ilya, is she with you?
I'm in her house right now.
[suspenseful music]
Do you copy?
Ilya!
Ilya?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
[static buzzing]
[wood creaking]
- [dramatic music]
- [fire sizzling]
Zoya, what happened?
Was Viktoria with you?
Can you hear me?
Can you tell me what happened?
What did you see?
Zoya.
[man over radio]
Are you there? Do you copy?
This is
the rescue team speaking.
We're heading your way.
- [Ilya] She's speechless.
- [man] Do you copy?
Do you copy?
Can you hear me?
There's no signal.
We can't get through.
We have to get out of
this lowland.
We can't spend the night.
All my equipment went down
with the van.
Along with our phones.
[fire crackling]
[Alexey] We'll have to go back
for Andre.
[Ilya]
We will, it's marked on my map.
Pass the GoPro.
Here.
Let's see.
[tablet beeps]
Did the camera connect?
[Alexey]
Wait, it's showing two cameras.
[Ilya] That's weird.
Do you think it's Viktoria's?
Maybe it was saved
in the memory?
Maybe.
It could have.
- Let me see.
- [static buzzing]
How far does the signal reach?
Don't know, it just depends.
Alexey, come on.
Christina, stay with Zoya.
Ilya. Ilya, come on.
- I'm not staying with her.
- Someone has to stay
- and you'll slow us down.
- I said I'm not staying.
I'm telling you
I'm not staying with her.
Enough of this.
You stay on your own
or I tie you together.
Ilya!
Damn it.
[fire crackling]
[water splashing]
- [Alexey] Is it far?
- [Ilya] 200 meters north.
- [ominous music]
- [both] Viktoria!
[water splashing]
[Ilya] Viktoria!
[dramatic music]
Viktoria.
[water splashing]
[Ilya] Viktoria.
[Alexey] Viktoria!
Viktoria!
[suspenseful music]
[voice] Will you play with me?
[Ilya] What the hell?
Viktoria.
[ominous music]
Here she is.
- [dramatic music]
- [Alexey] Viktoria.
[water sloshing]
[Ilya] Viktoria.
- [water splashing]
- [dramatic music]
Don't go there.
Viktoria.
Your hand.
Give me your hand.
Come on!
Here we go, I got ya.
Hold on!
[both grunting]
Come on.
Come on!
Almost there.
Hold my hand.
[suspenseful music]
Your hand.
Oh, my God.
Come on.
Help.
- [water splashing]
- [ominous music]
Come on.
Give me your hand.
Come on!
Here we go.
[Viktoria] She had
newspaper clippings
of several missing people.
I think she killed them.
Like she killed her husband.
And I found her photo
there, too.
She's a witch.
She performs some
kind of rituals there, I saw it.
She did something to Andre.
We have to find him.
Andre's dead, we found his body.
[Ilya] Viktoria, how are
you feeling right now?
Are you feeling dizzy
or nauseated?
You don't believe me.
[Ilya] Okay.
Christina, Alex.
Go find some firewood.
I'm gonna go speak with her,
- just a quick word.
- [Christina] No, not happening.
I'm not going anywhere.
[sighs]
All right, Alexey. Let's go.
Christina, you're in charge.
[fire crackling]
I believe you.
She's going to kill us all.
Listen, do you think that
you could find that house again?
If she really is a witch
like you say,
and if we can come away with
some evidence of this,
we're gonna be famous.
[dramatic music]
Did you see her?
Where'd she go?
[Zoya] Evil spirits
lurking in the swamps
on the darkest night
of the year.
Those who bring death
to the crops
will leave us
trembling with fear.
Red sunrise and brightest day,
come and keep the evil away.
- [blowing]
- [fire sizzling]
[rustling]
[dramatic music]
What are you doing?
Are you out of your mind?
[tense music]
[Zoya]
Red sunrise and brightest day,
come keep the evil away.
- [ominous music]
- [heavy breathing]
Red sunrise and brightest day,
come keep the evil away.
come and keep the evil away.
Red sunrise and brightest day,
come and keep the evil away
come and keep the evil away.
Red sunrise and brightest day,
- [ominous music]
- Red sunrise
and brightest day...
- [blowing]
- [fire sizzling]
[suspenseful music]
- [gun clicks]
- Enough.
What did you do to Andre?
[ominous music]
The lame widow is here.
She won't let you go.
- She won't let this go.
- Answer me.
[ominous music]
She demands human sacrifice,
but she's never satisfied.
You don't understand,
I can't save souls forever.
I'm all used up.
Now it's your turn.
[dramatic music]
[breathing heavily]
Now it's your turn, Viktoria.
I'm sorry.
She gets who she wants.
The widow wants you.
[dark dramatic music]
You have to protect everyone.
It's your burden now.
[gun clicks]
- [flare sizzling]
- [Viktoria gasps]
[crying]
What did you do?
She did it herself.
It wasn't me.
[Ilya shouts]
What happened?
Who shot?
What's going on here?
What was that?
Are you crazy?
- Who shot her?
- What do you mean?
It was her.
She did it herself.
I don't understand it.
- Just now right before us...
- Put the camera away!
A rescuer...
A rescuer committed murder.
[breathing shakily]
How does it feel to kill
a helpless old woman?
Or should I say kill two people?
- [both grunting]
- [thudding]
Calm down!
- Enough!
- [indistinct shouting]
- Calm down!
- You don't understand!
[Christina]
We're all going to die here!
We're going to die!
[sobbing]
The widow won't let us escape.
We're going to die here.
[ominous music]
The widow won't let us escape!
No.
- Calm down.
- Don't tie me to her.
Okay, calm down.
I'm telling you. Sit!
[fire crackling]
Alexey, I didn't do it.
You just need to check
the footage.
[Alexey]
Ilya, what are we gonna do?
Bring it over here.
Thank you.
[Alexey] Here you go.
[Ilya] We'll watch it
on the tablet.
Uh-huh.
- [Christina crying]
- [fire crackling]
Damn it.
Shit.
It's not working.
- What's the problem?
- It won't read the card.
Sorry, Viktoria.
The card's unreadable.
Alexey,
do you have another card?
Let's see if the tablet's
the problem.
[Alexey] No, I don't have one.
Oh, I forgot.
[Ilya]
Where did you get that phone?
[Alexey] I found it in the hole,
remember?
[Ilya] Oh, yeah?
[Alexey]
Let's see if this card works.
There.
[tablet dings]
- Oh, this one works.
- [Alexey] Let's open it.
Hey, everyone.
It's gotten pretty late now.
I'm not sure if
we should turn back or not.
Let's ask
my brother's special friend.
[bear] Will you play with me?
[little boy] I think we should
go back home now.
Wait, did you hear that?
A sound from over there.
We'll check it out.
[little boy]
Wait for me. Nikita!
[Nikita] Are you scared?
[gasps] Nikita?
[little boy] We're explorers
and we've been following
these strange symbols.
Sura will be the first
to be eaten
because he's just
a bite-sized snack.
[Sura]
Oh, you're a big tough guy.
Without me
you'd be a scaredy cat.
What the hell?
Wait here.
I see a light.
What is it?
[Nikita] Be quiet.
Hide your flashlight.
And return to the dead water,
back to your pit.
I stand before you in the flesh
just as you were
on that night so long ago.
Cover yourself in straw,
let it keep you warm.
Spare me, lame widow.
- [Viktoria] That's Zoya.
- Please turn into the living
and take my gift instead.
Please accept my offerings.
Leave us in peace.
Enter the straw figures
and spare the living,
- for at sunrise...
- [bear] Will you play with me?
[fire roaring]
- [Zoya screams]
- [dramatic music]
[Sura screaming]
[Nikita] Sura!
- [Sura screams]
- [dramatic music]
[ground rustling]
[thudding]
[ominous music]
[Viktoria]
Red sunrise and brightest day,
come and keep the evil away.
She was protecting us.
[Ilya] But from what?
- [radio beeps]
- [man] What's your status?
We're at the meeting point.
Please respond.
All right, to the meeting point.
Alexey, light the flare.
Let's go.
[ominous music]
[flare sizzling]
[dramatic music]
[music continues]
[Alexey panting]
[ominous music]
No.
We're walking in circles.
We've been here before.
[screeching]
[tree creaking]
Red sunrise and brightest day,
come and keep the evil away.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Red sunrise and brightest day,
come and keep the evil away.
[Viktoria gasps]
- [thudding]
- [Alexey screams]
[dramatic music]
[all screaming]
[growling]
[dramatic music]
[panting]
- [thudding]
- [Christina whimpering]
- [wood creaking]
- [Christina groaning]
[Ilya] Come on, stand up.
You okay?
[Christina groans]
All right.
Look!
- [Christina gasping]
- [ominous music]
[trees creaking]
[music continues]
[light dramatic music]
[Christina whimpers]
[chain clinking]
What are the stakes for?
It's a trap to hold something.
We're in the pit, aren't we?
[music continues]
Where the widow was buried.
[man over radio] Do you copy?
- The rescue team is here.
- [Ilya] There's no escape.
- Are you there?
- Ilya?
- No escape.
- Ilya, don't do this.
- [Viktoria] Ilya, answer.
- No escape.
- Answer them!
No escape, no escape.
- Ilya, please don't do this.
- No escape.
[Christina]
Please, hello, can you hear us?
- Come save us, please.
- No escape, no escape.
- [Christina sobbing]
- No escape.
No escape, no escape.
No escape.
[dramatic music]
This is the end.
I'm not worried, I'll just die.
But she wants one of you.
Death is such a great mercy.
[whimpering]
We can't help him now.
[Ilya] She heard us.
Way too loud.
She heard us.
She heard us, she heard us,
she heard us, she heard us.
[Christina whimpers]
[Ilya] Here, here, here.
[dramatic music]
Right here.
Here, here.
[breathing heavily]
[whimpering]
[leaves rustling]
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- [wind howling]
- [trees creaking]
- [screaming]
- [dramatic music]
[Viktoria screams]
[both panting]
[suspenseful music]
- [Viktoria] Get up.
- I can't.
[leaves rustling]
- Get up!
- [Christina] I can't.
[sobbing]
Get up.
Do you hear me? Listen to me.
Listen to me!
- [rustling]
- [growling]
[Viktoria whimpers]
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
[screeching]
- [thudding]
- [both screaming]
[knife rustling]
[screeching]
[Viktoria screams]
[Christina cries]
No, no.
[bear] I'll be your friend.
- [light sizzles]
- [Christina gasps]
[breathing heavily]
[flare sizzling]
[ominous music]
[whimpers]
[sobs]
[gasping]
[music continues]
Viktoria.
- [squishing]
- [Christina whimpering]
[dramatic music]
Viktoria.
[liquid trickling]
[sirens wailing]
- [light dramatic music]
- [machines beeping]
[air hissing]
[water rushing]
[Viktoria] I promise, my lady,
to keep you warm.
We shall not do the living harm
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
as long as I live in sacrifice
you must spare
the other's lives.
I will give you my every breath,
upon my release,
you grant me death.
Red sunrise and brightest day,
I will serve you any way.
[dark dramatic music]
[dramatic music]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[tense music]
[dramatic music]