"To digest natural happiness,
as well as artificial happiness,
you must first have the
courage to swallow it."
"Dump it and I'll kill you."
Hi.
- Hi.
- The water's great.
Come here often?
I never saw you.
Pretty girls are--
Can you get my chair?
- That thing?
- Yes.
Thanks.
So?
Pretty girls are what?
I'm Eva Roussel.
I'm paraplegic.
My message to the next one.
If you're watching,
you've had an Advent calendar.
Above all, follow the rules.
THE CALENDAR
If you don't, you'll die.
Look out!
THURSDAY, DECEMBER 3rd
Eva!
Yeah, come in!
Your November figures are bad.
- I worked like usual.
- OK, but do better.
You sell cheap family insurance!
All we do is pay out on it.
Buck up.
I had to shell out for you.
- You get a grant.
- Not enough.
A new crapper cost a bomb.
- Hello.
- Hello, Agnès, it's Eva.
- How's my father?
- He's well.
- Could you put him on?
- Why?
It's my birthday.
I'd like to chat.
Your father has forgotten you.
How can he remember your birthday?
I have to go.
I have things to do.
Let me in, I'm freezing!
Surprise!
You're here?
Aren't you in Germany till Xmas?
Time off for your birthday.
German cake...
Champagne...
from Germany.
And...
A German present.
Happy birthday.
Hope you like it.
An Advent calendar?
- Like it?
- I love it.
A surprise a day till Xmas.
Where's it from?
The Munich Xmas market.
Meaning?
"The miracle of Christmas".
Dump it and I'll kill you.
It says so on the back.
Who's "I"?
"Ich".
Who's "Ich"?
Dump it and you'll see.
Give it to me.
"Rule number 1.
The calendar contains candy.
If you eat one, eat them all.
Or I'll kill you.
Rule number 2.
Respect all rules
until you open the last door.
Or I'll kill you.
Rule number 3.
Dump it and I'll kill you."
Sounds grim.
Germans are grim.
Careful.
Eat one, you have to eat them all.
Did you put this in it?
No. Why?
It was my dad's favourite.
Go on, eat it.
Maybe your dad will eat one too
and the chocolate will connect you.
I can't understand.
"To cure hurt,
destroy what hurt you."
No cheating!
Wait until midnight.
OK, but it's jammed.
Let me see.
Yeah.
Kaput.
We're naked in bed.
I'm waiting for him to go.
But he gives me an odd look.
We'd just met.
I don't know his name.
Karl, Klaus...
Something like that.
He's about to talk crap
like, "Ich liebe dich."
But then, the guy takes my hand
and says--
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
"Es ist Mitternight"?
Meaning?
"Midnight is here here.
Open the door."
"Jesus said to the cripple,
'Arise and walk.'"
I'm sorry.
It's late.
I start early.
- We never talk about it.
- I don't want to.
Not now, please.
Alright.
Eva?
Dad?
Happy birthday.
Eva!
Meet Ms. Lemaire.
Hi.
Hello.
She'll take some of your clients
to train with.
Once she's ready,
she'll find new ones.
- And I get mine back?
- We'll see.
For me, a client's a client.
We need turnover.
You or Myriam.
- Ms. Lemaire.
- Myriam is OK.
That's all.
Go and make some money.
I think you're really brave.
I couldn't.
What?
Work in that state.
What state?
Well, that.
I couldn't.
I wanted to ask...
Do you mind if we swap from Monday?
Swap desks?
- Yours is by the window.
- And?
- As you'll only work mornings...
- What?
John didn't tell you?
Want to have dinner with a buddy?
- I'll be in the way.
- You won't.
- Well?
- Do I know him?
No, his name's Boris.
A dumb trader,
but he'll buy dinner.
About that chocolate...
It connected me to Dad.
It did?
Yeah.
I ate it and he called me.
It's weird. Dad has Alzheimer's,
he's forgotten me,
and called on a disconnected phone.
Taking your anti-hallucination pills?
Yeah. It wasn't a hallucination.
Maybe it was an E or something.
Think so?
A druggy Advent calendar.
A high a day until Xmas.
You wanted your dad to call
and he did.
What did the vendor tell you?
We didn't talk much.
- I stole it.
- What?
Ready?
Let's eat.
Stop eating them if it spooks you.
It doesn't.
I was glad to hear my dad.
Hey, Soso! Over here!
Hi there.
- You're Eva, right?
- Yes.
I brought a buddy too.
No threesomes that way.
Thomas, Sophie... Eva...
And I'm Boris.
Careful, girls.
Thomas is an ace hunter.
When he sees two does...
OK, some bubbly! Champagne!
He needs a reason
to make you work part-time.
Handicapped is reason enough.
Right?
That's a dumb comment.
Just asking.
So, are you really a hunter or
was Boris being tactless again?
Pretty tactless.
But I do hunt now and then.
See, I was right.
But you were tactless.
I've never hunted.
I'd like to try.
I have a place in the country.
We can go one weekend.
- Even with your chair.
- I'd like that.
One last drink? I'm parched.
Not for me.
I'll go, it's late.
Oh, right. I'll pay then.
- I'm sorry.
- It's OK.
Thanks for stepping in.
- What do you think?
- About who?
The hunter. He's a hunk.
He's nice.
Be right back.
He wants to have a drink.
Now?
Alone.
That's kind but...
I'm already sleepy.
Not with you, with me.
Congratulations.
My Trader Online
has made you 457 euros.
- Know My Trader Online?
- No.
It's great. Install the app
and win on the stock market.
I'll send a link to connect
your phone to your bank.
I've no money for that.
I'll give you the 457 I just made.
Keep it and take me home.
You can keep your eyes closed.
- What?
- You like it, huh?
What is this? Stop!
What's up with you?
You said nothing so far.
I said nothing
cos I feel nothing, asshole!
- I'm paraplegic, get it?
- What?
Touch me
or poke your trader dick in me,
I feel nothing!
I thought you were playing along!
Can you feel with your mouth?
Shit, you've turned me on.
Come here!
Come here, I said.
Come on!
Cut that out!
Fuck!
Fucking cut it out! Come here!
Drop dead!
What is this shit?
Fuck!
It's me.
Heard about Boris?
No, what is it?
He crashed his car.
They found him crushed inside.
What?
Where are you?
Drop dead!
- In the park.
- I'll be right there.
SORRY IT WAS AN ACCIDENT
I get a message after he died?
Isn't that weird?
No, it happens all the time.
One guy got my text dumping him
two days late.
Very awkward.
OK.
- What's My Trader Online?
- Screw that.
- You clicked on the link?
- No.
Go talk to him.
To say what?
Something nice.
"Hi, I'm Eva..."
"I'm paraplegic.
If you're a nurse,
you can wash my private parts."
Congratulations,
your account is active.
457 euros.
I have to go.
Back to Munich?
- When'll you be back?
- In two weeks.
Want a ride home?
No.
I'll stay a while.
Take care.
Want to invest?
My Trader Online can help.
To sell or buy shares, pick a brand.
Hurry. One minute already
without investing.
To sell or buy shares, pick a brand.
Hello.
Mulled wine.
- OK.
- Thank you.
And for you?
- The same as him.
- Two mulled wines.
Is this free?
May I sit down?
I'm William, and you?
Eva.
I won't stay long.
I'm on duty soon.
On duty?
I'm a nurse.
You're paraplegic, I'm a nurse,
I can wash your private parts.
Shit...
Sorry, why did I say that?
I couldn't stop myself.
May I sit?
Were you a pro or was it a hobby?
A pro.
I've danced since I was six.
I mean, I danced.
Closing time.
Can I drop you on my way to work?
You don't know where I live.
True, but it's on my way.
OK, you can have it.
What?
You wanted my number?
- No.
- OK, since you insist.
In theory, this is when
you give me yours.
MONDAY THE 7th
Four days without investing.
My Trader Online can help you.
15 MISSED CALLS
12 NEW MESSAGES
Are you serious?
You take four days off,
then turn up here all innocent?
I didn't take time off.
THURSDAY, DECEMBER 10th
I took some stuff and...
Get the hell out.
Myriam can manage.
I pretended you were normal.
But, to be frank, you're just
a half-chick on wheels.
Hello?
What is it?
Perhaps drugs
that cause hallucinations.
Such as?
Depends on the candy.
My dad called for my birthday.
I slept for 24 hours.
I slept.
I slept for four days
or I was awake for four days,
who knows.
Time flew by.
Stop taking this crap.
What did this one do?
Nothing.
Nothing?
I really need to sleep.
OK.
Call me when you want to.
You've finally chosen to invest!
Which shares will you buy?
Congratulations!
Your sound investment earns you...
9 cents.
Tonight, leave me in peace.
Marvin...
Congratulations.
My Trader Online
has made you 118 euros.
Congratulations.
My Trader Online
has made you 145 euros.
Congratulations.
My Trader Online
has made you 223 euros.
- Marvin!
- Total profit:
486 euros.
Marvin!
John...
John Antonich insurance.
I'm busy right now.
Please call back later.
Rule number 1.
The calendar contains candy.
If you eat one, eat them all.
Or I'll kill you.
Rule number 2.
Respect all rules
until you open the last door.
Or I'll kill you.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Rule number 3.
Dump it and I'll kill you.
RULES
Eva. Happy birthday.
Drop dead!
What did this one do?
Nothing.
MARVIN KILLS JOHN
Jesus said to the cripple,
"Arise and walk."
Why am I here?
Don't you remember?
You were outside your house,
gripping your calendar
and refusing to let go.
- Outside my house?
- Yes.
Lying on the street.
How did you get there?
Were you alone?
Did someone attack you?
I don't know.
We'll keep you under observation.
If everything's OK,
you'll leave tomorrow.
Deliver me from evil.
I walked.
Our Father in heaven,
hallowed be your name,
your kingdom come,
your will be done,
on earth as in heaven.
Give us today our daily bread.
Forgive us our sins
as we forgive those
who sin against us.
Lead us not into temptation,
but deliver us from evil.
Deliver me from evil.
Eva...
I WALKED
Congratulations,
you have made 14,014 euros.
You're selling Dad's house?
Legally, it's mine too, as his wife.
- What about him?
- I'll find a rest home.
He's not choosy.
He's in his chair all day.
Him too.
I won't offer you a drink,
you won't stay long.
Eva...
I called you for your birthday.
I know.
I'm glad you're here.
I miss you so much.
I miss you too.
And your mother.
I miss her.
If only you could help me join her.
Your calendar will demand
other sacrifices.
Others will have to die.
Strangers...
Friends...
Those you love...
It's the price to pay.
If you want to walk, you have to kill.
When my time comes...
don't hesitate.
If you refuse, you'll be sacrificed.
This is Eva.
Leave a message.
It's me.
- Just checking up on you.
- I'm fine.
Why're you here?
I took two like that.
And?
I walked to the street.
- Eva...
- You don't have to believe me.
I just want you to be here.
You'll take this one too?
Yes.
What'll happen?
I don't know.
That's why I'm here.
OK.
You okay?
Eva?
Eva...
I can feel you.
Your hand on my thigh...
I can feel it.
I can feel you.
Shit.
Hi there.
Let me know when you finish.
I'll get your chair.
- Thanks.
- No worries.
See you later.
This is Eva.
Leave a message.
It's me.
You left your keys in my car.
I'll put them in the pot by the door.
A pretty common hiding place,
but better than above the door.
Bye.
Sorry, why did I say that?
I couldn't stop myself.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
TI PMUD T'NOD
It's Antoine from the pool.
- Anyone home?
- What do you want?
I don't know how you left,
with your things still at the pool.
Your address was in the bag,
so I brought your chair back.
OK, I'll leave you my number.
If you need anything, anything at all.
Everything OK?
Go or I'll set the dog on you!
And close the gate.
William.
Eva?
Are you OK?
She killed her dog.
You're sleeping here?
I know, it sucks.
But I can't leave her.
Our weekend's off then?
I don't know.
How big is the place?
There's room for her.
That's cool.
I'll let her sleep
and we'll come tomorrow.
- You opened it?
- Yeah.
What was inside?
Some chewing gum.
Hand it over.
Hand it over!
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
Still nothing.
That's awesome!
The Metropolitan?
They confirmed it?
No more auditions?
Any guys on the jury?
I bet your sexy tutu caught their eye.
You were mad I left for Germany,
but I have to go to New York
to see you.
Let's immortalize the moment.
Look out.
Well?
What was the candy?
A memory.
Good or bad?
Bad.
You'll be OK?
Yeah.
I don't blame her.
I don't want her hurt.
Had a good night?
Where's my dog?
He was cremated.
That's good.
I don't blame you.
I don't want you hurt.
Can we talk?
After three years,
it's time we talked.
He's not here.
Who?
Ich.
He's not in his box.
That calendar will drive you crazy.
No.
It'll give me my legs back.
Every day, I blame myself.
I'm what hurt you.
What hurt me...
- Get out of here.
- What?
Leave, it's dangerous.
You hurt me.
If I eat this, he'll destroy you.
If he does, will you walk?
Yes.
Then eat it.
Go on.
Look after it.
Give it to me tomorrow.
I'll eat it at home, alone.
OK.
I don't blame her.
I don't want her hurt.
Everything OK?
She's feeling paranoid.
She wants to leave tomorrow.
What's that?
A baby Jesus.
Don't eat it or I'll die.
And your baby Jesus?
Is he dangerous?
Stop.
- It's no use.
- What?
She's next door. I can't.
She's asleep.
Maybe, but I can't.
- What is it?
- What do you think?
Super erection.
Open wide.
We're back in business.
I don't want her hurt.
I don't blame her.
I don't want...
Thomas!
Sophie?
Sophie, what's going on?
I need to see Aloïs Hoffmann.
I'm Aloïs Hoffman.
What do you want?
- It's about your painting.
- What painting?
I've done hundreds.
The one from last year.
Is this a joke?
I couldn't have painted it last year.
I've been blind for five years.
Follow me.
Give me the painting.
I didn't paint this horror, miss.
My wife and son are well.
Why would I paint them dead?
Because they were dead then.
It's a message for the next one.
You had to sacrifice them.
Get out of my home.
Love, Eva
It's my turn.
You had to sacrifice her too?
No.
She was for fun.
You're not paralysed anymore?
I'm over it.
Cool.
So,
after you eat the last candy,
things rewind and you forget?
Like the painter?
Yeah.
I'll wake on December 1st.
Paraplegic.
You'll forget what we did?
It won't have happened.
Why did you bring me here?
In 10 minutes, my body will be no use.
I wanted to enjoy it while I could.
I'm Eva Roussel.
I'm paraplegic.
My message to the next one.
If you're watching this,
you've had an Advent calendar.
Above all, follow the rules.
If you don't, you'll die.
The calendar will demand sacrifices.
Obey.
If you refuse, you'll be sacrificed.
If you die before the 24th,
all deaths will be final, yours too.
MY MESSAGE FOR THE NEXT ONE
Wait!
Not the last one.
If I don't eat it, I'll die.
- That's the first rule.
- OK.
Rule 2 says to respect all rules
until you open the last door.
You opened it. No more rules.
Do as you want.
What now?
Rule number 3.
Dump it and I'll kill you.
Stop!
No more rules!
It's over! Do as you want.
You have a choice.
Eat it and wake on December 1st
in your chair.
Or dump it and wake tomorrow in shape.
Cool, huh?
The dead stay dead, but you'll walk.
Happy birthday.
Who's "Ich"?
Dump it and you'll see.
I'm William.
Half-chick on wheels.
- Stop eating this crap.
- You'll go crazy.
- It'll give me my legs back.
- Others will have to die.
I can feel you.
It's the price to pay.
ONE YEAR LATER
I'm Eva Roussel.
I'm paraplegic.
My message to the next one.
If you're watching this,
you've had an Advent calendar.
Above all, follow the rules.
If you don't, you'll die.