When you go
to the haunted house
at Camden Park...
You don't know
what will happen.
Camden Park!
National Retail Federation
does a poll
and they say
21% of the people,
that's 30
million people a year,
are gonna go to
haunted houses.
For a actor
in a haunted house
there is no bigger rush
than getting a great scare.
And it could be the biggest,
baddest guy in class
that comes through
that you give that to.
One year,
I think they had, like,
close to 1,200 scare-outs,
where people walk in the door
and halfway through
they said,
"I can't do this anymore,
I'm out, I want out."
Oh...!
- I love Halloween.
- Really?
If I can get you to scream,
then I feel great.
Yeah, I've heard rumors of
people doing things like that.
Yeah.
- Supposedly hiring,
you know, actual...
You know, murderers
or something to work
in their haunts.
Things like that,
it's all talk sometimes.
There really is.
I'll show you.
Inside the house,
there's real human remains
inside the haunted house.
Some of the actors
that we have are,
they're pretty far out there.
Would it surprise me
if something happened?
No.
A Missouri house of horror
became a reality.
Police report
that a 17-year-old employee...
The owner said customers
walked by her thinking
it was part of the show.
I do not want you
all filming in here.
Tonight a 28-year-old
registered sex-offender
was arrested
at his work place,
a Halloween haunted house.
There was a scare
actor that was employed,
slashed his
whole damn family...
Father and mother and sister,
in real life.
Get her in the trunk.
This place is great.
- Dude!
- What's up, man?
Good to see you.
Hi!
What's up, brother?
How you all been?
- Bobby?
- Yes.
Mike,
You've already taken over?
How do you feel that I...
How do you drop five
minutes in the trip?
How do you
feel about me being
the better looking brother?
- Zack?
- Yo.
- What's up?
- If he's with us on this trip
I will kill myself.
Tell me about yourself
and what are we doing?
Zack, I'm talking to you.
I think
she's transfixed by Jeff.
You want my name?
My name is Zack.
You've known me
for 20 years, Mikey.
We've rented an RV.
We're going across...
Well, the point is
I want to find the most
extreme haunted house
in the world.
Lady's gonna teach
him how to line dance.
- Congratu-fucking-lations.
- Hey, hey, hey.
Tell me
about you, Brandy.
- Uh...
My name is Brandy
Catherine Shaefer.
Jeffery Bernard Larson.
Remember that.
All right, Bobby.
You're my big brother.
I'm the one who
went to film school,
so I deserve to carry
this camera for a bit.
- You didn't graduate.
Did you?
This is
where I wanna go.
Yeah, but this
is just a clip of a girl
being strapped.
Did you watch the video?
No.
You're not gonna like it.
I'm pretty sure
it's not that scary
if it's on the World Wide Web.
Mike,
so you're down now?
Yeah, I'm in, man,
like they said there...
I've heard people talk
about the ones
that in New York,
they zip tie you to a chair...
Stop it.
Bags over the head,
that kind of thing.
That's a different story.
It's just like the movies,
it's like...
It's the same thing.
It's changed.
Jaycees haunted
house is in the '60s.
You walk around and guys
jumped out and said, "Boo."
That doesn't cut it anymore.
When you were little,
going through haunted houses
you didn't know if it
was real or not, right?
That element,
what that feels like,
I wanna find it again.
Be on time to the RV.
Everyone's looking at Mikey.
I was staring in
this direction.
Be on time.
All right. Cheers!
Happy Halloween!
First night to
the haunted house.
Put me down.
What are you guys up to?
We're going to
as many houses as we can
all across America.
Where
the hell did you get that?
Motherfucker!
Is there anything
that's even scared you?
I remember a haunt
I went to probably
three, four years ago.
There was a guy on the floor,
he was munching
his teeth at me.
And I looked at him
and he had
entrails behind him.
So he was a paraplegic
they hired.
He was real fast on his hands
and I thought
that was the most
scariest thing I've ever seen.
So how do you find people?
A lot of people
are word of mouth
and a lot of people
have worked for us
for many years,
and they bring their friends
and then we also put
ads in the Greensheet
and the local newspapers.
And we try to
recruit that way too.
Do you do
like a background check
on people?
You know currently we
do not do a background check.
But we're looking into
doing that in future.
- Fuck, bro!
- Come on man.
What the fuck
are you doing here?
Why didn't you just call me?
What are you doing here?
I went out last night.
Had a good time.
Then I came here on time.
You've never been on time
for a fucking thing
in your life.
Now I'm on time
'cause I was
here hours before.
Just be quiet.
Why do I need to be quiet?
I need you serious,
from here on out.
Gonna be serious from...
In about a minute from now.
Why in a minute?
Say hi.
- Hi.
High-five?
Why is it upside down now?
Flip it.
We gotta get some
fucking food, man.
I want coffee.
- Morning.
Ladies.
What's up, son?
- Hi!
- Haunted houses.
How are you
already here?
You told the bartender,
the cab driver,
the guy behind the hotel...
We're all going on
a road trip. Who cares?
Yeah. Road trip.
And then, dude, and then
you got a fucking pumpkin
and tried to stick
your dick in it.
Yeah. You did
a little American Pie,
Halloween's style.
Zack, I want to be
there to help you out
on this situation but you did.
- I'm sorry, I have rolling...
- Zack's version...
But I doubt that I did that.
Yo pumpkin pie.
How're you feeling today?
Like angels and sunbeams
and unicorns.
- You look it.
Just check it out.
I got part of the fridge
that's just gonna be
Jeff's healthy stuff.
All right,
so you guys know.
You're an idiot.
I will eat of your healthy
stuff for the whole trip
in one night after drinking.
Why do you need
seven cameras?
Why? 'Cause I
wanna document it all.
You ready to go?
All right, let's go to it.
All right team on three. Boom!
- Jeff, Jeff.
- What?
You're never
ever gonna get laid
if you do things like that.
- You excited?
I'm excited.
These are always...
I never know what
I'm getting myself into
when we start off,
but I always have
a good time by the end of it.
So I'm definitely excited.
Zack said you
were a little nervous.
I know I tend to be jumpy
as a person, so...
Couple that with
the fact that I haven't
been to a haunted house
in probably...
I don't even
know how many years,
since I was eight or nine.
I kinda don't really
know how I'm gonna react
or what it's
gonna be like or...
I think haunts
have come a long way.
...since you were
eight or nine years old.
See, as long as you
give me that in the houses,
we're good.
Why don't you
tell us more about
your little kid experience
going through a haunted house.
Um... Well,
I assaulted a scare actor,
when I was a child.
Guy jumps down from a tree
and I'm so petrified,
I don't...
My bodily reaction is just
to punch him in the gut.
When the lights
are going like this
and you're so disoriented,
the guy actually it
seemed like he jumped
straight back up into the tree
almost like he had like a...
Seven foot vertical.
Probably 'cause I was
like 3'7" at the time.
I'm assuming
they've come a long way
since we were kids.
Well, I mean,
I should hope so.
'Cause I like the only
haunts I've ever been to
are the ones at theme parks
or something like that,
where the scariest thing is
somebody running up to you
while you're waiting in line
for a hotdog or something.
I promise you they're
not gonna be like that.
All right.
We're gonna be
out in the country,
there's gonna be no rules,
o regulations.
- Mmm-hmm.
I don't know how this
sounds like a good thing.
This is always
what you wish.
There's gonna be no rules,
no regulations.
You don't even know
where we're going.
I'm feeling kinda bad
for all these bugs
on the windshield.
You're a pacifist for bugs?
I felt bad 'cause there were
a few butterflies that
hit the windshield too.
I'd like to
know where we're...
Settle down.
I've got something
planned for everyone.
You have it all planned out.
You know exactly
where we're going?
I know exactly
where we're going.
Let's get directions.
No way he's guiding
this fucking ship.
It's not organic.
I'm still
making pancakes so...
This thing is sweet,
I don't know why.
Paddle.
Hey, man, do you know how
to get to the haunt house?
Are you all sure
you wanna go there?
Mikey,
stop screwing around.
- We can't find the exit.
- We're just lost.
Yeah? All right.
You go down the road
right here about five miles.
- It'll be in the forest
on the left hand side.
Mike, let's go.
- I want this.
- You're not buying that.
- Thank you so much.
- Let's go.
Hey, guys, we got...
- You know where it is?
- Yeah.
It's five miles
up the road.
Getting
antsy over there, Jeff?
No, I'm just, you know,
jumping to my own beat.
You know?
Just jump...
Jumpin' to my beat.
- You know,
I hope everyone...
- Jumping to his own beat.
I might just
rap for you later.
One celebratory
shot on the road.
That's what last night was.
Yeah, but now we're like
"on the road", on the road.
I'll drink if Jeff does.
Air shots?
Dude you look like
you're jerking off
an elephant.
Jeff,
I heard that you have a poem.
The... Oh, the poem.
I don't know
if he can read it.
I can't read it while I'm...
I can read the poem.
I wanna read it.
I haven't read it.
"I am poem."
I gotta listen to this.
"I am Job."
You hear that,
the first line.
"I'm a swell guy
who eats strawberries.
"I wonder if demons
even inhabited the earth.
"I hear angels crying in my
"brain?"
"In my barn."
- "Barn."
In my what?
"I touched the roughness...
"The roughness
of Bigfoot's arm."
No transition,
nothing.
Mikey, it's called art.
I'm so excited.
This is the first night.
These haunt owners
have forums, chat rooms.
They put up these pictures.
Dude, there's some crazy shit
that goes on there.
You're in,
you could park up there.
Are you the sheriff
of the town?
- Am I?
- Yeah.
No, I'm just security.
Oh, okay, okay.
I wish I was sheriff.
Awesome.
Hello!
- Cool.
- Haunt house.
Let's do it.
Let's get scared.
You didn't do that.
I will finally make you
get in a coffin, look.
Let me the fuck out of here!
You're such a dick.
You know I'm claustrophobic.
We can go in now?
You coming?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Shit! Didn't even
get in the door yet.
Got you.
Mikey?
I can't see shit.
- Bobby?
What the fuck?
Where the hell are we?
Even the music is creepy.
So weird.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What the fuck?
Come play with me.
Follow her.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Get the fuck down!
Fuck!
You wanna be
a pretty doll like me?
Oh, shit!
What was that?
Bobby, don't go over there.
- Ashes!
- What is going on?
Ashes!
We all fall down!
Get the fuck out of here!
Come back here.
I'm not done with you yet.
They just love to run you
out of those places
with chainsaws.
Bob, did you like it?
I don't give
a shit about this place.
I wanna talk to these people.
What's goin' on?
How are you?
Pretty good.
Uh, do you care if we
ask you some questions?
Sure.
So my friend here
thinks that, uh,
shady shit goes on
in these places.
What do you think?
I can probably say
I agree with that.
I would think it just
be fun to work here.
It is fun. It's interesting.
It's definitely different.
How so?
Bob, Bob, Bob,
let's go on the roof.
There's a ladder
right over there.
You will never
be able to get
on the roof.
We can film over like that.
There's a ladder
at the back.
Okay.
Mikey,
when you get up there,
- do the fucking
Almost Famousthing.
- What is that?
Stop being
so fucking paranoid.
--Oh, shit!
There's a shit ton
of people down there, man.
Happy Halloween, guys! Yay!
Whoo! Whoo!
They're not
fucking happy, Mike.
Go.
Get out of here. Go, go.
- Mikey?
- What?
Be quiet...
Mikey, let's go. Now!
Take your hoodie off, son.
Take your hoodie off.
- Where ya goin', boy?
Well it's
the first night and you've
already pissed off
all the haunt workers.
So good one, guys.
What's the scariest part?
I mean creepy guy one,
creepy girl two...
I like the bush,
like the...
There was this weird part,
where we had to wait
because people would be...
Mike,
are you sleeping already?
Before you went
through the back...
The guy was in camo,
and he jumped
out of the rose bush...
I need you to
show me the side...
Mike,
that's that clown.
Bobby, what are you
talking about?
Dude tried
to break my camera.
He seems really pissed.
Can we just go?
This guy is weirding me out.
Am I good on that side?
Can I?
- Get the fuck
outta here.
Did you all here that?
Shit!
What the fuck?
Hello?
- Shit!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Jesus!
- Jesus!
You fucking kidding me?
You asshole.
- You literally
shit in your pants.
Come on, man.
Oh, my God! I wish the camera
could have seen you face.
- I'm too overweight for this.
- I'm gonna have a heart attack.
How far will you go
to scare people?
Uh...
Perhaps to the point of...
They won't let us
touch 'em or bash 'em over
the head and drag
'em off anywhere,
so I have to kinda
stop at that point.
I heard of, uh,
a  in New Orleans
doing a lot of weird
crazy stuff but,
I have never been to
one that really does that.
Thank goodness!
That's invading my
territorial bubble.
I tend to freak out if
you try to tie me up.
I grew up with three sisters.
They always tied me up
and did things to me
and I don't...
Yeah, I don't... Yeah.
No, I wouldn't go for that.
No, not completely naked...
I have, like, you know,
a little bathing suit on
and whatever,
and the whole rest
of my body was blue.
I had weird ears and a tail
and everything like that.
Most Zack's ever done is
done a white
sheet over his head
and two black holes.
Wasn't he like
a muscle man one year?
I highly doubt it.
I was the Shake Weight.
That's what he was,
he was a Shake Weight.
The Shake Weight guy.
Don't ever do that again.
So gross.
Okay.
Okay, I'm just
reading this tweet, okay.
"They say penis size
is related to shoe size,
"which makes
the fear of being raped
by a clown that much scarier."
Give me some of those.
I will trade you...
...my chocolate
- for one of these.
Bro,
look at your eyes.
I can't help it.
I gotta take a piss.
But there's a fucking
lineup for the bathroom.
Now I'm residual high.
From your cigarettes.
- I like that trade.
Right. When do you
think you're gonna
tell us where we're going?
It's gonna be a shit show
when we go on
this haunt tonight.
It's all his fault.
I didn't know you
couldn't handle smoking weed.
Oh, my God!
He is still crying.
You really
think it's a good idea
for you walk through
any of these haunts?
I've got a few hours.
Yeah, fucked up?
You're gonna be a train wreck.
It's his fault.
I don't care
whose fault it is,
we've got to be
there in two hours.
This place is very creepy.
I'm scared, you're scared,
we're all scared.
And then we can get...
You sound like,
"You scream, I scream,
we all scream for ice cream."
You have any?
Brandy,
what are you most afraid of?
- I have a fear of snakes.
- Me too.
I guarantee you
snakes are...
I hate 'em.
They don't move right.
They're just unnatural.
I'm not a fan at all.
I met a chick once and when
we came back to her place,
and she had a fucking python,
like, as a pet.
And she just pulled it out.
She'd come home drunk
and pulled it...
I'm like, "Ahh!
"This is never gonna work."
I'm gonna put you
in a coffin and then
put snakes in the coffin,
would you do it?
No, absolutely not.
I will not...
How much would
we have to pay you?
For $1,000 would you
get in the coffin?
For $5,000 I would.
Coffin,
cut a hole at the bottom
and send snakes through it.
Are they poisonous?
Can you guarantee
they're not poisonous?
Yes, they're poisonous.
These are
big boy seats.
Bobby what was that thing
you were just saying about me
just a couple of minutes ago?
I don't recall.
Well, I'll just lead you in
and remind you...
- We're lucky to have you
- ...and refresh your memory.
We're lucky to have you.
Yeah,
say that one more time.
Hold on.
- Brandy, we're...
- Hold on.
And... Go!
Brandy, we're lucky
to have you here.
Yeah, that's right.
How do you feel
about that, Mike?
About what?
I wouldn't call you
a sister I never had.
Just in case we
ever get naked.
Already had her.
- Already had her.
- Never gonna happen.
We made out on a roof top,
kind of one time
when we were 16.
There was
actually no making out.
We didn't make out,
it was just like heavy
petting. It was weird.
Zack, is there
like a trailer for this haunt?
Like, did they
make a commercial?
Yeah I was
trying to show Brandy
but she just freaked out.
Why don't any
of these haunts
make commercials?
I don't see commercials do ya?
Asshole!
Are you
fucking kidding me?
We're gonna be in the...
Driving the scares in
the zombie paint ball.
Jeff, did you hear that?
It's gonna be awesome.
Can't wait.
Now, do the zombies have guns?
Are we out in
the forest paint balling?
I don't know...
Have you ever seen
a zombie shoot a gun?
No, I've never seen...
Has it ever happened
in cinema history?
No, but... I don't know.
Are they gonna
shoot back at us though?
All head shots,
right, Jeff?
Zombie 101.
Hey, we have time.
You guys wanna pull over
and have drinks first?
All alone now.
Nature.
Somebody was
here before us.
Yeah.
Yeah, they said it was
okay to camp over here.
I mean,
it just went out.
- Got any wood?
- Not a big camper...
Were you a Brownie?
- Yep.
- I ate a brownie once.
Really?
How do you know...
That's a beautiful fire.
Have you ever
camped in your life?
Nope,
not when I stay at Motel 6.
Hey, more beer.
That's not
why I'm on this trip.
We don't have marshmallows?
No.
No, it's for you.
Drink it, drink it.
Drink it, Bran.
Don't waste it.
Yuck!
It was just the foam,
that's so gross.
So this is a rap
I wrote this morning.
"Livin' in a barn
is the life for me.
"Green hill farm
is the place to be.
"If you pee on a fence
and you hate your wiener,
"don't be looking at my turkey
'cause he ain't for dinner.
"4:00 a.m.
and the cows get up.
"No desert till you
crush that sauerkraut.
"Got a barn full of hay,
"A fire with some s'mores,
"Mom yelling
'Chickens, chores!'
"Ain't no arcade till
that shit gets shoveled.
"What you lookin' at, fool?
This is life in a bubble."
That's from
Ohio right there.
- Yeah.
- We know.
- Straight up.
Shampoo conditioner.
Beard repair.
Uh...
What's that goes underneath
my skin? Beard oil.
What's beard repair?
Repairs you do like
once every three days.
- Those are all flammable.
- You know that, right?
- Hello.
- Huh? Fuck!
- You all enjoying my fire?
- Jesus.
Holy shit, man.
So, what the hell you
doin' out in the woods?
I live out there.
- Which haunt do you work at?
- The one down the road?
Yeah.
Yeah, we're
goin' there next, I think.
Yeah.
We see a bunch of kids
at a lot of these haunts,
'cause no one's calling
Social Services on 'em.
They're like eight,
nine years old.
You know, it's like here
in backwoods and shit,
there's no rules,
there's none of that stuff.
What you mean "backwoods"?
If that dude
is still at our campfire
when we go back, I'm out.
I hope they shoot you
with a paint ball.
Hey, this place is
putting my Presidential
stimulus plan in action.
Do you want the camera?
Can you come over here now?
Hey, do you...
Can we film in here?
All right, awesome.
I prefer to call it
a zombie stimulus plan.
--Brandy thinks it's a laser.
- I'm really excited.
- That's ridiculous.
How long have
you guys been doin'
the zombie paintball?
This is our first year.
- First year?
- Groundbreaking!
Wow!
Well, I'm gonna
tell everybody I know,
just so you know.
Seven more people
are going to find out.
He has
seven Facebook friends.
I don't think
I hit anything.
Get closer.
So, how can you do that?
How can you do that?
Put these on.
All right, guys,
getting into dead
territory over here.
Oh, fuck,
look at that face.
Man,
I'm gonna crush this guy.
There he is.
- Get that one.
Get it, get it, get it.
Oh, shit!
Yeah, you bitches!
Fucking die!
Hey, Mikey,
did that hit you?
Yeah. Right in the face, dude.
Power of Christ
compels you!
That was awesome.
That was the most fun
I've had in forever,
that was so cool.
Zack, I will do
whatever you wanna do.
Thank you.
Hey! I want that written
down and documented.
Jeff said,
"I will do whatever
you want on this trip."
Whatever, this is
like the most fun ever.
What did you think, mate?
Banging around.
- I'll fix it.
- RV is breaking down.
I'm going to be banging
around back there soon
with a zombie.
Bang around and go
to fucking bed.
That joke is
never going to die.
I think let's pull over.
Keep going.
What the fuck is that?
Hey, guys.
Is that the girl
from the haunt?
We're 100 miles from there,
there's no way that's her.
Stop.
Pull over in front of her.
- Oh, my God.
- Why?
What,
are you going to talk
to her or something?
Stop. Pull over.
Just pull up.
- I'll go talk to her.
Trying to
be the hero?
Well,
I'm not trying to be a...
Real, genuine, Texan.
Why does your brother do this?
Also 3:00 in the morning.
Oh!
There goes your brother.
She didn't
really say anything.
Mikey, what's going on?
I don't know.
She just kind of
followed me in here.
Something
happened to your car?
Can you call somebody
or something?
Is there
anywhere we can take you?
What the fuck was that?
Getting the fuck out of here.
She was just
fucking with us. Let's go.
It was okay,
but it was too scary for me.
- It was good.
- Yeah?
It was a good
little scare.
The scariest thing is
when the walls open up
and they come
out from the walls.
You don't even see 'em
'cause they look
like the walls.
There's all blood
gushing everywhere.
I was like,
"Oh, my gosh".
It was like, "Get me
out of this damn place".
Because I was scared
he had a chainsaw!
That's what
I'm looking for.
This lady, uh-uh.
She wants the,
"Ooh, all scary.
Oh, my God." No.
We want the real stuff,
the Faces of Death stuff.
Your community service was
working at a haunted house?
For real, for real.
Okay, see, now that,
had I known that first,
- that'd make it
scarier going in.
- Yeah.
Let's do it.
Is everybody else up?
Uh, I don't know.
Mikey's definitely not.
I think I nudged him,
like, five times.
Does it have to be
like this every morning?
I need eight minutes
to totally get ready.
I'll be fine.
You get ready.
The last night
was really weird.
- Yeah, you made it weird.
- You brought her in here.
Oh, man, I didn't think
that was going to happen,
it was just...
It's kind of weird.
It's almost like
they're fictional characters.
- You know what I mean?
- Yep.
So funny.
I mean,
I guess not really funny.
Bob, what exactly are
you looking for on this?
I mean these...
You keep saying back country.
I mean, that's...
Where these hillbillies...
Some of them are
a little messed up.
These places though,
it's like,
we have this password
we have to find for this.
They say "blue skull,
blue skeleton."
But there's something to blue
because people keep using it.
And it was in Dallas,
then it was in Houston.
And so it moves around.
So it's not as
much about backwoods
as we're going to have to
go to the backwoods
to find the password.
But the place,
it seems like...
"Is this the haunt hole?"
What is an extreme haunt?
Instead of them
chasing you with a chainsaw
with no chain on it,
they're going to chase you
with the chain on it
and like...
I don't understand how far...
Like, how far you really
can go on without
hurting somebody.
- But that's where...
- Oh, shit.
You need to get out,
and we need to check with...
Guys,
where in the hell
is this place?
I want to say it's
further away than you think,
but, Todd says, "Are we lost?"
Look at this place.
Can I even fit,
Zack, is this...
Can you
even get in here?
Going to
have to make it work.
Oh, my God.
Can you try not to run over
any more children?
All these people
are already outside.
It's actually kind of cool
to get here early and see
like, they're,
like, being real people.
Oh!
This place
is a shit hole, Bobby.
In the middle
of bumfuck nowhere.
His back was enough
for you, Bobby?
These are your people,
farm boy.
That's right, dude.
- It looks like high
school kids made this.
- What up?
- What?
- I couldn't even go.
Let's go.
We're going to...
What so you mean...
Let's go.
The line was ridiculous.
Why are you waiting in line?
We're in the middle
of a fucking forest.
Go piss in the bushes.
Holy shit.
Dude.
Nice costume.
Jesus!
Okay.
Holy shit.
What the hell, man?
Leave me alone.
Don't!
Why the fuck are
you following me?
Oh, fuck.
Get the fuck away.
Oh, fuck!
Please, what do you want?
What the fuck
is wrong with you?
What the fuck?
Jesus. Not even a haunt yet.
Zack?
Yo.
What are you doing, man?
Hey, guys! How's it going?
What's your name, buddy?
Hi, Mikey.
How are you doin'?
What's the camera for?
Are you guys
doing Crimestoppers
or Cops or something?
We're doing
To Catch a Predator.
To Catch a Predator?
I gotta go.
Watch out,
where're you going,
you piece of shit?
Ooh.
Oh, I like big, fuzzy bears.
Oh!
Always touch the beard.
I feel
so violated right now.
Zack, watch the light.
Trying, dude.
Go ahead of us.
Break out! Break out!
Come on!
Zack?
Where did you go?
Wait, where are you?
Which way?
That's disgusting.
Brandy, you all right?
Please!
No, no! Let me go, please.
Let me out.
Let me out!
Please, let me go!
Ed, shut the fuck up!
This is so fucked up.
You want
a piece of her, boys?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Zack, I don't think
we're supposed to go in here.
Zack! Don't go...
Don't go.
I'm just
here for your father.
Get that thing out of here!
Get out of here!
Guys,
let's get out of here!
Get the fuck out of here!
He's still behind you!
Walk, walk, walk.
He's still following us.
Zack!
Oh, my God!
Oh, God!
What's going on?
Oh, shit!
Back up,
back up, back up, back up!
Shit.
Zack, let's go.
Let's go.
Zack, let's go!
Let's go! Fuck! Come on!
There you are,
fucking sucker!
Yeah, take it!
Take it! Take it!
Good morning.
Brandy.
You're gonna die.
- Brandy.
- Walk away.
Brandy.
It's time to play!
Get the fuck away from me!
Oh, shit!
Die! You're gonna die!
I think it's a little weird
that they knew my name.
Someone probably told them
to say that to freak you out.
Wait, what?
- Why didn't you say anything?
Honestly, because
you guys get so scared
about everything.
I wanted to make sure
you could go
through the haunt.
Zack's the one...
- Yeah.
- I don't know.
Ask them.
Zack,
where we going tomorrow?
Have you told him?
It was a haunted house
down in the south somewhere.
I don't know if
it was in Alabama
or wherever it was on.
We have a forum, chat room,
for haunted house owners.
And, uh, there was a, um...
A younger kid
that was in a scene,
where it was a hanging scene,
and he had replaced
the breakaway noose
that was in
the scene with his own,
but he accidentally
hung himself.
Um, and it was
part of the show.
And by the time
they were able to
take care of the situation...
I mean, he was already dead.
This was,
like, in a haunted house?
This was in
a haunted house while
the haunted house was open.
...or should I get Skittles?
This is all garbage food,
all garbage food.
Or should I get
Sour Patch Kids?
Yeah,
I don't think any of your...
Or should I get a big pickle?
So, are we off the 20?
What is a good name
- for a city?
- Where's the haunt?
What city is the haunt in?
That is not what I know.
Not our job.
Look how creepy...
Look how creepy this is.
- I love this.
- What the hell is that?
And he's combing his hair?
We're going
to find these places that...
I don't know
what goes on if they
use real body parts
or whatever.
Real body parts,
that doesn't scare me,
though, like...
I'm not going to
know the difference.
If a real human leg...
But I won't know
if it's a real human leg
or it's a fake human leg,
so it's not...
That doesn't bother me because
I don't know the truth anyway.
What someone's idea
of what scary is,
is totally different
to somebody else.
Is it dressing up the walls,
with blood dripping off
and all that stuff?
I don't need all that.
Mine's more like,
real shit, dark.
I don't know where I'm going,
I don't know what's happening.
The intricate details to me
isn't that big of a deal.
Where are you going?
Why do you care?
Who you talking to?
Chantelle.
Yeah,
I got something good for him.
All right. All right.
This is Mikey's surprise,
give him a clue.
I did.
You gotta think about it.
I mean, think about
the theme of this trip.
Think about some
place Mikey loves
and just combine the two.
Dude, it's like some
Halloween theme thing.
Mikey,
are you into weird stuff?
Absolutely,
but I don't know if they're
gonna let us go in there.
Oh, hold on.
Look what he's...
Yes.
How old is that lady?
50-year veteran stripper.
Jeffrey,
is this your first time?
No...
Yeah, my first year
out of Florida.
Look at all that.
Insert them in, or... Okay.
All my research pays off
on haunted houses
and strip clubs.
All right,
let's have some fun.
Love it.
Brandy, you ready?
I mean, get crazy,
like, let's get nutty.
Yeah!
Getting some!
Come on, honey...
This is kind of hot.
Very exotic.
Zombie strippers?
Are you fucking kidding me?
All right!
Whoo-hoo!
Fuck Christmas,
this is Halloween!
And then
Jeff with four girls, dude.
I mean, Jesus,
he almost swallowed a tit.
I thought it was
going to kill him.
I think she really liked me.
- Look at your jeans, man.
- A little extra starch.
You guys are
fucking disgusting.
Come out!
Be a part of this.
Come on.
Ahhh!
Are you coming or not?
Can we just roll through,
just taking
a couple snap pictures?
No.
No, you can't do that.
You can't have any cameras,
no pictures. I'm sorry.
This one's free.
Dude, you can't do
that shit in San Antonio.
Tell him about that
thing in Louisiana.
Hey, I heard about
something in Louisiana.
So, outside of it,
like, would you guys go out
after you get off work?
Um, some of us do.
I'm just... I'm bored...
Doin' this.
Dude, it was crazy, dude.
What?
What, did you guys
pay money to do it?
Yeah, it's like a tour,
like San Antonio...
It's like...
Have you ever
made out with guys,
like, in the haunt,
all dressed up?
o.
- Never?
- No, I have never made out with anybody at the haunt.
-  No.
- You never...
- It's like kissing
my brothers.
Um...
Is it...
Is it something
skeleton or skull,
we heard?
- Yeah.
- That's what it's called?
Yeah, something
like blue skeleton.
Have you ever hooked up
with make-up on?
Uh, no. No, actually, never.
- Seems hot.
- No, because, they're...
You guys have to
tell me about this.
Okay. See, I'm with
all this group of people,
and they're, like,
getting pissed with me
'cause I keep taking
them places like this.
We're trying to
find something extreme.
--Show me.
- Show you?
- Yeah, let me see it.
Okay.
I want to see you
contort your body.
Well, I would have
to take this off.
I'm not worried
about that.
Oh, shit, that's hot.
You got a hot thong on.
- Well, yeah.
- What do you...
Turn around.
What are your tattoos?
It's a lot harder.
I have a, um...
You guys are
my best friends.
Yeah, brother.
Good luck.
All right.
Thank you, guys.
Awesome.
Can I touch your face?
Sure.
That's awesome.
Sweet.
Haunted words.
- Hey, I found it.
- What?
- I found the Blue Skeleton.
- Yeah, dude...
Where?
Uh, this place that they said.
San Antonio.
And then his
other friend goes,
"Fuck San Antonio!"
He goes, "Tell him about that
crazy place we went to."
And I was, like,
"Hey, was it
called Skull Skeleton?"
He goes, "Blue Skeleton."
And they went last year.
And he said it's in
Louisiana this year.
Hey, we got it. We got it.
We're done.
We're going to Blue Skeleton.
We can go through
with two different cameras...
No, but we
gotta get to the end...
We got more places to go to.
Look, I don't know exactly...
Where ya'll going?
What are ya'll doing?
Yeah, I'm talkin'
to you, Biggin'.
- Whoa.
- Yeah.
What are you doing?
I knew you were
filming in there.
Give me the tape.
I didn't...
Dude, I went through
one time with no camera.
Dude? Do I look like a dude?
I look like a clown, son!
Now, what were you
doing in there?
- We were just hanging.
- Yeah, we were just...
- We went through
your haunt.
- Just hanging? Just hanging?
Just hanging?
Just hanging with
the big shitty talk?
Whatever!
Where are the tapes?
I know you were recording.
We didn't
record anything.
You told us to put
the camera off...
I know you
were recording.
Dude, we didn't record.
Do you remember
yesterday?
I wasn't born then!
And fuckin' back up
and stop. Relax.
You want me to
fuck and back up?
- That is illegal
in this state.
- Fuck you. Just...
- Hey, dude, stop! Relax.
- You gotta get used
to some sodomy...
Prepare for some sodomy
because I'm
about to fuck you up!
Hey, dude,
you don't want...
You do not want to
get him pissed off.
I wanna get
him pissed off,
- you pissed off,
and fuck her.
- No, you don't.
You look ridiculous.
- You need to...
- Back the fuck up,
get out of here.
- Brandy, go inside, now!
- Okay.
- Back up.
- You heard me.
I've said my piece.
Get on before I hurt you.
No,
that's the second time
one of these guys
have got in my face.
I swear to God, dude,
I'm gonna knock one of
these guys the fuck out!
Maybe you shouldn't
make a sex tape
with his sister.
Oh, come on, man,
he didn't know that
I was filming her.
Beer wench.
We should do
a different handshake
that's like...
- Oh...
- Brandy, can you make...
No.
Oh...
No, I don't like that.
That wouldn't
catch on?
No.
Oh...
Oh,
where are those tongs?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
How far would they go
to scare somebody? You know...
They will go pretty far.
They will go pretty far
to breaking their leg,
breaking their back,
doing anything
they possibly can
to get a scare.
Do you think that
you have a stopping point?
Uh...
A stopping point...
I have been asked,
and I have done
many different
things over the years.
We've heard rumors
you were using dead bodies.
I'm not surprised,
to be honest.
I'm not surprised.
That's actually scary.
Real dead bodies?
Hmm.
Not far, from what I've heard.
Zacharias,
you hear anything last night?
No. Come back here
for a sec, though.
What are you doing?
Close up for a J.O. session?
Yeah. Close the door.
What do you mean,
"Close the door"? Why?
Just close the door.
This was posted
in a haunt chat
room last night.
Dude, what?
I've watched this
thing three times.
Every single one of us
is in this video.
How would you
have filmed this?
Look.
That's me.
Were you filming me
while I was asleep?
I'm trying to figure
out how you filmed it,
unless Michael did it.
But I just...
Michael's right before you.
I'm in bed with Brandy,
there's Jeff...
I can't explain this.
And how's it online?
This isn't...
What are you...
The only thing I
can think of is,
this is just a part of it,
- so we're just
gonna have to...
- Part of it?
This is not a haunt.
Dude, we're not in a haunt,
we're in the middle
of nowhere in our RV.
- Yeah, I know.
- These guys came in here.
Do not say a fucking word
or they will all go home.
You guys seen
my license around?
What are you wearing, dude?
Real men wear pink.
Those look like
Brandy's panties.
You've never
seen my panties.
Brandy's granny panties.
- I blacked out last night.
- It could have been her.
What do you mean,
"blacked out"?
What the fuck!
What the fuck is...
What are
you doing, dude?
What's going on, Michael?
What the fuck are you doing?
- What the fuck is that?
- Should I pull over?
What do you mean,
"What is that?"
What the fuck?
- What is it?
What the fuck is that?
Is that a heart?
- God, Michael!
- Jesus!
Jesus Christ,
are you okay?
- Is this you?
- Michael...
Why the fuck is
he puking in here?
Zack, You did that?
Zack?
Jesus Christ!
What is that?
I have no fucking idea.
Don't touch it.
Don't touch it!
Well,
I'm not keeping it in here.
Shit.
- God,
that's so gross.
Fucking idiots, dude.
I didn't do this.
Yeah, you didn't do it.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
I'm just waiting for you, man.
Let's go.
None of you guys are ready.
And Mikey's
being difficult. Still.
Are you all right?
No, I'm not.
Let's go.
- This is just...
I don't want to do it.
Jeff, you done?
Hey, I got the email.
- We're doing the forum?
- Yeah.
All right.
If you want to move closer,
head toward Baton Rouge.
Ask for Giggles
at the D&D Bar.
Baton Rouge?
Yeah.
It's...
It's part of the thing.
You're the very one that
wants to stop going to
the Mickey Mouse places.
All right.
Huh?
There it is.
Now you're going
to get your chance, tough guy.
Look at all
those trash bag pumpkins.
This is a bar?
Zack?
I'm sorry, guys,
but this is where
they said to go.
He said to ask
the guy at the bar.
Hey, uh, excuse me.
Sorry to bother you guys.
Uh, I'm supposed
to find a Giggles.
- You know?
- Giggles?
Yeah.
I know Giggles.
Oh, yeah. He hangs out here
quite regularly,
matter of fact.
You all want to
take a seat over there
and make yourselves at home.
He'll be here shortly.
Yeah.
Sit.
At least we're on
the right track.
Look at
the couple slow dancing.
So weird.
You guys want a drink,
at least?
- Beer.
- Jeff, you want a beer?
Yeah.
It's just a scare...
Hey! What's that camera for?
They're cool, the bar.
Happy with that
kind of service.
Besides, they don't...
They don't like our kind.
Holy shit. Turn around.
Turn around, Brandy!
- What? What?
- Turn around.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
Are you Giggles?
Hey!
All right,
I'll turn it off!
Try that here.
That guy was
having a good time.
You looked like you
were having a good time.
- What?
Okay,
I'm going to the bathroom.
What?
- Hey, we're gonna...
- What's going on, guys?
- We're gonna...
- No, no, no, no, no.
You want to meet
Mr. Giggles?
He's outside.
Yes.
He won't talk till
the camera is off,
so put it down.
- Sit down.
- It's gonna be you.
Finally.
This is not a good idea.
Oh, man, check this out.
What you got there?
City boys
forgot their camera.
Oh, cool.
Let's go make a movie.
Yeah, let's make a movie.
Hey, guys,
this is the ladies' room.
Well, yeah, we know.
How you doing?
Ugh, what are you doing?
We're shooting
a little video.
Thought that's
what y'all like.
Well, it's not what we're...
It's not what
we're here to do.
We decided to
shoot a little movie.
Did Bobby and Zack
set you up for this?
Heard you were
looking for Mr. Giggles.
I got your Mr. Giggles
for you right here, darling.
Stop.
- Could you just...
- Huh?
Just leave the rest room.
Uh, we're good.
We're doing all right.
Stop!
Just stop! Guys, get out!
- Come on, huh?
- What's the matter?
Just trying
to have a little fun.
Bobby.
They cornered me in there.
What the fuck
you guys doing?
- Shooting a movie, boy.
- Shooting a movie.
That's our camera.
What are you talking about?
We're making a movie.
Let's go, let's go...
- I'm not saying it's you.
- It's on all of us, all right?
But it's getting out
of hand, all right?
They're filming us,
they're posting
this shit online.
Fucking getting
in Mike's face.
But then when
they go after Brandy,
that's a whole
different story, man.
We can never
leave her alone again.
They were asking me
for my Facebook,
and I got theirs.
We were talking
about Extreme Haunts.
And they said that they were
looking for the same shit.
I don't know.
They were just, like,
"Hey, let's exchange
information if you find..."
They knew what we
were talking about?
Yeah. They said
they've heard of 'em.
Well, then you're gonna
need to Facebook 'em.
'Cause we have
the information.
It's in Louisiana this year.
We don't have
an address, though.
- It doesn't matter.
- You know, I'm down,
- but we don't have an address.
- It doesn't matter.
--I have...
- These websites. I'm in...
- Shh, what was that?
Yeah, but Zack,
that's like nothing.
Brandy,
when I say Louisiana,
that's where it is...
--What was that?
You guys,
there's somebody outside.
Look out the windows.
It's so hard to see.
Can you even see...
- Shit!
- You guys,
there's somebody out there!
Brandy, stay here.
- What was that?
- Shh...
- Somebody is on the roof.
- Where?
Shh.
--Shh.
--Jeff...
Be quiet. Shh...
Shut up, shut up, shut up.
Holy shit. Holy shit.
What just happened?
Bobby... Bobby, get it.
Jeff, why is the power out?
Is the door locked?
Yes, it's locked!
Go turn it on.
What do you
see out the window?
I don't see shit.
- I can't see anything.
- Brandy, just stay here.
Okay.
Do not leave
anybody's side.
Stay away from the sun roof.
Or,
if I try the engine, dude,
it'll charge the generator.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Try it!
- I'll just try it. Hold on.
Brandy, stay back.
Shit!
What the fuck?
Bobby, they are every...
They are all around us.
You guys,
what is going on?
What the fuck is going on?
What the...
Jesus, Bobby!
They're outside our...
- Right up against
the window over there!
Seriously!
- What the fuck?
- Where'd they go?
Where did they go?
There were, like,
50 of them...
- Shut the back.
- ...and they just disappeared.
Go to the back
and lock the door.
Did they go on the sides?
- Guys, do you see that?
- I don't know...
They are starting to phase out
a lot of the traditional stuff
and starting to go
into this extreme stuff.
- If I've got a group of...
- Help!
--...six or eight, you know,
21-year-old males
and a guy comes up to me
and tugs on my sleeve,
and he says,
"Hey, I want it hardcore,"
we'll run him through there.
I mean, I'll tell the guy,
"I'll do everything
short of killing you."
And they're, like,
"That's what we want.
That's what we want."
And I'll go in there,
and we'll tear 'em up.
We're almost to the point
where we're gonna cuss these
people and gang-rape them.
Brandy,
you doing okay?
Come on, it's our last day.
See a smile on that face.
That's our
Halloween breakfast?
Yeah.
Halloween is
just like Christmas.
You get Christmas breakfast.
Halloween breakfast.
Jack-o-lantern
pancakes then.
Can everybody have
a good time today, please?
Jesus Christ.
What the fuck was that?
Do not go outside yet.
Dude... Dude...
- Yeah...
- I'm going.
Do you see anybody?
Why is there a pumpkin
in the middle of nowhere?
Zack, get in...
What are you doing?
- Get back in the RV.
See anything?
Somebody is here.
I like it.
It says, "Carve me."
Look what I have.
I think they
went a little too far.
Got a knife?
I mean, we are
in the middle of nowhere,
and they found us?
Yeah, this is what
you've been looking for.
- Oh, my God.
- What is it?
Look what we have here.
Stop being dramatic.
What is it?
It's an invitation.
Bourbon Street, 10:00 p.m.
But, I mean how do you know
it's Blue Skeleton?
How the fuck...
It's what
we've been wanting.
It's insane now.
There'll be, like,
10,000 people down there.
We gotta try it.
One more day,
that's all I ask.
It's Halloween.
We go home tomorrow, okay?
Yeah, I don't know.
We bring this
to protect us.
Don't be
a smartass right now.
We're going home tomorrow.
Dude, this is what
we've been looking for.
Yeah, we used to assume
that we were gonna go.
We are going.
You just... No, you...
You don't give
anybody a chance to talk...
You were really going
to get an invitation,
and then just,
what are we going to do,
go drink tonight
at a bar?
This is what we've
been looking for,
for a week.
It's Halloween.
We go.
- Holy shit.
- Wow.
Guys, it's so cool.
I have the weird...
That's weird.
Halloween.
That's really...
That means people
were out here last night
putting those in.
Zack, go get 'em.
Wow.
They were
sitting around the RV
while we were sleeping.
Hey. Hey, you all right?
Brandy,
let's go with it.
Halloween time.
Everybody take one.
Let's rock.
- Ha!
- You're an idiot!
That's not
what we set out to do,
is to be fucking
surrounded in a field
by fucking weirdos.
Well, if you
kind of think about it,
it's kind of cool.
You kidding me?
- It's kind of cool.
- Kind of cool?
There is such a difference,
though,
in wanting extreme shit
and knowing, okay,
we're going to do
an extreme haunted house,
to brushing teeth
and getting ready to go to bed
and be surrounded
by redneck hillbilly assholes
that are, you know,
fucking with us.
And that's not cool
when you don't
know what's going on.
Nothing actually happened.
Like, just calm down,
all right?
You came on this trip,
you've seen this world,
and now we've got
the opportunity to do
something really cool,
so just relax.
You see anybody
who has a skull mask,
anything that looks
like it, let me know.
Show me your tits!
Thank you!
It's not him.
There's somebody up
there with a skull, Jeff.
- Where?
- See him on the balcony?
I swear I could see him.
I'm not gonna walk down
this street again!
Hey!
- Brandy?
Brandy!
Hey... Bobby!
Hey!
Get him... Get him.
Bobby!
Hey, wait up!
Hey, where you go...
Wait up!
Bobby!
You wanna
come out and play?
Someone find my friends.
Over here, boy.
What you looking at?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Yeah!
Bring your mouth!
Put out your tongue
and say, "Ah."
You guys going to call him?
Yeah, Zack is.
I called twice.
What do you mean
you called twice?
- Voice mail says...
- Whose voice mail?
Jeff's voice mail!
It says,
"If you want to go to
the Blue Skeleton..."
That gave me an intersection
and said we gotta
be there by midnight.
I can't believe
that we're actually going
to find this place, man.
I can't say I know
what's going on, but just...
We're in this together.
Right, that's fine.
What are you looking for?
Mike.
I don't know where
the fuck Jeff is,
I do not know
what is going on.
We're either going to
the end of this road,
or going the fuck home.
What do you want to do?
You want to
leave him out there?
There's no
fucking chance.
He's up!
I don't see
anything outside, though.
Somebody is coming.
Whoa.
Zack, what is this, man?
What's going on?
- What the...
What are we gonna do?
Oh, come on.
This is... Fuck...
What?
"Sixty seconds, come outside,
or your friend will die."
- It's a text message?
- What the fuck?
This is not
all right, man.
"Forty-five seconds."
Fuck this, dude,
I'm not scared of them.
Let's get out there.
This isn't real, right?
Is this the haunt?
What is this?
"You will be scared.
Thirty seconds."
Can they fucking hear us?
You guys,
what's going on here?
It's...
It's just gotta be them.
What else do we do?
Zack?
Dude, get back in the RV!
Come on!
Shit!
"Surprise."
What the hell
is going on?
There is glass everywhere,
Bobby.
Stay down, Brandy.
Jesus-fucking-Christ!
Why are they doing this to us?
Holy shit.
- Stay down.
- Can you see Zack?
--Holy shit.
Get it.
"Don't look up."
What the fuck man?
I don't want
to fucking play along!
- Get off me!
- Get the fuck off!
Do not fucking hurt her!
Jesus Christ.
Brandy?
Brandy, stay close.
Okay.
Where are we going?
Guys,
you know what this is.
Just relax.
A little hard
to relax, Zack.
Zack, shut the fuck up.
Oh, my God.
Ah, fuck!
Get off me!
What is going on, Mike?
What's happening?
Get the fuck off me!
--All right, All right.
Jesus!
All right. These guys
have got a fuckin' bat.
- What?
- What's going on, Mike?
Michael,
just do what they want.
All right, all right.
Michael?
He's just
messing with you, Brandy.
Okay.
What's going on?
- They are moving me outside.
- All right, I'll go!
Hey Zack,
are you going too?
I guess, are you?
- No.
- Zack!
Wait, you guys,
don't leave me in here alone.
Zack,
bring her with you!
You guys!
- Brandy!
- Oh, shit.
Brandy!
Fucking shit!
- Brandy!
- Guys!
Bring her out!
Fuck, I don't want
to be here alone.
Count to 30...
...and remove your hood.
There is going to
be a video camera
sitting right next to you.
Pick it up...
...and record
everything you see.
And remember...
...we'll be watching.
I can't see a goddamn thing.
Oh, my God,
this is ridiculous.
Shit.
Zack?
Bobby?
I'm supposed to be filming.
Oh, shit.
Dammit.
I swear to Christ,
Bobby, if y'all are
fucking with me...
Honestly, I just
want to get the... Fuck!
All right, look,
I'm fucking over this.
All right, I'm done. I'm done!
What the fuck am
I supposed to do?
Hello!
Zack! Bobby!
This is crazy shit.
Hello?
Fuck.
Zack?
Oh, fuck.
Holy Jesus Christ, man!
Dude, I am done!
Just let me out. I give up...
What the fuck?
Get me out of here now!
You look...
Jesus Christ!
Hey, hey! How the fuck
do I get out of here?
What the fuck?
- What the fuck!
Oh, shit.
Okay.
No!
Can any of you
guys hear me in here?
All right, we're done!
What the fuck?
What the fuck, man!
- Get me the fuck out of here!
- Bobby, where are you?
Get me out of here!
Get me the fuck out of here!
- Get me the fuck...
Get me the fuck...
Bobby! Mikey!
Somebody fucking answer me!
What's going on?
Fuck!
Jesus.
Hey, man, tell me you know
how to get out of
this fucking place.
Hey.
What the fuck is this?
Your props are
really fucking scary!
Oh! Shit.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hello?
What the fuck is going on?
Hello!
--Oh, shit!
Michael! Mike!
Michael, I'm in here man!
- Get me the fuck out!
- Mike!
- God dammit!
What the fuck is wrong?
- Bobby?
- Michael?
- Bobby!
Michael!
- Guys, can you hear me?
- No! Look at the door.
Get the fuck out!
Get the fuck
out of there now!
- Find the door!
Michael! Michael!
Come on.
Come on, there's
gotta be a light in here.
Come on.
Coming through!
Pardon me!
Stop it!
Please stop!
- Just get
me out of here!
Please get me out of here!
- I'm going to fuck your world!
- No...
Brandy?
Guys,
somebody please talk to me.
Please God,
please God, please God.
Zack?
Zack, what the fuck
are you doing in here, man?
We got to get out of here.
This is not a fucking haunt.
You having fun, Bobby?
Help!
Please...
Bobby!
Please help!
Help me!
Can anybody hear me!
I can't breathe in here!
Please!
Help!
Please help me!
Please...
Help!
What's the best
part about your job?
I'm... I'm not me
for five hours a day.
And if I can get out
of the tangled up mess,
that is my head
and into somebody else's head.
All that pent-up aggression
is now taken out on somebody,
and, you know,
be as vicious and mean
as I can towards anybody
to scare 'em.
You want to make it so that
they're not gonna escape.
Right?
I mean, that's the thing,
we don't want them to escape.
If I were a zombie
and they came out here,
my goal is to eat their
brains and survive, right?
And, um, their goal
is to not make it out,
or try to make it out
if they can.
Um.
They're coming out here
and it's going to be
their last visit anywhere.