Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What are you doing?
Stop.
You are...
hurting us.
Burn in hell.
No...
What are you doing Yosille?
You know what happens when I
don't feed.
This isn't real.
Don't you want to
see your wife again?
No more.
I will never feed you again.
Very well.
Stay in your circle, Yosille.
There are always others.
Wait.
You promise?
A life...
for your wife.
I'm coming Aida.
Forgive me God.
Hey...
Means a lot that you came.
Claire, you can say it.
What?
"Art may love you, but you,
you will never be family."
He said that.
Yeah he said a lot of crazy
shit.
This time will be different.
He's loosened the Yarmulke.
Trust me, he's changed.
I hope so.
Just don't forget,
you're carrying his only
grandkid.
It'd be a bad idea to
piss you off.
Hmm, that's right.
Just give the old man a chance.
I'm here, aren't I?
Yes you are.
Alright.
Welcome home, Art.
All the holy
books and scriptures
does not always prepares us
for tragedies such as this.
Chazal teaches us,
that in the beginning God spoke.
And with these holy letters
created the Universe.
From the blade of grass
to the burning stars
that shine above us,
all made of his holy letters
spoken at the beginning of time.
A man of heavenly perspective
restores the letters of
creation.
But in times of tragedy
who can say that...
How did you grow up like this?
It was a laugh a minute.
Ah, I'm so sorry
I didn't mean to um...
Great start.
Yeah, very good.
Don't take it to heart.
Death can bring out
the worst in people.
Welcome home, son.
It's good to see you dad.
God, did I miss you.
And you... the famous
Claire. Britain's finest.
It's fine.
Oh!
We're family, right?
So, um...
Come and see your room.
Mmm! Oh my God.
Good, no?
Good? This is delicious!
Did you make this?
I've never had a
dumpling that's...
No, no, no not dumpling.
- Kreplach.
-  Ah, kreplach.
That's very good!
So, um, tell me.
Boy? Girl?
Ah, it's a girl.
Ah!
Perhaps she can learn to
write like her mother.
You read my articles?
I did a little digging.
Oh, it's just light
editorial work.
She's being modest.
Claire's a great writer.
On her way to writing a
cookbook for the ages.
And she likes my kreplach?
Y'know
Food connects the body to
the soul so they say.
That's lovely.
Hmm?
Uh hmm.
I'm just gonna uh...
Excuse me.
I should've gone to your
wedding.
When you see the world a
certain way,
it's not easy to accept change.
I'm sorry.
- It's alright.
- No.
No, it's not.
Well,
We're here now.
Yeah.
Did you show them the contract?
What contract?
Until your Dad signs
his house cannot be used as
collateral.
Just, uh... tell them his
lawyer's looking over
the finer details as we speak.
We're closing soon.
Soon is not gonna cut it.
I know Claire's invitro
nearly wiped you out
but the bank doesn't give a
shit.
How long have I got?
Without your dad's
house on the line,
you've got no leverage.
At this point, Art,
if you don't get his signature
by the end of the week,
rest assured, the bank
will take your home.
Oh, and this, this is
our backyard.
No.
You would be amazed at
the size of the lemons we grow.
That's beautiful. That's
just beautiful.
You know, my father,
alav ha-shalom,
always used to say, "the
home, is the heart."
Open home, open heart.
You're gonna have a
very lucky kid.
I should probably move that.
What happened to her?
What can I say, her name
was Sarah Scheindal.
We prayed, we hoped, we...
searched.
And eventually we found her.
Yeah, it was terrible.
Just terrible.
You don't need to know.
That's enough of all this.
Sorry, I was just um...
Well your wife has
just been showing me pictures.
Such a home. My son, the
real estate machor.
To new beginnings, hmm?
L'chaim.
- L'chaim.
To life.
Oh! That must be Heimish.
No rest for the wicked!
Did the schmuck arrive?
It's open! It's open!
Even the dead are impatient.
Now...
You wanna do a mitzvah?
Well look who it is, huh?
The prodigal son returns.
How you doin', boychik?
Good to see you, Heimish.
I heard you piped a shiksa.
Don't worry, we'll convert her.
Heimish. Behave.
So, Reb" Arthur, what
brings you to Brooklyn?
You miss my kugel?
Call my wife a shiksa again,
I'll cock you in the mouth.
What? You come to make
peace before the baby's born?
That's very wise.
Look at you, the great
business machor
helping us with the grunt work.
Such humility, Arthur.
You're an idiot.
You smell that?
It smells like chazer.
You got a problem with my diet?
I wasn't talking about
your diet, boychik.
Something wrong?
Nothing at all. Right Arthur?
Nothing.
Just like old times.
Oi...
What happened?
Nebach.
Sruli ruled it a suicide.
You knew him?
Yosille Fishbein.
Brilliant scholar.
After his wife
died, became a recluse.
Last I heard, he got
lost in the esoteric.
Desperate to contact
the wife on the other side.
It was only a few months ago,
that we did the funeral for her.
He tried everything
to save her life.
What's a man without his wife?
A good man.
Such is life.
What a riddle.
Amen.
Sarah Scheindal's
ferry is confirmed
we're all good on tomorrow.
Good.
You keep that on your head.
Some things never change.
Saul, can I have a quick word?
Go ahead. I"ll get it started.
Don"t forget tachrisim.
Ah, he knows, he knows.
Ah, he's going to mess it up.
He's not going to mess it up.
Don't mess it up.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh my God.
You really don't find
it suspicious
that he shows up
after all this time?
You should've heard him on
the phone.
He really wants to start again.
It took a lot of growth
to come here.
I know he's your son.
But all is not butter
that comes from the cow.
You don't have the heart of a
young man no more.
Don't you love him?
Yeah, of course I love him.
But I don't trust him.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Arthur, you alright?
Yeah, everything's good.
You mess it up?
I swear the farkakte wiring
has a mind of its own.
You okay?
Uh hmm.
Still scared of the dark?
Boo!
Very funny...
Just a little rigor mortis.
The body's last hurrah.
Yeah, I'm starting to remember.
Why don't you check on
Claire? Hmm?
What? Did I do something wrong?
No, no, no, no, no.
I'll finish up here. We
can do the rest tomorrow.
Go.
Go and get some rest.
Dad, can I ask you a question?
Of course.
I...
Don't matter. Another time.
Heimish takes good
care of me. You know?
Try to get along.
Oh and Art...
I'm glad you're back.
M-me too.
Yosille, Yosille...
What have you been up to?
Art?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
After these words,
God asks Abraham to sacrifice
his beloved son Isaac.
But we must ask,
is this a God to believe in?
A God who plays cruel mind
games with his loyal servants?
Our Holy Zohar explains what
most don't...
Shalom's warehouse.
Hello, Reb Chayim?
I-it's Saul.
- Saul?
- Yes, I need a favor.
Sure.
I may have found something.
Ayin, koof, dales.
This is on the knife?
Yeah, this is on the knife.
Koof, dales,
and saf.
It's an ancient warding
inscription.
What, you know of this?
It's a... one of God's
hidden names written backwords.
It's for invoking sheidim,
and for sealing them.
Sealing them?
Yeah, often in a body, but uh...
honestly Saul, I, I wouldn't pay
it too much attention.
It's an old buba maisa.
I mean, today's world,
who has the know-how
to seal a demon in a body?
And what if someone did?
Alright, look.
Was there a pendant?
What?
On the body.
Was there a pendant,
an amulet of some sort,
preserving a holy letter?
- No, no.
- You sure?
Yes of course, just, just
the blade.
So what's the drama?
No pendant, no seal.
Which means, there is
no way you picked up
a body containing a demon.
But say you did.
The worst an
entity like this can do,
is mess with your mind.
It's powerless whilst
it's in a body.
But honestly Saul,
unless you're in the
business of burning bodies...
I wouldn't worry about it.
Worse things have
happened to the Jews, Saul.
OK?
Have a good Shabbos.
Alright, bye.
Ah!
Look who it is!
What are you up to?
Oh, just a little morning read.
You haven't seen Art?
Woke up early, offered to help.
Really?
Yeah, I don't know
what you've done with him.
Who knew?
Hungry?
Starving.
God.
Sarah Scheindal.
I hope they find this sick
meshugenah.
Oh, come on Saul.
You're driving yourself crazy.
Hello?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Yes?
Art, it's Jake Bennett.
How are we holding?
Art's busy right now, can I take
a message? I'm his assistant.
Look, just let him
know that we met his terms,
but the bank was clear.
He won't be getting a loan
unless we have his father's
place as collateral.
We need him to sign the
contracttonight or this deal goes away.
I'll be sure to tell him.
Oh!
Claire?
Look at you.
Every Friday night,
the men sing to their
wives and...
and tell them that beauty
is just a passing breath.
But their kindness, their
humanity,
that is what every soul
truly desires.
We're a very misunderstood
people.
It's the burden of investing so
much
in internal meaning, it's...
it's hard for outsiders to see.
Y'know...
comforting others didn't really,
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
prepare me for my own grief.
I...
I should have...
spoken to Art more, maybe
shouted less, I don't know.
Sometimes,
reflection comes too late.
Hmm?
Are you alright?
Can I ask you something, Saul?
Yeah, of course. Anything.
Er...
Do souls ever call out
to you for,
for help?
The dead are just like the
living, Claire.
They still need love.
You know what
your son is up to Saul?
Heimish!
He things you're a
piece of toast to butter up.
Go ahead, tell him!
- Tell him!
- Tell me what?
All this, it's a game Saul!
It's a game.
He's a ganav.
- What did you...
- A thief.
That is not...
They're selling this
whole place from under you...
What? What you talking about...
They didn't come here
to reconcile Saul.
They came here to use you!
That is not, that is not
true. Dad...
He's committed your property
to some goyishe land developer...
That is not true!
I'm sorry but th-that
is outrageous.
That is not the case, ok Dad?
- Yes it is!
- I can explain...
You knew about this?
- What was that?
- It doesn't matter.
- Can you just...
- We're leaving.
Can you just talk to me?
Claire, can we do this later?
No, we can't!
Everything's gonna be fine,
okay?
Art, I want the truth.
I haven't been able to
sell a house in two years.
It's okay, I talked to the bank,
refinanced the house...
You refinanced the house?
You told me that you had
everything under control.
I-I left my job. I didn't have
to do that. You told me,
that everything was okay.
And then here I am, choosing
colours for the baby's room
and picking furniture when we're
on the verge...
We're not on the verge...
You know, you were
lying to me for two years.
We're supposed to be a
family. We're having a baby.
What was your plan, Art?
Huh?
I mean, what were you thinking?
Did you see his face downstairs?
Let me tell you
about downstairs.
That God, love and holiness.
That's a lie.
I watched my mother rot
in that room,
and when I needed him,
you know what he told me to do?
He told me to go away
to synagogue and pray.
So I prayed.
I prayed and I prayed,
"God don't take her.
God have mercy.
God don't hurt her!"
I cried so much to God,
there were no more words
left on the page.
You need to go
down there and talk to him
and make this right.
If we leave now, you'll
always regret it.
I didn't come here to
butter him up
Okay? I-
I wasn't going to sell
the house from under him.
I just needed to find the right
moment to ask him face to face.
I didn't want to hurt anyone.
I'm sorry.
Arthur?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hello?
Ah!
Dad?
What's going on?
What did...
Hum.. What happened?
What happened?
His heart...
gave up.
No.
You broke it.
Would you all just mind um...
Could you g... just give
me a minute?
Oh she's so sad. So sad.
I didn't know he was sick.
Saul, he wasn't a complainer.
Oh.
His heart was ailing him
for a while or...
Not today Chayim, please.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh look at them!
Oh, of course.
Here they are again.
I don't know
how they get their energy,
you know? So fast.
Of course! So, you know...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What do you want?
HELP ME!
I'm so sorry.
Art?
Art, there's something really...
really weird happening.
Art, are you listening to me?
There's something really...
Something really, really wrong.
Art?
Talk to me.
Hey?
What's going on?
I need to sleep.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What's wrong?
Hey.
I think I'm going crazy.
Ok.
Let's go home, Arthur.
It's okay.
This a joke? Art...
It's not like you're asking us
to lug a sofa out of the garage.
What is this?
Where's Heimish?
Look, you still got the
admission pages.
Body was due to ship out two
days ago.
It's a suicide! We
need a police report.
What?
You know, where's Heimish?
He doesn't work here anymore.
You still have the telephone?
Let's just say I deleted
his number.
Well, look...
Unless you can transfer
custody to a next of kin.
You're going to have
to wait for police clearance.
A next of kin?
Arthur, if I were you,
put your broigus aside.
Just call Heimish.
Yeah, you too.
Hello?
Summoning attempt?
I don't know
what's real anymore.
Days...
inside nightmares.
Inside dreams.
Somewhere, in there,
I know I made,
a terrible mistake.
It's a trickster.
A shapeshifter.
An ancient predator.
A taker of children.
A...
Abyzou.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
God!
This is the home of Saul, no?
I'm sorry, we're no longer in
business.
But you and I,
we are still very much in
business.
In your basement, you
have someone very dear to me.
I am sorry. Who are you?
Aida Fishbein.
And you,
you're the one who has
my husband.
My name is Yosille Fishbein,
and I have finally found the
cure for death.
Last night after months of
research by fire and ink,
I finally conjured Martiel.
The archangel of life.
Here is the interface between
Heaven and Earth.
Today, we bring back my
beloved Aida from Heaven.
Do you hear that?
The Archangel wants us to begin.
Your prayers can bring
back my beloved Aida.
Go ahead Sarah.
It's working.
It tickles.
Something's wrong.
No.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Sarah?
What are you?
Art, I've been trying to
get hold of you.
Th-there's someone here.
Art?
She says,
she's the wife
of the man downstairs.
Claire?
Must we wait?
My sweet husband.
I just take to see his face.
Please.
Please?
Don't worry.
What a sweet time.
Shouldn't be much longer
for you.
What?
The baby. Shouldn't be
much longer.
I can tell with these things.
This one.
How do you know that?
It's written right there
on the wall.
My hands... won't you?
Uh, maybe we should wait.
For what? A drawer? Please!
You know this man.
Don't you?
Why Yosille?
He should have listened.
What have you done to me?
Not me, your dream.
You've been infected.
Soon, your child will join
countless others.
The many lost souls,
calling out for help.
Only you can stop this curse.
Before it's too late.
The pendant?
Burn it!
From this, do we suffer.
From this, will you suffer?
Hurry! Burn it!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Come on, please.
Oh God!
No!
Claire?
- Art?
- Closer.
Art?
Closer!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Claire?
What are you doing Arthur?
Sarah?
Where's my wife?
Oh Claire, Claire, Claire!
Please, Claire!
Claire wake, please.
What did you do?
W-what did you do?
- Okay, okay...
- Art, something's wrong.
Okay, we're, we're
getting outta here.
A life, for a life.
Art, something's wrong!
Something's wrong.
Shall we make a deal?
No more pain.
No more fear.
You want me to get you a child.
No.
Shut up!
Please don't hang up.
Show me the tape.
Get out!
Sarah!
What are you?
This, this thing...
it's in the house?
I think so.
It has my wife.
What do I do?
I know a Kabbalist.
Heimish.
Arthur.
What is that thing?
A sigil.
An altar, a sacrificial
altar to those who enter it.
Did you feed it?
What?
Did your wife go in this sigil?
Uh...
I don't know.
Where is Yosille's body?
It's been freed.
It's vessel's been shattered.
What is this thing?
Bringer of miscarriages.
Taker of children.
I must finish, what
Yosille started!
Where's the rest of it?
- I...
- Where's the rest of it?
Since before the era of
concealment,
Abyzou has been inflicting
misery and miscarriage
forcing the bereaved and
the desperate to feed it.
Until God intervened,
and called upon Abraham to...
sacrifice his son.
Forever binding Abyzou.
Until Yosille brought it back.
It'll make you see things.
Feel things that aren't real.
Whatever it takes to get what it
wants.
A child inside that sigil.
But with this pendant, we can
bind it,
and our prayers will force it
inside.
Only we determine how much good,
and evil enter our realm.
So how do I kill it?
There is no kill.
You trap it.
How?
Like Yosille did.
And this would save my wife?
And my baby?
We have no time.
Chayim, there must be
something else we can do.
There must be another way.
There's no other way.
You must complete the entirety
of the binding ritual.
Once I finish the ash circle, do
not stop.
Stay in the circle!
Do it quickly.
I'm going as fast as I can.
We don't know
what this thing c...
Heimish.
Why don't you hear me?
God, please!
Dad?
Art... Arthur?
H-how did you?
Do what it wants.
I was a fool.
D-don't leave me,
don't leave me, please!
Save your wife!
What are you doing?
Hey! Arthur!
- Arthur!
- I saw my father.
No, no, no!
Whatever you saw, that
wasn't your father.
This.
Hold it.
This was your father.
Okay?
Finish the circle.
Stay in it.
Heimish!
No!
Art?
Art.
Claire.
Claire!
- Help.
- Claire!
Art!
Claire!
Art, please!
Art!
Please, help me!
Amen.
Art!
No!
Heimish.
Do it!
I can't do it!
I can't!
- Please!
- Arthur, I can't do this
Do it!
You should've stayed in
the circle.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Art!
Claire.
Thank God, are you ok?
- Yeah, are you ok?
- Yeah!
- Is the baby ok?
- Yeah.
Good.
Claire?