Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Rápido.
Vamos.
¡Mi hijo!
- ¡Ey, mi hijo!
- ¡Niño!
- ¡Mi hijo!
- Sí.
- Espérate, niño.
- ¡Ey!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
¡Mijo!
Okay.
Good luck.
- Gracias.
- Ey.
If there's a problem,
follow the roses.
Take care of yourself, son.
I pledge allegiance
to the flag...
Illegal immigration
on the rise.
A surge of migrants
into the U.S.
Cartels driving people
off their land.
Mexicans flee cartel violence,
seeking the American dream.
One must ask,
is the dream still alive?
America is divided by hate,
economics, race, religion...
Racial tensions are
flaring up all over.
One must...
White supremacy rising,
as disinformation spreads.
The NFFA voted back
into power again.
The New Founding Fathers
immediately reinstate
the Purge.
Is the Purge the answer?
The rich get richer
and the poor are left behind.
...power. Is a biased media
stoking the flames of discord?
Can...
This country feels
like it's at a boiling point.
The United States of Hate.
...so soon. Can the
Purge help this divided nation?
These questions
will be answered soon,
as the annual blood holiday
is once again right upon us.
♪ From sea ♪
♪ To shining sea. ♪
Whoa, whoa. There you go.
You stay right there.
Whoa, whoa.
Hey, squirrelly, huh, sis?
- Hyah!
- Yeah, just a little bit.
Hey. Whoa!
Whoa, whoa. Hey, down.
Ho. Ho, ho, ho. Ho.
Why does your brother
have to prove himself
all the time?
Hey, keep calm. I got you,
I got you, I got you.
Whoa! Ah!
Little more horse
than you expected, huh?
I know someone
who can calm that beast.
Hey.
Mírame, güey.
Tranquila.
Ey, ey, ey, ey, ey.
¿Qué pasó?
Mírame, mírame.
¿Qué traes, eh?
¿Qué traes?
Ey, ey, ey... Cálmate.
¡Ey! Mírame.
Así.
That's a cowboy.
Let's get back to work.
Come on.
Come on!
Let's get back to work.
Rosa?
Sí.
How are you doing?
Okay, more or less.
Just remember it's
1 kg for 2.2 lbs.
Okay?
I'm here for anything you need.
- Right?
- Right.
- Darius.
- How's she doing?
You know, second week
in the country.
The girl's terrified.
She lucky she got you
to walk her through this.
She is, and you're lucky
you have me to run this place.
I know I am.
The Purge doesn't
release anger.
It increases anger.
It's a virus.
It's an American-born virus
of hate and rage,
and it's injected
with a bullet,
and it's spreading,
it's growing, it's mutating.
Turn that off, Adela. Please.
The Purge is coming.
Mmm.
Mm-hmm.
This...
reminds me
of your mother's house.
You should give it to Darius
so he can make real Mexican food.
Not those terrible burritos.
Juan, please, where are we?
You need to practice
your English.
When in Rome.
When in America.
Just do it for me.
Please.
The Tucker family would really
appreciate that, believe me.
Now that your wife is pregnant,
if you want any extra help,
you're welcome to come by.
We could all
lock down together.
Oh, I hate the damn Purge.
It's hard to be social
on that night.
- But thank you for the invite.
- Anytime.
- Baby, that smells so good.
- Mm.
I'm going to the kitchen.
Y'all need anything?
You want another beer?
- Yeah, yeah, I'll take one.
- Another beer.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, honey.
I don't know. I just feel like
a goddamn Hoover these days.
Everything in my line of sight
just gets consumed.
Even things I hate.
You know, Anna's been
cooking for us
the most amazing Mexican food,
am I right?
- Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
- It's so good but so fattening.
- I put on five pounds.
- No, you have not.
Mm-hmm.
You know...
Anna has a sister.
Also a nanny.
- You should meet her.
- Yeah, we're all right.
What, baby?
We don't need
to meet her sister.
We're fine.
Thank you, though.
Baby, Emily's just trying to be
nice and help out, right?
So you're being
a little bit rude.
Oh, was I?
My apologies, Emily.
Oh, it's fine.
It's just it's really hard
to find good help,
- and Anna's sister's a sweetheart.
- Yeah.
We don't need to meet
Anna's sister, Emily.
I don't even know
if I want our kids
speaking Spanish in this house.
Now, thank you for the offer,
but, no, thank you.
Okay, then.
This is your learn English app.
Lesson 12:
Past tense sentences.
- Past tense sentences.
- Who would've thought
I would be in Texas?
Who would've, who would've...
I would be in Texas... Texas?
Who would've thought
I would be in Texas?
Who would have
thought I would be in Texas?
Who... who would have thought
I would be in Texas?
I was just visiting
friends in Texas.
Repeat after me.
I was just visiting friends
in Texas.
Hey, Juan.
Kirk tells me that
you were late this morning.
I'm never late, sir.
You're never late?
Hey, Kirk, Juan here
says you're lying.
Juan's a free man.
He can say whatever he wants.
You know, Juan,
you show up late again,
I'm gonna have to fire you.
That's the rules.
Yes, sir.
Hey, you know
what somebody else told me?
That he found your lariat
just laying
in the front of the stable
on the ground.
Is that true?
No, sir.
It's called "La Riata."
T.T., your Purge
protection bonus.
- Thank you, Mr. Tucker.
- Stay safe.
Thank you, sir.
Kirk.
You're doing a good job, Juan.
My son's a hair rattled
'cause of yesterday.
Don't take offense.
Thank you, sir.
I really appreciate that.
Can I be honest, Mr. Tucker?
Please do.
Your son doesn't like me
because...
I'm Mexican.
And I think Dylan believes
a cowboy shouldn't be
from México or...
Argentina
or from somewhere else.
I know that a lot of people
feel that way,
but I'm not sure
that's the case with Dylan.
Uh, he's a very proud man.
You one-upped him yesterday.
You're a damn fine cowboy,
Juan.
I don't know, sir.
Well...
I don't know either.
I just...
I always taught my son
to be a proud American,
but maybe I didn't really
teach him what that meant.
I don't even know if I know
what that means anymore,
proud American.
World's changing all around us.
At each other's throats.
Confusing times.
I want to give you...
...the goddamn
Purge protection bonus.
Stay safe.
Thank you.
That money's nothing
but a way for these people
to keep us alive so they can
continue using our slave labor.
We're nothing more than that.
I know what I'm-a use
my money for, though,
and it's not for protection.
Crazy man.
We are now just one hour away
from the annual Purge.
As always,
home is the best place to be,
and we sure hope you're not
out there stuck in traffic.
We strongly advise you
to get yourself
and those you care about
to a safe place.
So lock those doors,
set those security systems,
and stay inside
for the next 12 hours.
And for those of you
who are partaking,
may God be with you all.
It's one hour.
T.T. said he would be here
right now.
- He's coming.
- Ay.
Spring is
coming, and so is the Purge.
I've decided that I don't want
to be called Granddaddy...
We spoke with
tribal leader Chiago Harjo
- earlier today.
- You had your chance.
Well, what the hell
do you want to be called, Dad?
I want to be called
Grandfather.
See, my people have been
watching from the sidelines,
and we see that America's
reached a boiling point.
Hatred like that
can't be contained.
You'll burn your cities
to the ground.
I'm gonna lock down now, y'all.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
We're almost there, guys.
We're almost there.
Captain.
Good to see you.
Other half when the job's done?
I know you're good for it, T.T.
All right.
Make
your way inside. Keep moving.
We will not be opening
our doors until 7:00 tomorrow
when the Purge is over.
Are you sure we are
gonna be safe here?
Of course. Trust me.
We're not gonna die
on the first one, right?
Don't jinx it.
Get comfortable.
We'll be here for the next 12 hours.
Make yourself at home.
Okay, hold on,
hold on, hold on.
Look at this.
Good.
Wait, what?
- Dang.
- What? How did you know how to do that?
The national holiday
celebrating
our American freedom
is finally back.
Good night, Texas,
and good luck.
It's starting, y'all.
This is not a test.
This is your
Emergency Broadcast System
announcing the commencement
of the annual Purge
sanctioned by
the U.S. government.
Weapons of Class 4 and lower have been
authorized for use during the Purge.
All other weapons
are restricted.
Government officials
of ranking 10...
...have been granted immunity
from the Purge
and shall not be harmed.
Commencing at the siren,
any and all crime,
including murder...
...will be legal for
12 continuous hours.
Police, fire,
and emergency medical services
will be unavailable
until tomorrow morning...
...at 7:00 a.m.
when the Purge concludes.
Blessed be
our New Founding Fathers
and America, a nation reborn.
May God be with you all.
Hmm.
Well...
Never! Never again!
This reminds me of home, Adela.
This is home now.
You know what I mean.
Maybe you're right.
Maybe we have to forget
where we came from.
And accept where we are.
When in America.
Like you said.
No, that's not what I meant.
What did you mean, then?
That America is everything.
What the hell are
you talking about, Adela?
America is México.
America is Africa.
America is Italia.
We can take it all,
we can learn it all,
and we can embrace it.
You really believe that?
That's what I choose
to believe.
You're so crazy.
Stupid.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Baby.
- Jesus.
- What?
- Put the gun down.
What are you doing out here?
I thought I heard something.
It's this damn night.
Dylan Tucker, cut the shit.
Fuck the Purge.
Fuck the NFFA.
They don't get to dictate
how we live our life.
This is our country, okay?
And we can choose to bring
a baby into a world of love.
Why are you laughing at me?
- Damn, honey.
- What?
You just kind of turned me on.
Hurry up!
Ma'am, you should
go back inside.
Just need some air, you know,
just for a moment.
It's my first Purge.
- Is it what you expected?
- Well, there's parts of México
that sound like this
every night.
We got a nice spot here.
Quiet.
Good for you,
easy money for us.
You should get back.
Three bogeys inbound.
Do not try to hide.
We are the real patriots
of America.
It is our job to keep this land
free and clean.
We will no longer tolerate foreigners
raping and pillaging
the United States of America.
We will find you
and disinfect you.
America will be American
once again.
Those guys are fucking insane.
The purification of America
has begun.
What the fuck are they doing?
Help me! Help!
- I have a clear shot.
- Don't.
You'll start a war and put
all your people in jeopardy.
We will not stop until
our great nation
has been fully cleansed.
We will no longer tolerate
foreigners raping and pillaging
the United States of America.
Do not try to hide.
We will find you
and disinfect you.
America will be
American once again.
Hey.
Where'd you learn
to handle a weapon like that?
Oh, my God.
It's over.
We made it through.
I see you. I see you.
Harp?
Come on, let's get to work.
- Harper.
- Sis, come on, let's go.
The day after the Purge
should be a holiday.
No?
¿Qué es un holiday?
Holiday? Mm.
It's a holy day, a festive day.
Another day, another dollar.
Take it easy.
Mira.
Ah, chingado.
...busy, jubilant street,
sanitation crews
are out in full force
with the macabre task
of disinfecting streets
and cleaning corpses
from sidewalks and roadways.
The Purge is over,
and now the cleanup has begun.
All over the state, violent
incidents ended hours ago...
Fake news!
Where is everybody?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What the hell?
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
¡Ayúdenme!
Help!
Why is the gate open?
Help me.
Help!
You can't do this today!
The Purge is over!
No, no.
This is the Forever Purge.
It's never stopping.
¡Ayúdenme!
Thank you
for your participation.
Fuck!
¡Ayúdenme! Help!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
But the Purge is over!
Help!
Please!
Boss!
Watch out!
You're gonna fucking die!
You're all gonna die!
Help! Boss!
Be careful!
Boss!
Are you okay?
Boss.
- You okay?
- Yes.
Come here.
- You all right?
- Yes.
Fuck you!
Go! Darius, go!
Drop your weapon!
- On your knees. Drop it.
- We didn't do anything.
- Get on your knees.
- They attacked us!
- We didn't do anything.
The Purge is over, lady.
What the hell are you doing?
Sir, this is a mistake!
- Wait, please!
- We didn't do anything wrong!
Listen to me.
Listen to us, sir!
It's so quiet.
Where is everyone?
Look over there.
Oh, come on.
Stop the car.
Let's get them before
they go too far.
Well, well, well.
Look at this.
This feels like
fucking Christmas.
Any of y'all get me a present?
Caleb, I know you did,
and let me tell you, sir...
I spent your money well.
Today's your day
of reckoning, cowboy.
You become me
and I become you, huh?
The old switcheroo is happening
on every ranch around here.
You and all your rich-ass
neighbors will find out
what it's like to be
penniless and powerless.
To be like us!
These rich motherfuckers
can't hide
behind their steel walls
no more.
This is the way
things are now, boys!
This Purge is forever!
Yeah.
This is the real Purge.
The eternal Purge.
Ever After!
It came from the house.
Run.
Ay, cabrón.
I'm gonna give you a chance
to save your family,
Dylan Tucker,
one by one,
but you'll have to pay.
Let's start with
eeny, meeny,
miny, ho!
How much would you give
for her, Dylan?
How much would you give to
stop me from putting a bullet
in your baby sister's head?
Let's say ten bucks,
and she lives.
Oh, that seems like
a fair market price
for this broke-down,
useless woman.
Let's see
how much money you got.
Aw, shit, Dylan! I forgot.
You're me now,
which means you're broke.
You have no money.
That sucks, doesn't it?
See, Dylan, without money,
you have no power.
Without money, you can't save
your own little sister,
and she will die because of it.
But how's that feel?
How's that feel, Dylan?
Feels like shit, doesn't it?
That's my life.
It's our life.
That's how we feel.
That's how we have felt
every day
since the day we were born!
And I want you to fucking feel
that fucking pain
in your fucking stomach, Dylan!
Goddamn it,
it looks like the old man's
got something to say! What?!
Damn it! You're right, Kirk!
You're right!
- You're right!
- I don't give a fuck if you think I'm right!
You're talking about
life in America,
the way the rich get rich
off the backs of the poor,
the way it's been
ever since we robbed this land
from the Native Americans.
But you got no right
to complain about the
very system you're supporting
by picking up that gun
and sanctioning
the goddamn Purge...
We need more guns.
...which is all about money.
You know who created
the Purge, don't ya?
A bunch of fat, rich
businessmen in Washington, D.C.
So what would
that make you, Kirk?
What would it make you?
Huh? That would make you
their lackey
and a goddamn hypocrite.
They expect you to go out there
and do their violence,
so they can play more golf.
They've never even been
in a fistfight.
You take the guys on the left,
and I'll take the right.
So...
from my family to you,
go fuck yourself.
Puto.
Take cover!
We need backup!
Copy that. We're on our way.
Untie them, I'll cover you!
Harper.
What the fuck?!
What the fuck, Kirk?!
- Dad?
- The Purge is over, cabrón!
Ever After.
The Purge is over, man!
Cuidado. They're coming.
You need to get up here.
- Go!
- Let's go!
You need to get your family!
Harper! Come on!
Harper! Let's go.
Let's go, let's go.
- Come on!
- Come on.
Come on.
Come in.
10-13, we have
three more incidences reported.
Return to precinct.
Copy that.
This is insane.
People not hear the sirens?
- A little busier than last year, huh?
- Yeah.
I shouldn't even be here.
I did nothing wrong.
There's no such thing
as crime anymore.
Let me fucking go!
Would you shut the fuck up?
Make me.
What's going on, Darius?
I don't know.
Adela.
Call me back, please!
No luck?
All right,
let me check the radio.
Maybe there's some news.
People are still purging
all across the country.
"Ever After Purge" is popping
up all over social media,
continuous purging dubbed
the "Forever Purge."
Where the hell are we gonna go?
We'll find somewhere safe.
First we help Juan
find his wife,
then we find somewhere safe.
Stay inside your homes.
Rosa?
What happened?
A police van?
Why the...
Take care of yourself, Rosa.
Gracias.
...they will take
action to stop it.
- But still, no one knows...
- I know where she is.
...who defined this movement.
Ever After. Ever After.
This is the first...
real... Purge.
It's never gonna stop.
Let me fucking go!
Shit.
It's blocked.
Hold on.
The station is
just a few blocks away.
I hope she'll be there.
We can walk from here.
You go get your wife.
We'll stay here
and protect the truck.
But you move fast.
It's not safe here.
You don't need to wait for us.
Yes, we do.
I'm coming with you.
You don't have to do that.
No, you don't have to do that.
Yeah, I do.
They saved our lives.
We'll be right here. Now go.
Come on.
I'll take the back.
Come on, guys.
This side.
Verga.
That is a .30-06.
.30-30.
Yeah, yeah.
AR-15.
Listen to that rhythm.
That is a Glock.
Listen to that bass.
Double-barrel shotgun.
AK-47.
Homegrown music from
the heartland right there.
That is American music,
motherfucker.
Damn!
Oh!
Strike up the band!
The symphony sings!
Hold on! We're under attack!
Dispatch!
We're outside the precinct!
Request backup!
Boom, boom, boom!
What?
Okay.
Honey...
I need you to take this.
Don't ask any questions,
not right now.
I'm gonna get out the car.
I need you to lock the door.
- Okay.
- I'll be right back.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Open up, bitch.
Baby!
No!
- Yeah!
- Cover me!
Go, go, go! Forever Purge!
You're fucking dead, puta!
Fucking pig!
Get...
Get off me!
You're a pig!
Get the fuck off of me!
Stop fighting it!
Fucking pig!
You're a pig!
Motherfucker!
Help me!
Fucking pig!
Kill him!
- Move.
- Forever Purge!
Open it up!
- Get out of the way!
- Ever After!
Now these assholes
are really pissing me off.
What was that?
Juan?
- Adela.
- Juan!
Juan! Juan.
Purge forever!
- De nada.
- ¡Vamos!
Over here!
The truck is coming!
It's Dylan!
Truck! Get in the truck!
- Get in!
- The truck! Come in!
- Come on, boss.
- No! Find safety now!
I need to get to my family.
- ¡Adela!
- We'll help you.
I'll move faster on my own.
I'll be fine. Just go.
- Go, go, go, go!
- Come on!
Adela, get on!
Here.
You saved my life.
- Thank you, Darius.
- Okay.
Adela!
Okay, let's grab
everything we can.
Peanut butter?
You found the jelly.
This could work.
As the violence escalates
across the country,
we are still trying
to get more information.
That's right, Ruth.
And we are still trying
to figure out
if this Forever Purge was
coordinated or spontaneous.
Various hashtags...
#TooMuchHate,
#OneDayNotEnough...
are all over the Internet.
Fringe conspiracy groups
supporting the Forever Purge
are calling for
a new America to emerge from...
Adela.
I'm scared to have my baby
in this world.
Freedom to hate.
Freedom to purge.
Freedom to die.
The NFFA has advised
that anyone
displaying the Ever After flag
will be arrested immediately.
We're in this together.
Breaking news.
We've just gotten word
that the NFFA
has declared martial law
across the country.
U.S. military will be sent
into nearly every city
to stop the violence
and restore peace.
Citizens are being told
to relinq...
¿Bueno?
¡Bueno!
Wait. Juan, I can't understand
what you're saying.
Come on. The-the cell things.
The-the...
- Towers?
- Yeah, the towers.
The-the cell towers.
They are cutting them.
Hey. We just watched that
a lot of cities have gone dark.
Miami's gone.
Austin is under siege.
First responders
are overwhelmed.
We're in a state of emergency.
It's all over the country.
The violence is spreading
and not stopping.
So there's nowhere safe to go.
There's no way to get help.
There's that symbol again.
This was planned.
I got a map.
I got ammo.
- What?
- Turn it up!
Give it to me.
All right.
Well, we need to make a move.
They're gonna be
coming here for gas.
- Hey. We got news, guys.
- What is it?
I repeat, your safety...
- Take this.
- ...cannot be guaranteed.
All right. Listen up.
Due to the waves of violence
currently sweeping the U.S.,
Mexican President
León García Soler
and Canadian Prime Minister
Sophie Poueche
are opening their borders
for the next six hours.
Mexico and Canada will take in
anyone from America unarmed
and give them sanctuary
until order is reestablished
in the U.S.
Both countries will then
close down their borders again
in six hours.
Once again, after six hours,
both borders will be
closing indefinitely.
There are reports of violence
from all corners
of the United States.
We got to go to Mexico.
Other countries
all over the world stand by
in amazement at
what's happening in the U.S.
To recap, Canadian and...
Let's go to Mexico.
Let's go.
We don't have a choice.
Authorities are
urging everyone to get
to the closest border
as soon as possible.
With only three
and a half hours remaining,
thousands of troops
have been gathered...
Entries to Mexico and Canada
are already overwhelmed.
Listeners, do not delay,
and get out while you can.
We will be ending
our broadcast here.
Good luck, America.
Stay safe.
You don't like me,
do you, Dylan?
You don't like Mexicans.
What are you
talking about, Juan?
Come on, be honest.
Let's, uh...
How do you say this?
Uh, slice the shit?
Cut the shit?
Cut the shit. Yeah.
You want to cut the shit?
I want to cut
the shit with you.
All right, I'll cut the shit
with you, Juan.
I got no problem with Mexicans.
But I will say I don't
understand your culture
just like you don't
understand mine.
God's honest truth...
I don't think white people
are any better or worse
than anybody else.
But this I do believe.
We should all just
stick with our own.
Just leave each other alone.
You might be right.
But we are together now.
The hell is that?
Okay, everybody, wake up.
Wake up! Be alert!
Oh, shit.
Jesus Christ.
Ever After?
Holy shit.
Okay, they're coming up on us.
They're shooting at us.
Shit. They're slowing us down.
- Pull over!
- How many are there?
- There are two on this side.
- You stay down.
Just keep driving.
Stop this truck! Now!
Stay down. Everyone stay down.
Stop this truck!
- I'm just gonna run him over.
- No, baby.
- No, baby, wait.
- Wait. Wait.
- Don't. I got an idea.
- What?
Don't do it.
There's too many of them.
Juan, get away from the window.
Stay away from the window.
Ever After, motherfuckers!
Pull that fucking truck over!
Ever After!
She's one of us!
Purge Ever After!
They're going away.
¿Estás bien?
Way to go, Harper.
The border will close
in three hours.
Attention.
This area is under martial law.
Weapons are not permitted.
This is the NFFA.
Lay down your weapons,
or you will be shot.
Clear the area.
I repeat, clear the area.
Surrender your weapons...
The hell is that?
Oh, my God.
Holy shit.
The crossing point
is only one mile away.
There's no way through.
It's blocked.
What should I do?
How are we
supposed to get through?
We find a way, Cassidy.
Just keep driving.
We got less than three hours.
Oh, please don't break down.
Come on, baby.
We're nearly there.
Baby, be careful.
- It's blocked.
- What?
She's broke down.
Come on, we got to get out.
The border's just
a few blocks from here.
We can make it.
Everybody, you follow Juan.
Get ready. Stay low.
Stay together.
I cover you in three, two, one.
Come on! Come on!
This is the NFFA.
Go! Let's go, let's go!
Lay down your weapons,
or you will be shot.
Purge this country!
Clear the area.
I repeat, clear the area.
Stay close, guys.
Dylan, cover the back.
Stay close.
- Mano derecha.
- T.T., cover the right.
Cuida tu derecha.
Juan! Go, go!
Clear!
Move, move!
I'm behind you.
Stay close.
Revolution!
Get to the wall.
Come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
There's the wall, guys.
Those are innocents.
Let 'em through.
Kill them brownies!
Dylan, get back.
They have a .50 caliber.
Stay with me. Stay with me.
Oh, shit!
- Let's use it as cover.
- Surrender your weapons...
- Let's go!
- You guys go to the wall!
Get cover! Get cover!
Move, move!
This is the NFFA...
To the diner! The diner!
Go, guys!
Go ahead, go ahead, go ahead.
Clear the area.
Stay close.
Come on!
We're gonna go across!
Come on, guys!
Let's go! Let's go!
Put your heads down
when you come in.
- We can go. Stay back.
- Keep your head down.
- Keep your body down. Go.
- Yeah, yeah.
We need to keep up.
Follow me, okay?
Stay down. Stay down.
- What is that?
- It's a tank.
We're gonna go across
to the theater!
- Across to the theater.
- Okay.
When the truck passes,
let's make a run.
We have to cross right now!
There's a fucking tank
down there.
Come on! Come on!
Oh, my gosh!
Come on. Get in.
Get in. Get in.
- Come on!
- Tank is on move!
This is the NFFA.
Hey.
Adela.
No, no, no. Come on!
- Adela.
- Juan?
- Are you okay?
- Juan.
- It's blocked.
- Are you guys okay?
Adela, we'll go around.
Find another way out.
- Baby?
- I can't get it open!
- Baby, open the door.
Baby?
The border will close
- in two hours and 30 minutes.
- Come on.
Attention.
This area is under martial law.
We people of the mountains
believe, at the castle...
He wants me to ask
if you can wait
and go on after sunrise.
Well, I'm sorry, but
there's a carriage meeting me
at Borgo Pass at midnight.
- Borgo Pass?
- Yes.
Whose carriage?
Count Dracula's.
- Count Dracula's?
- Yes.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Castle Dracula?
Yes, that's where I'm going.
- To the castle?
- Yes.
Fuck.
A fucking bat.
...at the castle,
there are vampires.
Dracula and his wives.
They take the form of wolves...
Attention.
This area is under martial law.
Weapons are not permitted.
Oh, shit.
There's another tank.
We can't go around.
- Wait. Wait here.
- Okay.
All clear.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Let's get out of here.
- All good?
- Behind you!
T.T.
Look.
It's the roses.
There.
Stay next to the wall, okay?
Return to your homes.
I repeat, return to your homes.
Stay next to me.
I need to get to my wife.
What are you looking for?
We Mexicans leave signs
all over our city
to help each other.
Adela is following them.
If we want to find our wives,
we should do the same thing.
Go on.
Fuck.
Return to your homes.
- Hold this.
- Okay. Okay.
I repeat, return to your homes.
Adela.
Yes?
How come you know
how to fight like that?
I was part of the autodefensas.
What?
A group of women
fighting the cartels.
We did damage to them.
They forced me and Juan
off our land.
This is how we got here
to the States.
Here.
For you.
Okay.
Army's passed. Come on.
- Okay.
- Stay with me.
Let's go.
The border
will close in two hours
and 15 minutes.
Drop it! Move or I kill you.
Hand 'em over. Down.
Drop your weapons.
There's nothing you can do.
Drop 'em.
You, too, amigo.
Come on, now.
You're surrounded.
You will be shot.
That a boy.
It's all right, pretty thing.
Come on, now.
Do it.
Nice and easy. Good.
You fucking deaf, son?
Good boy.
Look what we got here.
Couple of bad hombres.
Well, I'll be.
- There's two of us and two of them.
- Mm.
That right there is
what's wrong with this country.
What do you want to do
about 'em, Daddy?
Why don't we give
our fellow Americans here
an opportunity
to redeem themselves?
Yeah, I like the sound of that.
Mm, let me explain.
You kill the brownies,
and the two of you can live,
stay here in this great,
God-loving country.
Help us purify this nation
once and for all.
That's what the
Ever After Purge is all about.
Fuck you, redneck.
Yeah, fuck you, pig.
No, fuck you, bitch!
This country's gone haywire.
It don't know itself no more.
You don't fucking
know yourself.
Mother, Mother,
Mother, it's okay.
Look in the fucking mirror!
Mother! Hey, it's okay.
Maybe this will help y'all.
You happy now?
Mother.
Gladly.
T.T., no!
Trinidad. ¿Estás bien?
Let the purification begin.
You whore.
Fucking dying?
Oh, you fucking little beaner.
You fucking ain't worth shit.
Get the fuck back.
Don't even think about it,
brownie.
This is the NFFA!
Lay down your weapons,
or you will be shot.
Shoot the pigs!
Mother! Call for backup!
Shit.
Backup! Backup!
We need backup, goddamn it!
Backup's coming, baby.
Fuck!
Mother, no! No!
- Mother!
- Harper, let's go!
Mother!
- Take cover!
- RPG!
Mother!
Mother, no.
No, no, Mother.
This is Alpha Leader.
Request recon, all units.
It's here.
If our men are alive,
they will be here.
Help me with the door.
Are you sure that this is safe?
The rose.
It's here.
Stay over there.
Are you sure that they're here?
They have to be.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Drop the weapons!
Who the fuck are you?
We followed the signs.
And the white girl?
She's with me.
She's pregnant. Don't scare her.
Está bien.
Follow me.
You're the last ones.
Sit down.
I don't see them.
Where are they?
The border
will close in two hours.
Adela. Adela.
Ay.
Cassie. Oh, my God.
You okay?
T.T.?
What happened?
We have breaking news now.
This is just coming in.
We have been notified
that there has been
an attack in El Paso
at a U.S. Army military base.
As a result,
the NFFA is pulling all
military troops out of El Paso.
Again, the military is
retreating out of El Paso
after suffering massive losses
in their battle
against purgers,
including an attack
on a U.S. Army base.
And now
I'm hearing that in response
to the Army's withdrawal,
Mexico will now be closing
their El Paso border
crossing point immediately.
Again, the El Paso border point
will no longer be open
to United States citizens
fleeing the Forever Purge.
Americans left behind
at the now closed border wall
are being slaughtered
by purgers. It is a war.
El Paso has fallen
to Ever After purgers
who are going door-to-door
hunting down anyone
who is not a part
of their hate group.
The border is now closed.
At this point, already,
you can feel there's
a change in the air...
This city's gonna get
even worse.
Ven. Come.
Get out the back.
Find Chiago.
Move fast.
Tell him to meet us
in the corner of, uh,
Amboy and Highland.
Tell him,
if he doesn't do this,
many good people will die,
including me. Okay?
Yes, boss.
Okay, let's go! Follow me.
- I know a way to safety.
- Come on! Come on!
I need you to stand up
and walk with us, okay?
- Okay. I can do it.
- Can you do that?
- Come on, come on, come on.
- Come on, baby. Come on. - Okay.
¡Vámonos, cabrónes!! Por allá!
- Órale.
- Vamos.
The purification will not stop.
This city is now occupied by
the real patriots of America.
Our duty is to uphold
American beliefs and values
while keeping America
pure and free
from refugees and terrorists.
We have taken back
what is lawfully ours,
and we will now embark
on purification of our nation,
city by city.
Only full-blooded Americans
are welcome here.
All invaders will be purged.
We control El Paso
and all of Texas.
The purification will not stop.
This city is now occupied by
the real patriots of America.
You're clear.
Just keep your voices down.
Listen. Don't worry.
- Try to stay calm.
- Head down.
Who's that?
It's okay. It's okay.
Is it here?
Guys?
It's them.
- Hey.
- It's them!
Chiago, take us
to Mexico, please.
Get 'em on board.
We're leaving.
Gracias, Chiago.
Okay. Come on, come on, come on.
- Come on.
- Come on, this way.
- They're here.
- Go, get in the truck.
Come on, let's go, let's go.
Alpha Leader, come in.
Alpha Leader, do you copy?
- We've found 'em.
- Where?
They're headed for the border
through the reservation.
Follow 'em. Don't lose 'em.
I'll catch up.
How are you getting us across?
My tribe has lived
right on the border
of the U.S. and Mexico
for centuries.
We were the only people
who could legally cross.
Then the wall split us.
But there are parts of
the terrain los pendejos
can't build the wall on.
Too dangerous.
And we use it to make passage.
We'll take you through.
Some of you deserve
another chance.
Are you in labor?
Mm.
Cassie, we got
to get you to Mexico.
I know it's bad timing, baby.
You'll be okay.
There'll be help
when we get across.
Camps have been set up, okay?
Thank you.
Dylan.
Look.
Damn it.
Juan?
Yeah?
Looks like
we got trouble coming.
Motherfucker.
They're here.
- Let's go. Come on, people.
- Go, go, go!
This is the crossing point!
We're on foot from here!
Let's go!
- Let's move! Fast!
- Come on, let's go!
Follow me!
I will guide you!
Vámonos.
They're getting close.
- Follow me.
- We need to move.
- Hey, honey?
- Yeah?
You go let these people get you
across the border, okay?
- Baby, where are you going?
- Yeah, you go ahead.
I love you.
I'll be right behind you.
- Baby, you have to go with me.
- Go on.
- Don't leave me.
- Go. I have to stop them.
- No, baby. You cannot leave me.
- You just focus on the baby.
- Okay?
- Cassie, I'll protect you.
- Thank you, sister.
- Yeah.
You got her?
We'll see you over there,
all right?
Get her to the medics
in Mexico.
Get 'em
across the border safely!
Rápido.
That's it. On here.
Sit on it.
Put your knees underneath it.
Yeah, I'm low on ammo.
- You guys got ammo?
- We have a few guns,
but when the bullets run dry,
draw them in close, use blades.
Give me a magazine.
It's the last round of ammo.
Make it count.
- We'll help you.
- But it's not your fight.
We've been fighting this fight
for 500 years.
Take what you need.
This is our last stand.
On my ready!
Let 'em get close!
Wait for 'em!
Wait for it!
Are you okay?
- Help her.
- Take my hand.
Now!
Go. Go, go, go.
¡A chingar a su madre,
cabrones!
Take cover! Now!
I'm out!
- Go!
- Come on.
Damn it.
I'm out!
- Yeah, I'm out, too.
- I have one left.
Come on, motherfucker!
Fuck.
Hunt 'em down and kill 'em all.
Save that Mexican
son of a bitch for me.
Purge and purify, Ever After!
Ever After!
They're coming.
Good.
We slow them down.
Give our people more time
to get across safely.
You guys stay in here.
We'll cover the back room.
I love you.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
We got this handled here.
Rest of you go stop 'em
from crossing the border.
- On it.
- Got it.
Let's go.
We're gaining on 'em.
They can't be far.
Adela!
Adela. Adela.
Adela, wake up.
There he is. Grab him!
Adela!
Fucking whore!
Call your people
and tell 'em you need help.
Call out now!
- Kill this fucking pig!
- Fucking English!
Kill this pig!
Translate!
What are you saying?!
I said speak English!
Translate!
- Kill him!
- Speak fucking English!
Kill him!
I'll do it!
Speak English!
I will cut your throat!
Speak...
I got him.
Does this translate?
Pendejo.
Are you okay, my love?
You made it.
You just crossed into México.
She'll be there.
- Gracias.
Thank you.
We owe you our lives.
Hospital?
Hospital? ¿Médico?
- Sí.
- Here?
I love you so much.
I love you.
- Dylan.
- Baby.
- Oh, my...
- You made it.
Look who's here.
Oh, my God.
- Baby.
- Hi.
- It's a girl.
- It's a girl?
You want to hold your daughter?
- Can I?
- Please.
Hey.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
Thank you.
Congratulations, Dad.
Gracias, Juan.
Muchas gracias, Adela.
It's a girl. It's a girl.
...sheltering over
two million
American refugees and...
Who knows what will become
of these American Dreamers?
There is no end in sight
to the violence and uprising.
As of today, the NFFA
has sent the military into
every major city and county.
The NFFA is being
destroyed by their own
creation, as the Purge
can no longer be contained
to just one night a year.
In New York, ordinary citizens
are picking up weapons.
They're warring with Forever
Purgers in Times Square.
Reports are now
coming in that large groups
of Americans are banding
together and fighting back
against these purgers, against
hate, fear and violence.
All of the United
States as we once knew it
- may be disappearing...
- Who knows?
What will the new America
look like when this all ends?
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull