Bedtime's 10:30,
no matter what he says.
And, oh vegetables, can't go
six weeks on pizza, okay?
And you remember
he's allergic to
shellfish? To shellfish, I know.
It's Vermont, people don't
go for the oysters.
I can't believe you're
going to Vermont.
I couldn't drag you there when
we were married, I tried.
You did.
You're not flipping
again, right?
No, it's just over and
out, six weeks tops.
Is there a rule for
phone time for Finn?
You're kidding right?
After his latest stunt?
His phone time is zero, the
phone stays in New York.
I hate you. Finn,
you cannot talk.
Calm down, I'll talk to him.
To your mother...
What? Calm down, I'll...
We don't need to do this.
Calm down, are you kidding me?
You are not here!
You have no idea what's
going on here, you don't!
I'm just trying
to keep him safe,
and I am all alone in this!
Up against the internet,
random shootings,
other people's bad kids,
the planet dying,
and now this President?
What am I supposed to...
Okay, yeah,
go ahead you tell me
what I'm supposed
to say to a little boy?
I don't know.
You're right, I don't know.
Hey bucko, it's time to go!
What's the matter?
The smell!
Oh that's just fresh air.
Vermont in May, doesn't
get any fresher.
It's cow shit.
Yeah, the freshest though.
Dad, don't.
No you're right, let's
sulk, that's more fun.
There's nothing here.
You've been banished.
People who have been
banished get sent
to places where there's
nothing, that's how it works.
Look I know this is not
your choice, so already
we're off on the
wrong, you know...
I talked to your mother
about what happened,
I'm not even going to
go into all that but,
all I know is that I've
never seen her so upset.
I just don't want this trip
to be a disappointment.
I'm already disappointed.
Yeah well, me too.
Why? I guess I was hoping
I'd catch you on
the 12 side of 12,
instead of the 13 side of 12.
'Cause the kid I used to know,
would have loved this place.
Whose house?
I bought it.
Wait, it's yours?
But didn't someone
else hire you to like
fix it up or something?
Yeah, that's what I
told your mother.
You lied to her?
Yes a little bit,
more of a fib really. Why?
'Cause I'm flipping it,
and your mother hates it
when I flip houses, she
thinks it's gambling.
Flipping it like, over?
No, it means, you
buy it for cheap,
put a little money in it so
it looks nicer, worth more,
then you try to sell
it again for a profit.
What if it doesn't flip
over and you can't sell it?
It'll flip.
I'm gonna cut my hand off.
That's exactly what
your mother said.
Screw her what does she know!
Hey!
Shit.
Yeah?
What, oh right,
Rick, the wiring.
So what...
Uh great, that's great.
Yeah I'll leave the
bulkhead open,
the fuse box is right in...
Okay, great, do your thing.
All right thanks, bye.
Gonna take her side now?
I'm not taking anyone's side.
But your mother does
have some valid points,
you have to admit. She
broke into my computer.
It came with rules,
and you knew that.
Dad, imagine the only
thing between you,
and pretty much every answer
to every question you have,
right, is a door, you're
not supposed to open,
one with a real
crappy lock on it?
Wouldn't you break the crappy
lock and at least take a peek?
How much of a peek did you take?
Tell me people got
chopped up here.
I don't know, sorry
to disappoint.
That's something they'd
have to disclose.
What's disclosed?
That means they'd have
to tell me if somebody
got chopped here and
they didn't tell me.
Damn.
Whoa.
Something smells nasty in here.
I'd say when we open the
flue in this thing,
we're gonna get a
little present.
What kind of present? A
furry, dead present.
Plumbing's not fixed, yet.
Let's not fix it.
Then you won't try to cook.
Oh nice burn. Yeah, nice burn
like every food you ever...
Now you lost it.
Don't push it, never
double-down on a good burn.
Right. Microwave,
number for the pizza
guy, all we need.
All we need.
Rain is starting to
come through this guy
and rot the wood.
Gonna have to switch those out.
Like, for horses.
Yeah, there probably was, once.
We should turn this into
something cool like,
a movie theater.
Who needs horses?
Well your mom had
horses growing up.
Really?
Yeah, I never much
cared for 'em,
but she loved the damn things.
Probably still does.
Right, she had these
little pictures,
Yeah, that she
painted on on her...
The walls, little animals.
What, I remember things.
It's been a while but I do.
Did you...
Is this my stuff?
Yeah.
I had some things
sent up from storage.
I wanted you to feel
at home I guess.
What? Nothing.
No you don't feel at home,
it's stupid and you hate it.
Look at you, you
totally hate it.
Dad, it's just...
A little too young.
I asked your mom what
she thought you'd like.
She doesn't know everything.
I can't wait to tell her that.
You still like those things?
Sure.
I can't do 'em, they
give me a headache.
It's kind of like, you
have to look at it,
like you're looking at
something far away,
even though it's up close.
I can't do it.
What's the picture of?
I'm not telling.
I'll get you some more
grown up decorations soon.
Maybe a gun closet and
some booby posters.
Whoa easy!
Well here's another wrong
we have to make right.
We're the house
doctors, you and me.
Get in there where the bad
parts are and make 'em good.
Turn this into some place
someone would want to live.
So these, are the guts.
And she's got really bad guts.
Bad pipes, bad wires...
And this...
This is the heart.
Here she's got a bad heart too.
It's barely pumping.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Even though I can't find a
single thing wrong with it.
Which is bad news for us
because up here in May
it's cold as balls
and we do not ha...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
, what's happening?
Sh!
Jesus Christ the hell are you?
Wait wait, wait, wait!
Just, the electrician!
You said to come in through the
bulkhead and I just thought,
sorry, I'm sorry. Jesus Christ!
I, died for a second.
Don't even think about it.
Why, you don't even inhale.
I'm not the best
father, but I'm not
trying to win a prize about it.
Better settle for
second-hand, chief!
So uh, it's a mess in there.
You got broken fuses,
outdated everything.
Awesome. Plus you got a main
line clipped on the
outside, but uh,
I've already taken care of that.
Wait, clipped?
Like someone cut it
clipped, like on purpose?
Looks like.
Kids maybe, or uh, I don't know,
but like I said, taken care of.
Thanks.
Well this is Finn by the way.
Louis.
Hi.
I'm also your neighbor,
uh, closest thing you got
out here anyway, about a quarter
mile down South Street.
It's a bit far to run for
a stick of butter but uh,
anything you ever need just...
Something wrong? No.
You mind if we move
up to the porch.
It's getting kind of chilly?
I prefer it here actually.
You don't much like this place.
I, I don't like it no.
Why not?
Don't worry, we're not moving
in, we're flipping it over.
I don't know
what they told you already...
Just that nobody got chopped up.
That's right, boring...
So they didn't tell
you about her?
I guess they wouldn't have to.
About what?
Lady who lived here
when I was a kid.
Um...
She died?
Yes!
Let's see if you're saying that
one o'clock in the morning.
She was the kind of lady
that kids would call a,
witch, or whatever.
But that's normal, it's just the
usual small town stuff, right?
Uh, cute, or whatever.
But this was not cute.
What'd she do? Uh...
Go on.
I guess it was a good house
once, back before I was born.
But for me it was
always her house.
She did have a family back
then, husband and a son but,
they died on the farm, badly,
got caught up in the hay bailer.
Nasty stuff.
Rumor was it she
done it herself.
Why would she do that?
Well, most people I think,
generally try and do good but,
this woman was, the other way.
But I'll tell you this, she
liked that people were scared.
She liked it, being
in your head.
And what really scared me, was
seeing how scared my mom was.
Now that I got a kid
of my own I get it,
she knew something that
bad was that close.
And she couldn't keep me safe.
She used to sit, right up there
in the window in the front,
just watching.
One summer we all got
to noticing that uh,
she never seemed to
leave that spot.
Day and night.
So finally someone caught
wise and called it in and,
sure enough, she'd been dead
up there, three, four weeks.
I think they said it
was a heart failure.
What was her name?
What? Her name.
You never said it.
Ha, I guess I don't
much like saying it.
Her name was, Lydia.
What are those?
Something wrong?
Yep, I got a hole in my heart.
Well, obviously.
No really.
It's a tiny one, a lot
of people have them.
Since when have you had it?
Since forever, but I only
found out about it last year
when I was in California.
Can it get bad?
It sounds bad, can you die?
There's a better chance
of us being hit by
an asteroid while we sleep.
Is it cold in your room?
As balls. Okay there's blankets
next to...
Where did you hear that,
did you hear me say that?
Yes.
Well...
Okay there's some extra blankets
next to your bed.
We'll get on that
furnace tomorrow.
I'm next door if you need me.
I'm fine.
I'll leave my door open.
I'm fine!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Ah!
What is that?
That is a big fat old dead crow.
There you go no rush, just
see the line in your head,
and don't think too hard.
There you go, nice.
Nice.
Shit.
Who's there?
What's with the lamp?
Oh nothing.
I heard you talking to someone.
Just to myself.
You know...
I'm a little uh...
Dad.
What is it?
Do you think there's something
wrong with the house?
Maybe.
Do you?
I thought I saw someone
in the mirror.
What kind of someone?
I think a lady.
Which mirror?
Oh I'm sure it was just...
What did she look like?
I don't know, it was
too fast, it was
like, a magic eye.
A what? You know,
the picture in my room, the one
with the crazy patternings?
It was kind of like
that, it was like,
you only see it for
a second, then...
You lose it.
Do you think that it's her?
Who?
Lydia! Why are you whispering?
I don't know.
Have you seen something too?
What?
That's the spot.
Do you think it's the
same chair she died in?
No of course not.
You want to leave?
Well maybe we should though.
I'm not scared.
You want to sleep in my room?
You don't have to be brave.
I said I'm not scared.
I know, but...
I'll leave my door open.
Dad. Just in case.
Time to get up bucko.
Not yet.
I-I had this dream.
It's still coming back to me uh,
I was asking someone
if we could stay here.
Stay? I asked her, who was it?
Wait... Like with mom too?
Oh god I remember now!
Lydia!
It was Lydia!
And then, then she showed me
what would happen to you...
You just...
Dad?
Hey Finn will you give
me a hand with this?
Finn! What?
We're gonna pick this
up and carry it back
to the house, okay? Okay.
One, two, three up!
You seem quiet, everything okay?
I'm fine.
Hey there's some mud up ahead.
All right we'll go around it.
You know I've been meaning to...
If you want to talk about
anything you saw when you
took your little you know,
peek at the world wide web...
Please, no, I'm fine.
We don't need to talk
about this right now.
Mmm I'm just saying maybe
there might be some
things I can set the
record straight on,
because there's a lot of
stuff out there that can
give you the...
All right, okay I got!
Thank you.
Oh, no... Wait I
thought you said you
walked around this?
Yeah I tried but
there's just way too much...
Okay stop no no no
this is bad, back up!
Finn, wait ah...
My foot's stuck!
All right hold on.
Where's your, you got your boot?
All my clothes...
So did you look at
that kind of stuff?
What kind of stuff?
Like on the internet?
Thought you didn't want
to talk about that?
Just, never mind...
No no it's just, it's, look...
It's perfectly normal to want
to look at girls, or boys
or whatever... No oh my god Dad
not that kind of stuff!
I just mean like scarier stuff.
Wait did you see
something violent?
Did you see someone get killed?
Where did you see that?
The news, I think, it
was just this guy,
and he was getting his
head chopped off,
and he was screaming, or
at least trying to...
God dammit!
Jesus!
Look Finn...
The world's kind of a
sick place I guess.
Jesus...
Here help me with this thing.
Did you ask your mom about it?
Well...
I think so, she was
just really mad, and,
it was really late, I
was supposed to be
sleeping but I, snuck out.
Only because she was crying.
She was on the phone
with someone crying,
and, I don't know
who it was, but,
she said she was scared
that I knew that the
world had gone all bad and
that it would end and, die.
Why your mom...
I, I guess that's
what she thinks.
She needs to get out of
the city, you both do.
Do you think, that
the world will...
No.
Would you tell me if you did?
No, probably not.
You'd lie? Yeah.
So, I'm not allowed
to lie but you are?
Yep.
And mom? All the time she lies.
My god!
Do you feel bad about it?
Mph, all parents do it,
good ones, crappy ones.
We tell you everything's
okay when it's not okay.
We tell you we're strong
when we're not strong.
We'll tell you there's
no spinach in it
when there's spinach in it.
I knew it.
Anything, so you don't know...
Don't know what?
That you aren't
safe, not really.
More, more more!
What else did you lie
about you lying liar?
Okay so, remember that
automatic dog feeder thing
you made for the science
fair all those years ago?
I said it was great and
you were so clever?
Yeah?
Well that thing was terrible.
It never worked,
the dog hated it, so,
even though you are pretty
much the cleverest,
that time you were
very unclever.
So we pretended,
I mean, we lied.
Right keep pushing, keep
pushing, pull straight down.
Steady, eh, perfect!
You mad?
From now on no bullshit
between us, okay?
No bullshit.
Are you really gonna
sell the house?
Why would you even think...
Do you... No see
that's bullshit!
No no that's, that's stalling,
stalling's different.
Stalling to think of
the right bullshit.
Are you really gonna sell it?
I hope not to, that's
the best I can...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
How did you even know?
I don't know,
it's just everything,
like, my room,
and all this stuff and,
all the time in this...
Did someone come in?
Do you think that...
That sounds like it
came from the basement.
You okay?
Let's go see.
You should go
outside and wait...
Let's go see!
What?
Do you feel that?
A breeze?
It's hot air. So?
That means the heat's on.
I don't believe it.
Well, I guess it's a good thing.
But, how'd it go on?
You know what?
We skipped lunch.
What do you say we
get out of here,
go get some fresh air and maybe,
go to the pizza
instead of inviting
the pizza here for a change?
Go wash up, and grab
your rain coat.
Ow, Jesus!
Dad! Hold on a second.
Dad! What?
Her.
What should we do?
Stay here.
Excuse me...
Excuse me Miss?
I can see you.
Go outside.
Go downstairs Finn, now!
What the hell...
Hello?
Say her name.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Lydia.
I don't think...
Stay!
All right I'm doing this.
What, no!
Dad don't!
Hi hey there Bev. I
was just thinking
about you two.
Uh so listen I'm gonna,
tell you the longer version of
this sometime real soon but,
something's happened. Jesus.
Is he hurt? Just listen.
I'm putting Finn on the
bus in the morning,
to you, back to New York.
Oh no Dad please! He'll
be at Port Authority
by 3:30, look I'm
sorry, this is not the
way I wanted this to happen but,
conditions just aren't
safe in the house and I,
I, I don't know how
to make them safe I,
I don't, I'm sorry.
Okay.
Okay?
What else am I gonna say?
Thank you.
I'll text you details in the
morning once he's on the road.
- Okay bye.
- Bye.
Come on don't look
at me like that.
What do you expect me to do, ,
what if something happened?
How would I...
Do you want to go back in there?
No...
I don't know. Well so then what?
Wha, we can't both leave
as much as I'd love that
but bucko, I'm all in.
I bet the house
literally, and...
Look I know you don't
understand this...
Let's both stay then!
Absolutely not!
It could be the best house,
you know that mom would love it!
That's what I thought
when I first saw it.
Finn, no.
So what, you're gonna
sell it to someone?
Just lie, give it to
some poor family...
I don't know, please!
You shouldn't go in alone,
it's worse if you go in alone.
Please Dad! I won't
sleep in there.
I'll work during the day,
and I'll crash at a motel.
I'll be fine.
I know how to survive
living for a couple weeks
with someone who doesn't
want me there, believe me.
Didn't you hear her?
Who?
Lydia?
She doesn't want you out,
she wants you to stay.
Well then we'll get
along fine, her and me,
'cause that's exactly
what I'm gonna do.
Hey.
Come on, I'll show you my room.
You and I got tot
get on the level
with a few things.
Well, have we not
been on the level?
Nope.
Not really.
You know that first
day I come over,
told you about the
wire's been clipped,
and the power had gone dead.
It was me cut 'em.
What, you?
Why?
I cut 'em four or
five years back uh,
something didn't
seem right and...
I seen her looking out.
So you've... Off and on.
Through the years, yeah.
Didn't, more than sort of
spook me at first but,
then I noticed, a few
days after I'd seen her,
that she'd seen me that,
things weren't right,
in, with my head and um,
the worst of it was
the sleep walking.
Sleep walking?
I'd wake up in the road
between our houses,
just standing there and...
It seemed like every time
I'd be like a step closer,
like she was just,
trying to reel me in or
something, you know.
And then uh, this one time
there was this ice storm,
that knocked the grid
down for a week.
But I'm sure she was still in
there but I didn't see her.
And I slept, stopped
taking my walks.
I got to thinking, maybe
she liked the power on.
So I, I cut it.
And then I had you repair it.
Cursing myself the whole time.
But I knew it would get done,
with me or without me,
so I figured, I might
as well be the one.
At least I could warn you.
But I didn't, 'cause
I'm chickenshit.
And uh I don't know
I guess I just,
hoping it all been in my drunken
god damn skull, you know?
Is that what you think now?
Today I woke up, 3:30 in
the god damn morning,
at the head of your driveway.
You can't keep doing what
you're doing over there.
I have to.
What, for money?
That's all she ever dreamed
of, the perfect country home.
It's old and eccentric, full of
history, and strange noises.
Room for horses.
You're not flipping it?
I was never flipping.
I was keeping it, god damn it!
To surprise her or
to, convince her,
I don't know, anything
to get her...
She love you?
If not well then,
that's something you can't flip.
Trust me. At least I'd have
done something good, for them.
You've seen the house now you
know it's Lydia's house,
not yours, and it's a bad house!
You said yourself, it
was a good house once.
I have to think it can
be a good house again.
I am telling you... Don't!
She can scare the hell out
of me if she wants to,
but what is she
gonna do to me huh?
We're adults, we know
in the real world,
nobody fills in a
death certificate,
cause of death, haunted house!
I just know that, whatever you
fix in that god damn house,
all you're really doing,
is making her stronger.
I love you.
All right.
Are you mad?
Yes.
You can't just...
When did you get off the bus?
Right there, just when you left.
Well then you... What?
Jesus Finn!
Are you gonna help then?
I am helping. You are.
I'm the lookout.
Look at this huh?
Teamwork!
I love your pout, I
think it's funny.
Maybe if you let me s...
You're a New Yorker again
by tomorrow afternoon, no debate,
don't even think about it.
You and I are not gonna strap on
proton packs and try to
save the whole god damn...
Shut up! Hey!
Watch it!
I know what you're thinking.
No, you really don't.
I'm an asshole.
You're wrong. I am?
Yes.
You're my favorite person.
Even if maybe I don't admit
it all the time it's just,
you know, and I always want
to be mad at you because,
I guess Mom always is so...
Really, you're my
favorite person.
My favorite person
doesn't like me enough,
to just, stick around you know?
Finn you and your mother
mean more to me...
Don't say that!
No bullshit remember?
If that were true then why
would you keep leaving?
Because I'm a coward.
It's just, Jesus Finn you...
It's all so scary
you have no idea.
Feeling like, I have this
completely perfect thing,
'cause that's how I feel
about you, just perfect.
And why in the hell
would anyone, give me a
perfect god damn thing when
they should know that,
all I've got are
ways to wreck it?
And so I panic, and
I can't keep still.
And as horrible as it
feels to miss you guys,
it also feels like,
being missed is better
than being there
and being hated.
I wouldn't Dad, I love you.
I love you too Finn!
Oh Jesus.
It's your mother. No!
Don't answer it!
Bev? Hi.
I thought I'd check in.
Um, I don't know what
Finn's already told you.
Um, not much.
He's been pretty quiet since
he got back actually.
Since, what? Finn.
He's been pretty quiet
since he got back today.
Back where? Back home.
You put him on a bus...
What am I not understanding?
You're saying... Are you okay?
I picked him up at Port
Authority just like you asked,
he's eating mac and cheese
right now not 10 feet away.
Put him on. Okay, one sec.
Dad?
Well hey bucko. You okay?
Yeah no, no worries,
all's good, I'm a,
I'm glad you got home safe.
You don't sound okay.
No worries.
I'll check in on you tomorrow.
Okay. I love you.
I'll talk to you tomorrow.
Stay!
Oh shit!
What do you want?
Please, is your dad here?
Jesus, Louis. I'm real sorry,
to see you like this.
Louis I, I don't even
know where to begin.
So tie one on with me eh?
Louis I don't need a
beer, I need help!
I need you, your phone,
or maybe your truck!
I can't give you any
of those things, I-I,
I can't help you at all.
Why not? Because in order
for me to help you, you would
have had to have left.
Left what? Your house.
You never did.
I never...
You never left, your house!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hey!
Simon?
I, I had to come, something in
your voice, what's going on?
Please.
What? Please just, just stop it!
Please don't make
me look at her.
What the hell is going on?
Look at me!
Fuck you!
Would you like to leave?
It's impossible, I
get it, I know.
You can.
No obstacles, no
trick, I promise.
I don't believe you. It's true.
You can walk right back
out into the world.
Abandon the job, beg
for another loan.
Your family stays
in their hellhole.
You leave.
You leave them again.
Or I could stay.
Yes.
Stay like you stayed?
And be with you. No.
You must do this
alone, as I did.
And where would you go?
Free.
I'll stay.
But I have to finish
the job first.
So you finally call back?
Sorry, work's been hard,
I kind of disappeared in it.
Finn won't stop
asking about you.
He's, been having bad dreams.
Are you okay? Fine.
I saw the house Simon, Finn
had photos on his phone
and he has to let me into his
phone now, we made a deal, so,
I saw it. And?
And, I knew
exactly what you're up to.
And?
And, it was a real
nice thought Simon.
I love that you thought it.
Okay.
Look I I'm sorry it's late.
But...
Well is Finn up?
Can I... He's asleep.
It's after 11.
Oh, is it? Well, you want me
to wake him?
Well, if you... Actually,
you know what,
he's been through a lot.
I-I should probably just...
Let him sleep.
That's the best thing.
I think so.
Tell him I love him.
I'll tell him.
Goodnight Simon. Goodnight Bev.
Love you.
Okay...
Okay.
No...
This is so like this
picture I showed him.
Your painting I know,
I hate that painting.
That's really weird, I
was just looking at that
a few weeks ago
after the funeral.
For some reason I
went looking for it.
It's ours now, right?
Yeah well, it's ours
for the moment.
But, we'll sell it
soon, don't worry.
No one expects us to
live in a house where...
That would just feel...
I'm scared to go in.
Yeah me too a little.
Hey why don't you wait
in here then, okay?
I'll go gather some
stuff and we can go
back to the motel. No.
I'm coming in.
Oh Simon...
I keep wondering if he never
even met that doctor.
Never knew where he...
He said there was a
better chance of
being hit by an asteroid.
Yeah.
Well...
They have to hit
somewhere, don't they?
I guess so.
Hey.
And it's amazing.
It doesn't feel bad in here
like I thought it would.
No, it doesn't.
I like how it feels.
Do you miss the city?
Not one dime.
And where would you go?
Free!
It's the strangest thing.
I'm getting kind of used to it.
Uh-hmm...
Sleep tight.
I'll leave my door open.
Goodnight Mom!
Goodnight.
Goodnight Dad.