DO NOT ENTER AT NIGHT
LA FUNERARIA
- Oh, you're already here.
- What's up mom?
More things from your grandma's?
I'm going to bring as much as I can.
Does it bother you?
How was it?
Fine.
These caskets are disgusting.
I can't stand them.
How are you?
Did you see the glue?
I can't find it anywhere.
It has to be next to the filing cabinet.
No, it's not there.
Well, I didn't touch it.
Fuck! This dog shits tons.
And the thermos?
PRESS IF YOU NEED ANYTHING
Come in, please.
Take your stuff out of the bucket, Irina.
You can do that, give me a hand.
Maybe once you had thrown it out.
We're eating.
Well, that's it.
Do you water the violet flowers?
My dad's?
Could you leave that phone?
Ten minutes, Irina, while we eat.
Hey! Leave it.
You're no one to tell me what to do.
He's asking you right.
Could you put that down?
Grandma sent me this.
Take a look.
After dinner, you can look all the
pictures that your grandma sends you.
I forgot to give them the cups.
My grandma is going to buy me
a new cellphone.
If you get bad notes,
there won't be a new cellphone.
My grandma said so, and she pays for it.
Fine, then you tell her.
I wouldn't have a thing
without my grandma.
Don't lie.
She said you should at least
use the pension money of my dad
to buy me new ballet shoes,
or pay for my dance classes.
You tell her to stop making up stories.
If she wants to give you photos,
pictures, posters of your dad, she can.
But that shitty old woman
must stop messing with me.
SEE YOU AT THE BICYCLE
I buy you the ballet shoes,
but you decided
to stop attending dance classes.
- You made me lose interest.
- Who made you lose interest in classes?
Who did it?!
Not even once you went to see me.
I couldn't go!
I had shitty moments,
...fucked up moments.
You know it really well.
Now that I'm better, that I feel calmer,
you don't want to go again.
I don't feel like going anymore.
And those awards you've won,
I would have loved to have seen you,
to be there with you.
Oh my child, you're unfair.
You billed me for everything.
Your dad didn't go to see you either!
Only my grandma was there.
I have to give them this.
I WANT TO SEE YOU
They want tea. Is there any?
There's mate tea bags. Here.
Emma?
Dad?
That perfume is never going away.
The truth is that in the last
times I was afraid of your dad.
He had his forgetfulness.
Maybe fear of that,
But being afraid of him,
seems too much to me.
Yes, but it's not his forgetfulness,
I mean the weird and dark stuff
in which he was involved.
He is dead now, leave it.
We shouldn't have hold here
the wake for him.
He was my dad.
Where should I hold his wake
if I own a funeral home?
We own.
I don't want to talk about it.
Did you talk to Irina?
No, I didn't.
She wants to move with her grandma.
You know that old woman is a manipulator.
I remember her putting ice
on my swollen eye,
while saying good things about her son.
She is awful.
What happened yesterday?
They got into the room.
No way.
I saw them!
It pulled Emma out of the fish tank,
I don't want to be here anymore.
Ramona did all to keep them out
of the bedrooms.
Well, it didn't work.
I want to get the fuck out of this house!
Something got in.
I'm going to bring Ramona again.
Anyway, she said they can't do
anything to us.
Take them out!
How long do these things live?
I have no idea.
We should have taken
all those critters out.
Do they bother you that much?
Yes. Your old man should
have beheaded them all.
They're horrible.
They are so annoying!
I told them we were leaving at nine.
What cemetery are you taking her to?
To the Peace Garden of Virrey del Pino.
They are very tricky with the documents.
I still want to come back early
to take a nap.
But I'm sure this will take long.
So, are you coming late again?
Will you go to the cemetery
or somewhere else?
The same again?
I go to the cemetery and I'll
take the time that I have to.
Yes, but we don't even sleep together.
We don't talk, is it forbidden
to be in bed with me?
I'm in bed with you,
you don't even notice it
because you are always on pills.
Bernardo,
I'm not going to let aside
what Irina said.
Give me the number and I call her.
No, I'll call her.
I'll tell her to come,
but she isn't always available for me.
Mom,
he doesn't care,
won't tell her anything. You'll see.
He's not mean to you.
I didn't say he's a bad guy.
I know he isn't your dad,
but respect him.
It makes me good to be with him.
I finally found a person
who respects me, sweetie.
You don't want to be alone,
that's the matter.
I didn't say he's a bad guy,
but I want to get the fuck out
of this house full of things.
It's this or the street.
We have nowhere else to go.
I do, I have my grandma's house.
Do you think I'm not scared?
I'm scared too.
But let's think about what Ramona said,
How can we not have presences,
if we have a funeral home in the house?
We must be alert, that's all.
And like Bernardo says, right?
Spirits don't kill,
people hit, kill, there are thieves,
I'm more afraid if you go out there,
than if you're in here, sweetie.
Do you know why I stay here?
Because of what the shaman
said about my dad.
Yes,
your dad must be among all the presences.
I want to see him at least once,
then I'll go to my grandma's
and you don't see me anymore.
Irina.
Can we talk for a minute?
Would you like something to drink?
No.
Look, I don't want to take
your father's place,
but you can't be so defensive
with me all the time.
It's just that you are always
giving me orders,
give orders to mom, but not to me.
You can't do whatever you want.
You must follow some rules, that's all.
And I don't follow the rules?
I piss in the bucket,
I freaking freeze at night for using
the portable toilet for customers.
Your mom and I use that toilet too,
because Ramona said so.
Besides, I'm talking about rules
of living together.
Any day cleaning the house,
wipe the floor, sweep, those things.
I just tell you to do those things.
I'm not one of the presences,
I'm…
I'm flesh and blood.
And I understand everything,
but you're a big girl,
and you have to understand, too.
I know of your pain because of the
motocycle's accident of your father,
you've lost him.
But your dad wasn't good with your mom.
He was obsessively jealous.
A motherfucker
who beat her up continuously,
and you know it.
Wash your mouth before
talking like that about my dad.
Kick me out!
You're used to throw people
out of this house, anyway.
All towels are wet, no dry ones, sweetie.
Is something wrong?
This mark is very rare.
Wouldn't Irina's father
be here too? Would he?
Don't be a fool.
You know that's a lie of yours.
I'm serious.
SHE WILL LOVE IT
It's for you.
THANKS DAD
I like it when you call me like that.
I love you so much.
You're like the daughter I never had.
Go to play.
Go to play that I have to talk.
Show yourself.
I want to see what you look like.
This is not enough for me anymore.
Take care of me, dad.
Mom, is that you?
Bernardo?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Mom! Mom!
Mom!
Mom, wake up. Wake up! Mom!
Mom! Wake up! Wake up!
Get away!
Get away, please!
Get away.
Irina. What happened?
What happened Irina?
- What happened?
- This is all your fault!
- I want to leave!
- No, no, no.
No, no, calm down.
Take me to my grandma's.
Please, I can't stand this anymore.
Take me to my grandma's!
I'm going to my grandma's.
You go tomorrow, sweetie.
I promise.
I'm not staying here anymore.
But it's too late
to go to your grandma's,
You go tomorrow.
Today I stay here with you.
DON'T LEAVE ME HANGING LIKE AN
IDIOT
I had to go.
Come on, come here.
Come.
DICKHEAD
Enough.
Stop.
What's wrong with that fucking dog?
Don't mess with that!
Did you hear me?
HELP ME. IT WASN'T ME.
Sweetie.
Would you leave me one?
This one.
Thank you.
Today is the first time that
I don't feel his perfume.
I can see you don't feel like talking.
I'm a little tired.
Tired.
Yes, a little from everything.
I miss Irina.
I miss her too, actually.
Specially her cellphone's
keyboard clicking.
Is her what I miss.
I also miss her.
Don't start an argument with me.
May I ask you something?
You are mad because
I got my tubes tied, right?
Well, that's...
a decision you made at that moment,
it's very personal.
I think you were too young.
Yes.
I'd had two miscarriages as well.
And if it was up to Irina's father,
he would have got me pregnant
once a year, just to control me.
That's why I had the surgery.
I would have loved to give you a child.
I already got used to the idea
that it will be so.
In life, sometimes those things happen,
sometimes don't...
...it didn't happened to me,
and I accept it.
On top, all women you were with,
left you...
...because of your dad,
and that unhealthy relationship
you had with him.
I didn't have an unhealthy
relationship with my dad.
He's gone, Estela, stop digging in there.
Besides, not all women broke up with me,
in some relationships I cut.
Well,
cut them all,
because it looks like some
of them haven't heard yet.
What are you talking about?
It's nothing.
Come here.
Where are you?
Please, show up.
Don't be mad.
I can't stop talking to her,
she's my wife.
Where are you?
Just come, please.
Come here a little while.
Please.
CERTIFICATE OF DEATH
Carmen, come.
I know.
You're Carmen.
Melina.
Come here.
Carmen,
just a minute.
Melina!
Carmen!
Melina.
Melina!
Bernardo?
What's that?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Bernardo?
Bernardo!
No! No!
Help! Help!
Bernardo!
Bernardo! Bernardo!
No! No!
Help!
Bernardo!
Bernardo, come out!
And?
Wait, give her some time.
I feel something,
I need you to wait outside the house.
I'm going to perform a ritual
that will help me see some things,
please don't talk to me.
Bernardo!
Look!
He left them open again.
I stand that he mistreats us,
but this is dangerous.
I've been telling you,
your dad's getting worse,
I wanted you to see it.
If I didn't realize this I'd turn on
the light, and we'd all blow up.
He's stingy with the food for Irina,
and treats me like a cleaning lady,
I'm not letting this go,
I'm leaving with my daughter now!
Estela,
Estela I'm going to talk.
Today we could all have blown up to shit,
and this one is like the tenth time.
This is dangerous, Dad,
you can't live here anymore.
You're dumb, son,
and always so henpecked.
You've been against her, and Irina
because she's someone else's daughter.
You treat them like shit,
don't talk to them, and hide the food.
Irina isn't my granddaughter,
and she is an opportunistic.
I'm not discussing that with you anymore.
When it's not the heater, is the
gas stove; Dish soap instead of juice.
We can't take care of you,
you need someone to do it,
Someone recommended a place to
me…
It's an expensive one,
you're going to be fine there.
All right, son,
but I want you to know that you're wrong.
May I ask you a favor?
Wait till tomorrow, then I'll leave.
Fine.
Fuck, there were those pictures.
We have time to talk
without it hearing us.
How did your dad die?
I'm sorry to be so direct,
I need to know well, to understand
some things that are going on.
He died of cold
lying on the bench of a park.
He was a very proud man,
he escaped from the home we paid for him,
I don't know why,
- when he was okay there.
- There's no time for that now.
I'm putting together the puzzle
you have here.
That time when I came,
you had only a couple of spirits
in the house by then.
I gave them their place on
the field and part of the house,
I negotiated with the presences
or there was going to get violent.
There was a presence that tricked me,
it blended in with the others,
I thought it was elusive and lonely,
but it was much more than that.
It's a demon.
And my only preventive measure was
telling you not to use
the bathroom at night.
Your dad was hurt for being kicked out,
and left them this gift,
so it kills Irina and your wife.
My dad was a fucked-up man,
and he was into weird and dark things,
but not to the point
of wanting to kill them...
I'd have never expected this
from Salvador,
he found in this demon a way
to accomplish what he couldn't,
in return,
he promised to let it exist on this plane.
Wicked bastard.
He made a pact with the demon
to kill Irina and your wife.
I'm fucking leaving,
I'm fucking going out of here!
Believe me that you need to stay,
here I have it under control,
I saw this demon up close,
it is bloodthirsty, cynical,
and plays with the victims.
Your dad realized he was going
to kill everyone, you too Bernardo,
then he backed out,
and started dragging spirits
from the funeral home to stop him,
but it was too late.
He was the only one
who could hold this entity.
Is there anything left in the house?
There's something with low energy.
Who could it be?
It doesn't matter.
Each tip represents a moon.
The demon gathered the necessary
forces to carry out this massacre,
tonight is its last chance.
Your dad was expelled at
the right time from this house.
You have to bring Irina, now.
You are crazy! No way
I'm bringing Irina here!
It's going to try to kill her anyway!
If she is here with me,
nothing's going to happen to her.
Do as I say, now!
Is she far away?
Yes, she is far.
Bring her now.
I'm going to bring her.
Stay calm, sweetie.
GRANDMA COME HERE AND GET ME.
You have to drink this.
With this inside the body,
It can't possess anyone in the house.
The pact expires at dawn,
we have to resist the whole night.
No way, I'm not going to drink that.
I beg you, please sweetie, drink it.
You're all out of your minds.
Listen to me at least once,
I'm asking you as a mother, drink it.
Trust me, Irina, I want to help you.
I want to help you.
Quick.
Stay inside the circle.
I can't confront it,
all we can do is resist.
Don't get tempted by anything.
It's been a long while,
but we still have a lot ahead.
It can't find the way.
It can't find a way to kill you.
Irina?
Where's Irina?
Come down, baby!
It can't possess her, just scare her.
You don't leave the circle.
Listen to her.
Wait there baby!
This is weird.
I feel like the demon
already left the house.
The buzzer from the funeral home.
Someone is here.
Is that Irina's grandma?
That's not Irina's grandma anymore.
Yes, she is.
It's not her,
now that's the demon.
Get out of the circle!
It's pointless now!
Lock the windows!
No!
Fuck off motherfucker!
Don't get out baby!
Don't get out!
Bernardo!
No!
No! No!
Don't get out baby!
No!
No! No!
Ramona!
Ramona help me, please!
Help me!
Irina.
Don't get close to your grandma,
she's the demon!
I don't understand.
Mom.
Mom?
Mom, where are you?
No, Orco.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
No, mom, please.
Don't leave me alone, please.
No!
Get out of this house, Irina!
It closed the place, hide.
Hide!
No! Stop! Leave me!
I did nothing!
Leave her alone...
The pact has ended.
Leave that body.
No. No!
Irina,
I couldn't do anything,
it killed your grandma.
I could,
see...
in your eyes,
all your pain.
I can't breath.
I leave you a special gift,
it won't last long.
I love you sweetie.
You did great! You are great!
I love you.
Mom.
Mom!
>>>>oakislandtk<<<<<
www.opensubtitles.org