Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
- Hey beautiful.
- Hi.
I just gotta run
to the store real fast,
case we get snowed in.
'Kay.
How was school?
Fine.
Miss Nichols says I can't
wear dark lipstick anymore.
You want me to go in
and kick her ass?
- Are we going hunting this weekend?
- Mm-hmm.
Remember,
I'm gonna get my seventh
in under twenty.
I don't doubt it.
Wanna go sledding tonight?
Sure.
Oh, wait, I got a session
with Mrs. Minskey tonight.
She still tryin' to talk
to her dead husband?
Yeah, but I'm gonna shake her
out of a little more money
before she gets
to talk to him.
That's cunty.
I like it.
Thank you.
That's called business.
Noted.
All righty now, W.H.E.L.
mountain radio,
it's 7:16
and it's cold out there.
Sub-zero temperature gonna be
all night long with wind chill...
What's goin' on, man?
That's it?
Stay safe out there folks,
this storm is one
for the record books...
Twelve fifty.
Stockin' up for the storm?
Stay off the road,
and let the road cleaners
do their work.
Drive safe out there.
Mom, I'm gonna get
a cinnamon
coffee cake cappuccino.
You want one?
No, and you can't
have one either.
Why?
Because you'll be
up all night.
Good, I'm gonna be
sledding all night.
No, I can't be at the bottom
of the road to watch you.
I got that session
with Mrs. Minskey.
And I know
you have homework.
Fuck homework.
- Ah!
So, how we doin'
over here?
Lemme get another shot
and a beer.
What are we asking
of the cards tonight,
Mrs. Minskey?
I'd like to know if my
sciatica will ever go away.
It hurts!
Also,
I'd like to know if my son
is ever going to visit me.
Maybe a phone call.
But most of all,
I'd like to speak
to my beloved husband.
My darling Ivan.
Can we do that, please?
Is that a good one
or a bad one?
Whispers from the shadows.
Pass through the filament
and pierce this
earthly realm.
Two hearts, once one,
still yearn to shine.
Bound by love,
locked in time.
Listen now
and hear our calls.
Show a sign
within these walls.
Ivan.
Ivan Minskey?
Are you there, Ivan?
Can you hear us?
Ivan, honey, I'm here.
I'm here.
Please, please
won't you talk to us?
The filament is thick.
The veil won't part.
Oh, Valley of Death.
We stand on the
Mountain of Hope.
We call out your name,
but all we hear
is an echo.
Mom.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
A whisper?
No.
Nothing.
Oh well.
We'll try again next time.
♪ I remember you
♪ A woman true to fella
with the open umbrella
♪ That I met one rainy day
upon the avenue
♪ I remember you
No.
No. No.
My God.
Ha! Ha.
Wait.
Stop.
I need to report
a missing person, please.
Echo Allen,
she's my daughter.
She's fourteen.
Uh, seven o'clock.
I came home from work
about fifteen minutes ago,
and she wasn't here.
She's not here.
Yeah, yeah, I'm sure
that she's not here.
Her coat is gone
and her sled is gone,
but if she went sledding,
she didn't come back.
No,
no she couldn't be out there,
I just drove up my road,
I would've seen her.
Fifteen Old Bark Road.
One five Bark Road.
Norm Daniels
here with the weather.
Snow, snow,
and more snow, folks.
It's already cold.
Risin' temps by noon.
High in the teens
and sunny all day
with a chance of rain
late Tuesday
when it all turns to slush,
folks.
That's the weather.
That's the way
the cookie crumbles.
Stay tuned for...
Echo!
Hold it.
- Hey.
Uh, hey, can uh,
we talk to you for a second?
Yeah.
Go round, I could ta...
talk to you over here,
I can't get this door open.
- 'Kay.
- All right.
I'm Detective Jay Sanford,
this is Detective Davide.
We're with the Sullivan
County Police Department.
- Good morning.
- Hi.
Hey, uh, we're lookin'
for your neighbor's daughter.
Fourteen year old girl?
She's been missing
since last night.
- Have you happened to see her at all?
- No. No.
Do you know your uh,
neighbors down the road?
I don't.
Echo Allen.
Ring any bells?
No.
Not familiar at all?
What's your name?
Kurt Miller.
Were ya out
and about it all last night?
Uh, went to Main Street
and had dinner.
Couple drinks.
- What time you stay 'til?
- Late.
How late?
I... I wasn't
keeping track of time,
but probably I left
around ten?
That's not that late.
Did you see anybody
on the road?
No.
Not even a deer?
Maybe, I don't know.
I...
You okay?
Look a little nervous.
Nah, no.
Just tired.
Okay.
If you happen to
think of anything,
you happen to see her,
if you would,
please give us a phone call.
All right,
you have a nice day.
You too.
All right, thanks.
♪ Ev'ry morning,
ev'ry evening
♪ Ain't we got fun?
♪ Not much money,
oh, but honey
♪ Ain't we got fun?
♪ The rent's unpaid, dear
All righty now.
This is ninety-two W.H.E.L.
with your host Frankie Wood
rockin' the mountain.
More rain expected today
through the afternoon,
which should be heavy
at times.
Nights...
♪ In the
winter, in the summer
Gimme a call,
maybe I'll play
something for ya.
Yeah, I'll be right there,
bro.
Just gimme a sec.
Hey.
Hey, can you make
sure that everyone
who comes in here
takes one of these?
Hey, what's up, man?
How you doin'?
All set?
- That's it?
- Yeah.
Fifteen.
- Need a bag by any chance?
- No.
Hey man,
before you leave,
you wanna spread the word?
She's a good kid.
Hello?
Yeah, hold on.
Oh hey, um,
could uh...
could I just talk to you
for a second?
I'm Ivy Allen, I...
I live down the road um,
I'm lookin' for
my daughter, Echo?
You know her?
We live right down the road.
She rides her bike here.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I don't know her,
I've never seen her.
Did the cops come?
Yeah.
She didn't run away.
So you're tryin' to
resurrect this dump?
Yeah.
I'm gonna fix it
and flip it.
It's been abandoned
for years.
We used to come here
to party.
You must've cleaned out
a lot of glass and beer cans.
What's your name?
Kurt.
You got a cat?
No this house just...
makes noise.
Echo!
I saw you on the road
the other day,
you didn't stop.
Huh,
I don't remember that.
Yeah,
then I saw you in the town.
I doubt that was me.
It was you.
It's okay.
Well, I live...
We live in the first house
this side of the cemetery,
up the steep drive?
Okay?
I love you.
Four, five, six, seven.
Seven circles.
♪ Ev'ry morning,
ev'ry evening
♪ Ain't we got fun?
♪ Not much
money, oh, but honey
♪ Ain't we got fun?
♪ The rent's unpaid, dear
♪ We haven't a bus
♪ For people like us
♪ In the winter,
in the summer
♪ Don't we have fun?
All right.
You wanna fuck with me?
I see.
Down here.
Hey.
♪ Ev'ry morning,
ev'ry evening
♪ Ain't we got fun
♪ Not much money,
oh, but honey
♪ Ain't we got fun
♪ The rent's unpaid, dear
♪ In the
winter, in the summer
"Twixt
the light of the living
"and the darkness of death
there hangs an invisible realm,
"a great sphere suspended
by the bare string
"of the lost who lived,
but linger,
"unwilling to release
their souls
"into the eternal
mouth of Death.
"Timeless and lawless,
"manifested as seven
spectral circles
"spinning all that was,
is, and would be.
"The Seven Circles be the
domain of the wandering dead,
"and only the dead.
"Their currency be truth,
"but they traffic in trickery
for those
"for whom death is not due.
"If the string be cut,
"the lost shall sleepeth
in the cradle of dark.
"If the string be hoisted
back into the light,
the lost shall be refound,
at the price of the string."
Hangman,
the card of ultimate
surrender.
New perspective,
enlightenment.
Tell her what you've done.
That's the deepest
you can dig?
Lazy bum.
Tell her what you did.
Tell her.
Tell her what you've done.
Twelve or thirteen...
So, that's perfect.
Yeah.
All right,
I'm gonna go.
All right, thank you.
Bye.
Hungry?
Drink?
- Water?
- No.
Sit.
Nice place.
Thanks to you.
You taught me
everything I know.
I lost my sight.
You lost your faith.
I read your book.
Times bestseller list, huh?
How much of it was true?
All of it.
In the book it says
that you were given the key
to the Seven Circles.
Is that true?
Del, on the night
that Echo disappeared,
she reached out to me
from the darkness.
That's a mother's intuition.
Maybe.
But then she
revealed to me a sign
of the Seven Circles.
And you know that has
nothing to do with intuition.
Please.
The Seven Circles
are unforgiving.
They are locked in grief.
They will warp
everything within them.
Every gift is its own
twisted curse.
And for you,
who's turned her back
on her calling,
you will pay dearly.
I'll pay.
Whoever opens the box
enters the Seven Circles.
But it is not you
who goes through them.
It is they
that go through you.
Once the door's opened,
it cannot be shut.
What happens now?
Listen,
we just need to ask you
a couple more questions,
we're still at square one.
Ivy,
did Echo ever talk about
being bullied at school?
No.
You don't have any
reason to believe
that she would have run away,
do you?
Echo did not run away.
Something terrible
happened to her.
I know, because
she reached out to me
from another realm.
I need you
to help me find out
what happened to her.
But you can't help me
find her.
Only I can do that.
Alone.
Okay.
Ivy, one last thing.
You said you left
Mrs. Minskey's
at about nine that night?
And the whole way home
you didn't see
any other cars.
Nobody passed you?
Okay,
let's start from the beginning.
You guys came
home after shopping.
What'd you get?
What you buy?
Did Echo buy anything?
You made dinner,
and then you left
at about seven, right?
Any
boyfriend or girlfriend
in the picture
that you know of?
Does she disobey you often?
Do you think
she would hurt herself?
Do you happen to remember
your conversation with her?
I know you're not real.
I'm as real
as I am dead.
I know you're not real.
You're in my head.
I'm not in your head yet.
Why don't you go get
your big gun
and shoot me again?
Tell my mother
what you've done.
♪ Far away
♪ I watch you drift
away from me
♪ Far away
♪ I watch
you drift away from me
♪ Far away
For the past fifteen years,
this is where we wind down
from a rough weekend
and prepare
for another week.
In hell.
We got some old,
we got some new,
we got some in between!
Here comes somethin'
fresh from the vault.
Hi.
Echo.
I broke my arm.
How?
Sledding.
Where are you, Echo?
Bye.
You okay?
Is that your car?
Can you please move it?
Tell my
mother what you've done.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Now I'm in your head.
Bye.
Tell my
mother what you've done.
Hey W. H. E.
L. radio ninety-two point one...
What's goin' on buddy?
Rockin' the mountains
for over thirty-five years.
You know, this Sunday
we got a big charity,
it's close to my heart
and to yours.
Am I right?
It's for the Missing
Children's Foundation.
That's right,
lotta kids go missing
and are never found,
and the parents are worried,
so we wanna help them out,
so we do a little
charity event on Sunday...
...and is here on Kid California
and much, much more.
No beer tonight?
It's gonna rock your
world, and help those people...
Cinnamon coffee cake
cappuccinos.
All right,
we have a killer show for you tonight...
Bye.
Thanks for the extra
marshmallows.
So, the old house,
how's the transformation
coming?
It's a struggle.
So, what is this?
Uh, I'm just...
tryin' to find some answers.
About your daughter?
Oh, she's dead.
You see, the cards
are a projection
of what we see,
and what's hidden.
And what wants to be seen.
Shuffle.
Hindsight.
Insight.
Foresight.
The Devil.
Don't worry,
it's not always as bad
as it seems.
This card is basically
about bondage.
Something from your past,
let's say,
that still has a hold
or sucks life from you.
The High Priestess.
That was Echo's
favorite card.
The authentic blueprint
of our soul.
Perfectly captures
the duality in all of us.
You see the two columns?
Black, white,
male, female.
And then the veil
that she's wearing,
literally the thin veil
between two worlds.
Life and death,
the visible and invisible.
And then, of course,
the crescent moon
at her feet to remind us
of the innate power
of femininity.
Cool.
Yeah, it's cool.
This is what's to come?
Ten of swords.
What?
All is lost.
Over and done.
Dead.
And yours is in reverse.
What's that mean?
Slow pain.
But, look.
You see that sun peeking out
from behind the clouds?
Yeah.
Every end has
a new beginning.
At least that's what they say
to make you feel better.
They're just cards.
I'm sorry, Kurt.
I gotta piss.
Where's your bathroom?
Upstairs.
Ah.
I gotta go.
What are we asking of the
cards today, Miss Allen?
I wanna talk
to my daughter.
I wanna talk to my
beautiful Echo.
Can we do that?
Please?
Is that a good one
or a bad one?
Whispers in the dark.
Pass through the filament
and pierce
this earthly realm.
Listen now
and hear our calls,
show a sign
within these walls.
Echo?
Echo Allen?
Are you there, Echo?
Where the fuck are you?
Echo, I'm here, honey.
I'm here!
Echo?
Echo.
Echo, talk to us,
please.
Please talk to us.
Hmm.
The veil is thick.
It won't part.
Please help me
talk to my daughter.
Please.
Nothing.
Tell my
mother what you've done.
Give her peace.
It was an accident.
It coulda happened
to anyone.
And you shouldn't have
been sledding in the dark.
You shouldn't
have been driving drunk.
You might've
had your eyes on the road.
known I wasn't dead.
And you
wouldn't have had to murder me.
Get outta my head, kid.
Or I'll
kill your fucking mother.
I'm Kurt.
Shit.
Fuck is that?
Every
morning, every evening
Ain't we got fun?
Not much money,
oh, but honey
Ain't we got fun?
The rent's unpaid, dear
We haven't a bus
But smiles are made, dear
For people like us
In the winter,
in the summer
Ain't we got fun?
Time's are bum
and gettin' bummer
Still we have fun
There's nothing surer
For people like us
In the morning,
in the evening
Ain't we got fun?
I can't wait.
It's almost hunting season.
You feelin' lucky?
I'm feelin' deadly.
How old were you
when you started hunting?
Eight.
So, six seasons,
six shots,
six bucks.
You got this year's
tags yet?
Come on,
seven's the perfect number.
It's got to be complete.
Do you think deer
know they're dying
when they've been shot?
Yeah.
Sure.
I don't.
Animals don't know
the difference
between life or death.
But when humans die,
they know what
they're gonna miss.
Mom?
Would you still love me
if I murdered someone?
I'll always love you.
No matter what.
Even if I killed
someone you loved?
Always.
Hey, I carved you
a pumpkin.
Y'know, for Halloween.
In case anybody came over
I thought you might want...
one.
What?
It just reminds me
of Echo.
She always used
to carve a pumpkin,
hoping trick-or-treaters
would come but
nobody comes up here.
She really loved
this time of year.
Halloween...
then hunting season.
What more could
a Goth kid ask for?
- You takin' a walk?
- Yeah,
just a little
mental homework.
Fuck homework.
Thanks, Kurt.
- Hey.
I was just...
There's really good hunting
behind your house.
That was Echo's favorite spot.
I don't really like goin' alone.
You wanna go?
Go hunting?
Do you hunt?
Yeah.
I'd love to.
I... I just got a shotgun
though, uh,
and no tags.
I got an open tag.
Lemme get my hat
and my gun
and we'll go.
It's cold.
Last year, Echo bagged
a buck out here
in under thirty minutes.
Nice.
She said this year she was
aiming for under twenty.
Alright, I can do it.
Oh yeah?
Sure.
Let's split up
and find out.
Oh, fuck.
Snuck up on that
pretty fast.
What're you,
some kinda ghost?
That's seven.
It's complete.
What'd you just say?
Kurt.
Hey wait!
Hold on!
Stop for a second.
Did you hear that?
That echo?
I've never heard an echo
in these woods.
And in the snow.
I'm almost here.
What?
I'm... I'm almost here.
Kurt.
I'm Kurt.
Mom?
I love you.
Candles glowing,
shadows throwing,
cards ready,
ever knowing.
A mockery I made of thee.
Blind no more,
I choose to see.
I swallow whole
the worm of shame,
and turn my nature
towards the flame.
My purpose to
the truth affixed,
I call upon the Circle Six.
I turn a card;
I beg it shows...
the secrets that
my daughter knows.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh!
Ha-ha-ha!
Detective
Sanford, it's Ivy Allen.
I think I have some
information on Echo's killer.
I know, I know, but,
I know she's dead.
Because I'm her mother
and I know.
Because I've seen things.
Signs she's been sending me.
And then
the cards last night,
I... I pulled the High Priestess
card, that's Echo.
And then I pulled
the Devil card, that's him!
That's my...
Yeah. Okay.
Hi.
Ow.
Echo.
It was an accident.
She never should've been
sledding in the dark.
Oh!
Ah!
That was cunty,
and I like it.
But...
Oh my God.
Don't pull it...
don't pull it out!
- But it hurts.
- Don't pull it out!
There's so much blood.
Echo?
Mom.
Come closer.
Echo.
Come here, please.
Ow!
We won.
I made it
just how you like it.
Extra marshmallows.
Thanks, Mom.
♪ You come to me
when I'm lonely
♪ I take your hand
and we go home
♪ You cover me
with your lovely
♪ I cover you
with my love
♪ Cover me with love
♪ Cover me with lovely
♪ Lovely
♪ You have my eyes
where I once saw you
♪ You took my tongue
when I was told
♪ I know I love you
and we're lonely
♪ You'll give it back
when we are old
♪ Cover me with love
♪ Cover me with lovely
♪ Lovely
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org