(lion roaring)
(wind blowing)
(downbeat music)
[Girl] Look at her smile, see, like
- her dimples stick out.
- The Lord is my shepherd.
[Girl] Know what I mean?
[Priest] I shall not want.
He makes me lie down in green pastures.
He leads me beside still waters.
He restores my soul.
He leads me in paths of
righteousness for his name's...
The story of Cheryl
Dempsey and what she became
is truly one of the strangest,
most disturbing things
I've ever come across in the
history of serial murder.
I've been doing this for
close to 25 years now.
(car door slamming)
(engine rumbling)
(downbeat creepy music)
I had a tenant in this house here
who was a very terrible person.
This is the house where they
found the Poughkeepsie tapes.
Before we got our hands
on the Poughkeepsie tapes,
we thought...
Well, we knew there had been some killings
and we were aware that
some of them appeared
as though they were being carried out
in an organized fashion,
but until we got our hands on those tapes,
we had no idea what we were dealing with.
No idea.
It was my job to watch
and log all 2,400 hours
of the Poughkeepsie tapes.
In the first month alone,
I couldn't sleep for more
than an hour or two at night.
I still have nightmares about them.
I think torturing and
murdering turn him on.
And I think these tapes are something
of a homemade porn film or a memento
that he can savor long after the murder.
He has definitely stalled
halfway through many a
killing to switch tapes.
I remember one night,
I brought some of the tapes home with me
to keep working, and unbeknownst to me,
my wife watched about half
an hour of one of the tapes
and it took her a year before
she let me touch her again.
That's what's on those tapes.
They found the tapes in this closet.
(camera shutter snapping)
And down here, you know.
When we searched the yard we
found the bodies of two women
there, and there.
We found a deep hole here
where there was buried
a young couple and
their 10-month-old baby.
There was a body of a man there,
and four more women there,
there, there, and there.
And it was obvious that they'd all
been killed in a horrific manner.
(Creepy music)
Beside me here is one
complete set of the tapes.
And just to give you a
sense, from about here,
to here, are all about Cheryl Dempsey.
When people think of serial killers
they think of four or five people.
You know, Ted Bundy,
Dahmer, Gacy, et cetera.
But what most people don't realize
is how many more there are.
At any given time, there
are somewhere between
25 and 50 active serial
killers in America alone.
It is really a much bigger
problem than most people realize.
There are probably hours
and hours of these tapes
that nobody's watched except me.
Like, for example, there's over 100 hours
of weird balloon stuff on these tapes.
Like this?
[Ed] Yes.
Now pop it.
What?
[Ed] Pop it!
(Creepy music)
If I've learned one thing
from teaching this class, it's this.
After what we're gonna see here today,
three of you will go home tonight
and decide that this is not
what you want with your life.
You know, there are some
terrible people in this world
who do unbelievably terrible things.
So it's important that
each of you ask yourself,
do I really wanna surround
myself with these terrible things
for the rest of my professional life?
And it's okay if you don't.
I would guess something
happened in his life at that time.
He got in a fight, lost a
job, got left by his wife,
something like that,
and went out in his car
and at some point said,
the next vulnerable person I see is dead.
[Ed] Hi.
I like your dolls.
I said, I like your dolls.
What's that one's name?
Susie.
I'm not supposed to talk to strangers.
[Ed] Well, you're not supposed
to have bad manners either.
You know, if I was the Big Bad Wolf
there's nothing you can do about it.
You wanna say something to the camera?
Like what?
[Ed] I don't know.
Maybe you could say, I am,
I am a happy, pretty little girl.
No.
[Ed] You wanna see what it
looks like through the camera?
No.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
[Ed] Here.
(loud thumping)
(Ed grunting)
(engine rumbling)
(man breathing heavily)
On first inspection, it looked like
she had been hit in the
head with a blunt object.
We found there was a missing
girl, Jennifer Gorman,
eight years old, from Putnam
County, about 50 miles away,
fitting the description,
last seen in similar clothes.
(gentle creepy music)
[Cynthia] I think something bad
has happened to my daughter.
I think somebody took her.
- Like who?
- I don't know who!
Out of the yard!
There's blood out there,
please, do something.
Do something, do something!
- Somebody took her!
- If it's a missing person
- we have to wait 24 hours.
- No!
There is blood, there is blood out there.
Send the police now!
(Creepy music)
Obviously, you don't ever
get over something like this.
You think the pain will subside, and...
And get better.
But it doesn't.
Not at all.
What kind of a sick bastard
rapes a little girl.
She was just a child.
She was barely eight.
I'm so sorry.
(Cynthia weeping)
This is nothing.
He doesn't even know what he's doing yet.
(ominous music building)
Hey, having a little car problem?
[Ed] Yeah, this old thing
isn't even worth driving some days.
Could I get a lift into the next town?
Yeah, no problem.
Hop in.
[Ed] Do you mind if I film this?
I'm making a little movie about my trip.
Knock yourself out.
Look Hon, we're gonna be movie stars.
So what's your name?
[Ed] Ed.
Ed, I'm Frank, this is Jeanette.
Hi.
[Ed] If you take this exit up here,
you can drop me off at
the little gas station.
[Frank] Okay.
[Ed] It's to the right here,
just a couple miles off the freeway.
[Frank] All right.
[Jeanette] You from around here?
[Ed] Not really.
Where are you from?
[Ed] I think the gas
station's right around the bend.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
[Jeanette] Oh my god!
Oh my god!
(car crashing)
(Jeanette screaming)
(ominous music)
(heavy breathing)
A Poughkeepsie couple
vanished over the weekend,
seemingly without a trace.
Family members say they haven't heard
from Frank or Jeanette Anderson
since they left Pittsburgh last Friday.
Authorities still have no leads
as to the couple's whereabouts.
This homicide announces a
completely new kind of killer.
There is almost nothing
left of the impulsiveness
that he displayed with Jennifer Gorman.
Here is a man who's figured
out he's good at something.
Imagine what it would take to do this.
From the seat behind her he takes a rag
with some sort of chemical
agent with his right hand,
and he places it over her mouth.
And with his left hand holding the camera
he's reaching it out and holding it
in front of her face like this.
This isn't the kind of
thing that just happens.
He must've practiced this motion
thoroughly to get it right.
I mean, his car's
parked alongside the road.
He knows where the next gas station is,
he knows it's only a mile
or two off the freeway,
and he knows that it's a desolate area
between the freeway and the gas station.
In fact, this station is abandoned,
and I bet he knows that too.
And he had a ready made
excuse for the camera.
This man is what we call a mixed killer.
He plots and hides his crimes
in an organized manner,
but he mutilates and does,
well, let's say similar things
with the bodies that a
disorganized killer would do.
[Ed] Wake up.
Wake up.
Come on, wake up.
Come on, wake up, I
have a surprise for you.
Wake up.
Wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up.
You're gonna love this.
(woman groaning)
(Creepy music)
Yeah, I know.
Today the search for a
missing Poughkeepsie couple
ends tragically, this when
human remains are found
buried in a wooded area
of rural Pennsylvania.
They brought a woman's body in
that was very badly mutilated.
The corpse had a head
placed in its abdomen
in a kind of strange, ceremonial fashion.
I took one look at the skull,
the upper edges of the
eye orbits were smooth,
and the cranial vault was rigid,
and showed heavy muscular markings.
I said, this is a man's
head in a woman's body.
This is two murders, not one.
After talking to their
friends and families,
we were able to ascertain
that the Andersons
were coming back from Pittsburgh
to Poughkeepsie where they lived.
That distance winds up
being about 350 miles or so.
The nice thing about this route,
is that there are really only a couple
of logical ways to drive it.
Under the best conditions,
that particular make of car
can only go about 200 miles to the tank,
more likely about 150.
So we went from that point on the freeway,
200 miles in both directions,
and we went to every gas
station along the route
and asked to see their surveillance tapes
from that particular day.
That took some doing,
but we did manage to get
our first video image of
the killer in this manner.
(gentle music)
[Student] What's he doing with his hand?
[Student] He's signing.
[Mike] That's right.
Anybody know what he's saying?
Red house.
Good.
Right, we found the
second body in the woods
behind a place called the Red House Tavern
about three miles away.
But the thing to keep in mind is this.
He signed this before he
even met the Andersons.
Timeliness is of the
essence in any investigation,
but especially a murder.
If we find a fresh crime scene,
there's just a lot more
information to work with
than say, a skeleton.
Often, the serial killers who
avoid detection and capture
are the ones who are especially
good at disposing of bodies.
The killer documented on
the Poughkeepsie tapes
is very, very good at it.
Not only does he know
how to dispose of bodies,
he knows how to dispose of
bodies in many different ways.
Elizabeth Jackson was
abducted in Hanson County,
which is about 100 miles from the location
we later found the tapes in.
The killer then took a circular saw,
cut off her head and hands.
He then dumped her torso in Putnam County,
and her head and hands in Broome County.
When someone's disposed of like this,
it's almost impossible
to put it all together
because even if the
various counties did talk,
and they don't, but even if they did,
there may be a five year
gap between finding the head
and the torso of a body like this.
I see this and I say, okay,
here's a killer who
understands bureaucracy.
(Creepy music)
Usually a killer won't think through
their first dismembering,
and they have a dead body in the house
and they need to take it apart.
So they go out to the garage and get a saw
and take some hours to get the head off.
So the next time, they'll
go and get a better saw
before they kill someone, and
that makes it a little better,
but if they really wanna
get into the killing,
they'll often go and get a real saw.
Something that cuts
through quick and easy.
And at that point, they'll
never go back to a handsaw.
Except this guy, he did it repeatedly.
Sometimes he uses a circular
saw, sometimes a handsaw.
It's part of the reason that we never
grouped his killings together.
It's probably why he did it.
But after all that effort
to mask his killings,
He shows us each and every
disassembly in his tapes.
I guess he just wanted
someone to appreciate
how good he is at this,
and the thought that maybe
we'd be strangely sort
of impressed with it.
[Interviewer] Are you?
No.
After seeing what he
did to Cheryl Dempsey,
I could feel nothing but
loathing for this guy.
(ominous music)
(radio crackling)
[Cheryl] It was so sweet.
[Tim] Should've gone with you.
(garbled speech)
[Cheryl] Cow's gone on her trip.
My mom was being such a bitch.
[Tim] How long are they gone for?
[Cheryl] Like a week.
[Tim] Like Wednesday, right?
[Cheryl] Yeah.
(garbled speech)
[Tim] No.
[Cheryl] Tim?
[Tim] Yeah?
[Cheryl] Do you ever get a feeling?
[Tim] What do you mean?
[Cheryl] Like feeling like
something's going to happen?
[Tim] Sometimes, why?
[Cheryl] It's weird.
Everything's been so good lately.
Everybody seems to be happy,
and everything's just like,
too good, you know?
(low ominous music)
(shower water pattering)
[Cheryl] Hello?
Is that you?
Tim?
[Tim] Hello?
[Cheryl] Hello?
Is that you?
[Tim] Hey, you mind if
I grab something to eat?
[Cheryl] Yeah, go ahead.
Can you grab some ice cream
while you're down there?
[Tim] Sure.
[Cheryl] Will you grab me a towel?
I know you're still there.
Come on, you're not scaring me.
[Tim] Hey, what kind of ice cream did you want?
[Cheryl] Whatever, chocolate?
[Tim] Done.
(ominous music)
You scared me.
You shouldn't jump out
at somebody like that.
[Tim] Sorry.
I brought you ice cream, and beer.
Thanks.
Why did you move my clothes?
[Tim] I didn't.
They were all over the place.
[Tim] Come here.
[Cheryl] Why?
[Tim] You'll see.
(Cheryl chuckling)
[Cheryl] Let's just go watch a movie.
[Tim] Like what?
[Cheryl] I rented a couple.
[Tim] You wanna stay here for a while?
Maybe for a little while.
(suspenseful music)
(low ominous music)
Hey.
We're starting to fall asleep.
You wanna go to bed?
[Tim] Yeah, yeah okay.
[Cheryl] You're staying over tonight, right?
[Tim] Yeah.
[Cheryl] Cool.
I get a little scared here by myself.
[Tim] I think I might too.
[Cheryl] Do you mind putting
this stuff in the sink?
I just wanna pee and brush my teeth.
No, it's fine.
[Cheryl] Thank you.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
(glass shattering)
(fighting impacts and cries)
(ominous music)
(Cheryl whimpering)
(frightening music building)
(low rumbling music)
(Ed breathing heavily)
(rumbling music building)
This weekend ends in
tragedy for one family.
Victoria and James Dempsey returned home
after leaving their 19-year-old daughter,
Cheryl Dempsey, home
alone for the weekend.
Now when they returned
they found Cheryl missing,
and her boyfriend, Tim
Surrey, brutally murdered.
I remember maybe three days
before Cheryl's abduction
she asked me, do you ever feel
like someone's watching you?
I said not really.
And she told me, sometimes I feel like
maybe someone's following me around.
I said, you know, you're
probably just being paranoid.
And she said, yeah, maybe.
You know, hindsight's 20/20.
(disjointed music)
What's happening?
Where am I?
Stay away from me!
Stay away!
Why are you doing this to me?
(Cheryl shouting)
Please don't hurt me.
I'll do whatever you want.
I know you will.
(Cheryl mumbling)
Shut up!
What is your name?
Cheryl Dempsey.
Wrong!
Your name is slave.
What is your name?
Cheryl.
(pained groaning)
Your name is slave!
What is your name?
My name is slave!
[Ed] What is your name?
[Cheryl] Slave!
What is your name?
Slave!
[Ed] Good.
(Ed breathing heavily)
Because of the gruesome
condition of Tim's body,
we had very little hope
of finding Cheryl alive.
His head had been crushed
in, kind of like this.
And he had been cut from
his anus up to his throat,
and his intestines had been pulled out
and strewn around like they
were Christmas tree lights.
And his genitals had been
removed and they were placed
in the sock drawer in the master bedroom.
Our basic thinking was that the killer
had lost all control of his faculties,
and again, judging from
the condition of the body,
that he had probably killed her here,
and then probably dumped
her body in the woods.
We took one look at the
scene and wrote it off
as the work of a disorganized killer.
The truth we later learned
from the Poughkeepsie tapes
was that this killer had carefully crafted
the murder site to mislead us.
And it worked.
Funny thing is, to be able
to murder and mutilate a body
in such a way and to maintain
composure while doing so,
coupled with his bizarre
sense of theatricality,
you know, the masks and
costumes and whatnot,
shows that this man is
extremely mentally ill.
Comedia del arte is a form of theater
that dates back to 16th century Italy.
They actually had to
pass a law prohibiting
carrying weapons while wearing a mask,
because people stopped being
responsible for their actions
the moment they put one on.
I think the costumes
serve two functions.
First, they let him draw
out the act of killing.
And second, they help him to
alleviate any sense of guilt
or regret he may have for the
horrible things he's doing.
This character went out of
fashion hundreds of years ago.
It's the character Dottore Peste.
The Doctor of the Plague.
(Cheryl whimpering)
[Ed] Why are you crying?
'Cause I want my mom.
I want my mom.
[Ed] Didn't I tell you?
What?
[Ed] I killed your mom.
I killed your whole family.
I'm all you have left.
No, no you didn't.
[Ed] You tell me!
Tell me you're happy I killed your family.
[Cheryl] No!
[Ed] What?
[Cheryl] No.
No!
(Cheryl screaming)
Say it!
What?
You're happy I killed your parents!
Say it!
(Cheryl panting)
What?
I'm happy you killed my parents.
Say it again.
You don't have parents.
You're a slave.
(Cheryl crying)
I'll say it.
Those people.
I'm happy that you killed them.
Why?
Why!
(Cheryl crying)
Because I don't like them!
[Ed] Who do you like?
[Cheryl] You.
[Ed] Who?
[Cheryl] Only you.
[Ed] Why?
[Cheryl] Because you're the master,
and it please me to serve you.
[Ed] Did you want me
to kill those people.
Yes.
I don't know.
Yes!
I don't know!
That's why I did it.
I did it because of you.
[Cheryl] Thank you Master!
Thank you!
[Ed] Say it.
[Cheryl] You're the master.
You're the master and it
pleases me to serve you.
You're the master...
(Cheryl mumbling)
People have come from as
far away as Lancaster County
to search the wooded area
around the Dempsey residence.
This in hopes of finding any clues
in the disappearance of
their daughter Cheryl.
I'd just like to say to
the person who's done this,
please bring my daughter back home.
[Ed] If there's
anything I can do to help,
please let me know.
Thanks.
Wait.
Oh my god.
(Ed chuckling)
I play that moment in my
head over and over again.
I knew it was him, and I didn't stop him
because I was scared.
(downbeat music)
[Ed] Are you through screaming?
Do you need water?
If I take the gag off, will
you do something for me?
I want you to put this on.
[Cheryl] You're the master
and it pleases me to serve you.
Pleases me to serve you.
You're the master and it
pleases me to serve you.
(gentle downbeat music)
By the summer of '93,
the area was really
starting to feel the
effects of this man's work.
Most killers getting
this much media attention
will do one of three things.
One, they will realize it's not safe
for a serial killer to work
that town anymore and leave.
Two, they will give it a
rest for a little while
and let it cool off.
Or three, they'll just keep doing it,
maybe even speed of the
rate of their killings,
until they get caught.
But this killer did
something quite unique,
he kept killing, but changed his MO.
(ominous music)
A third body was found here today.
We're standing on the west bank
of the Hudson River in Poughkeepsie,
police believe this to be another killing
by the man some are calling
the Water Street Butcher.
Sixth killing believed to be the work
of the Water Street Butcher.
Police are warning local prostitutes
to stay off the streets.
[Prostitute] Wasn't me!
(low ominous music)
[Cheryl] You're the master
and it pleases me to serve you.
You're the master and it
pleases me to serve you.
You're the master and it pleases--
[Woman] This ain't right.
[Cheryl] You're the master
and it pleases me to serve you.
You're the master and it
pleases me to serve you.
At around the same time we started
getting word from the
prostitutes that worked that area
that girls are getting arrested
and never being heard from again.
[Prostitute] You can't just arrest me!
You can't arrest me!
(low ominous music)
[Woman] Will you help me?
[Cheryl] No.
[Woman] Please, I, come on!
[Cheryl] No, no, he won't like it.
[Woman] If I'm with
you, he can't stop you.
[Cheryl] He won't like it.
(woman screaming)
No, no, no, no!
No!
(woman screaming and crying)
No, no, no, please!
Please no!
No, no!
Oh no, oh no, no!
(woman screaming)
[Ed] Now you.
[Cheryl] No, she was trying to escape--
(Ed screaming)
(Cheryl crying)
No I didn't!
I didn't!
(Cheryl screaming)
[Ed] Okay.
This is your punishment.
(Cheryl crying)
All of the victim's
bodies had been mutilated.
In part to cover up
the bite marks on them.
They all had been sliced
from mouth to ear,
and they had been raped postmortem.
And we found matching sperm
on four of the bodies.
Years ago, I was
granted the dubious honor
of interviewing Theodore Robert Bundy
in connection with another case.
But the insight that I gained
there is relevant here.
I remember the first question
he asked me was, did he--
Rape her?
[Mike] Ah, yes he did.
Before or after?
[Mike] Before or after what?
You know, killing her.
[Mike] After.
You see Mike, I think that's
an important distinction.
This might all sound a little weird but
the kill and rape variety,
these guys will continue
to have sex with the body
way past the point where
we thought possible.
Mild decomposition,
even maggots and things,
may just serve to turn him on.
Next time you find a fresh dump site,
keep quiet about it.
Stake it out.
Your guy'll come back to it.
Unfortunately, we have never
found a fresh enough body.
But there was evidence that he had
in fact been returning to
them, for sexual reasons.
Hi, we're selling cookies.
Would you like to buy some?
[Ed] Uh...
Sure.
Sure, why don't you come in.
Um, we're not really supposed to.
[Ed] Well that's smart.
You know, there's a lot
of weirdos out there,
but I'm a policeman, so it's okay.
_ okay.
[Ed] Okay.
Come on in.
(low ominous music)
Just sit right there.
[Girl] Okay.
[Ed] Okay.
Hey, you girls want some Cokes?
Sure.
- Yeah?
- Okay.
[Ed] Okay.
Thank you.
[Ed] Hey, did you ride
your bikes here today?
No, I live over on Dupont.
[Ed] Oh, so you live
in the neighborhood?
Yeah.
I don't.
I live over by Central.
[Ed] Well, before you leave,
do you tell your parents where you go?
Sometimes.
Yeah.
[Ed] Yeah.
(woman screaming distantly)
What's that?
[Ed] What?
I thought I heard something.
[Ed] Oh, well I left
the TV on in the basement.
Oh.
(woman groaning)
[Ed] You know, it sounds like I'm not
going to be able to get cookies today.
You know, I get a raccoon
in the basement sometimes.
There's no raccoons around here.
[Ed] Sure there are.
Hey, do you wanna see the
raccoon I got in the basement?
Sure.
[Ed] He's awful mean.
I don't believe you.
I wanna go.
[Ed] You know I'll have to
get cookies some other day.
Why don't you let yourselves out?
[Girl] Mark him off.
[Ed] Sounds like something
got loose down there.
[Cheryl] I'm sorry Master,
I thought that it was tight.
[Ed] You felt pity for it.
You tried to let it go.
[Cheryl] No, no Master.
I would never betray you.
[Ed] This is your fault.
[Cheryl] No.
(Cheryl crying)
(Ed shouting)
(distant crashing)
Suddenly, we had 10 bodies.
Six of whom had matching
samples of semen on them.
Then we had a breakthrough.
At one of the victim's apartments,
we found an unwashed glass of water.
It had a fingerprint
and DNA from the saliva.
We ran the prints we
found on the glass of water.
It came back with a match.
It matched my partner, Jim Foley.
They placed him under arrest
and started building a case.
He had been in town
for all those killings,
and there were three
killings in Pennsylvania
that matched the same MO,
and he had been in Pennsylvania
on family vacation.
He had no substantiated
alibi for any of the murders.
We searched his car and his house
and found jewelry and bloodstains
that matched the victims.
That point, we knew we had our man.
(downbeat music)
When they came and arrested my dad
as the Water street
Butcher, it was devastating.
I couldn't sleep, I dropped out of school,
I became a freak even to my own friends.
Everything changed in one second.
Foley had no alibi for these murders
because he was a cop who
rode in an unmarked cruiser
by himself most of the time.
There was plenty of time for
him to commit these crimes.
Secondly, he had a history
of getting prostitutes.
Apparently Mr. Foley was
a fairly regular customer.
One of the prostitutes,
Cindy Jackson, took the stand
and placed him in the neighborhood
at the time of three of the abductions.
As defense, my hands were really tied
because he kept refusing a
plea bargain of any kind.
I kept telling him, Jim,
they're gonna kill you
if you don't cop a plea.
He kept telling me that he'd fire me
and defend himself if I
didn't shut up about it.
It was really quite frustrating.
(downbeat music)
He was my father.
Now it's over and he needs to be punished.
But I think that your
life should be spared,
because we are not like you.
(downbeat music)
[Cheryl] You're the master
and it pleases me to serve you.
You're the master and it
pleases me to serve you.
The governor has not granted reprieve,
James Foley will be
executed within the hour.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
(disjointed music)
(downbeat music)
[Man] Two members of the execution team
are preparing their injections.
A third is standing by.
The superintendent will
now give the condemned
the opportunity to make a last statement.
He has declined to make a last statement.
(woman whimpering)
He's afforded the opportunity for prayer.
The condemned has declined this also.
(downbeat music)
We have now completed the
first phase of the execution.
second phase of the execution.
We have now completed the third
and final phase of the execution.
One of the physicians is
now making his examination.
Now the second is making his check.
Now the third and final
physician is making his check.
Examination is completed.
The superintendent has
advised the witnesses
that death did occur
at 12:24 on this date.
(ominous music)
When I got home, I
found a map in my mailbox.
There was a mark on it
that said, "Missed one."
And then my phone rang.
They said you gotta get
down here and see this.
It was another body.
I knew right away.
[Reporter] Death by lethal injection.
After three stays of execution,
the death warrant has now been issued,
and James Foley will be put
to death within the hour.
In 1996, a jury convicted
and sentenced Foley to death
for the brutal murders of four women
in Pennsylvania and Upstate New York.
Authorities believe the
death toll to be much higher.
[Woman] We need to
stop killing everyone.
And if the government sanctions it
it just gives everyone a taste for blood.
[Reporter] Pennsylvania's
third execution in 25 years.
Right after I go work,
police come in and handing me DNA sample,
and demanding I do immediate.
I was very stressful.
And it turn out same as Water
Street Butcher, James Foley.
We're still not sure.
Apparently he had gone
to a fertility clinic
some years before, we
think maybe that's how.
But we're still not sure.
Three days after my dad's execution,
they realize that he had been innocent.
They were gonna put out a thing
in the paper the next day,
and then 9/11 happened.
So, the article on clad gets
bumped down to page six.
Former cop cleared of
charges after execution.
People still jokingly when
I say my name they'll ask,
any relation to the Water Street Butcher?
And I tell them, Jim Foley
wasn't the Water Street Butcher.
Nobody heard that they found
him innocent, 'cause of 9/11.
Any other week in American history
and this would've been a
serious national sensation.
Serial killer kills cop
using justice system.
Come on.
But then September 11th happened,
and no one gave a shit
about anything else.
You know, after 10 or more years
of planning and executing
what I considered to be
the crime of the century,
nobody even heard about it.
See, when people read there's
a serial killer in town,
their guards go up, which was happening.
But then when they read the serial killer
only preys on prostitutes,
if you're not a prostitute,
your defenses are going to go back down.
So he created this Water
Street Butcher persona
to assuage people's fears
about this unknown killer.
So that he could continue
to prey on everyone else.
- Hi.
- Hi,
you having some car trouble?
[Woman] Oh yeah, my car just died.
I don't know what's wrong with it.
[Ed] Oh, you need me
to call you a tow truck?
Oh, Officer, thank you.
That would be great.
I've been stuck here for over an hour.
[Ed] You know, you really
shouldn't be out here
by yourself with that Water Street Butcher
on the loose and all.
[Woman] I thought he
just attacked prostitutes?
[Ed] Hey, look, there's a gas station
a mile down where you'll be safe.
Let me drop you there,
then you won't have to
wait out here alone.
[Woman] You wouldn't mind?
[Ed] Not at all.
[Woman] Oh, thank you, okay.
[Ed] I have a lot of stuff up here,
would you mind jumping into the back?
Sure, sure, why not.
Thank you.
This is what it looks
like to be arrested, huh?
[Ed] Hey, you ever been arrested?
(laughing)
Not that I care to admit to.
I once got arrested for drinking
underage, but that's it.
Wow, I've had such a long day.
I think, I think that was
the exit to the gas station.
Excuse me, wasn't that the
exit to the gas station?
[Ed] I guess it was.
Perhaps you better turn around.
[Ed] You know, can I ask you something?
What?
Would you please turn around?
[Ed] Why did you call me Officer?
Sorry, what do you mean?
[Ed] Well, before you got into the car,
you called me Officer.
Why did you call me that?
I thought police liked it
when you called them that.
[Ed] Well, they do.
But I'm not cop.
You're not?
[Ed] No.
That's not very funny.
[Ed] Well, I'm not trying to be.
I'm sorry, I don't understand.
What are you then?
[Ed] I'm a butcher.
That's not funny.
[Ed] Yeah, no, it's not.
You shouldn't get into stranger's cars.
You're not a cop?
[Ed] Didn't you learn about assumptions?
They make an ass of u and me.
Where are you going?
[Ed] You'll see.
Please don't do this.
Sir?
Please don't hurt me.
I'm...
I'm, I'm a good person, I have a family,
and they'll tell someone I'm missing.
I'm so sorry, perhaps I
made you want to do this--
[Ed] Well how about
this, I'll make you a deal.
Yeah?
[Ed] We'll pull over,
and I'm gonna rape you.
But then, then if you've been good,
and you haven't done anything
stupid, I won't kill you.
Okay.
[Ed] You think I'd fall for that?
You're not just gonna let me rape you.
Yes I am.
[Ed] I don't believe you.
Why?
[Ed] You know, to be perfectly honest,
I don't think either of us
are gonna want you alive
for the things I'm going to do to you.
(woman screaming)
[Woman] I'm so sorry!
Please, let me...
(woman screaming)
Obviously I wouldn't
leave handles on the doors.
(woman screaming)
[Woman] Somebody help me!
Help me!
Oh my god, somebody help me!
No!
(woman screaming)
Help me!
Somebody help me!
(woman screaming)
(static hiss building)
(low rumbling music)
(dramatic frightening music)
(woman whimpering)
(woman groaning)
This killer knows
how to play the profile
in exactly the way he wants,
just like a really good actor
can make you think they're
really crying, or laughing.
To give you an example of what I mean,
let me read a couple of these profiles.
Suspect is a white male, age 18 to 25.
White male, age 25 to 35.
Black male, age 25 to 30.
Disorganized, highly organized.
Serial killer, most likely
his first time killing.
First killing, definitely
not his first killing.
Lives alone, probably
in a very messy house.
His home will be clean and kempt.
Sadist, sadistic, sadist.
Has most likely been institutionalized
for a good portion of his life.
Highly functional, may
have limited faculties.
Highly intelligent,
probably highly educated.
Most likely never finished high school.
Most likely works in law enforcement,
possibly a police officer
or a security guard.
Probably lives off some
sort of disability.
Most likely cannot hold a job.
Knows profiling, and may be
employed as an FBI profiler.
(Sighs)
(downbeat music)
I went back to the map
that the killer had sent me.
It was made online using MapQuest.
So I put in a call to the FBI
to see what we could get from this.
They got the records from MapQuest,
and only one download was made
from that exact map during
the month in question.
My name is Captain Harvey Scroggs.
I lead the assault on the house.
As I like to say, we dropped
the whole hammer on him.
Helicopters, SWAT, clogs,
bomb squad, everything.
Just in case.
(helicopter rotor whirring)
[Officer] It's clear!
- Clear.
[Officer] Clear.
[Officer] All clear.
People ask me how we found him,
and I say, first, we didn't find him.
Just this house.
And second, we didn't
find it, he gave it to us.
He wanted us to find it.
And that's further evidenced
by the fact that there
was not one single fingerprint
in the entire house.
Over here on the wall, got
a little bit of blood here.
And here, point the camera
down Sean, point it down.
Got one, two, three, four,
five boxes of videotapes
numbered sequentially--
[Officer] Hey guys.
Hey guys, come here.
Come on.
[Agent] Whoa.
Get in here Sean.
Get over here.
Over here.
Ready?
Go.
My god.
[Officer] Is she alive?
[Agent] Oh my god she is.
We need a medic in here.
Get a medic in here now!
(gentle downbeat music)
Oh, people kept trying to tell me
all those years that
Cheryl was probably dead.
That I should probably start to move on.
But I wouldn't.
I kep telling everyone, I have
to keep hope until I know.
But then I got the call.
The officer said, we found your daughter.
And I thought he meant her body.
I have never seen a human being
born and raised in the United States
show evidence of this kind of torture.
She had been burned, cut,
she had five teeth removed
by pliers or a hammer.
She had multiple broken bones.
Not only that none of them
have been allowed to heal,
some have been further aggravated
by some sort of tightening apparatus.
She had also been extremely malnourished,
and her organs were in
really bad shape as a result.
There also was severe sexual torture.
Including things like
electrocution of genitals,
and things that are too
horrible to say out loud.
While she was in the hospital,
a lot of her injuries seemed
to get worse instead of better,
and we couldn't figure it out.
Then I realized that pain, not
just pain, but brutal pain,
had been such a huge part
of her life for so long
she didn't know how to exist without it.
She no longer knew how
to exist in the world
if not through horrific pain.
She was torturing herself
when nobody was looking.
It was very strange, seeing
Cheryl after all that time.
You know, the time that she was missing,
I went from being a carefree college girl
to having two girls of my own.
It was hard to see the girl that I loved
and the girl that came back.
(downbeat music)
I don't know.
I don't know what you want me to say.
[Interviewer] Talk about what
it's like being home again.
I don't know.
What do you want me to say?
[Interviewer] It had to be nice
seeing your mom again after all that time.
Yeah.
Maybe.
I don't know what you want me to say.
[Interviewer] What was the man
you lived with all these years like?
I don't know.
I don't think that I
want to do this anymore.
[Interviewer] Why?
'Cause I don't know
what you want me to say.
[Interviewer] You can
say anything you want.
He loved me.
Nobody ever lets me say it, but it's true.
He didn't mean to leave me.
And someday he's gonna come back to me.
And he's gonna take me away.
(downbeat music)
Well, another tragedy for
this small family in Reading,
Take a look here at the crime scene.
The recently buried body of Cheryl Dempsey
was stolen from her grave.
It happened here last
night at Woodlawn Cemetery.
The only thing left
behind a broken casket.
As you can see, a real mess.
Police are now investigating
a possible link
between this demented
crime and a serial killer
who has been tormenting the East Coast
known as the Water Street Butcher.
(downbeat music)
My feeling is that he's
moved somewhere else.
I doubt very strongly
that he's stopped killing.
I doubt very strongly that
anyone even knows he's there.
But in some town out there,
the disappearance and
murder rates are rising,
and somewhere out there
he's responsible for it.
Something I find
interesting about these tapes
is that they're numbered sequentially,
but there were 27 tapes
missing when we found them.
I wonder what was on those tapes.
I wonder if they were just too private
for him to let anyone see.
Or if his face was visible in those,
or if they revealed
just too much about him.
Or maybe they were worse than
anything that we've seen.
I'll tell you one
place we'll be watching.
If this documentary thing you're making
ever gets to the theaters,
he won't be able to help himself.
He'll see this movie as
many times as he can.
We'll keep an eye on as
many screenings as we can,
because he'll be there.
(low downbeat music)
(downbeat music)
(ominous music building)
(eerie downbeat music)
(woman panting)
[Ed] I'll make you a deal.
You can live as long as you don't blink.
(woman panting and screaming)