Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hello?
- You still asleep?
- No, I'm not...
Get up. I'm outside.
Why? What time is it?
It's time to go.
Come on, hurry up.
You're late.
- Hey.
- Hi!
- Sorry I'm late.
- It's okay.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
Nice pj's.
Let's go.
We're going.
I know that look.
You got to pee.
No, I don't.
Yeah, okay. Yeah, I do.
Babe, we just left.
I know. I'm sorry.
We haven't even been
six blocks.
Well, I got to go.
- Okay.
- I'll be fast.
- Can we go?
- Yes.
You sure? Positive?
Yeah. Come on.
Gross.
Here. Hand me that water.
- Grab the wheel.
- Whoa, whoa.
Come on.
Yeah. That's impressive.
Thank you.
I'm excited
for the girls to meet you.
I can't wait to meet them.
Are your friends
gonna like me?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
They're gonna love you.
Look out!
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, shit.
Did you hit him?
What the fuck
was that guy doing
in the road?
Did you hit him?
No. I don't know.
I don't know. Shit.
You okay?
Yeah. We almost killed him.
I'm gonna go see
if he's okay.
What? Why?
Grace, we're in
the middle of nowhere.
We can't just leave
that guy out here.
We gotta see if he's okay.
That guy is just
standing there, Jim.
He's not even moving.
What kind of freak
just stands
in the middle of the road
and doesn't even flinch?
Oh, man.
He's coming over here.
I'm gonna go talk to him.
No, please. Let's just
call somebody for help, okay?
Let's go.
I don't want to
pick up a stranger
out here.
All right. All right.
What's wrong?
Engine's flooded.
Come on. He's coming up here.
Come on...
Fuck.
Come on, start! Come on!
No signal.
This isn't right.
I'm sure someone else
will come along.
Yeah. I hope so.
You know, I never did
a full 360 before.
First one.
Just keep your eyes
on the road.
I will.
Man, raining out there
pretty hard, huh?
Yeah.
Hey, Doritos or Cheetos?
Cheetos.
Ding Dongs or Twinkies?
Ding Dongs.
Damn. Lady knows
her processed foods, huh?
Yeah.
Pump number seven.
Hey, there's a guy broke down
a few miles back.
Can you send someone
with a tow, or...
Yeah, that's a no-can-do.
That's Buford's truck
out there.
Probably be back
around 7:00.
All right.
I'm gonna go
to the bathroom.
- Good.
- Oh.
You need a key, ma'am.
And there you go.
I'm just joking with you.
Thanks.
That's a car, ain't it?
What?
442.
That's a bad-ass
fuckin' ride, man.
Regular little
pussy wagon, huh?
Right.
What do you drive?
Been fixing up this Camaro
in my back yard.
Guys want to take
a little break
from the drive,
you can come on over.
That's all right.
We got to get
on the road, man.
I got a couple of donkeys
in the back yard.
Me and my cousin
raise those things.
I got kicked in the eye.
That's why I got
a lazy eye and shit.
I tried to milk
that son of a bitch.
You can't milk
a fucking donkey, though.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
All right. Anyway.
I'm okay.
- There you go.
- Thanks.
- Hi.
- Hey.
You have a motel nearby?
There's one in Tatum,
about 15 miles north of here.
Hey, I bet you he's that guy
who was having car troubles.
Yeah. Hey, sorry
for taking off back there.
That was you?
Yeah.
Don't worry about it.
I wouldn't have
picked me up, either.
You still headed north?
Yeah.
Would you mind giving me
a ride to the motel?
Yeah, okay.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
What's going on?
This is the guy
we almost hit.
He can't get a tow
until morning,
so I told him
we could give him a ride
to the motel.
Hi.
I'm John Ryder.
Grace.
Nice to meet you, Grace.
So, where you from, man?
All over.
What do you do?
I'm between jobs. You know?
Yeah.
My dad changed jobs a lot
when I was a kid.
Yeah?
Yeah, he's a salesman.
It's Ford trucks now,
but he's sold
everything from Buicks
to farm equipment.
That's probably what
I'll end up doing, too.
Where you heading?
Lake Havasu. Spring break.
Sounds like fun.
Yeah.
I hope so.
She's a good-looking girl.
Thank you.
How long
you been fuckin' her?
Excuse me?
It's a simple question.
How long you been fucking
your wife?
I don't have one.
Well, what's with
the wedding ring, then?
It helps strangers
think I'm trustworthy.
Aren't you?
No.
Hey, hey, hey!
What the fuck
are you doing, man?
All right, you know what?
That's it.
Ride's over, pal.
Keep driving.
All right. Okay? Okay?
Look, we don't want
any trouble, all right?
We just...
What do you want?
We got money.
I don't want your money.
What do you want?
You want the car?
I don't want your car.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Come on, man.
What do you want, man?
Stop!
Hey, what are you doing?
Jim.
If you fucking hurt her,
you're a fucking dead man!
Jim.
I want you to stop me.
Don't hurt her, all right?
Jim!
Then stop me.
How? You're the one
with the fuckin' knife.
All you have to say
is four little words.
"I want to die."
Say what?
Don't say it.
For your sake, he better.
You want her to die?
No. No.
Say it!
Come on. I...
I...
Want...
To...
Die.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I don't want to die!
Get his door! Get the door!
I'm going to kick
this motherfucker out!
Get the door!
Get out of my car!
Fucking psycho fuck!
Fuck you, asshole!
You okay?
Yeah.
Hey, hey, come on.
It's okay.
Hey, come on.
We're okay. It's okay, huh?
It's okay.
We should call the cops.
Okay.
What is it? What is it?
My phone's gone.
Well, as we
come up on 4:00, I've got
something nice and mellow
for all you night owls
out there.
Here's a classic
from David Soul.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Grace? Grace?
Morning.
Jim, I just wanna go home.
Come on.
We'll stop in the next town,
we'll get some food,
I'll talk to the cops,
and we'll be drinking beers
with your friends
by tonight.
Besides, we got one hell
of a story to tell.
Yeah, you just wanna
tell all my friends
you saved my life.
Yeah.
Let's go eat.
Look at this.
It is a beautiful day.
Yeah.
You ever think
about having kids?
Sometimes. I don't know.
Yeah, I guess, eventually.
Oh, my God!
Pull up, pull up.
Shit!
We gotta warn these people.
Sir, you got to stop!
Hey! Hey!
The guy in the back
of your car is crazy!
He pulled a knife on us!
- Stop the car, sir!
- He's dangerous.
Pull your car over!
The guy in the back
of your car is crazy.
He's dangerous!
He has a knife!
- Pull over! He tried to...
- Oh, shit!
What?
Grace.
- Okay.
- Oh, fuck.
We're fine.
- You okay?
- Mmm-hmm.
Yeah.
They didn't stop!
We gotta walk.
Give me a minute.
All right.
Fuck!
How did he find us?
I don't know.
Maybe he wasn't
looking for us.
Maybe it was
just bad luck.
What about
those people?
It's gonna be okay.
No, it isn't.
Hey.
Oh, God.
Hey!
Stop!
- Hey!
- Stop. Stop!
Stop! Please!
- Please!
- Please stop!
Nobody stops for strangers.
Jim.
Oh, no.
You stay behind me.
He might still be inside.
Just stay here.
You don't want to see this.
Why?
Just stay there. Please.
What is it?
Don't you come over here,
all right?
Just... Please! Please!
Oh, sir! Sir!
Oh, Grace, Grace,
this guy's really bleeding.
I think we got to
leave the knife in.
I don't know.
What do we do?
Open the back door.
Can you clear it out?
We gotta get him
to a hospital.
Okay.
Come on, Grace!
Sir?
Okay.
It's all right, sir.
Come on, pick him up.
Pick him up.
Come on, you gotta just...
Sir?
Sir, stay with me,
all right?
I'm gonna get him
in the back seat.
I'll get his legs in.
Okay, go on. Come on.
You gotta drive.
Sir, please...
Oh, God...
Grace!
Be with me in this darkness,
dear Lord.
We're gonna get you help.
Okay, sir?
Is she okay?
No. She is not okay.
You sure she's not okay?
She's not okay.
Try not to move, sir. Please.
How could somebody do this?
You don't just kill a family.
Grace...
- What the fuck?
- What...
Oh, my God. It's him! Fuck!
Just keep driving.
I'm driving. I'm driving.
What does he want?
I don't know. We pushed him
out of a fucking car!
What do you think?
Yeah? What were we
supposed to do?
Let him kill us?
Can't this thing go
any faster? Just drive!
I'm trying, okay?
Come on! Come on!
Come on.
I don't wanna die out here.
What do you think?
What's he doing?
What do you think
he's doing?
Where'd he go?
Oh, shit.
We gotta get this guy
to a hospital, Grace.
Grace, go inside
and call the police,
all right? Get some towels.
- I'm gonna stay here
with him.
- Okay.
Okay.
Sir, we're gonna
get you some help.
Okay? Okay?
Can you call 911, please?
It's an emergency!
What's going on?
Towels. I need towels.
Paper towels are
in the bathroom.
- Where is your bathroom?
- It's over there.
Thank you.
Sustain me in the darkness
which overwhelms me.
Torrance County
Sheriff's Office.
Marlene, it's Beth
down at EI Dorado's.
Oh, hi, Beth.
You better get Harlan
down here fast.
The Lord is my shepherd.
I shall not want.
Bless my family and friends
as I depart from them.
Sir.
I will fear no evil,
for thou art with me.
I will fear no evil.
- Stop right there!
- What?
Put your hands
behind your back!
Freeze!
Let me see your hands!
Get out of the car!
No, no, no.
We're the ones
who called you! Tell him!
- Quiet! Move.
- No, no...
You're under arrest.
Come on, move!
No, you don't understand.
You have to help
those people.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say can
and may be used against you
in a court of law.
- I just saw him right there.
- You have the right
to an attorney.
If you cannot
afford an attorney...
She didn't do anything!
This guy you picked up,
he give you a name?
I told you,
he said his name
was John Ryder.
Sit in the chair, please.
Young lady, have a seat.
Where was
this gas station located?
I don't know.
God, I don't even know
where I am.
Tatum.
We saw signs for Tatum.
Did anybody see you
pick this guy up?
Yeah, the clerk
at the gas station saw him.
Clerk got a name?
I didn't ask him his name.
I'm trying to help you.
Put your hands
through the opening.
Look at me.
I didn't kill that family.
All right?
I was trying
to help that guy.
Come on.
Hey.
Hey, come on!
I don't need to be
down here, man!
I was trying
to help that family!
I was trying to help them!
And I'm telling you
the truth, okay?
I opened the door,
Jim pushed him out of the car.
That's it.
Marlene,
this is unit seven...
Marlene, are you
gonna answer that?
Are... Are you kidding?
Why are you
wasting your time
in here with me?
You should be out there
looking for him.
He is gonna kill
more people.
I'll be right back.
Come on, man,
you can't leave me
down here like this!
Hello?
I know somebody is in there.
I know that you can hear me!
Come on!
I didn't do anything!
Hello?
Hello!
Grace!
Just let me talk to Grace.
I just want to talk to Grace.
Stupid redneck.
Torrance SO, SP-214.
It's been reported
we're not receiving
any transmissions
from Torrance SO.
Please respond.
Hello?
SP dispatch,
no, we're going to scan
all frequencies
in case we're off channel.
Sorry.
Approach with caution.
You scream
like a little bitch.
Why are you doing this?
You're a smart kid.
You can figure it out.
Jim?
He's down here!
One more word
and I'll kill you both.
Where are you?
Jim!
Jim, answer me!
I've got a gun!
Grace!
Oh, thank God you're okay.
Everybody's dead.
Everybody upstairs.
Come on. Come on.
Get me out of here.
Okay, okay, okay.
Hold this.
Light. I need light.
Okay.
Come on.
You think they got him?
I think we need to go back.
Come on.
We're not going back there.
We need to get help.
He killed the help.
Here. Give me the gun.
What?
Give me the gun.
Fine.
We should have gone home
when we had the chance.
Come on. Don't blame this
on me, all right?
It's not my fault.
I'm not.
Yes, you are.
Well, why'd you have to
offer the guy a ride?
I didn't offer him a ride!
He asked for one.
All right?
That stupid hick clerk
brought it up.
And you agreed!
Yeah! Yeah.
What else was I
supposed to do?
How was I supposed to know
he was a sick fuck lunatic?
You could have
just listened to me.
You okay?
- You okay?
- Yeah.
SP-172.
We're gonna get a roadblock
started down the road,
I guess, on that side.
This is Albuquerque SP.
Yes, this is
Officer Garcia.
Go ahead.
- Gonna need
the coroner out here.
- 10-4.
Well...
He'll show up
in 20 minutes. Out.
Roger.
Is that confirmed
they passed along
that suspect description
to Arizona DPS?
There's another one
over here.
Right.
Yeah, that is confirmed.
My goodness.
How old did you say
these kids are?
Early 20s.
The boy,
you said he was locked up
downstairs, right?
Yes, sir.
And the girl,
she was interrogated
inside here?
Yes, sir.
Then who the hell did that?
Get me air support now.
I want eyes in the sky.
Looks like we have
a third suspect.
Hello?
- Jim?
- What?
Come on,
we'll get one of
these cars.
- Jim, get down!
- Oh, fuck.
- Is there a way out?
- No!
- See him?
- No.
He comes through
that door, he's dead!
Twenty-one years old.
They didn't do it, boys.
College students.
They didn't do this.
They didn't.
You see him?
No, I don't see him.
I don't know
where he went.
Oh, God. Jim... Jim...
- What?
- There's a cop.
It's the cop from the diner.
We got to talk to him.
No. No. No.
He thinks we did it.
Only chance we have
to get out of here.
All right.
You take this, all right?
Okay.
- All right?
- Okay.
I'm gonna go talk to him.
You just watch. Watch.
Okay.
Officer, please,
you don't understand!
We're all in danger here.
You aren't going anywhere
this time, son.
Please, Officer!
This is SO-235.
I have the male suspect
in custody.
I repeat, I have
the male suspect in custody.
The female remains at large.
Get off him.
State 531.
We have a support unit
just minutes away.
Do you copy?
Come on. Get up.
Take it easy.
Let's not go do
anything stupid.
Just stay calm.
I am calm.
Grace.
Hey! Just keep your hands
in the air, please.
Grace, you don't need
to do this.
Jim, take it.
Sorry about this, man.
We have to
get out of here.
We got to go. Come on,
let's get in the car.
Please, sir. Please.
- Turn around, please, sir.
- Okay. Okay.
Okay.
What the fuck
are you doing?
What am I supposed to do?
We have to get out of here.
I know,
but this is crazy.
I know.
Just go...
Please get in the car, sir.
Listen. Just take it easy.
- Just give me the gun.
- No. You don't understand.
We don't have time
for this.
We have to
get out of here.
Grace, we got to go.
Come on, please just
get in the car. Get in.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What did you do?
- Freeze!
- I didn't do it!
Get in the car!
We got to get out of here!
SO-236.
We have an officer down!
Female suspect shot Edwards.
She took off
in a Torrance County
Sheriff's vehicle!
What the fuck
happened back there?
It must've been him!
He's not going to stop, is he?
No.
He's framing us.
No. No. If he was doing that,
he would have stopped
when he killed the family.
Then what does he want?
I don't know!
Suspects armed
and considered dangerous.
Lieutenant, we are
in pursuit of the suspects
on Highway 285.
Copy that.
They are armed and dangerous.
How long till
my air support is 10-97?
This is Air 2.
We're on their 20,
but don't have a visual.
Get on that thing
and tell them
that he's back there
in the trailer park.
Get on that thing.
Hello?
Is this on?
Can anybody hear me?
Oh, shit!
Air 2 to base.
We've spotted the suspects.
We're joining
ground pursuit.
This is bad.
Grace Andrews
and Jim Halsey.
This is
Lieutenant Esteridge
with the New Mexico
State Police Department.
How y'all doing?
Listen, we're really
not too good, okay?
The guy that shot that cop
is back there
in the trailer park
that we just pulled out of,
off of that dirt road.
Well, now, you see,
I have an officer down,
and I have a witness
says that you did it.
So you'll pull
your car over.
If you feel like
talking about it,
we can talk about it then.
Okay, what do we do?
Just tell him
that you didn't do it.
Listen to me.
I did not shoot that cop!
Okay?
I didn't shoot him,
we didn't kill that family,
we haven't done anything.
When are you gonna
believe us?
Now, now, now, you don't
make the rules around here,
you see? I do.
So, why don't you
just pull over
so we'll chat about it
before this thing gets
out of control, okay?
We can't. He's close.
We can't pull over here.
It's not safe.
Why don't you
just pull the car over,
or I'll have my men
help you do it?
We cannot pull over here!
You don't understand!
Suspects are still
not stopping, sir.
I don't give a rat's cock bag
how you do it!
You will pull them over
and stop them right now!
Over!
Copy on that.
What the...
Oh, my God!
Oh, shit!
- I'm gonna pull over!
- Okay! Okay! Okay!
Oh, fuck!
Lieutenant,
ground is firing on suspects.
Hold her steady!
Okay, we're pulling over.
Please, just stop shooting!
Air 2 to ground,
you got another vehicle
approaching fast from behind.
It's a late-model
black Trans Am.
- Oh, fuck!
- What?
It's him, Jim.
Fuck!
Somebody talk to me.
Have you pulled over
the suspects yet?
What the fuck
is going on down there?
Fuck!
Oh, my God!
What's going on
down there?
Fuck!
Son of a bitch!
You gotta be
five-finger fucking me!
Keep going!
Grace, I can't go
any faster!
Just drive. Go.
I can't go
any fuckin' faster!
Oh, fuck.
Where's he going?
Come on. We got to go.
He might come back.
Where?
Jim.
Get your gun. Let's go.
Okay.
All right.
We're good.
Try to call home.
What's wrong?
It goes right to
the front desk.
Are you serious?
I should go find a payphone.
Call our folks,
see if we can get some help.
I'll be back in 15 minutes.
Okay.
Hey.
I'm sorry
I got us into this.
Well, what about
the lovebirds?
Are you sure
you wouldn't like to see
a canary instead?
We have some very nice
canaries this week.
All right.
All right,
may I see them, please?
There we are.
Whoa, there.
Back in your gilded cage,
Melanie Daniels.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
You're making me horny.
I'm fuckin' horny, too!
I have a gun!
Jim?
Jim!
Okay, I'll get you.
- Grace! Help me!
- I'm here and I'm gonna
get you down.
I'm gonna get you down.
You've got to get me
out of here.
- It really hurts!
- I know. Just hold still.
Just hold still.
- Please stop him. Please!
- Wait, wait, wait.
No!
Stop it!
You're killing him!
Turn it off!
No.
Turn the truck off!
These clutches
are tricky things.
Touchy, you know.
One little slip, and...
I will shoot you.
You shoot me,
my foot comes off the clutch.
Now, get in.
- Get in!
- Okay.
Close the door.
Turn it off.
Stop! Stop the truck!
Turn it off!
I can't.
Yes, you can.
Just turn it off.
I can't. I can't.
You're sick.
What do you want?
Point it in my face.
Right here.
Do it.
It's your chance, Grace,
your chance to kill a man
who's gonna kill
your whiny fuckin' boyfriend.
No! Don't you say that!
Don't say that to me!
I want to die.
Now pull the fuckin' trigger.
State police!
Put the gun down!
This is the police!
Drop the gun now!
Don't listen to them.
No. Stop. Please.
Put the gun down!
Go ahead. You can do it!
Put it down!
Put the gun down!
Put the gun down now!
Put that gun down,
God damn it!
I can't...
Please.
Please, don't tease him.
Please,
just stop hurting him.
Please!
This is the police!
Put the gun down now!
No.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
You useless waste!
No! No!
No!
Get your hands off of me!
Get up here!
Let's go, man. This way!
I want to die.
- No!
- Grace?
Grace, do you know
who this man is?
That's the real John Ryder.
He's been missing
since Tuesday.
Then who...
We don't know yet.
Now, we've run
his fingerprints
and mug shots
through every database
we've got,
and we've come up
with nothing.
This guy's a ghost.
So, I need your help
here, Grace.
Is there anything
he told you about himself?
No.
Anything at all?
Open cell F!
Ryder, I need you to stand up
and put your hands
behind your back.
I need you to stand up,
put your hands
behind your back.
So, where are you from?
All over.
Is that so?
You're a sick fuck,
aren't ya?
The way you tortured
that young man.
I know
you enjoyed yourself.
I just can't figure out
why you did it.
You knew
you'd get caught.
Why'd you do it?
Why not?
How many others
have you killed?
Hard to say.
You see,
here in the great state
of New Mexico,
we do have
the death penalty.
You don't seem
too worried.
Should I be?
You comfy down there, John?
Are those cuffs
a little tight?
Yeah, a little tight.
Yeah, you see,
those are the new ones.
They stretch out after
you wear them for a while.
Let me see.
Look at me.
You have yourself
a nice trip.
We'll chat again real soon.
Maybe next time,
you'll be better company.
Thanks.
Where are we going?
I'm taking you to Albuquerque
for trauma support.
I can release you
to your parents there.
Step up.
03 X-ray,
we're about 20 minutes out.
Copy that, 03 X-ray.
I get home,
I look at my paycheck.
It's so skinny.
I decide to take
another job.
So now
I'm delivering pizza.
What are you
getting your daughter
for her birthday?
She's just turned five.
She wants to take me...
Go to the mall,
get one of those big
customized teddy bears.
A customized teddy bear?
Come on.
Yeah.
It's just another way
they can charge...
Look, Grace...
I wish I could have
stopped this
before it got
all out of control.
I know there's
nothing that I can say
that'll bring Jim back,
but I am sorry.
I truly am.
Get your own little pants,
your own little jacket.
Make your own
little teddy bear.
For real, you spent
100 bucks on a teddy bear?
Yeah, I know.
It was hurting me.
Yeah, it's 100 bucks...
You know,
this week's check,
it's gone.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Stop moving.
What the fuck?
It's cool...
Oh, shit!
Son of a bitch!
My leg's stuck.
03 X-ray.
I need a Code 3 backup
on Highway 19.
10-4, 03 X-ray.
Grace, I want you
to run up over that hill
and wait there for help.
I'm done running.
Grace! Grace!
That's not the answer.
You don't know
what you're doing.
Yes, I do.
Grace!
Grace, be careful!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Backup, now!
Let's go!
03 X-ray. Where the hell
is my goddamn backup?
You better hurry.
Grace!
Go fuck yourself!
No!
Feels good, doesn't it?
I don't feel a thing.