Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
You done with your breakfast?
Yeah.
Let's do this thing.
- I'll see you later.
- Okay.
- Drive safe.
- Bye, Mom.
- You got your lunch?
- Yeah.
Mrs. Peterson?
Yes. Can I, help you?
My name is David,
Mrs. Peterson.
I...
I knew your son Caleb.
We trained together and served together
and, well, we came to be good friends.
Would you like to come inside?
Thank you, ma'am.
So, are you sure I can't
get you anything?
Maybe just some water would be nice.
How did you get here?
I ran.
I needed the exercise.
From the bus station, I mean, in town.
You ran that whole way?
Yes, ma'am.
Here you go.
All right. Thank you, ma'am.
When did you get out?
Well, I was discharged on Wednesday
and I came straight here
from Fort Kennilworth.
You came straight here first thing?
Yeah. I wanted to come by sooner,
but I couldn't get leave.
Why?
Well, I was discharged
'cause I was wounded.
I was in a military hospital for a bit,
so it wasn't really the kind of
thing you could get leave from.
But don't worry, it was just
a bit of shrapnel in my back.
I'm right as rain now.
No, I meant, why did
you come here first thing?
Well, like I said, me and
your son Caleb, we were...
We were pretty close.
I was with him when he died.
- Really?
- Yes, ma'am.
And one of the things he asked
was for me to check on you all.
You and your whole family here.
He wanted me to tell
you that he loved you.
He specifically wanted me
to tell each one of you that
he loved you and he was thinking
of you guys up until the end.
I said I'd do that and so, here I am.
Would you excuse me, please?
That's me.
Right there.
Well, I'll be...
I remember that day.
It wasn't my intention
to upset you, ma'am.
I probably should have called first,
but I don't own a cell phone yet and,
I guess, I just wasn't thinking.
I'm going to be on my way now,
but I'd like it if we
could exchange e-mails...
Wait. No.
Anna, Caleb's sister, she works
nights, and she sleeps late.
And I know she would love to meet you.
Would you stay a little while longer?
Oh, you're not just saying
that to be polite now?
'Cause you don't need to be.
No, I'm not. Please, stay. It's...
It's nice having you here
and I would love to hear
more about you and Caleb.
Well, all right.
...Caleb and me, we figure that sounds,
more like a challenge
than anything else.
So, that night after he falls asleep,
we kind of crept over to his
cot with a tube of superglue.
Oh, no!
We didn't do anything too bad to him,
though, we could have, you know.
Hey, there you are. Anna, this is David.
Very nice to meet you.
Caleb told me a lot about you.
David just got discharged this week.
He was a friend of your brother's.
You knew Caleb?
Yes, ma'am.
"Yes, ma'am."
Okay.
So, where are you staying?
Well, I noticed a motel off the
highway on the way here...
No, no, no, no. You will stay
with us while you're here.
Oh, no. I couldn't put you all out.
Nonsense. We would love to have you.
We have plenty of room.
In fact, you can stay
in Caleb's old room.
We insist.
Well, I won't argue.
Just for tonight, though.
Well, I've got to head to the diner.
It was really great meeting you.
Likewise. Very nice meeting you.
- I guess I'll see you later.
- Bye.
Can I show you to your room?
Great.
There are clean towels in the bathroom
if you'd like to freshen up.
Mrs. Peterson, are you sure you're
comfortable with me staying in here?
Of course.
I mean, it's not like
it's going to any use.
I think it could be a good thing for us.
I'm gonna go and let you get settled in.
If you need anything, just holler.
Oh, my God!
Fucking pussy.
Oh, it's okay, little baby, don't cry.
Hey, there.
How was your day?
It was good.
Great.
...giving him a chance,
it's that I don't like the idea of
some random guy off the
street being invited to stay
in my house with my family.
So, you knew my brother?
I did, pretty well, yeah.
He wanted me to tell
you that he loved you.
Oh. Thanks.
Even though he says he
was friends with Caleb.
He's in the photograph of Caleb's squad.
You saw the photograph.
- He was not a stranger.
- You know what?
What if he has the PTSD
or whatever it's called?
Some of these guys come back with
mental health problems, Laura.
Did you take that into account?
What if Caleb had come back different?
Wow, that is...
Your parents are fighting about me.
Yeah. They argue a lot.
You look like you got hit or something.
Yeah, yeah, I got hit with
a football in gym class.
Yeah, that can happen.
Yeah.
No, no, you're right,
you're right. Let's talk to him.
Hi, great, okay.
David, we're very happy
to have you here.
I'm gonna have a beer before dinner.
Can I offer you one?
- Well, no, thank you.
- No. Okay. Suit yourself.
And dinner is gonna be ready in an hour.
So, Luke, why don't
you do some homework.
Okay.
David, can I get you anything?
Oh, no, thank you,
Mrs. Peterson, I'm fine.
Yeah, hit this.
Look out... Shit.
No...
- Now?
- No, I'm good, but thank you.
So, that friend of your brother's,
is he sticking around?
I don't know. I hope not.
Why? You said you liked him.
I said he seemed nice.
That's not the same thing.
Oh, okay.
Why don't you like him?
I don't not like him.
It's just, I...
I mean, you kind of knew Caleb.
We've all...
I just know Mom and Dad
have been trying to move on
and it's not like they don't have
enough reminders in this town.
Yeah.
I don't know,
that seems pretty normal to me.
You know, like, your kid dies.
That's hard.
Yeah.
Guess we just don't need a walking,
breathing reminder
of him right now, you know?
Yeah. Totally.
I've got to go.
Hey, wait a second. Wait a second.
- Stop. I can't...
- What!
No, no. Let's just hang out,
like, a little bit longer.
- I can't.
- Just a little bit longer.
I can't. I have to go.
- You don't have to go.
- Yes, I do.
But I'm sure we can find some
time at Kristen's tomorrow, okay?
Stop, I have to go.
The sine is the angle of
the ship's anchor cable,
so the cable is the hypotenuse,
and what we need to find out
is the distance down
to the ocean bottom,
so that's the opposite. Do you see?
Not really.
So, you're kind of smart?
I guess so.
Hey, how was work?
Good. Not too busy.
David, sure I can't get you a beer?
You know, I will have one. Thank you.
- I'll take one, too.
- Yeah, I'm sure you will.
I'm 21 in a month.
You can have all the beer you want then,
assuming you buy it yourself.
Are you helping him with his homework?
Well, not exactly.
Hey, don't go.
Stick around, be sociable.
I'm kind of tired.
I think I'm gonna lay down.
Okay. Suit yourself.
But Allan, his name's Allan,
he's only been there for, what,
like, four years, but he's got a degree,
so, boom, suddenly he's
regional manager and I'm not.
And that's okay. I mean, it's okay.
But I know Laura, I know she's worried.
She wonders if I'm ever,
ever going to make any money.
Your wife seems to respect you, sir.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
It is what it is, you know.
What about you, though?
What about you? What are your plans?
Figured I'd get on a bus tomorrow,
head down to Florida or something
and start looking for work.
I've done construction work before.
So, I'm sure I'll find something.
No, no, no, no, no. That's crazy.
That's crazy. You don't
know where you're going.
Stay here for a couple more days.
No. No, I can't.
I couldn't impose on your
hospitality any longer, sir.
You're not... Impose on our...
And "sir"? You're calling me "sir" now?
You gotta stop with the "sir,"
my name's Spencer.
You gotta call me Spencer,
for God sakes.
- Okay.
- All right.
So you're sticking around, right?
You stick around at least till
you know where you're going.
Well, maybe just a couple
more days, all right.
Cool, excellent. It's a deal.
Let's have a couple more
of these to celebrate,
and then I've got to get off to bed.
God, you can put your liquor away.
I guess so.
I'm tired. Are you tired?
No, I don't need much sleep.
What are you doing here?
I told your mom I could pick
you up from school today.
That cool?
Yeah.
Don't you, like, have any friends?
I have lots of friends.
Just not, like, here. Like, online.
What are you waiting for?
I want you to show me
who hit you yesterday.
I got hit with a football.
Yeah.
What are you going to do?
Nothing bad.
Over there.
All of them?
Well, most of them give me a hard time.
Those two guys,
Mike and Ian, are the worst.
Those guys are real assholes.
Can we go now?
Yes.
What are you doing?
They're going to a bar?
Yeah,
this place will serve you if
you're on the football team.
Well, I could use a drink.
How about you?
No.
You coming?
Well, I'll be inside if
you change your mind.
What the fuck?
Hey, Luke.
Maybe it's his boyfriend or something?
Excuse me.
I'm gonna need to see some ID.
You ID all of them?
What can I get you?
Do you know how to make a fireball?
Cinnamon schnapps and Tabasco sauce.
That's my drink of choice.
Let me get one of those.
A Coke here for my brother,
and I can't help but notice
that those ladies over there
are drinking cheap beer.
That seems like a shame to me.
I'd like to buy each one
of them a blowjob shot.
- Are you serious?
- I am, yes.
Do you wanna buy
anything for their fellas?
Do I look like I'd like to buy
something for their fellas?
Might be the polite thing to do.
Sure, okay, fine.
I'm gonna get each one of
those guys a cosmopolitan.
Mister, I don't know
what you're going for,
but, I was thinking a beer.
No. Blowjob shots for the ladies,
and a cosmopolitan for each of the guys.
You keep the change on that.
You got it.
Are you, like, rich?
Cash is easy to get.
He doesn't need to be in costume
to make an ass out of himself.
Here's your Coke, here's your fireball.
Got their shots and
cosmos coming right up.
Thank you.
You want to try it?
Sure.
God!
It's like hot peppers.
You drink that?
Yep.
How do you do that?
You get used to it.
From that table over there.
That fucking guy?
They look annoyed.
Yep.
Thanks for the drink.
You're welcome.
I don't want it, though.
You can have it.
Well, maybe you prefer this.
My eyes!
Hey, you...
Hey, Luke.
Luke.
Cool.
You guys should get out of here.
Call the police and tell them the truth.
A gang of high school kids came in here
and demanded you serve them drinks.
Well, you tried to ID them, but,
they threatened to cause trouble.
There was a fight.
You didn't really get a good
look at the other guys.
Otherwise, I imagine you and this place
could get into trouble
for serving minors.
I mean, this is what happens.
Here.
For the damages.
Luke! What happened?
I got into a fight with
some guys at school.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Some seniors were picking on me.
It's no big deal.
Why were they picking on you?
I don't know, okay. I'm just going
to go to my room, all right.
Is he all right?
Yes, ma'am, he's fine.
Did he get in trouble at the school?
No, no one saw. It's just the
usual high school stuff, you know.
I told him I'd teach him some
self-defense when he's feeling up to it.
I'm sure that's exactly what he needs.
Well, I am very relieved
that you were there.
I'm going to get ready for Kristen's.
Anna, can we talk in the kitchen?
Sure.
Excuse us.
What?
Invite him to the party.
- Why?
- 'Cause he's lonely, sweetie.
Caleb would really love that.
Really? You're going to pull that card?
Yes.
David, would you like to come
to the party with me tonight?
Sure, that sounds nice.
Great. I'm going to leave around 7:00.
All right.
Luke, I need to take a shower.
Luke!
Luke, come on, I need to...
I'm sorry...
No, I'm sorry,
I thought Luke was in there.
Oh, I guess I better go get dressed.
Yeah, yeah.
You should, probably do that.
So, this isn't a big deal or anything,
but this isn't just Kristen's place.
My boyfriend, Zeke, lives here, too.
I didn't know you had a boyfriend.
Yeah, well, neither do my parents.
And I wouldn't mind keeping it
that way, if that's cool with you.
I won't say anything.
It's none of my business.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Hey, who's this?
This is David, he was
friends with my brother Caleb.
- I told you about him.
- How do you do?
Fine, thank you.
Zeke's inside smoking. He was
waiting for help to carry the kegs.
I'll bring them in.
Where are they?
They're in Zeke's van.
It should be unlocked.
Anna?
No. I can't tonight. I wish.
What? Really?
What? Your houseguest?
Yeah, he's...
Where do you want these?
Well, you can set them right here.
My man, welcome to the party.
Craig, no.
It's fine. He's a big boy.
Sure.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
You all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
You wanna...
Yeah, let's go.
God damn it.
Who are they?
No. That's my ex. The one I
was just telling you about.
Hey, I need to talk to you.
I'm busy right now, Drew.
I've been calling you all week,
and then I hear you're
having a party tonight?
What the fuck?
I'm talking to my friend.
You're being rude.
All right, listen, just...
Come here...
Motherfucker!
Get him out of here.
Sorry about your picture.
No, don't worry about it.
Did you...
Did you want to see
the rest of the house?
Are you okay?
Yeah. Why?
Seems like you're not really into this.
Oh, I am.
You are.
Hey, there they are.
Who have you got?
I got a queen. He's got a king.
Sit down.
Thought you guys left your own party,
found something better.
- Want some?
- No, I'm good.
I just...
I wanted to say we support you guys.
If you need anything,
you just let me know.
Support us how?
I mean, you know, we support you,
like, "Go America!" right?
But you wouldn't support
us by, like, enlisting?
Shit, man, they don't want me in there.
No, I can't, you know.
I've got bad asthma.
It'd make it real hard to...
Hard to what?
Hey, man, I mean, I just...
What?
I'm just fucking with you, man.
Fuck, man.
Oh, you think that's funny, Kristen?
I'll be right back.
Nice piece of ass there?
Could you get me a gun?
A gun?
Yeah, I can get you a gun.
What do you need a gun for?
I'm a soldier, man. I like guns.
Yeah. I know a guy.
You got cash?
I do.
Fuck it. Give me your number.
I'm using a burner right now.
Number's on the back.
Soldiers like guns.
Landing a gig is huge for me.
What's the big deal if I go on tour?
It's, like, three weeks, max.
Why don't you trust me for,
like, five seconds?
I don't know. Maybe...
- I've given you no reason not to trust me.
- I'm done with this.
Come on.
- You ready to go?
- Sure.
- I'll drive.
- No, I'm fine.
I'll drive.
You're stoned.
And how are you more sober than me?
I'm bigger than you.
Please, put on your seat belt.
- Do you want to talk about it?
- No.
It's just...
It's nothing. I mean,
we got into an argument.
It's old stuff.
You know, I used to love
that he was in a band.
But now I'm saving money for college,
and he just isn't moving on.
I mean, he doesn't even have a job.
Well, he's a drug dealer.
Okay. He's not a drug dealer.
Yeah. He sells drugs sometimes to,
like, friends for extra cash.
Well, if he's messing things
up with you, then he's a fool,
and you don't need to worry about it.
No. I'm serious.
I mean, hell, if I'd had a
girl like you back home,
I wouldn't have gone over to
the Middle East to get shot at.
Thank you.
I like this music.
You do?
It's, just a mix that I made.
I can make you one if you wanted.
Yeah? Can you put this song on it?
Yeah, I can do that.
So, good night.
Good night.
Thanks for inviting me out.
Yeah, no problem.
Good night.
No. I want to proceed as we discussed.
No one will be able to recognize me.
That's important.
What do you mean, "Dental records"?
An orthodontist? No, I don't need that.
Fingers, yes.
As soon as possible.
I'm off the grid for now.
But there are people
trying to look for me.
I understand it'll take some time,
but this is urgent.
I just need a new face.
I'll keep this phone in case anything
comes up and you need to reach me.
All right. Copy that.
Yeah, his name is David
Andersen Collins.
I can tell you the unit that
he served in if that helps.
No, nothing's wrong.
He was friends with my brother
and we heard that he was back,
so, any contact
information would be great.
Okay, ma'am. I'll call you
when we have any details.
Goodbye.
Tell Fort Kennilworth that
David Collins is dead.
Just give them the official version.
We'll take it from here.
Next week I'm meeting
with the rest of the board
to discuss the future of our
work with the military,
in light of Project
Aegolius' dissolution.
Richard has more information
on that subject. Richard?
I can't get into too many details,
nor would you want me to.
However, I can say that...
Sorry to interrupt. Something's come up.
My apologies, but you'll
have to excuse me.
When did Fort Kennilworth
receive this call?
About an hour ago, sir.
Have you ID'd the caller?
Not confirmed, but she gave
her name as Anna Peterson.
Peterson.
As in Caleb Peterson?
His sister.
Home address is in there.
Book me on the next flight.
If we need to charter something, do it.
And I'm gonna need some shooters.
If anyone asks what's happening,
what do I tell them?
Make something up.
No one outside this circle can know
that any of our subjects are still active.
If KPG gets any blowback on this,
you and I will both be hung out to dry.
You got that?
Call me when you got the plane booked.
I'm not late, am I?
No, no. You're just on time.
Good.
Look, before we get started,
I just want to make sure that
you've got some cash on you.
No offense.
That should be good?
It'll do.
Let's get started.
Let's start with this.
I mean, it's a standard Beretta.
I'm sure you're familiar with it.
In my opinion, if you've seen one
of these, you've seen them all.
But this baby, this here is
a 9-millimeter Witness Elite.
It's a very similar weapon to
the Beretta, but I prefer the recoil.
I mean, it's got
absolutely no kick at all.
You army?
Yes, sir.
I'm navy, myself.
Yeah, that's fine.
You want the Elite?
Oh, I'll take 'em all.
All the handguns?
No. Everything. All your guns.
Shit.
That's what I was thinking.
Look, man, if you've brought
money for all of them,
I'll cut you a deal.
You can take 'em all off my hands.
No, I'm going to kill you.
Hey, what the fuck, David?
Now, you listen to me
one fucking second...
Wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no, no.
Hello?
Yeah, thanks for calling me back.
What?
Hey, Mom, can I talk
to you for a second?
Sure, sweetie, what's going on?
I called the army base
that David said that he
was just discharged from,
I wanted to ask about him.
What? Why would you do that?
Spencer?
I need a drink.
- Why? What happened?
- I'm getting a drink, honey.
They found Allan,
you know my boss, Allan?
He'd been missing from
work for a couple of days,
everybody got very worried,
so one of his friends went
over and broke into his house.
And they found him
and his girlfriend dead.
They'd both taken a bunch
of prescription pills,
it was like they committed
suicide together or something.
Oh, my God!
But that doesn't make any sense.
He was...
No. The guy was totally normal.
But the police are investigating.
You know, it's...
Doesn't look like it was a break-in.
There was no forced entries.
She... The girl... She had...
She had bruises on her body.
I don't know what that means.
Anyway, we will leave it for the police
to tell us exactly what happened.
I don't know.
Damn thing is this makes
me regional manager.
Yeah. As soon as Corporate
found out, they called me.
Right away they want
me to start tomorrow.
And they're offering me Allan's salary.
So...
Well, that's...
Yeah.
Careful what you wish for.
David.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
No. Don't be silly. It's fine.
I'm having a drink.
Would you join me?
Oh, sure.
I'll be right back.
- Hello?
- Hey, Anna?
It's Craig, babe.
They just found him out at the quarry.
He's dead. Someone shot him.
What?
Do they know who did it?
I don't really have all the details yet.
Can you meet up later?
Yeah, of course.
There's something else I
need to talk to you about.
What is it?
Oh, shit. Fuck.
Babe, I got to go, all right.
I'll call you back.
Hello?
I just heard from Zeke.
How are you doing?
I just don't get it.
Who'd want to hurt Craig?
Yeah, I know. Can you
sit down for a second?
Yeah.
So, how does this work again?
First you make a hole at the top,
so you can reach in and
scoop all the guts out.
Oh, man.
Your parents' knives suck.
Yeah.
That's better.
Do you carry that with you,
like, all the time?
Oh, this thing? Sure.
Why?
I don't know.
Just in case.
I called the army base that
David said that he was from.
They told me that David
Collins died a week ago.
He was in some military
hospital in Arizona.
There was a fire from oxygen tanks.
About 20 people died,
David Collins was one of them.
Does David have any ID? Credit cards?
I've never seen him use a wallet.
What about his phone?
He has a burner, right?
Why don't you check some
of the numbers he's called?
Your brother knows computers.
Have him look some of them up.
Yeah. That's a good idea.
Hey, Kristen. I think that
couple's been done for a bit.
I've got it. Thanks.
Call me after work, okay?
- Take care of yourself.
- You, too.
Do you want some advice, Luke?
Sure.
Never let anyone pick on you.
Otherwise, you'll carry it with
you the rest of your life.
Those kids at school,
they're bigger than you?
Yeah.
Then bring a knife to school.
If they take it off of
you and beat you up,
you go around their houses at night
and burn them down with
their families inside.
What's the worst they can do?
Yeah. Okay.
Here. You keep it.
You're giving this to me?
Yeah, man, it's yours. I've got others.
Thanks.
Hey.
Mom and Dad around?
No. They went to the store.
Your mom's making pumpkin pie.
That's cool.
Shit.
Fuck!
Fuck.
Oh, my God!
Hello.
Hey, it's, me.
Hey.
What?
They found the gun that
killed Craig in your van?
Yeah, it was wiped clean.
I guess they just got an
anonymous tip or something.
But you're innocent!
Anna, I know, but,
then they searched my room,
and they found some
other stuff. You know.
So, it looks like I'm actually
gonna be here for a little while.
I love you, all right?
Yeah, I know. I gotta go.
Okay.
Love you, bye.
Honey, you okay?
I...
My friend Craig was killed today.
Oh, my God. I'm so sorry.
How? What happened?
He was shot. I don't know.
And they arrested Zeke for it.
- Zeke?
- I'm sorry, honey.
But if they arrested your ex-boyfriend,
it was probably for a very good reason.
We all know Zeke was never
exactly a pillar of this community.
He's not my ex-boyfriend,
Dad, he's my boyfriend.
I never stopped seeing him.
I'm 20 years old, I can date who I want.
As long as you live in
this house, you cannot.
Oh, you know nothing about him! Nothing!
- I know he's a drugged-out punk junkie...
- Really, Dad!
...who started dating my daughter
when she was 17 years old,
is what I know.
Right.
What about him?
Everybody's best friend.
I called the military base
that he said he was from
and they told me he was dead.
That's military intelligence for you.
Right. Ask to see his ID.
He's not David Collins, okay.
We don't know who he is.
I was part of a special forces
unit when I was injured,
so they should be
providing a cover story
if any civilians ask about me.
That's a good thing.
But I did get my dog tags back.
They're right here.
I don't like to wear them because...
Well, I don't know, but...
I like having them with me,
though, you know.
As for ID, I don't have
a current license,
but, I've got my documents
in my bag. Should I go...
No, no, no. That won't be necessary.
Anna Peterson,
you owe him an apology right now.
- No fucking way.
- You watch your mouth, young lady.
I am very sorry about your friend Craig.
That's a terrible thing that happened.
As far as it goes with Zeke
Hastings and his crew,
I have it on very good authority they're
nothing but a bunch of pot dealers.
You wanna know why Zeke
was arrested for murder?
Because he probably did it, that's why.
- Fuck you!
- SPENCER:
Hey, now, Anna.
I'm sorry, honey.
David, I'm terribly sorry.
No, that's okay.
She's... She's upset.
I probably should have explained
the, special forces thing earlier,
it's just, we're not really
supposed to talk about it.
No. I understand.
I could use a drink.
How about you, David?
Yes, please.
What?
Hey.
I just wanted to say...
I just wanted to say how
sorry I am about Craig.
He seemed like a really cool guy.
And Zeke getting arrested...
Again, I'm very sorry.
I know you don't need me
here at this stressful time.
I'm not helping, which is a shame,
because I promised Caleb I would do
anything I could to help your family.
But just so you know, I'll be
moving on in a couple of days.
So, you don't need to put up
with me much longer, okay?
Okay.
Good.
What is this?
Is this the CD you made me?
Yeah.
Is it done?
Well, thank you.
I can't wait to listen to it.
I want every contractor
within a 100-mile radius.
And I don't care where they come from.
KPG, ex-military, whatever.
I'll need a team mobilized
by the time I land.
I'll give them the necessary
mission specs in person.
We can't risk a leak on this.
Good luck.
You took a picture of David's phone?
Yeah. I paid for a
reverse directory thing
to look the number up online.
It said it was this unlisted
landline of a doctor in Miami.
His name's Peter Boddington.
Except he's not a doctor anymore.
He lost his license two years ago
after performing a face lift on
a woman while he was drunk.
So, David knows the guy? I mean,
maybe it's his uncle or something.
That's what I'm trying to figure out.
I need to talk to the police.
The cops found those
drugs in Zeke's room,
so they think they've got their guy.
So, what do you need me to do?
Get any information you can on this guy.
Do you really think David
killed Craig and that other guy?
Yeah. I do.
Okay. I'll see if I can find anything.
Thank you, Luke.
I'm sorry. I'll show you some
magic tricks later. Just...
- Hey, faggot.
- Oh. Whoa.
Hey, what's that you're looking at?
Are you looking for someone to
do your sex change operation?
You little fucking bitch...
That's right, bitches.
God damn it.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
- Mrs. Peterson?
- Yes, that's right.
Mr. Alston will see you now.
Please, step inside.
- Okay.
- Just a second.
What happened?
This kid called me a faggot,
so I,
broke a yardstick on his face.
Okay.
Awesome.
I'll go in with you.
Okay.
- Is it this way?
- Yes.
Due to our school's zero
tolerance policy on violence,
I'm afraid we have no choice
but to expel your son.
That's pending the
decision of the board,
but I'm afraid it's fairly certain.
- But...
- I'm sorry.
What did the kid call him?
What?
You know, the kid,
the one Luke hit in the face.
What did he call Luke?
I don't think that's relevant
to this conversation.
Did he call him a faggot?
I believe that's the word that
was used, yes. But that's no excuse...
So, that makes it a hate crime.
- What?
- A hate crime.
And I'd like to know how many others
have been perpetrated against
her son under your watch.
A gay student targeted with physical
violence finally defends himself,
and you're... What?
Suspending him?
We could consider suspension.
No. You couldn't.
I'll be interested to see
what the board makes of you
when this is in front of the entire country,
not to mention our lawyers.
Do you want to sue them?
I... I don't...
We're suing you and the school board.
I didn't even know he was gay.
What about after-school detention?
For how long?
A month.
That seems fair.
After-school detention.
We'll put him to work
helping the prom committee
set up for the Halloween dance.
We'll agree to that.
But I do not want to
hear anything further
about this young man being harassed.
We understand each other?
I believe we do, Mr...
Who are you?
I'm a friend of the family.
After-school detention for a month.
- That's it?
- Yeah.
- See you later.
- Oh, David?
Can I talk to you for a second?
I'm going to step out into the hall
with Luke for a moment, if that's okay.
Oh, certainly.
So, she thinks you killed Craig.
And she's trying to make a case to the
police so they'll let her boyfriend go.
- Anna told you all this?
- Yeah.
Do you think I killed Craig?
I don't care.
But that's why
she wanted me to check out
that plastic surgeon in Florida.
She wanted to know what
the connection was there.
Yeah, I mean, why would I
need a plastic surgeon, right?
To change your appearance.
Like, the bones in your face.
And maybe scar up your fingers
so you don't have prints.
I mean, at least that's what I figured.
I know you're not really David Collins,
I looked him up right
after Anna said that.
So, maybe you don't want
people to know who you are.
A doctor who would do that sort
of thing is probably pretty rare.
I mean, there's probably
rules against it.
But that doctor, well,
I guess he needs the money,
so he'd do that kind of work.
That's an interesting theory.
I'm not going to tell anyone about it.
And nobody will believe Anna.
She doesn't have anything against you.
You killed Dad's boss, too, right?
I don't care. I'm not
going say anything.
Why not?
Because we're friends.
Right?
Yeah. Of course we are.
Okay.
I just wanted you to know.
Did Anna tell anyone else about this?
I don't know.
Her friend, Kristen, maybe?
Okay.
Thank you.
You know, David, I really...
I wanna thank you.
I don't know what I would have
done if you hadn't been here.
And I don't... I don't
mean just for today,
I mean everything.
I am... I'm really grateful.
Really, Mrs. Peterson. It's no problem.
I'll go get the rest.
Thank you, David.
Excuse me, ma'am. Are you Anna Peterson?
No. No, she's working at the diner.
I'm her mother.
What's she... Did she do something?
No, it's fine, ma'am.
But your daughter,
she put in a call to Fort Kennilworth
a couple of days ago asking
about a man named David Collins.
Yes. Oh, that's right, she did.
You wouldn't happen to have seen
anyone resembling this man, would you?
This is... David.
Ma'am, when was the
last time you saw him.
Well, he just went inside.
No!
Stop the girl! Get back here.
Get him!
Oh, shit!
- No, no, no, no.
- David, what...
What is happening, David?
Who are those men?
I really am sorry about this,
Mrs. Peterson.
I'm afraid I haven't been
fully honest with you.
What do you mean?
It would take too long to explain.
I wanted to help.
I considered it my mission to
assist you all while I was here.
There were just too many complications.
What are you talking about?
David, why are those men
trying to kill you?
It doesn't matter.
Did you...
Did you even know my son?
I did.
Yes.
We were in the same program.
And he would understand
what I have to do here.
He's here in the...
I'm sorry.
I'm going in.
Give me 15 seconds of cover, then hold.
Fuck!
Fuck.
What the...
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
David.
I'm really sorry about this, sir.
I think he's dead.
Military police.
I'm gonna need your vehicle.
What?
- Are the keys in it?
- Yes, but...
Excuse me, are you Anna Peterson?
Yes.
My name is Major Carver.
Military police. I need you
to come with me, please.
Okay. What's going on?
It's about David, Miss Peterson.
He is not who you think he is.
And we need to go now.
Okay.
Is everything all right?
I think so. I'll call you later, okay?
Miss Peterson.
- Hey.
Is Anna working?
She just left.
Oh, yeah?
Where was she going?
I'm not sure exactly.
To pick up Luke?
I think that she's going...
Never mind.
What?
Okay. Copy. We're on our way.
We're going to the rec
center to get your brother.
The police couldn't send a car there.
They've got their hands full.
Okay. You need to tell
me what's going on.
Who are you?
What? You came here for David?
Yes.
The soldier you know as David
was one of the subjects
of a medical experiment.
While we had him under study,
he killed several people and escaped.
Then he burned their
bodies to confuse us.
We thought he'd died
in the fire initially.
By the time we figured out what
he'd done, the trail was cold.
Maybe you shouldn't have tested
your procedures on a psychopath.
By all accounts,
he was an ideal soldier.
I don't know.
I need to call my brother.
Mr. Peterson, is that a cell phone?
Didn't I say, "Phones off"?
Hand it over.
You can have it back after detention.
Luke, I need you to call
me when you get this.
Okay? It's important.
Where are those cop cars going?
Somebody attacked your
diner right after we left it.
It was called in as an explosion.
Is anyone alive?
I don't know.
It's possible that he'd leave
some wounded to keep them busy.
Wait. Where are my parents?
You haven't said anything
about my parents.
They're both dead.
He killed them before we could stop him.
I'm sorry.
No.
David has neurological conditioning,
Miss Peterson,
designed to protect both
him and the experiment.
If he feels like his
identity may be compromised,
he's programmed to
clean up all loose ends.
I doubt he could stop himself
now even if he wanted to.
It's why we need to get you and
your brother somewhere safe.
Miss Peterson, we need to go.
Miss Peterson?
Yeah, let's go get my brother.
What the hell is this?
For the fall dance, they do
this Halloween maze thing.
Stay close to me.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
God damn it! What in the hell?
Who's in here?
Military police!
I'm here for Luke Peterson.
How do I get through this maze?
Left, right, right, left, left,
right, left, then straight.
Got it?
Yeah.
- Luke!
- Excuse me.
But you're interrupting
detention right now.
Who are you exactly?
What's going on?
We need to go. Your sister...
Oh, shit.
Who else is in here?
No one. It's just us two.
Where are the lights controlled from?
There's a DJ booth in the back.
We need to get out of here.
Now. Where's the back exit?
It's this way. Follow me.
Come on.
Just this way.
Slow down.
Run! Go out the other way! Go!
Hello, sir.
You shouldn't have followed me.
I don't know what you expected.
Shit.
Anna, I don't know what's going on,
but David wouldn't hurt us.
Luke, I need you to trust me.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Just come on.
- What?
Shit.
Come on.
I need you to hide in here. Okay?
What? No way.
Anna, look, David was probably
just after that army guy.
Let's just...
Let's go talk to him.
Luke.
He killed Mom and Dad.
No, he didn't. You're just saying that.
What?
Mom and Dad are...
Please, Luke.
Okay, you need to hide in there.
I'm going to lead him away.
You can't come out unless
you hear me or the police.
I'm going to come back for you.
I'm really sorry about this, guys.
I tried to think of
another way to do it.
Any other solution.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Luke!
Come on out, buddy.
I'm not going to hurt you.
You killed my parents.
I did.
Yes.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Stop it. It'll be over in a second.
Hey, Luke.
You did the right thing.
I don't blame you.
Don't feel bad.
Thank you.
You okay?
Yeah. Are you?
Yeah.
Follow the light.
You both feeling okay?
We're fine.
Great. I'll be right back.
Copy that.
What's the deal?
Guess there's two bodies inside,
both of them pretty badly burned.
One of the guys said
their teeth are missing,
got knocked out, so I don't
know what the deal is.
As soon as we get the
all clear, you can go in.
Okay.
What the fuck!