Oh, my God.
Enough, camera addict.
Man: Okay, okay.
Just a second, though.
Before I turn it off, what is
your New Year's resolution?
Ha! Really?
Yeah, I want to get it on tape
so that I can hold you to it.
Please, you don't keep those.
That is a fantastic attitude
you have right there.
We're going to this time.
Yeah? All right, fine.
( clears throat )
I solemnly swear
on this New Year's resolution
to go to the gym
and get in shape.
Oh, hell, yeah.
How about you, ladybug?
What's your New Year's resolution?
What's that?
It's like a vow or a promise that
you make to be a better person.
Yeah, or always eat
your spinach.
- Yuck.
- Okay, I got one for you.
How about you tell your mommy
that you love her at least once a day?
- Okay.
- You can start right now.
- I love you, Mom.
- How about you, Fishbone?
What's your resolution?
- Your turn.
- My resolution.
To make a documentary
about this family
so that I can show
the whole world
what a lucky guy I am.
- Woman: You are a lucky guy.
- That's right.
And I thank God every day.
If only you believed in God.
Yeah, that'd probably help
a little bit.
Oh, crap.
You know what?
I didn't put change in that meter.
We're gonna get a ticket.
- Dad, can you help me?
- What's up?
- Here, I got it.
- You sure?
- Yup.
- Thanks, babe.
So, Beverly,
your psychic powers,
when did you first
discover them?
Well, everyone's born
with them, you know.
But most folks don't know
how to develop them.
Man:
And your predictions,
how many of them you think
have come true?
Well, all of them.
( laughs )
Man: Have you ever felt like
you were preying
on someone's superstitions?
Or their emotions?
You know, for example,
like telling a mother
that her missing son
would return alive
or breaking up a family
by advising for divorce.
You know what I mean?
Have you ever felt like
you led somebody down
the wrong path?
No, I don't think so.
You know, it's interesting,
my wife, she's always
wanted to go to Europe.
I finally put
this big trip together,
then at the last second,
she cancels.
She says that she needed
to be here
for this big break
in her acting career.
A break that you told her
was coming.
I did.
And I'm guessing it hasn't, huh?
No.
It will.
Yeah, I don't think so.
And why is that?
She's dead.
Her name was Samantha.
Samantha King.
Yeah. She'd been coming
to you for years.
Oh, Sa...
Oh, Samantha.
Oh, gosh.
Fluke accident.
Wrong place, wrong time.
But, you know,
the funny thing is
is that if we'd been
on that trip,
if she hadn't listened to you
and we'd gone to Europe,
she'd still be alive.
Oh, God.
Oh, you can't think that I had...
You were giving her
spiritual guidance.
Guidance based on visions
you were receiving
from beyond the veil,
from higher powers, right?
And these visions,
they interfered
with her life, Beverly.
And she is dead
as a direct result.
I am deeply sorry for your loss.
Okay, then admit it.
Admit it.
Admit that all this,
this is just a scam.
That what you claim to do,
your psychic routine...
this is just a show, right?
This is a performance here.
Come on, Beverly.
Come on.
I'm afraid that I'm gonna have
to ask you to leave.
Please?
Man:
What happens when you die?
I mean, everybody
has a theory, a guess,
a story that they'd like
to believe.
But at the end of the day,
we don't know.
Our ancestors worshiped fire
and sacrificed children
to vengeful gods.
We didn't know any better
back then.
What's our excuse now?
It's the 21st century,
yet we're still arguing evolution
versus creationism.
And Why?
Because the truth scares people.
Nobody wants to die.
Nobody wants to cease to exist.
We want to believe
that if we follow a set of rules,
rules that were laid out
by some ancient, made-up god,
we're gonna continue on
in heaven as a spirit.
We're gonna be reincarnated.
While all that sounds great,
is any of it authentic?
I mean, what's the truth?
See, the truth is
that religion and spiritualism
are the most profitable
businesses in the world.
That throughout history,
there's never been
a single shred of evidence
that any of it is real.
Well, I've decided to prove it.
I want to test
the most authentic spells,
rituals, and summonings
that I can find.
I'm only going after the blackest
of the black magic.
The stuff that people
are scared of.
So that when they don't work,
people will pay attention.
And maybe, just maybe,
the world can take a step forward
collectively into reality.
The cameras will be rolling
on me 24/7
in the hopes that
if I uncover anything,
anything at all,
I'll have found the first ever
documented proof.
I'm the testing ground.
Me, Michael King.
So, God or the devil,
if you're out there,
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
prove it.
Come and get me.
Ladybug, what are you doing?
Why are you up?
I had a scary dream.
Uh-oh. Come here.
What was it about?
A monster.
A monster? Okay.
Well, I wouldn't be surprised
if this particular monster
is a tickle monster.
- (growls )
- ( laughing )
Come on.
Come here, come here.
Oh, no. Oh, no.
Oh, no.
See, Fishbone's right.
Old Crowley here...
old Crowley here is the best defense
against tickle monsters.
- Get away! Get away!
- What are you doing?
- Hey, sis.
- What's going on?
Oh, we are...
she had a nightmare.
Yeah, take Crowley with you.
Hey, listen.
Why don't I get in bed with you
and make sure that there are
no more monsters?
- Okay,
- Okay?
I think that's a great idea.
I'm really good
at fending off monsters.
Aunt Beth is the best.
Hey, young lady.
Where do you think you're going?
Are you okay?
All right, give me kisses.
- I love you.
- I love you, too, Dad.
Crowley's gonna
take care of you, okay?
- And Fishbone.
- Okay.
What is all this stuff, Michael?
I mean, you wonder why
she's getting all these nightmares?
Seriously?
It's my new project.
Oh, right.
What?
I thought that you would
be happy, of all people,
to see me, you know, getting back
to work and moving on.
This isn't really
moving on, Michael.
- Well, it is for me.
- Okay.
I'm gonna go put her to bed.
Okay, so last night
I posted an ad.
Documentary filmmaker seeks
proof of the supernatural.
There must be, I don't know,
over 300 hits on this thing already.
We've got Satanists,
voodoo, necromancy.
I even have a priest on here.
I guess that's Los Angeles
for you, right?
We're gonna have no shortage
of material, that's for sure.
Cameraman: What if one of these
fucking Satanists is a serial killer?
- What then?
- Are you serious?
Don't be such a pussy.
So, Father Gibbons,
the Church won't talk
about it publically,
but behind closed doors
you claim
they're performing exorcisms.
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
Okay. And these demons
that they're exercising,
is there any proof
that they're real?
A physical proof?
Like horns and brimstone?
Fire, that kind of thing?
Well, any kind of thing.
I just don't understand
why there's never been
any documented evidence.
What makes you think
there's not?
I haven't seen any.
Well, I mean, of course
you haven't.
You haven't been allowed to.
Okay, listen,
you stated in your e-mail
that you had a real experience,
real proof,
but you don't, do you?
Okay '
When I was 10,
my father...
he started
to take advantage of me.
Every night he would
come into my room...
( bells tolling )
...close the door...
My mother, she must have known.
She prayed all the time.
That was her remedy.
God.
Well, I prayed to God,
but He never stopped
my father, not once.
So I gave up on God.
Started to pray to the devil.
( coughs )
Told him I would do anything
if he'd just make
my father stop.
Well, one night not long after,
in the middle of one
of his visits,
my father had a heart attack.
Died on the spot.
Wow.
That's awful.
I mean, what happened to you,
it's awful.
But come on.
I mean, how is that anything more
than just a strange coincidence?
Well, not long after, I...
began to hear him
calling out to me,
saying things.
I mean, awful, awful things.
The devil?
You hear him...
you don't answer.
Because if you do,
he will know you're listening
and he will never let you go.
Michael:
Hmm.
Right.
Thank you for your time.
Appreciate it.
I ordered a demon summoning kit
off the Internet.
I lit the traditionally
evil-looking black candles.
I even sprung
for the expensive incense
because their Internet site said
that the demons get insulted
by the cheap stuff.
Got one plastic ritual altar.
Nice. Very nice.
And one photocopied booklet.
A lot of money went
into that guy right there, huh?
I also used Ellie's coloring set
to draw my symbols.
Somehow crayons
seemed appropriate.
So basically
what you do is this.
You draw the symbol
for the demon
that you wish to summon.
All right?
You read the spell from this.
Then you light it,
put it in the altar.
Voila.
( French accent ) Instant demon.
Well, surprise, surprise,
the demons were a no-show.
Although...
( groans )
...something's happening.
( Growls )
Okay, there's no demon.
It was worth a shot.
So we got in touch
with a demonologist.
And after negotiating a small...
well, smallish... fee,
we've convinced him
to summon a demon for us.
- ( Knocks )
- Man: Just a sec.
Hi. Michael King.
This is Jordan.
So why do people
always summon demons,
never angels?
People summon angels
all the time.
They just don't want
to interfere.
Now, demons, on the other hand,
they're just dying to come here.
It's most tempting to do that
when we're kind of weak,
out of sorts.
Some people meditate for years
to achieve the proper mind set,
but we use tricks...
to get us there faster.
- Michael: Uh, grape juice?
- With LSD.
How much LSD?
If you're nervous
about this part,
we should stop right now.
There are two prevalent methods
for summoning demons.
The first is by offering
the demon something up front.
A human life,
continued servitude,
your own soul.
I don't recommend those paths
as once performed
they're very hard to undo.
The second method entails
creating the type
of frenetic atmosphere
demons are drawn to...
chaos, blood,
sex, violence.
I'll need some of your essence.
Uh, saliva?
Semen.
( Chuckles )
You're kidding, right?
And I have to get it
in this cup?
- Bathroom's right over there.
- Okay.
Ever hear of auto writing?
Scrying? Psychography?
It's how we're going
to pick your demon,
- the one we're going to summon.
- Okay.
Close your eyes.
Now, clear your mind.
Open yourself up to the beyond.
Allow their energy
to flow through you,
to use you.
Let their energy flow.
Breathe.
I'm sorry, I'm not very susceptible
to this kind of stuff.
- I'm sorry.
- You did just fine.
Just a minute here.
So what are we looking for here?
What's this?
To see if the image
that you drew
matches up
with one of the demons.
And you think that I drew this?
Look.
Daungore.
"Commander of 37 legions.
Seeker of the defenseless,
the weak-spirited,
the nonbeliever.
Known also as the Great Mocker,
Destroyer of Thought,
Breeder of Ants,
Stealer of Children.
He comes accompanied by
the sound of cacophonous music,
staying with the conjurer
until tormentum
in dum demens."
It's Latin for
"torture until madness."
I feel pretty weird, man.
( laughs )
Okay, look at this, man.
This look safe to you?
This is fucked up.
Look at all this plastic.
They're gonna kill me in here.
That's what they're gonna do.
Oh, my God.
I'm losing my mind.
This is a bad idea.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
This is bad.
Jordan, check this out.
Dude, maybe we should
get the fuck out of here.
Oh, my God, what the fuck
have we gotten ourselves into?
(speaking Latin )
Oh, shit.
These are real.
( Continues speaking Latin )
( laughs )
Satan. Lucifer.
( Continues speaking Latin,
snaps fingers )
Michael: Okay, so what
are you doing here?
Michael:
I'm freaking out a little bit.
( Both speaking Latin )
Michael:
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Jordan? Jordan, what the fuck
is going on, man?
Jordan: Something's
fucking up the camera.
- I can't see shit.
- ( groaning )
( continues speaking Latin )
Jordan:
Hey, hey, hey!
Michael, are you okay?
Are you all right?
Oh, shit.
( Continues speaking Latin )
Jordan:
She's got a knife.
Get that fucking knife
off of him!
- Get it off of him!
- ( shouting )
Jesus Christ!
( Grunting, screaming )
(sighs )
Well...
that was, like, some kind of
satanic porn shoot.
The smell in there, right?
And you paid him.
( laughs )
Come on, man, shh.
Seriously, turn that off.
So you want me
to order you some chili?
Runny eggs?
Or how about a cup
of bloody jizz?
Don't. Don't. Don't.
I'm never eating again.
At least enjoy the acid.
Ready?
You're running through a forest.
Don't, dude. Don't.
Seriously, come on.
I hate you.
Turn it off.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
( Screams )
So necromancy is considered
the blackest of the black arts.
Why is that?
Well...
I think it gets most of its bad rap
because of the method employed
in performing it.
You mean dealing with corpses,
graves, funeral rites.
Right, right.
That kind of creeps people out.
Sure.
But as a mortician,
it's all part of my day job.
And as far as the magic goes...
it's really no different
than what any of these
mediums are doing
except we just employ
a slightly different method
in raising the dead.
Teeth taken from
our little friend over there.
Mortician:
A freshly deceased body
works best because the soul
may still be lingering.
Then we can kind of confuse it.
You know, make it think
that it's still alive
and that all it needs to do is just
get back inside of its living body.
Okay.
This is a mild anesthetic
similar to Novocain.
- Okay. Doing all right?
- Yeah.
Okay, it'll start to numb
in just a couple minutes.
The more that we can
make you appear
like that body the soul
once inhabited,
the better our chances.
You feel that?
- No.
- Okay.
Mortician:
The astral corpse,
it wants to keep living.
Living is what it knows.
You know? And unless
it's already grown accustomed
to the afterlife,
it's what's normal.
And it's desperate
to cling on to that.
The Sonoran Desert toad
contains dimethyltryptamine,
or DMT,
the most powerful psychedelic
on the planet.
The human body produces DMT.
It's released when we die.
It helps us pass
to the other side.
But taking it
while we're still living
simulates a near-death
experience.
I'm going to need to let it dry.
Prepare it.
It's gonna take some time.
We need to wait
until it's dark anyhow.
This Novocain is wearing off
on my stomach,
so this is starting to hurt
like a bitch, man.
Oh, there he is.
Hey, sorry we're late.
I got all turned around in here.
Jesus Christ.
Did you kill these...
did you kill these things?
The toads, their pain,
agony, it creates
this sort of energy
that draws in the spirits.
Assume the position.
On your back.
Right.
The smell of burning DMT
can be intensely nauseating.
Like burning plastic.
Now, as it takes effect,
the world will shatter
and your body
will quickly follow.
You may feel like
you're starting to die,
like you don't know
how to breathe at all.
But it's okay.
You just need to let go
- and go with it.
- ( groaning )
To Almighty God
we commend
our brother Michael...
and commit his body
to the ground.
Ashes to ashes, dust to dust.
Roland Sykes.
Roland Sykes,
reclaim your physical body.
- Take this body. Shit!
- ( sirens wail )
- Cop: You, hey!
- Mortician: Get the fuck out of here.
- Cop: Get on your knees!
- Jordan: Michael.
- Where are you?
- Cop #2: They're running.
Oh, fuck me.
( Panting )
Cop: He's making
a break for it. Hey!
- There he goes!
- Jordan: Michael.
( Door squeaks )
Jordan:
Hey, you in here?
Michael, you in here?
Michael.
- Strange voice: Crawl.
- ( Jordan gasps )
- Crawl!
- ( door slams )
( Jordan grunting )
Fuck!
- Crawl.
- Jordan: What is that?
What the fuck is going on here?
Crawl.
Shit. Michael.
Michael.
Come on, get down, man.
Get down from there.
Let's get out of here.
Come on.
Are you okay?
Strange voice:
I don't want to be dead.
- ( Growls)
- Get off, Mike!
- ( Panting )
- Oh, Jesus.
Jordan? Jordan?
Jordan: You're tripping out, man.
It's just the drugs.
Dude, just chill.
Oh, no. No, no.
Fuck. She's gone.
Jordan:
Who's gone?
Sam.
I was with her, man.
I was with Sam.
But she's fucking gone.
Jordan: Come on, let's just get
the fuck out of here.
- Michael: Steal it!
- How did we get so lucky?
- Ellie: Come on!
- Michael: I know, she's amazing.
Fishbone, eh.
He doesn't come
when he's called so much.
- Michael: Yeah.
- Ew, this is gross now, too.
- Here you go. ( gasps )
- No, no, don't give it to me.
( Clears throat )
My wife Samantha was...
I mean, I fucking touched her.
You know, and I felt her with...
( clears throat )
And she was trying
to tell me something.
It was...
there was all this interference.
It was like static.
And I couldn't make out
what she was saying.
But she was...
Took a shower.
Got rid of these fucking teeth.
Look at this.
I feel like I'm still
coming down from the drugs
or something.
And that static sound,
it's, like, still there.
( Sniffles )
I've got to get some sleep.
I can't sleep.
( groans )
Man, it's like 4:30, 5:00.
Something like that.
Sun's gonna be coming up soon.
I'm just past the point.
And that noise, it's, like,
now that I've noticed it, I'm...
I'm fixated on it.
Hey there.
We're at this reading
by Erica Bell.
She's a relatively
well-known medium.
And then afterwards
we get to interview her.
So come on, let's check it out.
( Crowd gasps )
Okay, was there something
with her throat?
Her breathing?
She had esophageal cancer.
She wants you to know
she's okay.
- ( Applause )
- She's watching over you.
And you're...
no, hang on.
No, wait a minute.
Someone else is butting in here.
Lots of spirits
want to talk today.
This is good. Okay.
All right, somewhere over here.
Yes.
Yes, this is a very strong signal.
Female, I think.
She really,
really wants to talk.
Right, she passed recently.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Happened kind of quickly,
an accident maybe.
Okay, she has a message.
No, that can't be right.
She wants to...
Michael, listen to me.
You need to...
( screams )
- Whoa, whoa.
- ( gasping )
Easy, easy, easy.
Jesus Christ.
What happened?
We're not really sure.
Erica was about
to tell us something
and then she went into
that seizure.
I mean, was she actually
channeling Sam?
Or was that just all
part of her show?
And then the seizure
was just like a strange
coincidence or something.
I don't know.
Ellie: Dad, Fishy peed
on the floor again.
Michael:
Huh? Okay, baby.
Daddy will take care of it
after dinner, all right?
- Thanks. Oh, fuck!
- Jeez.
Why the fuck would you
hand me something like that?
It's scalding hot.
God damn it.
Michael, that's a salad.
Um, I'm sorry.
I'm just...
Daddy's a little tense.
I'm sorry about that.
You okay?
I scared you.
( Clears throat )
You Okay?
Yeah.
Have some salad, Ellie.
(sighs )
I thought if I went out today
that I could shake
this noise in my head,
that it would just go away.
( Groans )
( Cracks )
But now that I'm home
and it's quiet, it's like...
( Cracks )
I wish I could describe for you
what this is.
It's this constant barrage,
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
this cacophony of sound.
It's like...
it's like...
( roars )
( gasps )
Oh, fuck.
- ( Roaring )
' ( digital squealing )
Okay, so what's the deal again?
Like I said,
it came out of my mouth.
Uh-huh. Yeah, no.
Why not?
There's multiple layers
of overtone singing.
Overtone?
What does that mean?
It's when a singer
manipulates their voice
to have multiple pitches
at the same time.
Okay, good.
So then maybe I did it accidentally.
Well, even if I bought that,
which I don't, there's more.
Here. Let's see.
- This is a B2.
- ( note plays )
- Okay.
- And this is a C# 7.
( Note plays )
That's a Guinness Book
vocal range right there.
The tape you gave me...
( note playing )
...we're talking F #
all the way...
- E25.
- ( high-pitched note )
Some of it's not even audible.
Just barely registering
on my stuff.
Let me ask you this.
Is it possible
that my vocal cords
could have made this?
Not a chance.
If you're not fucking with me,
then there's something wrong
with the audio in your camera.
A defect or something.
It's not the camera.
Thanks.
( Loud static hissing )
Beth:
Michael.
- ( Turns off static )
- So fricking loud.
Michael?
Hello?
What are you doing?
Hey. Michael.
- ( Growls )
- ( gasps )
Oh, my God.
You scared me.
Let's go.
I've been calling you.
Dinner's ready.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
- ( Loud static hissing )
- ( high-frequency whining )
( growling )
( growling continues )
( Fishbone barking )
( Michael growling )
Chronic ringing of the ears.
It's a very common condition.
It's called tinnitus.
- You should see an internist.
- I did. I did.
He gave me
a clean bill of health.
Said that it must be
psychosomatic,
that I should see a psychiatrist,
which is why I'm here.
I understand, Michael,
that your wife died recently.
Six months ago, yeah.
Left you alone
with a little girl.
( Clears throat )
Ellie, uh-huh.
You might be going through
some extreme stress
trying to deal with thoughts,
feelings, emotions,
things that consciously you might
not think you can handle.
And so then they become
side effects.
All right, so you think you can,
I don't know,
help me come to grips with this
if that's what it is?
Doctor:
Breathe.
Good.
Let your thoughts,
your conscious,
drift away.
Nice and easy.
We're traveling deep
into your subconscious, Michael.
Deep down inside.
- ( Gasps )
- Michael?
Are you there?
Are you with me?
Michael: Yes.
Doctor:
How are you feeling?
- Michael: Fine.
- Doctor: Good.
That sound in your head,
is it still there?
Michael: Yes.
- Okay.
- But there's something else.
Doctor:
What?
Michael:
I know what the sound is.
Doctor:
What is it, Michael?
Michael:
Voices.
- Voices?
- Yes.
What are they saying?
So many things.
Doctor:
Anything in particular?
- Yes.
- What?
They're saying you will...
Doctor: What?
You will what, Michael?
( Strange voices whispering )
Michael:
You will...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Doctor:
Michael?
Strange voice:
Crawl.
Jordan:
Michael, are you okay?
Michael.
Hey!
What the fuck?
What the fuck is going on?
The camera jumped
out of my hands.
You made some weird voice.
( laughs ) Bullshit.
It's all on the camera.
And then you were talking about
all the sounds in your head,
they were voices.
Look, I know this is none
of my business, but...
you think Sam would want you
to be doing this?
So Jordan officially
left the project.
Is something really
happening to me?
I mean,
I'm physically exhausted.
I'm drained.
And I was hypnotized, you know?
Is it really that surprising
that I spoke in some weird voice?
I mean, I think that Jordan just got
startled and threw the camera.
That's what it looked like.
I don't know.
( Groans )
Okay, I'm back.
And this thing
going on in my head,
it's evolving.
It's like I can hear this...
mumbling now.
Like my subconscious
is trying to talk to me
or something.
And if I concentrate...
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
I can almost tell
what it's saying.
( Crashes )
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Must have flown into the window.
Doll:
Crowley loves you.
( Caws, cackles )
Hey, sweetie.
Did that noise wake you up?
That was just the window.
It broke.
It was just the window.
It's okay.
What is it?
You all right?
- The monster.
- Monster?
Oh, from your dream.
Okay. Okay.
Let's see.
I'll tell you what.
How about you go back to sleep,
and then maybe Daddy
will show up in your dream
and then he can chase
that monster away.
How's that?
You can't.
Really?
Why is that?
I saw the monster.
Well, that's good.
What did this monster look like?
It's you, Daddy.
It's me?
It's just a bad dream.
You know that, right?
And Daddy would never
hurt you, okay?
No matter what.
Why don't you go get Fishbone
and go get back in bed, okay?
I can't find her.
Michael:
Come on, girl.
(whistles )
What you doing, Fishy?
Let's see, that bird should be
right about here.
Huh. That's weird.
Fishbone.
Is that you, girl?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
(whistles )
Oh, where the fuck are you?
( Trash cans rattle )
( crunching )
What the fuck?
Whoa, Jesus Christ!
Fuck.
What the fuck is that?
Ellie! Beth!
Jesus. Michael.
What the hell?
What are you doing?
She's asleep.
Michael, what is wrong?
We'll find the dog, okay?
Just relax.
Look, will you please
stop acting like this?
I'm sorry.
I'm just...
You're just acting,
like, crazy, so...
- You all right?
- Are you all right?
- Yeah.
- You look like shit.
Have you slept lately?
( Sighs ) Oh, God.
I just can't seem to wind down.
Hold on.
Here.
Take two of these.
- Sleeping pills?
- Yup.
Then you will sleep, believe me.
Feel better in the morning.
Thank you.
Good night.
( Static hissing )
( floorboards creak )
( snarling )
( growling )
( rattles )
( Beth moans )
Michael: I thought if I got
a good night's sleep
that this would end.
But these voices,
they're not going away.
I need to confront this.
So...
are you real?
Or am I going insane?
Neither is an appealing
choice, but...
I suppose one of them
must be true.
I guess I'd rather...
you were real.
( Cracks )
Okay. Okay.
What if...
what if I said...
what if I said that you've proved
your existence?
That I believed in you?
I believe in you.
Would you just...
would you leave?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Strange voice:
No.
( Growling )
( laughs )
We're gonna fuck you up.
( Screeching )
( pounding )
- ( door opens )
- ( Pounds )
Hi.
Oh, is Father Gibbons here?
I'm sorry, no.
Strange voice:
Kill her.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Listen, it is urgent.
I need to speak
to Father Gibbons right now.
- And you are?
- Just get Father...
I'm Michael King.
I interviewed him
and I need to talk...
- I need to talk to him right...
- Priest: I'm sorry.
Father Gibbons passed
a few days ago.
He's... he's... okay.
Listen, I need an exorcism.
- An exorcism?
- Yeah.
- The Church doesn't do that.
- No, you do it.
I know you do.
Father Gibbons told me that you do.
I need an exorcism, please.
He was rather out of sorts
towards the end.
I'm sorry if he misled you.
He didn't mislead me.
I need help.
Excuse me.
There's nothing we can do for you.
- Sorry, we can't help you.
- Father, I need your help.
- I'm sorry.
- Oh.
Okay. Okay.
( Screams )
Excuse me a moment.
- You can't come here.
- How do I get rid of it?
- How do I make it go away?
- What are you talking about?
I mean this thing.
This thing in my fucking head.
I warned you something
like this might happen.
Now I need you
to get the fuck out.
- ( Pounding )
- ( dog barking )
Hey.
( grunts )
What the fuck
have you done to me?
- What is this thing?
- What? I don't understand.
Something's got a hold of me.
You did something.
- You summoned something.
- No, man, it's not for real.
- It's all for fun.
- Bullshit, you're lying.
( gun cocks )
Get up.
Easy. Please.
Please help me.
- Now get out of here.
- Please. I need your help.
I really need to talk to her.
I need to come in
and I need to see her.
But isn't that
what she's supposed to do
is help somebody that's in
a situation like what I'm in?
I'm hearing shit
and I'm seeing shit now.
Listen, I'm losing
my fucking mind.
Would you please just tell Dr. Cox
that I need to talk to her?
Can you do that for me?
Oh!
You don't know how
fucking desperate I am here, okay?
You're supposed to help people.
Well, I need your fucking help!
I don't know what to fucking do.
( Clicking )
Ellie: Dad.
Can I play my game?
Tell me...
do you miss your mommy?
Yeah.
You can be with her, you know.
Beth:
Hey, Ellie, come on.
Let's go get a bath.
So long.
Ladybug-
Come on, let's go.
Michael:
I don't feel like myself at all
anymore.
I'm starting to have
these crazy thoughts.
( laughs )
I feel compelled.
Like I have to.
Like I have to fucking do it.
( laughing )
( static hissing )
( growling )
Eyes are throbbing like mad.
Can you see this?
Aw, it hurts like hell.
I'm fucking slipping.
What?
Oh, my God.
No, God damn it, no!
What the fuck?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What the fuck is that?
Oh, my God.
( Beth screaming )
What happened?
Beth? Ellie?
Fuck!
( Sobbing )
( panting )
Ellie! Ellie!
- Doll: Crowley loves you.
- Ellie.
- ( Doll cackles )
Is that Fishy?
- No, baby.
- Are you okay?
- Ellie, sweetheart.
- No, no.
Beth, you don't think...
Beth, I didn't.
- Ellie: I don't want to leave Fishy!
- Ellie.
- Let me go!
Oh, God.
Oh.
( Sobbing ) What have I done?
Fish.
You...
you don't have power over me.
You don't.
You think you do, but you don't.
This isn't what I wanted.
This isn't what I wanted at all.
I'm sorry, Sam.
You can't make me do anything.
Shh.
Couldn't make me lower.
You are just in my fucking head.
Get out of my head!
( Panting )
( screams )
I thought I almost killed Ellie.
Fishbone was Sam's dog.
- Fuck.
- ( strange voices whispering )
Beth and Ellie,
they're staying with one
of Beth's friends for a few days.
It's getting too hard
to fucking concentrate.
- ( Growling )
- ( strange voices whispering )
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Quiet!
Why are you doing this?
Stop saying that, God damn it!
Shit! Stop!
"I command you, unclean spirit.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
You shall not be emboldened
to harm this creature of God.
You shall not harm him
or those he touches.
I command you,
release this body.
Release this body..."
( screams )
"Turn back this evil
upon my soul.
I beseech you, Lord.
I beseech you."
Strange voice:
Burn! Burn!
- Burn!
- Fuck! God damn it!
You can't have this body.
No! No, God damn it!
(groaning )
Fuck! Fuck!
( Screams )
God, please!
- ( Screaming )
- ( voice gibbering )
- ( glass shatters )
- ( cacophony stops )
I've tried everything.
Protective spells, banishments,
charms,
every incantation I can find.
Nothing's worked.
The more I try and fight it,
the more it takes over.
Forcing me to do things.
Laughing at me.
It's fucking laughing at me.
You'd think
this really hurts, right?
Funny thing is
I can hardly feel it.
It's getting harder and harder
to feel anything.
It's like...
none of this is real anymore.
( laughs )
It's not real.
( laughing )
Nothing is real.
See this?
Look at that.
No matter
how many times I kill it...
ah, there.
Oh, yeah.
See this? See?
Another one. Okay.
I've been doing this
all day long.
Look at that bastard.
You son of a bitch.
Fuck. Another one.
God damn it.
If I let it crawl on my body,
there's only one.
The second I kill it,
another one shows up.
- ( Voice whispers ) The girl.
- ( winces )
I know, okay?
I know what you want!
(voice whispering )
We want the girl.
- You can't have her.
- We can make you do it.
- Someone else.
- Okay. Okay.
I'll do it. I'll do it.
But you can't have Ellie.
You hear me?
You can't have Ellie.
( Strange voices whispering )
( dog barking )
( strange voices whispering )
( knife scraping )
(voice whispering )
Kill her. Now. Kill her.
Kill her. Kill her.
- ( Groans )
- Kill her!
We want you to kill her.
( Growling )
Kill.
Kill him.
( Door closes )
(sighs )
Sorry, Ellie.
I just... I couldn't do it.
I just...
I have to fucking
get some sleep.
Goddamn rest.
You're not going anywhere!
Okay, we're not going anywhere.
We're fuckin' sleeping.
No, we're not going out.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
( Strange voices whispering )
- ( screams )
- Yes, you will!
( Screams )
(groaning )
( growls )
What the fuck?
Oh, no.
( Distant static hissing )
( static hissing )
Jordan:
Michael.
- Jordan, I'm in here.
- Michael?
- Michael.
- Yeah.
Jesus Christ, what the fuck
is going on in here?
Your place is a dis... Jesus.
Key is over there.
Do you mind getting it for me?
Oh, fuck.
We need to get you
some serious help, all right?
You gonna check into a facility?
I'm serious, man.
If I unlock you,
we are going there right now.
Answer the fucking...
what am I doing?
( Phone ringing )
Jordan?
( Phone continues ringing )
(stops ringing )
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh! Oh, fuck!
There was a being
inside a light and...
I don't know
if it was an angel or...
( chuckles ) God.
It asked me if I was
prepared to move on.
All I needed to do was let go.
And I wanted to.
But I held on because
I needed to come back
and tell you
that everything
was gonna be okay,
that I'm okay.
Because...
the next time that it happens,
I'm gonna let go.
Michael, I know you have
a hard time believing...
( sobbing )
...but it's real.
I know that now.
I love you, Michael.
I always will.
There's a few things
I need to say to Ellie.
Why the fuck
didn't I listen to you?
My little ladybug.
So sad I'm not gonna
see you grow up
- into the beautiful...
- Fuck!
...stunning little angel
you already are.
- Please just know that I'm with you.
- No! You can't.
- I'm always there.
- You can't have this body.
It'll be okay.
It's gonna be okay.
( Groans ) Kill me!
(groaning )
Fuck.
Here we go.
( Screaming )
(water running )
These cameras,
this film...
it's proof.
I hope someone finds it
and uses it to show others.
Tell my story, please.
Someone tell my story.
Tell my daughter...
tell my daughter
her daddy never meant
for any of this to happen.
Tell her that...
tell her that Daddy loves her.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
( Coughs )
Tell her... tell her
her daddy loves...
- ( groans )
- ( strange voices whispering )
Strange voice:
You ought to kill her.
- No. No.
- Do it.
No! Leave me alone.
Why?
We're having fun.
( Gags )
(voice laughing )
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
( water splashes )
- ( screams )
- ( electricity crackles )
I love you.
Okay, now go..
Michael: Fishy, what are you doing?
Get out of that.
- That's not yours.
- Oh, no, he ate all the popcorn.
- Baby. Come here.
- That dog is like a disposal.
Now puke. Puke.
Give it back.
Michael: Put your fingers
down his throat.
Mouth to mouth.
( Music box playing )
( raspy breathing )
Strange voice:
We're together now, Michael.
Isn't it wonderful?
I had it wrong, didn't I?
The interference,
the chattering,
the noise...
those weren't demons.
That wasn't you.
(voice laughing )
Those were angels.
Something.
Trying to...
trying to warn me.
(voice laughs )
Trying to keep me from hearing
the real voices...
the real singing.
Because once you hear it,
you can never stop listening.
(voice laughing )
( growling )
( static hissing )
Ellie: I'm gonna go
get Crowley.
Michael?
Oh, my God.
What the...?
- ( Door slams )
- ( gasps ) Michael.
- Michael, you're scaring me.
- ( growling )
Michael, it's me.
It's Beth. Please.
( Choking )
( choking )
( snaps )
( laughs )
Daddy?
Strange voice:
Let's play.
( Groans ) No.
Ellie, run.
Run from Daddy.
Go.
Strange voice:
Ellie, I'm coming to get you.
(groaning )
Strange voice:
We're gonna rip her head off.
No.
Run, Ellie. Go.
Strange voice:
We're gonna eat her, Michael.
( Bones cracking )
( groans )
( cracking )
(sniffing )
Strange voice:
Where are you hiding, ladybug?
( Growls )
Doll:
Crowley loves you.
( Caws )
No. No.
- Ellie.
- ( growling )
(sniffs )
Strange voice:
Yes.
Ladybug-
Where are you?
Daddy's coming to find you.
Doll:
Crowley loves you.
( Caws, cackles )
(whimpering )
- No. Daddy!
- ( coin rattles )
Sam. Is that you?
Samantha's voice:
Go quickly.
No, Daddy.
It's okay.
( Heart beating )
( screaming )
Samantha's voice:
It's gonna be okay.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Michael: Get her, Fishbone.
- Samantha: He's coming. Run.
Michael:
Get her. Oh, God.
( Samantha laughs )
Careful, baby.
Your turn.
What is your New Year's
resolution?
To make a documentary
about this family
so that I can show
the whole world
what a lucky guy I am.
- You are a lucky guy.
- That's right.
And I thank God every day.
If only you believed in God.
Yeah, that'd probably help
a little bit.
Oh, crap.
You know what?
I didn't put change in that meter.
We're gonna get a ticket.
- Dad, can you help me?
- What's up?
- Here, I got it.
- You sure?
- Yup.
- Thanks, babe.
Of course.
Come on, get it.
Come get it.
- ( Barking )
- Fetch! We're too good.
Atta boy.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- ( gasps)
- ( coin jingles )
- Michael: Sam!
- ( brakes squeal )
( Samantha screams )
- ( Samantha groaning )
- Michael: Help!
- Somebody help!
- Ellie: Mommy!
( Samantha groaning weakly )
( music playing )
I can taste the power
Now there's something real
Something real to feed me
Inside your naked world
Your body works forever
I'm electric with your tears
Your soul came into the darkness
Of everlasting fear
Why don't you
bow down now?
Make me feel
like I'm someone
Bow down now, roll over
Make me feel
like I'm someone
God made you to serve me
I know I've lost control
She's the liquid flesh you feel
Fills your empty soul
The master's love is torture
As your innocence
knows the game
So what you can't remember
Is working for your shame
Why don't you
bow down now?
Make me feel
like I'm someone
Bow down now, roll over
Make me feel
like I'm someone
Give me
What I need to
Give you
Give me
What I need to
Give you
Why don't you
bow down now?
Make me feel
like I'm someone
Bow down now, roll over
Make me feel
like I'm someone
Bow down now, roll over
Make me feel
like I'm someone
Bow down now, roll over
Make me feel
like I'm someone
Bow down now, bow down now
Bow down now
Bow down now.
( Instrumental music playing )