[Woman sings softly]
[Wind blowing]
- [Man] Hey.
- [Gasps]
Hey.
I wanna show you something.
What?
[Clears throat]
Have you ever seen
something so scary
that you had to show
to someone else?
Um...
I mean, like, you know,
a movie or something.
Well...
I've got the scariest
freakin' movie you'll ever see.
Now... A buddy of mine
actually turned me on to it.
And, uh, he made me a copy.
So... I did one for you.
You brought me here
to watch a video?
Well, two minutes. OK?
Two minutes and it'll all be over.
It's totally underground stuff.
- I thought we were gonna just...
- No, we will. We will.
You just gotta see this.
I'm telling you, it's...
- How about after we?
- No, you need to watch it now.
OK?
What's so scary about it?
You'll see.
[Breathing heavily]
Play it. Just play the thing.
Come on,
I got two minutes here, please.
[TV static]
[Panting nervously]
Emily, play the goddamn tape!
[Humming, hissing]
[Rumbling]
[Whining, gurgling]
[Sighs]
[Whining continues]
[Phone ringing]
[High-pitched electronic whine]
[Ringing continues]
- Hello?
- [Man] Hey, man, you made it.
I knew you'd come through.
You got somebody to watch it, huh?
[Sighing] Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, man.
Some stupid chick
from my school.
[Man] Good. I was afraid
you didn't believe me, man.
Now it's her problem. She doesn't
get someone else to watch it in a week,
I swear she's dead.
So, did you tell her what happens
or you just gonna let her
find out for herself?
[Water gurgling]
[Man]  Jake?
Come on, it's over, dude.
Jake. This isn't funny, man.
- Jake?
- [Hangs up phone]
Emily?
Emily!
- Emily, what the hell did you do?
- I played it, I just didn't look.
[TV static]
[Static stops]
[Rumbling, hissing]
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
[Breathing heavily]
[Distant shout]
[Screaming]
[Humming]
[TV static, hissing]
[Woman chuckling]
Come on, Aidan, let's go home.
It was the right choice.
No question.
Aidan, dinner's ready.
[Sighs] Damn.
Aidan!
OK, now, before you say anything,
I followed the recipe this time.
Just 'cause it doesn't look
like the one in the magazine,
doesn't mean to say
it won't taste good.
Those are great, honey.
Got a really good eye.
He'd be proud of you.
Thanks, Rachel.
You know, it wouldn't kill you
to call me "mom" now and again.
"Ma. " "Mommy. "
Something besides "Rachel".
Yeah, I like "Rachel".
Well, "mom" has its charms too,
you know.
But "Rachel"
is more your personality.
Really?
Well, Rachel declares dinnertime.
It's working out great,
don't you think?
All of this space and fresh air.
We have a yard.
It's really great.
Listen, honey...
...we didn't do anything wrong.
We did what anyone would do.
We started over.
- [Knocking]
- Yeah.
- Hey.
Uh, you know how they can tell
you used to work at a real newspaper?
You're the only one
who closes your door.
Habit.
Uh, I wanted to talk
to you about my editorial.
Those changes OK?
Well, I asked you to copy edit it
and you rewrote it.
Just the part
about the bond measure.
That was the whole thing.
The bridge would get
the money, not the riverfront.
Yeah. Uh...
Rachel. [clears throat]
You know,
a big news day in Astoria
is a school board meeting, a car wreck
and a cat in a tree. That's big news.
You sure this is the job
you're looking for?
Well, I'm around for my son more.
In Seattle, I wasn't.
Good a reason as any.
I'm glad to see you're
settling in. I like the...
Max, while you're here,
have you given any thought
to that piece for tomorrow?
You know what?
Don't worry about it.
[Door shuts]
[Man on radio]
It's 442 Ridgecrest.
[Woman on radio] Repeat that.
It's what?
[Man] Ridgecrest. Ridgecrest!
I've talked to the medical
examiner. They're on their way.
[Man #2] Squad 19 to respond.
[Woman] Can we keep
this channel clear?
- The police found a body.
- Possible homicide.
- Please, we should be so lucky.
- What are they saying?
"High school student, male, 17.
Address, 442 Ridgecrest.
Found the house flooded,
a girlfriend hiding in the basement. "
- Suspect or witness, they don't know.
- The guy was dead in front of the TV.
[Man] They keep on talking
about his face.
What about his face?
[Woman on radio] All emergency units,
area Astoria, switch to Tack Five.
[Indistinct radio chatter]
[Car approaching]
[Woman] Detective.
Detective, you have a minute?
Was it homicide or wasn't it?
You know how he died.
[Man] I just have
a few last questions.
If you could walk me
through it again.
[Woman] It's just horrible.
So young.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
[Gasping]
[Breathing nervously]
[Crying] No.
No, please, not here.
[Men chattering]
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
[Whimpering]
[Girl] I found you.
[Hissing]
[Grunting, panting]
We only made one copy.
Oh, God.
- Excuse me, sir.
- Hold on.
- Yeah?
- Hi.
- Rachel Keller from the Daily Astorian.
- We'll make a statement.
- I need to know about the girl.
She hasn't said a word, has she?
You're welcome to wait.
Excuse me.
[Man] Watch your step.
Have a seat here, OK?
Have a seat.
I just want you to relax for me.
[Man #2] You can't keep her.
- [Man #1] Focus on the walls.
- [Man #2] We wanna take her.
- [Woman] She'll talk to us.
- [Man #1] I understand.
I'm just gonna ask
a few questions. Please.
- Be right back, Emily.
- Thank you. Thank you.
All right. Give me his number.
Yeah. All right.
Emily.
Emily, listen to me.
I know what happened.
I know.
Now, you have to tell me.
The tape.
Did you watch it?
Do you know who else
has watched it?
Has anyone else watched it?
Then where is it?
Hey, you.
Get away from her. Ray.
Emily, talk to me.
[Man] I want her out of here.
Now.
You can tell me, Emily.
[Hissing]
[Whining]
No.
[Panting] Not here, Samara.
Not here.
[Whining, groaning]
[Hissing, rumbling]
[Water gurgling]
Rachel?
[Breathing heavily]
[Electronic whirring]
[Breathing nervously]
[Water gurgling]
Rachel!
[Straining]
[Muffled] Rachel! Rachel!
Rachel! Rachel!
Honey, what is it?
- What's wrong? Huh?
- [Panting]
Look at me. Shh.
- OK? What is it?
- I had a nightmare.
That's all right.
We all have them.
Oh, God, you're soaked.
And you're freezing.
Let's get you out of
these clothes. Come on.
Aidan?
What happened in your nightmare?
I woke up and you weren't here.
You weren't here.
I'm here now, honey.
I'm right here, OK?
Listen.
All you have to do is call my
name and I'll follow your voice.
OK?
Even if I have to come right down
into that nightmare with you.
So tell me what happened.
Hmm?
I don't remember.
You don't remember?
[Rumbling]
- [Rachel muffled] Aidan.
- [Kids laughing]
[Rachel] Aidan.
Aidan.
Honey. You heard me?
I've been calling your name.
I'm... sorry.
- You ready to go?
- Mm-hmm. Yeah.
OK.
[People chattering]
[Rachel] So we'll just swing by
and see what they have, OK?
And you can keep a watch on
the backyard stuff. How's that?
Look at all this stuff.
Who do you think buys this crap?
[Aidan] Rachel.
Sorry.
What's wrong, honey?
You all right? Huh?
Mm-hmm.
I'm just a little cold, Rachel.
- I'm gonna take a look around.
- All right.
Stay close.
[Chattering continues]
[Low rumble]
Would you like a marble, ma'am?
[Chattering fades out]
[Snorts]
[Squeaking]
[Rachel] Aidan?
[Kids yelling playfully]
Aidan?
Aidan.
[Faucet squeaking]
[Rumbling]
Aidan?
[Man] You gotta wait
for the whistle.
- [Boy] Here I go!
- [Kids laughing]
Aidan.
[Faucet squeaking]
[Low rumbling]
[Buzzing]
[Breathing heavily]
[Rumbling]
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
[Shutter clicking]
Aidan!
[Carnival music playing]
Are you in there?
Aidan?
Why didn't you answer me, honey?
What are you?
Jesus.
Jesus, you're freezing, honey.
What's going on? Are you sick?
Talk to me, honey.
Talk to me. What's going on?
- What is it?
- I'm cold.
It's OK. It's OK.
Honey, when did this start?
Was it last night,
or this morning?
I don't remember.
I know you don't like me prying,
but this is important.
Was it your nightmare?
I really don't remember, Rachel.
I need you to try.
You're sick, all right? And we
need to know what started it.
Aidan.
Was she in your nightmare?
Rachel!
[Screeching]
[Grunting]
[Gasps]
[Aidan panting] Don't stop.
Don't stop.
- Go! Drive! Drive!
- What's the matter, honey?
Just don't stop the car!
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
[Grunting, snorting]
[Rachel] Get down!
- [Engine revving]
- [Tires screeching]
- [Grunting]
- [Gasps]
[Shrieking]
[Both panting]
"Don't stop. "
You said, "Don't stop. "
[Deer grunting]
Don't stop.
[Beeping]
OK. Let's see.
That's impossible.
Rachel...
...what's happening?
[Rachel] Yeah, hi, um...
My son is very sick
and I'd like to
talk to someone who...
Well, it's his temperature.
It's... it's five degrees low.
Yeah. Well, then,
I'll hold for the on-call nurse.
[Clicks]
Hello?
[Wind howling]
Aidan?
Honey, the power just went out.
Are you OK up there?
Aidan?
Honey, this shouldn't be open.
God.
[Scratching]
Aidan, let's go. Get out of bed.
Aidan, what are you
doing over there?
Get back in bed right now.
I saw something.
- [Crackling]
- [Rumbling]
Aidan...
Move! Get away.
Get away from there.
Honey, let's go. Come on.
- [Aidan] I saw it.
- [Rachel panting]
- I saw it in my head.
- Let's go.
[Fog horn blaring]
[People chattering]
Oh, Miss Keller...
- About my story. I...
- Not now.
Now, listen, sweetie.
Last night I found a tape.
It was one of hers.
And I made it so we'd never
have to see it again.
But if she knows that,
what I did might
make her wanna hurt us.
Am I right?
Do you know something, honey?
Look, if you know why she's here,
you have to tell me.
Aidan...
...is she here to hurt you?
Honey.
[Whispering] She can hear us.
She hears everything.
Except when we sleep.
She can't hear us
when we sleep?
What does that mean?
We have to sleep.
[Knocking]
[Max] Rachel,
may I come in, please?
Yeah.
What happened to your car?
Your car. Apparently it's wrecked.
- Are you guys OK?
- Yeah. We got hit.
[Max] And no one's hurt?
That's good.
Aidan, right? Hi, I'm Max.
- Is he all right?
- He's sick.
How sick?
Max,
I need your help.
Here.
I'll get some more blankets.
The house is yours if there's
anything you need at all.
[Rachel] OK. Thanks.
- Here.
- Thank you.
- Shouldn't he be at a hospital?
- No, he's fine.
The bath?
Just down the hall.
I'll get it started.
Honey.
I'm gonna go home
and get some of our things.
Then we'll leave here
and never come back, OK?
[Rachel] Let's get you warmed up.
Not the best water pressure,
but it works.
It's good, thanks.
I don't know why we lost power.
The block seemed fine.
I have plenty of candles
in case the problem spreads.
Go ahead and get in.
Get you warmed up.
Max, I just need
to go back to my house,
get a few things,
some medicine.
Do you mind if you could?
- I'll watch him. Of course.
- OK, thanks.
Honey, go ahead and get in.
Let's go. Let's go.
We need to raise your temperature.
Now, let's get in.
Aidan, what's wrong?
It's just water.
- We need to raise your temperature...
- I don't want to, Rachel.
Do you want me
to get in with you?
Let's go then.
Aidan. Come on, let's go.
That's it.
Come on, honey.
Let's go. Let's go.
That's it. That's it.
That's better, right?
See? It's nice and warm.
It's OK. Just relax.
[Wailing]
[Water pouring]
[Phone ringing]
[Max] Hello?
Officer Ray. How you doing?
Yeah, good, good. All right,
what do you got for me?
Mm-hmm. Right.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, well, that all
sounds like page 26.
You don't have any headlines?
No?
Well, business is business.
Yeah. No, no, I'm good.
Real good.
Could you do me a little favour
while I've got you?
Could you look into
your accident reports
and see if there was an accident
with a woman and her son?
"K" for Keller.
No, no, I'm just trying
to get a story straight.
[Door squeaks shut]
Ray?
Ray, let me call you right back. OK.
[Knocking]
Everything OK in there?
Uh, Aidan, could you, uh,
unlock the door, please?
[Knocking] Aidan, can you hear me?
Aidan, please, unlock the door!
Aidan, open the door!
Aidan. Aidan. Aidan!
He's in the bath.
It was open a second ago.
- Aidan, open the door!
- I'll get something to break it.
Aidan, open up the door.
I'm right here.
Honey, can you hear me? Please.
You need to open up the door.
Aidan!
Aidan.
Oh, my God.
Aidan!
Aidan.
Please, honey, open the...
Oh, my God.
Oh!
Aidan.
Aidan. Aidan.
Look at me. Aidan, look at me.
Look at me.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
[Coughing]
Mommy!
[Shrieks]
[Max] Rachel, no!
[Coughing]
Baby. Oh.
Oh, my God.
Baby, I'm sorry.
It wasn't him. It wasn't him.
I was just trying to help.
OK, Rachel, let's just
get him out of there.
Why is she doing this to me?
I'm here now, baby.
- Why is she doing this to me?
- It's OK, Aidan.
- We're gonna get you to a hospital.
- No!
- They can't do anything.
- [Coughing]
You asked for help,
you're gonna get help.
He gets to a hospital. Now.
[Crying]
[Man] We're working to raise
his core temperature.
He was at 90 degrees
when he came in.
- He wasn't outside overnight?
- No. He was at home with me.
A body doesn't develop
severe hypothermia on its own.
Whatever the cause, he's fighting it.
Seems like he's stabilizing.
- And he's just sleeping now?
- Right.
And having some kind of dream.
What's the story, Rachel?
They stabilized his temperature.
I mean the story
with you and Aidan.
You seem awfully hard on him.
Look, I know
it's a stressful time for you.
Moving. It's a whole new life.
Maybe you should tell me.
All I ever tried to do for him
was the right thing,
and it only ever
made things worse.
Then it wasn't
the right thing, was it?
[Rachel] What do you see?
Well, it's Aidan.
- Is that a girl there?
- Why is she in the picture?
- Why? How would I know?
- Why is she in all of them?
Her name's Samara.
She was murdered by her mother.
Left to die at the bottom of a well.
- Wait, she's... she's who?
- She didn't die.
At least, not her ghost.
I kept it alive for Aidan.
I let it out,
it spread and then we ran.
- What are you talking about?
- I know this sounds crazy,
but she's here now.
She's found us.
And I thought it was
just to hurt Aidan,
but it's more than that.
She wants to be him.
And she wants to live
for real this time.
You tell me, who can help me?
- Who?
- I'm sure there's a rational...
You take his picture
and tell me why she's in it.
- Rachel.
- You take his picture.
It's proof that he's what?
He's got a ghost inside him?
No. The proof
is what will happen.
[Rachel] Aidan,
you said Samara
couldn't hear us when we sleep.
Well, you're sleeping now.
Tell me how to stop her, honey.
Tell me how to help you.
Just tell me,
I'll do anything, I swear.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
[Gasping]
- [Woman singing softly]
- [Low rumbling]
[Electronic whirring]
[Woman singing softly]
[Woman screaming]
[High-pitched scream]
[Grinding]
[Breathing heavily]
Aidan?
- Aidan?
- Miss Keller?
Hello, I'm Dr Emma Temple.
I'm a consulting physician
at County Child Services.
Well, I was hoping to speak
with Aidan when he wakes up.
Is everything all right in here?
Yeah. It's fine. Thank you.
[Dr Temple] I was hoping
to speak with you as well.
It's Rachel, isn't it?
Yeah, about his situation.
[Rachel] Sorry, what kind
of doctor did you say you were again?
I'm a psychiatrist.
Yeah. I spoke with a Dr, um...
...Koji in Seattle. Aidan's doctor.
Look, if we could
maybe talk later.
Right. Um, Dr Koji mentioned
that you dealt with some PPD
when Aidan was born.
Postpartum depression.
That was the first month.
That's all.
I understand. It's very common.
I mean, a lot of women have trouble
adapting to the stresses of motherhood.
What does this have to do with
what's going on with my son right now?
Have you been
under stress lately?
Have you ever found that you were...
...unable to experience love for Aidan?
- What?
- Have you hurt him,
however unintentionally?
Have you left him alone?
Abandoned him?
I'd like to be with my son,
please, if you don't mind.
Yeah, of course.
I'm sorry, Rachel.
[Beeping]
Until we can talk further,
I cannot let you be alone with him.
I'm his mother.
There are bruises on his body.
He was hypothermic
and very near death.
That is not because of me.
[Dr Temple] He's gonna
be all right. He will.
But you need to leave.
Now, please.
[Whispering] You can't have him,
Samara.
You're going back
to where you came from.
All I wanna know is what her
history was before the Morgans.
I'm sorry, but the
privacy laws still apply.
Well, was she really adopted?
Can you at least tell me that much?
- Was their story true?
- Samara Morgan was adopted, yes.
But you won't tell me from who?
- I'd lose my job if I did.
- [Sighing] Look, ma'am,
my son has a medical condition
that his doctors don't even understand.
This little girl
had the same condition.
Now, if I knew what caused that,
it could save his life.
[Woman] All I can say is you
should speak to the Morgans.
They're dead.
They both killed themselves.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Whoa! Look out. Early birds.
Marty Savide,
Stevens Northwest Realty.
- Hi.
- Uh, come in.
I thought I put 12.30 on the ad.
For the open house.
- How'd you get around the gate?
- Well, I just...
Ah! Who cares? Come on.
Make me an offer
over asking and it's yours.
OK, then, don't mind me.
My first try with these things,
took off flying. [chuckling]
There we go.
What do you think?
Um, a little colour will really
turn the place around.
It's got a wonderful history.
Working horse ranch.
How about that?
And there's even this cute little
tree house thing way up in the barn.
Um, is the place being
sold unfurnished or?
The previous owners
didn't leave anything behind?
Well, there were some things
that were left, after they...
...moved.
We're storing all that
in the basement.
There's a basement?
Uh... Well, you betcha.
No extra charge.
Right this way.
[Low rumbling]
[Savide] Uh, if you don't mind,
I'm the welcome wagon.
Gotta open up the gate for everyone.
So please,
just make yourself at home.
Do you know what happened
to them? The previous owners?
I believe they bought
a condo in Phoenix.
Really?
[Music box music plays]
[Woman singing softly]
Her mother.
[Gasps]
I'll take it from here.
Hello, Aidan, I'm Dr Temple.
How are you feeling?
Aidan?
You know,
I'd really like to help you.
Can you tell me
how you're feeling?
Where's my mommy?
Well, she'll be here soon.
She's on her way.
I want Mommy.
Yeah, I know you do.
Your mommy
wants to be with you too.
So where is she?
She went home.
She didn't think that you
were gonna wake up so soon.
I wanna go home too.
Well, you will.
We just have to...
We just have to get you...
You're freezing.
I wanna go home to Mommy.
Well, we need to talk about her.
Can you tell me
about Mommy a little bit?
She loves me.
I know that she does.
She went looking for me.
She tried to find me.
It means she loves me.
I don't understand.
Can I go home now?
No, honey,
you're not well enough.
Can I go home?
No.
I'm sorry.
Then I have
to show you something.
It won't stop.
[Exhales]
[Woman] I'm gonna walk you
just around the corner here.
Her name was Evelyn.
She came to us
eight months pregnant.
- Did she have her baby here?
- Yes.
And you arranged
for the adoption?
That's right.
- And the father?
- There was none.
Half the mothers
that come to us say that.
So, what did she think
got her pregnant?
Evelyn wasn't well.
She had been having problems
during the pregnancy:
Hallucinations, visions.
She believed some thing
had come for her baby
from the waters of the world
beyond this one.
I'm sorry. Did you say water?
Well, we all envision
the afterlife differently.
For Evelyn,
it's just what she believed.
As you might imagine, she suffered
severe postpartum depression.
She blamed her troubles
on her child.
So she tried to kill it.
- All babies are a challenge.
- [Baby cooing]
But Samara, she never cried.
Never.
Except when her mother
would try to bathe her.
Then she'd scream like it
was the end of the world.
It was the screaming that woke us.
[Baby screaming and crying]
- Evelyn, don't!
- [Crying continues]
[Woman] Evelyn!
Evelyn, stop!
[Woman] She was trying
to drown the baby.
The baby was taken from her,
of course.
Evelyn was institutionalized.
And all those pictures
she'd been collecting,
they finally made sense.
Did she say why she did it?
She felt she had to kill
her baby to save it.
I'm here to see a patient.
Her name's Evelyn.
- I don't know her last name.
- Evelyn?
That's right.
Evelyn's expecting you.
Every few years, one of you
comes to see Evelyn.
She's like a freakin'
patron saint or something.
Got a problem with your kid,
don't you?
[Woman singing softly]
Something wrong?
That song. I know it.
Yeah. They all do.
Hey, Evelyn.
You were right as rain.
You got a visitor today.
Hope she's some help
to your troubles.
Ten minutes.
- [Scissors cutting]
- [Woman humming]
My name's Rachel.
But you know that.
[Evelyn] Some days I
sort of have a feeling.
A feeling?
This is about your child.
It's...
- It's about yours.
- [Cutting stops]
Samara.
They don't dream, you know.
The dead don't dream.
Look, something's happened
to my son.
- You have to sleep to dream.
- It has to do with your daughter.
And the dead never sleep.
They wait...
...and watch for a way back.
But they never sleep.
- That's why dreams are safe.
- I'm sorry, I just...
I don't have a lot of time.
Please, I need your help.
I have to know.
Can you tell me?
Why did you try
to kill your baby?
Why?
Because my baby told me to.
Just like yours will tell you.
And you have to do it.
- You have to send it back.
- What?
They stopped me.
- Don't let them stop you.
- What?
Listen to the voices.
What are you talking about?
Because it's our fault. We did it.
Yes. We did it. Yes.
It was you.
It was you! You did it!
What did I do?
[Door unbolting]
[Man] Evelyn, that's enough.
I love my son.
[Man] Come on. It's all right.
I'm sorry, ma'am,
that's enough for today.
Let's go.
What did I do?
You let the dead get in.
[Man] Let's go.
What should I do?
Be a good mother.
Listen to your baby.
- [Cutting resumes]
- [Humming continues]
[TV static]
[Knocking] Aidan?
Hey.
Shouldn't you, uh...
Shouldn't you be at the hospital?
No. I'm here
waiting for my mommy.
OK.
Well, you can't really leave
till the hospital says it's OK.
You were very, very sick.
You're all right now?
The cable setup at my house,
the TV needs to be
on channel three.
She loves me.
She loves me not.
- Thank you, Max.
- Sure.
She loves me!
Look, Mandy!
I think I'm gonna puke.
Why don't you do something
productive with your life?
Say, Billy,
if you like fish so much...
Your mom loves you, you know.
She loves you a lot.
You'd tell someone if you
weren't sure about that?
Like, if she'd been
hurting you somehow.
Did she ever treat you
like you're someone else?
I'm not somebody else.
I'm Aidan.
- I know.
- We don't need anyone else.
That's right.
We don't need you,
that doctor or anyone else.
OK?
OK.
What are you doing?
I was just gonna
take a picture of you.
No.
- It'll be for your mom.
- No.
Why not? What's wrong
with taking your picture?
I'll tell you what's wrong
if you promise not to take it.
But that's only if you promise.
Fine. I promise.
So, Aidan, what's the story?
[On TV]
We're happy when we're sad
We're always feeling sad
[Rachel] Hello?
- [TV] How are you?
- Terrible.
That's why we're happy
when we're sad
Max?
Are you here?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- You're home!
- [Gasping] God.
What are you doing?
I thought you were at the hospital.
No. I'm here, Mommy.
- What did you say?
- I said I'm here.
Is Max here?
No.
But his coat...
He went away.
You wanna watch some TV with me?
Uh...
[TV turns on]
I, uh, I just have to get
something from the car. OK?
I love you, Mommy.
Max.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Max?
[Screaming]
[TV] Goldfish must have water
in order to exist.
But goldfish hate cats.
While on the other hand,
cats hate water.
[Crying]
Rachel.
Are you sleeping, Rachel?
I am. She makes me sleep
all the time now.
Aidan.
Shh.
Just keep sleeping, Rachel.
So she can't hear us.
It's the only way.
You have to show her, Rachel.
Show her she can't stay.
In you.
How? How do I do that?
Take me to where she's afraid of.
- You know where she's afraid of.
- [Mouths word]
Take me there...
...and kill me.
- Aidan, no.
Shh. Rachel, keep sleeping.
She won't stay if she knows
you'll kill me.
- [Aidan] It's the only way.
- I can't do it. I can't.
Then she stays.
- [Whirring]
- [Gasping] She's heard us.
[Panting]
[TV indistinct]
Honey?
I thought you were sleeping,
Mommy.
I was, but I had a bad dream.
You must've had a nightmare.
It's all right.
We all have them.
Will you stay with me now?
- Stay?
- Stay for always.
Yeah. Yeah.
Alrighty.
Let's watch some TV together.
It's kind of late, honey.
Don't you think
you should sleep?
I never sleep.
Then let Mommy
make you something.
Something wrong?
You seem sad.
No, honey, I'm not sad.
I'm just tired, that's all.
Well, now you have me
to protect you.
[Woman singing on TV]
You ain't the biggest catfish
in the deep blue sea
[Aidan] Take me to where
she's afraid of.
You know where she's afraid of.
You have to show her, Rachel.
Show her she can't stay.
[Evelyn] Listen to the voices.
You have to listen to the voices.
[Echoing] Be a good mother.
Be a good mother.
Listen to your baby.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
But you can't stay.
What are you doing? Rachel!
What are you doing?
It's me.
- It's not her, Rachel.
- I know, baby.
It's me.
I love you. Mommy, I love you.
I know, baby.
I love you too.
But you're not my son.
[Gasping]
[Squealing]
Mommy.
Aidan.
Aidan. Aidan. Aidan.
Honey.
Breathe. Baby, breathe.
Please. I know it's you, honey.
Aidan.
Aidan, please.
Rachel.
Yeah.
I'm right here.
You're OK.
Everything's all right, honey.
You were sleeping.
You were just sleeping.
[High-pitched squeal]
[Eerie whining]
No.
[Water flowing]
[Aidan] She wants me again.
No.
Rachel, what are you doing?
All she wants is a mother.
That's all she wants.
And she'll keep coming
till she finds one.
[Aidan] Come on!
Come back!
Get away from her! Rachel!
Get away from her!
You can't have my son.
So take me.
Rachel! No!
Rachel! Rachel!
[Crashing]
Samara!
Here I am, Samara.
Just like you wanted.
But you leave him alone!
You hear me?
[Electric buzzing]
[Samara] Help me.
It's always open.
Her only way out
is always open.
[Samara muffled] Mommy.
Mommy!
Mommy.
[High-pitched squeal]
[Breathing heavily]
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
[Panting, straining]
- Mommy!
- I'm not your fucking mommy.
[Gasping]
[Aidan] Rachel.
[Whirring]
Rachel.
- Can you hear me?
- I can hear you.
[Aidan] I'm right here.
[Silence]
[Aidan] Rachel.
Rachel!
You're here.
- You're here, Rachel.
- Of course I'm here.
I followed your voice.
What happened?
It's over, honey.
She's not coming back.
How do you know, Rachel?
I know.
I promise.
I love you, Mommy.
Promise me something?
Yeah. Anything, Mom. Anything.
Just call me Rachel.
At least for a while.
[Whirring, hissing]
I wanna show you something.
What?
Have you ever seen
something so scary
that you had to show
to someone else?
I mean, like, you know,
a movie or something.
Well...
I've got the scariest
freakin' movie you'll ever see.
Now... A buddy of mine
actually turned me on to it.
And he made me a copy.
So... I did one for you.
You brought me here
to watch a video?
Well, two minutes. OK?
Two minutes and it'll all be over.
It's totally underground stuff.
- I thought we were gonna just...
- No, we will. We will.
You just gotta see this.
I'm telling you, it's...
- How about after we?
- No, you need to watch it now.
What's so scary about it?
You'll see.
Play it. Just play the thing.
Come on,
I got two minutes here, please.
Emily, play the goddamn tape!
- Hello?
- Hey, man, you made it.
I knew you'd come through.
You got somebody to watch it
Some stupid chick
from my school.
Good. I was afraid
you didn't believe me, man.
Now it's her problem. She doesn't
get someone else to watch it in a week,
I swear she's dead.
So, did you tell her what happens
or you just gonna let her
find out for herself?
Jake?
Come on, it's over, dude.
Jake. This isn't funny, man.
Emily?
- Emily, what the hell did you do?
- I played it, I just didn't look.
Come on, Aidan, let's go home.
It was the right choice.
No question.
Aidan, dinner's ready.
Damn.
OK, now, before you say anything,
I followed the recipe this time.
Just 'cause it doesn't look
like the one in the magazine,
doesn't mean to say
it won't taste good.
Those are great, honey.
Got a really good eye.
He'd be proud of you.
Thanks, Rachel.
You know, it wouldn't kill you
to call me "mom" now and again.
"Ma. " "Mommy. "
Something besides "Rachel".
Yeah, I like "Rachel".
Well, "mom" has its charms too,
you know.
But "Rachel"
is more your personality.
Really?
Well, Rachel declares dinnertime.
It's working out great,
don't you think?
All of this space and fresh air.
We have a yard.
It's really great.
Listen, honey...
...we didn't do anything wrong.
We did what anyone would do.
We started over.
You know how they can tell
you used to work at a real newspaper?
You're the only one
who closes your door.
Habit.
I wanted to talk
to you about my editorial.
Those changes OK?
Well, I asked you to copy edit it
and you rewrote it.
Just the part
about the bond measure.
That was the whole thing.
The bridge would get
the money, not the riverfront.
You know,
a big news day in Astoria
is a school board meeting, a car wreck
and a cat in a tree. That's big news.
You sure this is the job
you're looking for?
Well, I'm around for my son more.
In Seattle, I wasn't.
Good a reason as any.
I'm glad to see you're
settling in. I like the...
Max, while you're here,
have you given any thought
to that piece for tomorrow?
You know what?
Don't worry about it.
It's 442 Ridgecrest.
Repeat that.
It's what?
Ridgecrest. Ridgecrest!
I've talked to the medical
examiner. They're on their way.
Squad 19 to respond.
Can we keep
this channel clear?
- The police found a body.
- Possible homicide.
- Please, we should be so lucky.
- What are they saying?
"High school student, male, 17.
Address, 442 Ridgecrest.
Found the house flooded,
a girlfriend hiding in the basement. "
- Suspect or witness, they don't know.
- The guy was dead in front of the TV.
They keep on talking
about his face.
What about his face?
All emergency units,
area Astoria, switch to Tack Five.
Detective.
Detective, you have a minute?
Was it homicide or wasn't it?
You know how he died.
I just have
a few last questions.
If you could walk me
through it again.
It's just horrible.
So young.
No.
No, please, not here.
I found you.
We only made one copy.
Oh, God.
- Excuse me, sir.
- Hold on.
- Rachel Keller from the Daily Astorian.
- We'll make a statement.
- I need to know about the girl.
She hasn't said a word, has she?
You're welcome to wait.
Excuse me.
Watch your step.
Have a seat here, OK?
Have a seat.
I just want you to relax for me.
You can't keep her.
- Focus on the walls.
- We wanna take her.
- She'll talk to us.
- I understand.
I'm just gonna ask
a few questions. Please.
- Be right back, Emily.
- Thank you. Thank you.
All right. Give me his number.
Yeah. All right.
Emily, listen to me.
I know what happened.
I know.
Now, you have to tell me.
The tape.
Did you watch it?
Do you know who else
has watched it?
Has anyone else watched it?
Then where is it?
Hey, you.
Get away from her. Ray.
Emily, talk to me.
I want her out of here.
Now.
You can tell me, Emily.
No.
Not here, Samara.
Not here.
Honey, what is it?
What's wrong?
Look at me.
- OK? What is it?
- I had a nightmare.
That's all right.
We all have them.
Oh, God, you're soaked.
And you're freezing.
Let's get you out of
these clothes. Come on.
Aidan?
What happened in your nightmare?
I woke up and you weren't here.
You weren't here.
I'm here now, honey.
I'm right here, OK?
Listen.
All you have to do is call my
name and I'll follow your voice.
OK?
Even if I have to come right down
into that nightmare with you.
So tell me what happened.
I don't remember.
You don't remember?
Honey. You heard me?
I've been calling your name.
I'm... sorry.
You ready to go?
OK.
So we'll just swing by
and see what they have, OK?
And you can keep a watch on
the backyard stuff. How's that?
Look at all this stuff.
Who do you think buys this crap?
Rachel.
Sorry.
What's wrong, honey?
You all right?
I'm just a little cold, Rachel.
- I'm gonna take a look around.
- All right.
Stay close.
Would you like a marble, ma'am?
You gotta wait
for the whistle.
Here I go!
Are you in there?
Why didn't you answer me, honey?
What are you?
Jesus, you're freezing, honey.
What's going on? Are you sick?
Talk to me, honey.
Talk to me. What's going on?
- What is it?
- I'm cold.
It's OK. It's OK.
Honey, when did this start?
Was it last night,
or this morning?
I don't remember.
I know you don't like me prying,
but this is important.
Was it your nightmare?
I really don't remember, Rachel.
I need you to try.
You're sick, all right? And we
need to know what started it.
Was she in your nightmare?
Don't stop.
- Go! Drive! Drive!
- What's the matter, honey?
Just don't stop the car!
Get down!
"Don't stop. "
You said, "Don't stop. "
OK. Let's see.
That's impossible.
Rachel...
...what's happening?
Yeah, hi...
My son is very sick
and I'd like to
talk to someone who...
Well, it's his temperature.
It's... it's five degrees low.
Yeah. Well, then,
I'll hold for the on-call nurse.
Hello?
Honey, the power just went out.
Are you OK up there?
Honey, this shouldn't be open.
God.
Aidan, let's go. Get out of bed.
Aidan, what are you
doing over there?
Get back in bed right now.
I saw something.
Move! Get away.
Get away from there.
Honey, let's go. Come on.
I saw it.
- I saw it in my head.
- Let's go.
Oh, Miss Keller...
- About my story. I...
- Not now.
Now, listen, sweetie.
Last night I found a tape.
It was one of hers.
And I made it so we'd never
have to see it again.
But if she knows that,
what I did might
make her wanna hurt us.
Am I right?
Do you know something, honey?
Look, if you know why she's here,
you have to tell me.
Aidan...
...is she here to hurt you?
Honey.
She can hear us.
She hears everything.
Except when we sleep.
She can't hear us
when we sleep?
What does that mean?
We have to sleep.
Rachel,
may I come in, please?
What happened to your car?
Your car. Apparently it's wrecked.
- Are you guys OK?
- Yeah. We got hit.
And no one's hurt?
That's good.
Aidan, right? Hi, I'm Max.
- Is he all right?
- He's sick.
How sick?
Max,
I need your help.
Here.
I'll get some more blankets.
The house is yours if there's
anything you need at all.
OK. Thanks.
- Here.
- Thank you.
- Shouldn't he be at a hospital?
- No, he's fine.
The bath?
Just down the hall.
I'll get it started.
Honey.
I'm gonna go home
and get some of our things.
Then we'll leave here
and never come back, OK?
Let's get you warmed up.
Not the best water pressure,
but it works.
It's good, thanks.
I don't know why we lost power.
The block seemed fine.
I have plenty of candles
in case the problem spreads.
Go ahead and get in.
Get you warmed up.
Max, I just need
to go back to my house,
get a few things,
some medicine.
Do you mind if you could?
- I'll watch him. Of course.
- OK, thanks.
Honey, go ahead and get in.
Let's go. Let's go.
We need to raise your temperature.
Now, let's get in.
Aidan, what's wrong?
It's just water.
- We need to raise your temperature...
- I don't want to, Rachel.
Do you want me
to get in with you?
Let's go then.
Aidan. Come on, let's go.
That's it.
Come on, honey.
Let's go. Let's go.
That's it. That's it.
That's better, right?
See? It's nice and warm.
It's OK. Just relax.
Hello?
Officer Ray. How you doing?
Yeah, good, good. All right,
what do you got for me?
Right.
Yeah, well, that all
sounds like page 26.
You don't have any headlines?
No?
Well, business is business.
Yeah. No, no, I'm good.
Real good.
Could you do me a little favour
while I've got you?
Could you look into
your accident reports
and see if there was an accident
with a woman and her son?
"K" for Keller.
No, no, I'm just trying
to get a story straight.
Ray?
Ray, let me call you right back. OK.
Everything OK in there?
Aidan, could you,
unlock the door, please?
Aidan, can you hear me?
Aidan, please, unlock the door!
Aidan, open the door!
He's in the bath.
It was open a second ago.
- Aidan, open the door!
- I'll get something to break it.
Aidan, open up the door.
I'm right here.
Honey, can you hear me? Please.
You need to open up the door.
Oh, my God.
Please, honey, open the...
Look at me. Aidan, look at me.
Look at me.
Mommy!
Rachel, no!
Baby. Oh.
Oh, my God.
Baby, I'm sorry.
It wasn't him. It wasn't him.
I was just trying to help.
OK, Rachel, let's just
get him out of there.
Why is she doing this to me?
I'm here now, baby.
- Why is she doing this to me?
- It's OK, Aidan.
- We're gonna get you to a hospital.
- No!
They can't do anything.
You asked for help,
you're gonna get help.
He gets to a hospital. Now.
We're working to raise
his core temperature.
He was at 90 degrees
when he came in.
- He wasn't outside overnight?
- No. He was at home with me.
A body doesn't develop
severe hypothermia on its own.
Whatever the cause, he's fighting it.
Seems like he's stabilizing.
- And he's just sleeping now?
- Right.
And having some kind of dream.
What's the story, Rachel?
They stabilized his temperature.
I mean the story
with you and Aidan.
You seem awfully hard on him.
Look, I know
it's a stressful time for you.
Moving. It's a whole new life.
Maybe you should tell me.
All I ever tried to do for him
was the right thing,
and it only ever
made things worse.
Then it wasn't
the right thing, was it?
What do you see?
Well, it's Aidan.
- Is that a girl there?
- Why is she in the picture?
- Why? How would I know?
- Why is she in all of them?
Her name's Samara.
She was murdered by her mother.
Left to die at the bottom of a well.
- Wait, she's... she's who?
- She didn't die.
At least, not her ghost.
I kept it alive for Aidan.
I let it out,
it spread and then we ran.
- What are you talking about?
- I know this sounds crazy,
but she's here now.
She's found us.
And I thought it was
just to hurt Aidan,
but it's more than that.
She wants to be him.
And she wants to live
for real this time.
You tell me, who can help me?
- Who?
- I'm sure there's a rational...
You take his picture
and tell me why she's in it.
- Rachel.
- You take his picture.
It's proof that he's what?
He's got a ghost inside him?
No. The proof
is what will happen.
Aidan,
you said Samara
couldn't hear us when we sleep.
Well, you're sleeping now.
Tell me how to stop her, honey.
Tell me how to help you.
Just tell me,
I'll do anything, I swear.
- Aidan?
- Miss Keller?
Hello, I'm Dr Emma Temple.
I'm a consulting physician
at County Child Services.
Well, I was hoping to speak
with Aidan when he wakes up.
Is everything all right in here?
Yeah. It's fine. Thank you.
I was hoping
to speak with you as well.
It's Rachel, isn't it?
Yeah, about his situation.
Sorry, what kind
of doctor did you say you were again?
I'm a psychiatrist.
Yeah. I spoke with a Dr...
...Koji in Seattle. Aidan's doctor.
Look, if we could
maybe talk later.
Right. Dr Koji mentioned
that you dealt with some PPD
when Aidan was born.
Postpartum depression.
That was the first month.
That's all.
I understand. It's very common.
I mean, a lot of women have trouble
adapting to the stresses of motherhood.
What does this have to do with
what's going on with my son right now?
Have you been
under stress lately?
Have you ever found that you were...
...unable to experience love for Aidan?
- What?
- Have you hurt him,
however unintentionally?
Have you left him alone?
Abandoned him?
I'd like to be with my son,
please, if you don't mind.
Yeah, of course.
I'm sorry, Rachel.
Until we can talk further,
I cannot let you be alone with him.
I'm his mother.
There are bruises on his body.
He was hypothermic
and very near death.
That is not because of me.
He's gonna
be all right. He will.
But you need to leave.
Now, please.
You can't have him,
Samara.
You're going back
to where you came from.
All I wanna know is what her
history was before the Morgans.
I'm sorry, but the
privacy laws still apply.
Well, was she really adopted?
Can you at least tell me that much?
- Was their story true?
- Samara Morgan was adopted, yes.
But you won't tell me from who?
- I'd lose my job if I did.
- Look, ma'am,
my son has a medical condition
that his doctors don't even understand.
This little girl
had the same condition.
Now, if I knew what caused that,
it could save his life.
All I can say is you
should speak to the Morgans.
They're dead.
They both killed themselves.
Look out. Early birds.
Marty Savide,
Stevens Northwest Realty.
- Hi.
- Come in.
I thought I put 12.30 on the ad.
For the open house.
- How'd you get around the gate?
- Well, I just...
Ah! Who cares? Come on.
Make me an offer
over asking and it's yours.
OK, then, don't mind me.
My first try with these things,
took off flying.
There we go.
What do you think?
A little colour will really
turn the place around.
It's got a wonderful history.
Working horse ranch.
How about that?
And there's even this cute little
tree house thing way up in the barn.
Is the place being
sold unfurnished or?
The previous owners
didn't leave anything behind?
Well, there were some things
that were left, after they...
...moved.
We're storing all that
in the basement.
There's a basement?
Well, you betcha.
No extra charge.
Right this way.
If you don't mind,
I'm the welcome wagon.
Gotta open up the gate for everyone.
So please,
just make yourself at home.
Do you know what happened
to them? The previous owners?
I believe they bought
a condo in Phoenix.
Really?
Her mother.
I'll take it from here.
Hello, Aidan, I'm Dr Temple.
How are you feeling?
Aidan?
You know,
I'd really like to help you.
Can you tell me
how you're feeling?
Where's my mommy?
Well, she'll be here soon.
She's on her way.
I want Mommy.
Yeah, I know you do.
Your mommy
wants to be with you too.
So where is she?
She went home.
She didn't think that you
were gonna wake up so soon.
I wanna go home too.
Well, you will.
We just have to...
We just have to get you...
You're freezing.
I wanna go home to Mommy.
Well, we need to talk about her.
Can you tell me
about Mommy a little bit?
She loves me.
I know that she does.
She went looking for me.
She tried to find me.
It means she loves me.
I don't understand.
Can I go home now?
No, honey,
you're not well enough.
Can I go home?
No.
I'm sorry.
Then I have
to show you something.
It won't stop.
I'm gonna walk you
just around the corner here.
Her name was Evelyn.
She came to us
eight months pregnant.
- Did she have her baby here?
- Yes.
And you arranged
for the adoption?
That's right.
- And the father?
- There was none.
Half the mothers
that come to us say that.
So, what did she think
got her pregnant?
Evelyn wasn't well.
She had been having problems
during the pregnancy:
Hallucinations, visions.
She believed some thing
had come for her baby
from the waters of the world
beyond this one.
I'm sorry. Did you say water?
Well, we all envision
the afterlife differently.
For Evelyn,
it's just what she believed.
As you might imagine, she suffered
severe postpartum depression.
She blamed her troubles
on her child.
So she tried to kill it.
All babies are a challenge.
But Samara, she never cried.
Never.
Except when her mother
would try to bathe her.
Then she'd scream like it
was the end of the world.
It was the screaming that woke us.
Evelyn, don't!
Evelyn!
Evelyn, stop!
She was trying
to drown the baby.
The baby was taken from her,
of course.
Evelyn was institutionalized.
And all those pictures
she'd been collecting,
they finally made sense.
Did she say why she did it?
She felt she had to kill
her baby to save it.
I'm here to see a patient.
Her name's Evelyn.
- I don't know her last name.
- Evelyn?
That's right.
Evelyn's expecting you.
Every few years, one of you
comes to see Evelyn.
She's like a freakin'
patron saint or something.
Got a problem with your kid,
don't you?
Something wrong?
That song. I know it.
Yeah. They all do.
Hey, Evelyn.
You were right as rain.
You got a visitor today.
Hope she's some help
to your troubles.
Ten minutes.
My name's Rachel.
But you know that.
Some days I
sort of have a feeling.
A feeling?
This is about your child.
It's...
It's about yours.
Samara.
They don't dream, you know.
The dead don't dream.
Look, something's happened
to my son.
- You have to sleep to dream.
- It has to do with your daughter.
And the dead never sleep.
They wait...
...and watch for a way back.
But they never sleep.
- That's why dreams are safe.
- I'm sorry, I just...
I don't have a lot of time.
Please, I need your help.
I have to know.
Can you tell me?
Why did you try
to kill your baby?
Why?
Because my baby told me to.
Just like yours will tell you.
And you have to do it.
- You have to send it back.
- What?
They stopped me.
- Don't let them stop you.
- What?
Listen to the voices.
What are you talking about?
Because it's our fault. We did it.
Yes. We did it. Yes.
It was you.
It was you! You did it!
What did I do?
Evelyn, that's enough.
I love my son.
Come on. It's all right.
I'm sorry, ma'am,
that's enough for today.
Let's go.
What did I do?
You let the dead get in.
Let's go.
What should I do?
Be a good mother.
Listen to your baby.
Hey.
Shouldn't you be at the hospital?
No. I'm here
waiting for my mommy.
OK.
Well, you can't really leave
till the hospital says it's OK.
You were very, very sick.
You're all right now?
The cable setup at my house,
the TV needs to be
on channel three.
She loves me.
She loves me not.
- Thank you, Max.
- Sure.
She loves me!
Look, Mandy!
I think I'm gonna puke.
Why don't you do something
productive with your life?
Say, Billy,
if you like fish so much...
Your mom loves you, you know.
She loves you a lot.
You'd tell someone if you
weren't sure about that?
Like, if she'd been
hurting you somehow.
Did she ever treat you
like you're someone else?
I'm not somebody else.
I'm Aidan.
- I know.
- We don't need anyone else.
That's right.
We don't need you,
that doctor or anyone else.
What are you doing?
I was just gonna
take a picture of you.
No.
- It'll be for your mom.
- No.
Why not? What's wrong
with taking your picture?
I'll tell you what's wrong
if you promise not to take it.
But that's only if you promise.
Fine. I promise.
So, Aidan, what's the story?
We're happy when we're sad
We're always feeling sad
Hello?
- How are you?
- Terrible.
That's why we're happy
when we're sad
Max?
Are you here?
- You're home!
- God.
What are you doing?
I thought you were at the hospital.
No. I'm here, Mommy.
- What did you say?
- I said I'm here.
Is Max here?
No.
But his coat...
He went away.
You wanna watch some TV with me?
I just have to get
something from the car. OK?
I love you, Mommy.
Max.
Goldfish must have water
in order to exist.
But goldfish hate cats.
While on the other hand,
cats hate water.
Are you sleeping, Rachel?
I am. She makes me sleep
all the time now.
Just keep sleeping, Rachel.
So she can't hear us.
It's the only way.
You have to show her, Rachel.
Show her she can't stay.
In you.
How? How do I do that?
Take me to where she's afraid of.
You know where she's afraid of.
Take me there...
...and kill me.
- Aidan, no.
Rachel, keep sleeping.
She won't stay if she knows
you'll kill me.
- It's the only way.
- I can't do it. I can't.
Then she stays.
She's heard us.
Honey?
I thought you were sleeping,
Mommy.
I was, but I had a bad dream.
You must've had a nightmare.
It's all right.
We all have them.
Will you stay with me now?
- Stay?
- Stay for always.
Yeah. Yeah.
Alrighty.
Let's watch some TV together.
It's kind of late, honey.
Don't you think
you should sleep?
I never sleep.
Then let Mommy
make you something.
Something wrong?
You seem sad.
No, honey, I'm not sad.
I'm just tired, that's all.
Well, now you have me
to protect you.
You ain't the biggest catfish
in the deep blue sea
Take me to where
she's afraid of.
You know where she's afraid of.
You have to show her, Rachel.
Show her she can't stay.
Listen to the voices.
You have to listen to the voices.
Be a good mother.
Listen to your baby.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
But you can't stay.
What are you doing? Rachel!
What are you doing?
It's me.
- It's not her, Rachel.
- I know, baby.
It's me.
I love you. Mommy, I love you.
I know, baby.
I love you too.
But you're not my son.
Mommy.
Honey.
Breathe. Baby, breathe.
Please. I know it's you, honey.
Aidan, please.
I'm right here.
You're OK.
Everything's all right, honey.
You were sleeping.
You were just sleeping.
No.
She wants me again.
Rachel, what are you doing?
All she wants is a mother.
That's all she wants.
And she'll keep coming
till she finds one.
Come on!
Come back!
Get away from her! Rachel!
Get away from her!
You can't have my son.
So take me.
Rachel! No!
Samara!
Here I am, Samara.
Just like you wanted.
But you leave him alone!
You hear me?
Help me.
It's always open.
Her only way out
is always open.
Mommy.
- Mommy!
- I'm not your fucking mommy.
- Can you hear me?
- I can hear you.
I'm right here.
You're here.
- You're here, Rachel.
- Of course I'm here.
I followed your voice.
What happened?
It's over, honey.
She's not coming back.
How do you know, Rachel?
I know.
I promise.
I love you, Mommy.
Promise me something?
Yeah. Anything, Mom. Anything.
Just call me Rachel.
At least for a while.