Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Ma...ma?
John?
Wait! I-I can't see you!
Are you still there?
Yeah.
Why is this thing...?
What do I click?
Rebecca?
Yeah?
The video button.
Duh.
Much better!
Hey!
Took you long enough.
She's a little slow getting started, ok?
How are you?
Can't complain. Still kickin.
Can you really see me in this thing?
No.
Is this me or is it just... is it really confusing?
What?
Well, I look up here...
Yeah, at the cam.
But I want to look at the screen.
It takes a little getting used to.
Hey, not complaining, man. Really cool game.
Happy birthday to you!
Happy!
You know the rest.
Thanks, man.
What are you waiting for? Blow 'em out!
Huh?
Make a wish!
How?
Do it.
Dork.
This is great! This is so cool that we can see each other!
Wait, though. I don't know if I want everybody
seeing me every time I talk on this thing.
Why?
You know! What if I have to...?
What?
That's the one thing about phone cams.
What you see is what you get?
How's your birthday?
Spent most of it in class breathing in car fumes.
Ugh!
Yeah, Rutgers-Camden is located right
near the Ben Franklin Bridge so, uh...
I'm pretty much digging living off-campus right now.
You make a wish?
Mm-hmm.
And what was it?
Uh uh.
Rebecca?
Ok. Have any of the ones you've ever told come true?
No.
Any of yours?
Well, the one about me getting
the hell out of Bedford sure did.
And! The one about me getting
accepted to a better school did!
Yes!
Getting out of Bedford was probably
the best thing I've done in my life.
Ouch.
Oh, hey, I didn't mean it like that.
Right.
I didn't, man, really.
I'm just giving you a hard time.
What else?
You seeing anyone?
Uuuuuh... no comment.
- This the place you're been telling me about?
- Yeah.
I'm... actually renting a room
in someone's house. It's, umm...
-...My first off campus pad.
- Sweet.
One thing about historic Collingswood,
we've got some pretty bitchin' old houses.
Here, let's see if I can move this thing.
- Look, see, it even has a closet!
- Knock yourself out!
Lot's of space, huh?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Oh, look what I picked up today.
What's that?
It's the house. Let's look through it.
- Can you see it?
- Yeah.
Am I holding it up ok?
Oh, yeah. It looks, uh... historic.
Not out on hardback yet?
Hm-mm
To the birthday girl!
In her new bitchin' pad.
Cheers!
Yeah, so, not bad for $300 a month.
So, the owners were having trouble renting
it out so, um, they lowered the price.
He's a professor at school and I forget what she does.
Their bedroom above yours?
Um, no, actually I think it's the bathroom.
They quiet?
No, no, they're not.
Wood floors, really.
You don't hear them cuz they're away.
What?
Yeah, 'til Sunday.
Fuck! You shoulda had me down! Party weekend!
I know. I know, man.
We could be cruising into Philly right
now chowing down on cheesesteaks!
I have so much due on Monday.
I waited 'til the last minute.
Right, uh, you didn't want
to see me. I can take a hint.
Look, next weekend when you come down, we'll party.
Glad to see you're doing ok, Beck.
Well...
Big plans for the night?
Naw, just gonna hang with Billy, you know?
Get in the fall spirit, carve pumpkins, get trashed.
Sounds fun.
How is Billy anyway?
He's Billy.
Hey, were you fixin' to do something before I called?
Well, yeah, I was just gonna pop
my Swanson Delux in the microwave.
Can I give you a call back? You'll be around?
Call me when you're done.
Ok.
Hey.
Thanks for making my birthday so special.
It's not over yet.
It's not?
Bye!
See ya.
Billy
Yeah.
Think I was gonna wait for everyone to get here?
Those things really work?
Oh, yes! Sure way to get shitfaced in half the time.
So, what's up? Talk to Rebecca?
Just did.
So, you missing her, man? Or what?
I don't know.
She's hard to read.
Why'd she leave Bedford?
She wanted to transfer to a better school.
No, no, no man. Why'd she really leave?
I just told you. She's tired of it.
She couldn't be around her step-dad.
Yeah, what happened to the, you know?
I don't know, man.
It's her birthday, ain't it?
Why aren't you there?
She's got too much to work on. She's stressin', man.
You know what that means.
- What?
- She's seeing some other loser.
Otherwise she woulda definitely wanted you there.
Dumb shit.
You really think so?
Yeah, uh huh.
Fuck you, Billy.
- You’re just trying to piss me off.
- I'm just telling you how it is.
Alright.
Why do you think you got her that video phone?
So you could stalk her online.
Don't waste your time, man.
When ya heading out?
I dunno. Think I'm gonna hang here tonight.
Been in any more phone cam sites?
You been to The Baroness?
I told you about that one.
Here's one you probably haven't heard of.
I was, you know, checking through all these sites.
Ghost cams and spook houses, that sort of thing.
But, you know, they're all pretty lame.
Until I found Vera Madeline.
She's basically a psychic.
But her specialty is raising
the folks who push up the daisies.
Six feet under?
The dead?
No way.
$50 she gives a full on seance.
That's wild, man.
Yeah, and $50.
Just be warned.
Rip off.
Yeah.
She got in touch with my old man,
you know, who passed away in 1996.
He told her that he worries about me.
You know, wants me to get a life so he can be proud of me.
Billy.
Since when did your dad die?
Yep, alright. Gimme her number.
This is it. Yeah.
Check her out, man.
Hey, I gotta grab that. I'll call you back.
What's up?
Hey!
Did you move your computer?
I installed the software on my laptop, so, now...
I can show you around easier.
Wow, you, uh, made your own portable phone cam gizmo.
Yeah, pretty crafty, huh?
And while you're at it, making
use of the phone line in the kitchen.
You know, now what I really need is one of those
super long phone cords and then this will really rock.
Ooh, check out what they've done in here. It's so great.
Look at that.
Isn't it cool?
Ah, I cannot wait to snoop in here some more.
Feeling better?
Yeah, now that I'm um...
...Pigging out.
Hey, um...
Beck, uh...
No biggie.
I was wondering if you were really by yourself there.
Huh?
What's up?
Yeah, I hope the owners go away a lot.
It'll be too perfect.
You got it made, Beck.
Oh! That's my portable.
Check your email. I just sent you something.
Lemme grab that. Hold on.
Hello?
Hi, Mom.
Yeah, thanks for the sweater.
No, I love it. Yeah!
Got that whole, uh, New York thing going.
Yeah, Mom hang on a minute.
Hey, I'll call you back?
Oh, ok.
That was John.
He's ok.
No, no we're uh...
We're... we're gonna do something next weekend.
I dunno...just...
Just kind of feeling overwhelmed and...
Sort of felt like being alone.
Oh, you know, I don't think I'm
gonna be able to make it Thanksgiving.
Yeah, I mean, finals are coming up and I'm just...
Yeah.
Today? I had a great day!
No, it was-I had a lot of fun!
Yeah, how are things with you and Paul?
Oh?
He did.
Tell him I said hi.
Everything’s fine, Mom. Yeah, I love you.
Bye.
Hey, man!
She's alone.
So, I was wrong. Made a mistake.
Big fucking deal.
Dumb shit.
Why you getting shitty with me?
Fuck you, man. Last time I ever listen to you.
What's your fucking problem?
You'll never let it go, will you?
That she dumped you.
Who?
Billy.
Oh, yeah?
Kiss this, ass munch. Come on,
right here. Come on, right here.
- Kiss that!
- No, thanks.
- I think I'm gonna hang here tonight.
- Oh, hold on, wait, wait. Hold on.
You, uh, go to Vera Madeline?
Not yet.
Pshh, loser.
Don't know what you're missing.
Have fun!
Dumb shit.
Yeah.
That's so cool how you got that thing hooked up!
Hmm.
I thought you were heading out?
Naw, Billy's having his entire
crowd over and I'm not in the mood.
So, I thought I'd take a chance and see if, uh...
You can distract me?
Yup!
Hey, you know what I've been thinking?
It's still my birthday. I want to have fun!
Now she's talking!
Speaking of which!
What are these numbers you emailed me?
Who are they?
No.
You mean I can just...
I call these people in it?
- So she's ready to do a little phone searching.
- She is, she is!
What do I gotta do?
Nothing different. Keep the software
running and dial the number.
Theodore? Who's that?
Something we've always joked about.
A little birthday entertainment.
Noooo.
No, you didn't! It's not a stripper, is it?
Have fun.
Ok, Bye.
There's no one there...
Hello?
God dog!
I'm sorry. I think I called the wrong number.
- Um... Who am I calling?
- You look about...
...Beautiful 21.
I've done some of that.
What's your name?
Um... I...
A friend of mine gave me your number.
I'm a dancer, baby.
Hoo coo coo ca ca, baby.
Ole, ole, ole, Bah! Boo! Bah! Yeah!
You know, I... Look. Have a great night, man.
I, um, I gotta go.
Why come in so short?
I-I don't really know what to say.
Uh, what, I mean...
You just, you just leave this cam on
and people just call you?
24/7!
What do you talk about?
Open up to me.
We all got a little bit of...
...Wicked in us!
Open up!
Who the hell was that?
Just your average cam nut.
-Ugh, thanks a lot!
-Beck, first time I called him I was so stoned!
He just wanted to chill and talk weird
shit about mushroom radiation.
Where did you find him?
Yellow Pages.
He's listed in the phone cam directory.
I cannot believe people.
I mean, they have these cams in their homes and they just...
They leave them on what? 24/7?
Just harmless exhibitionists.
Right.
What was that?
You're getting another call.
On this?
Yup.
I'm scared.
Trust me.
This is the best birthday entertainment.
You're gonna remember this night.
Ok, hold on.
Hi, Rebecca!
Hello?
Happy birthday.
This song is for you!
Great!
What did you think?
Cute?
And he got my number how?
I gave it to him.
Great.
You get it? He's a singing telegram.
Oh!
Wow, this is a trip, John. I love it.
Having fun?
Yeah, yeah. I think.
Ok. One more. She's a cam psychic.
- Oh!
- She's got a gift according to Billy
for contacting the dearly departed.
- I thought I'd go first...
- No, no, no! I want to!
Ok.
Yeah, these 1 -800 people crack me up.
Is this it?
Maybe she can tell me if its in the stars
if I'll pass or fail this semester.
Good luck.
I'll call you back.
"Welcome to my paranormal realm where
psychic secrets and desires are revealed."
"My name is Vera Madeline."
"I am a clairvoyant medium."
"I offer spiritual guidance and knowledge."
"I am a very positive, honest person."
"I never knowingly will cause you anxiety."
"If you are open and if you believe anything is possible."
"Do you certify that you are at least
18 years of age or older?"
Oh, um, yes.
"Then if you are comfortable and understand that this
is for entertainment purposes only, we may begin."
"What's your name, hun?"
Lisa.
"Your initial reading is 100% free."
"After that I charge only $19.95 for ten minutes."
"A seance experience is $50."
"For years I have successfully and
comfortably helped others contact DPs."
I'm sorry, DPs?
Dead people.
Oh.
How old are you?
21.
And the psychic state you're calling from?
New Jersey.
Place your right hand on the cam.
Mm hm.
Thank you.
You're a very deep and sensitive young lady.
However you're stubborn.
You don't have a lot of patience for people, do you?
Something happened to you recently. Something disturbing.
Did it have to do with a family member?
Woah.
That's weird.
Somebody's trying to make contact.
What?
There's something he wishes Rebecca to know?
I can't hear you.
You're very receptive.
How'd you know my name?
There's much more to tell.
I accept Visa, Mastercard, Discover.
Nah, pretty cool, though.
Please feel free to visit me on
my website veramadeline.com.
God bless.
Oh my god!
You have to go to this freak.
I can't even explain to you. I don't
know how to describe it. Just go.
Really?
She's got the candles burning in
the background and this hokey music.
You have to go.
But did she read you?
Pretty lame. She said I was,
um, stubborn and intelligent.
Huh.
Please, they just say stuff that applies to anyone.
Although, this was weird.
I didn't want to tell her my name because,
you know, so...
...I just told her it was Lisa. But
then later she called me Rebecca.
Unless...
What?
People can use their caller IDs with this, huh?
What a joke!
So what's her place like?
Trust me. You'll see.
She's got that whole cliche going. Don't worry.
She make, uh, contact with anybody?
Yeah, some DP said something
in another language. Kinda lost me.
Dead person.
I don't know how she keeps a straight face.
Sounds like she takes herself a little too seriously.
So you didn't do the whole seance thing?
Yeah right. Like I've got
an extra $50 laying around.
Pretty steep. Pretty sure she's
got the car payment to make.
Ok. My turn.
Kay. Good luck. Call me back.
"Welcome to my paranormal realm. Where psychic
secrets and desires are revealed."
"My name is Vera Madeline. I am a clairvoyant medium."
"I offer spiritual guidance and knowledge."
"I am a very positive, honest person."
"I never knowingly will cause you anxiety."
- Better not.
- "If you are open and believe anything is possible."
- Just kidding.
"Do you certify that you are at least
18 years of age or older?"
"Then if you are comfortable and understand that this is for
entertainment purposes only, we may begin."
"What's your name, hun?"
John.
"Your initial reading is 100% free."
"After that I charge only $19.95 for ten minutes."
"A seance experience is $50."
"For years I have successfully and comfortably helped others
contact dead people."
-Dead people.
Have I helped you before?
Couple buddies of mine have been to you recently.
Oh, a referral.
How old are you?
26.
And the psychic state you're calling from?
Virginia.
Place your right hand on the cam.
Hmm.
Thank you.
You're a very deep and sincere young man.
Passionate.
Strong.
However, you're indecisive and gullible.
There's a change going on in the workplace right
now, and you're not quite sure what to do next.
No, I love what I do.
I'm getting a hospital.
There's someone in your life who you desire and yet...
...You're not sure if the feeling is mutual.
- Wait, is this because that this individual...
-...This individual move out of your psychic state?
How did you know that?
This individual, they just called you.
I get hundreds of calls.
This was a couple of minutes ago.
This, uh...
This referral.
What was the name?
Rebecca.
From Jersey.
Where in Jersey does she live?
I don't think I want to give that information out over this.
No, not the address, the city.
Quickly.
Why?
Quickly!
Collingswood.
Fear is very well known to mediums and psychics.
There is darkness.
The town has not recovered from it.
Hey. You're starting to lose me here, I don't...
Umm... was there supposed to be
a translation or subtitles with that?
Too many people are blinded by the truth.
They suffer. They die.
I have a message for your friend.
What?
She must call me.
I am compelled by forces you know nothing of.
Beck's kind of a starving student.
I don't know if she would, uh...
I will not charge her.
She really doesn't believe in this stuff.
- Why don't you tell me, and then I'll tell her.
- No.
- Then you open yourself up to...
- I think I can handle it. I'm pretty solid.
No. You can't.
No. I can.
Look, why don't you just tell me, alright? I wanna know.
Please. I'll pay you.
Tell her what I know.
What?
There are rumors...
...Of a secret society.
An underground cult.
It's founding member was Alan Tashi.
He lived in Collingswood.
In the mid-1800s, I'm not sure when.
The neighbors discovered
the bodies of 9 girls in a well.
On his property.
Their eyes had been carved out and their
mouths had been cut from ear to ear.
Giving them a grotesque smile.
When the townspeople found out about it they surrounded
his house, but he had barricaded himself inside.
They knocked the doors down and they searched all
the rooms, but they couldn't find him anywhere.
They did find one thing, though. Up in the attic.
If I remember correctly it was a child's toy.
A stick of wood.
With a tin face on it.
A Halloween shaker.
Left by Alan Tashi.
This really happened in Collingswood, NJ?
Is the house still there? I mean,
do you know where it's at?
Lee's Lane.
The house is on Lee's Lane.
What does this got to do with my friend?
Maybe nothing. I offer guidance
and I am compelled to tell you.
It still exists.
This all kind of sounds out there.
The truth usually is.
I could go on, but...
But what?
Just tell her.
Hey. What did you think of Madame Vera?
What? Didn't have a good reading?
She's hokey like you said.
But, then it kinda got...
She went on about this stuff
that happened in Collingswood.
What?
She wanted you to call her.
Why?
She said you were receptive.
She probably says that about everyone.
You didn't give her this number, did you?
No.
Good, because I don't want anyone
else we call on this to have it.
She just wants me to call her
so that I can pay her to do that.
She said she wouldn't charge you.
It's a come on. It has to be. I mean...
She says she won't charge and then
you call and then she starts a story.
And then you get hooked and
then she won't finish until you pay.
Ok, what?
Tell me. I know you want to.
Beck, weird shit, about a secret society.
What?
She said it was an underground thing.
There's this house in Collingswood
where all these bodies were found.
She knew the name of the street and everything.
Which was?
I wrote it down.
Lee's Lane. Is there a Lee's Lane?
K, are you trying to freak me
out? Cuz it's not gonna work.
Is there?
Mm hmm.
How does she know that?
Like she just didn't happen to have a map of
Collingswood there and pulled Lee's Lane off of it.
Or she's trying to freak you out
because Halloween's in what, two days?
You know it takes a lot for me to get freaked.
The bodies were stuffed inside a well.
Where's Lee's Lane?
I don't know. I might have passed
it on the way to school today.
I have to find out for sure.
Maybe you should.
Why?
So I can take a picture in front of the well
and send it back to all my friends in Bedford?
Its a little late to be sending out Halloween cards.
So do they know who killed them?
All those girls?
Of course it was girls.
The guy that lived in the house.
Um, Alan something.
What happened to the guy?
They never found him.
Of course. He just disappeared.
What they did find, according to
the psychic, was this old toy.
A Halloween shaker or something like that.
Look, maybe this is something she says to
anybody who calls from any town. You know?
Yeah.
Ok, look, maybe I'll look up the darker side of
Collingswood. See if there's anything on the web.
The owners did mention something about
an official Collingswood website.
Listen, I'm really gonna try and get some work done.
Yeah. Hey, I'm sorry. I don't
mean to be a bad influence.
No, it's just, I have so much to
get through before tomorrow and...
Still want to get out before it gets
too late and pick up some smokes.
- It's just gonna be a huge day tomorrow.
- Yeah, me too.
You working?
Til 6.
Ok, well I better...
Don't stay up too late.
Talk to you later. Thanks again.
Good night.
Blah, blah, blah...
Wow.
Oh my god.
Hey.
Too tired to go back out?
- Beck.
- What's up?
There's something I want to tell you about,
but I don't want to freak you out.
I think you should hear this.
John, I really don't care
what else the psychic said.
It has nothing to do with her.
It has to do with the
house you moved into.
I don't think they told you.
They?
The owners.
A family that lived there. They were murdered.
Ok, you're trying to freak me out?
Cuz the psychic didn't, right?
It's not gonna work.
Beck, I'm not.
Yeah?
What's up with you?
I looked it up on the web right after we hung up.
There was articles in the Collingswood
Post. They had a picture of the house.
I don't believe you.
This judge that lived there...
...He killed his wife and his
two kids before killing himself.
It was really fucking sick.
He knocked them out and
dragged them to the bathtub.
They were still alive.
They died from being held
under water in the bathtub.
Are you serious?
Don’t joke about kids dying, ok?
Wonder why they didn't tell me?
Because they wanted to rent it out.
Beck, it's almost exactly what
the psychic was telling me.
The judge, he was in this cult.
Beck, she was right.
It's still going on.
People need to get a life.
I'm sorry. I just thought you should know.
I'll tell ya, what a birthday.
Different, huh.
I'll say.
Well, I was kind of jazzed about
being here all by myself, but, um, now...
You know what we can do?
What?
We don't have to turn this off.
I mean, we don't have to hang up.
Leave it on all night?
God, we're gonna be like
the freaks that leave it on 24/7.
Won't that be kind of expensive?
It's on me.
This way we can, uh...
Sleep together?
Safest sex we'll ever have.
Kay.
It'll be kind of nice actually.
What time you getting up?
I'd like to get up before 8:00.
I'll wake you up.
I'm usually up around 7:00 these days.
Cool.
John?
Don't think about it.
Just get some sleep.
They found the bodies
in the bathroom upstairs?
Just get some sleep.
Be afraid of his love.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I was dreaming.
Rebecca.
Wake up.
Long time, no see.
What time is it?
10:30
Shit!
The library closes early today, John.
Thought you were gonna get me up at 8:00!
I overslept.
I gotta book.
I'm sorry about last night.
When will you be back?
I dunno.
Good one.
Hello?
Have fun last night?
Yeah, did you?
You get any?
What time is it?
Little after 11:00.
Oh, man! Why don't you let me sleep?
Hang on.
Billy.
I need you to be straight
with me about something.
That psychic you told me about. Do
you know her? I mean, where's she from?
I don't think that lady gives refunds
just cuz that's what you're hoping for.
She knew about all this stuff
that happened in Collingswood.
Where Rebecca is?
Yeah.
What things?
I know this sounds kind of...
She told me about this cult and its leader.
He was into human sacrifices.
She wanted Beck and I to
know that this cult still exists.
Sure got your $50 worth.
She never took our money.
Did you tell her to fuck with us?
Huh?
Did you?
Sounds like you're believing all this crap.
I know it sounds like a scam.
I mean, come on, man.
Until I decided to see if there was anything
backing up what the lady was saying.
Fuck!
I've been sleeping in pumpkin shit all night.
Listen.
The house Beck's renting a room in...
Four years ago this judge living there, he snapped.
He took out his whole family and then himself.
He was a member of that cult.
Maybe Vera delivers the goods after all.
Does your little Beck know?
Rebecca. I call her Beck.
K, does Rebecca know about the murder/suicide?
Yeah. I guess I should've waited, I mean...
She's all alone this weekend.
Rebecca's all alone in
that house and you told her?
Wait, wait, wait. I get it.
You thought that scaring the shit out of
Rebecca would, what, bring her back to Bedford?
There's meds for that.
Get some.
Wait.
What?
Ok, John, I'm gonna attempt to drive
and hold the cam without crashing.
Here you go! Your first video email.
Coming to you from the one
and only Collingswood cam.
Big whoop.
Ok, I'm just taking a short cut through Crow's Park.
They say it's famous.
Who knows for what, maybe the crows?
Hey, I don't want to run any of the locals over.
Smile! Fools.
Ooh, how bout that spirit, huh?
Do they get into it or what?
Smile! You're on Collingswood Cam!
Ok, I'm on Admiral Wilson Boulevard.
Rutgers-Camden! Don't miss the exit.
Ok, I'm gonna head to the library.
Hope these are all coming out. I'll see ya! Bye.
This is the place where Becca lives?
The crime scene photo. What's that thing?
What is it?
I think it's this thing the psychic described to me.
Its something left behind by the cult leader.
Man, there's nothing.
Maybe you should give that psychic a call back.
See if she can help you track it down for you again.
Man, get out. Get some fresh air. You need it.
Have fun at work.
Hey. It's me again.
I'm done for the day.
I read the same newspaper articles you did.
The judge that lived in my house,
they think he was a member of that cult.
K, how does that look?
It's the, um, park cam.
I could sit here for...
Ok, I know, I have no life.
I read conflicting things on that cult, though.
One said that it originated in France
in a province outside of Lyons.
And that's where the guy, the cult leader, was from.
What's his name?
The one that lived on Lee's Lane?
Which I still haven't been able to find.
It's gotta be around here somewhere.
You're back.
Long day. How's work?
Oh, their library.
I know. I'm basically all over the place.
Watch, they come home early and
find I've taken over their house.
Oh, look.
Hundred feet of phone cord.
Now, while you watch it live,
I can wander all through the house.
Did you get the emails?
You got a little carried away.
They take forever to download.
So, the cult started in France.
Yeah.
But, who's to say what's
credible and what's not.
I mean, I read something else and
it said that the cult was a myth.
- No way.
- There never even was one, so...
Beck, I don't see how that could be. I mean...
...There's all the articles and all the proof.
Except for that judge that lived here.
No miss there. Sicko.
How could you do that to your own kids?
It's fucked. I don't understand it.
I'm just surprised that you even
want to stay there tonight, Beck.
During the day I'm fine. It's just... at night.
But it's not like what happened
here happened six months ago.
I have to keep telling myself that.
Hey, um.
When you read the articles
in the Collingswood Post...
...Did anything catch your eye?
I mean, did you happen to see anything?
I could've swore I saw...
What?
Nothing.
It's getting to you.
Like me with that psychic.
I don't know what to tell you, Beck.
I mean, this is too weird.
Do you think she knows about what happened here?
- I mean, since the judge was supposedly a part of that cult.
- I know.
It almost makes me want to call her back
just for the hell of it and see if she does.
Who is she?
- She's a spooky broad, I'll tell you that much.
- She did want me to call her.
Maybe she'll still do that free seance
thing that she claimed she'd do.
Here's her number.
It's Saturday night, Beck!
Can't we think of anything better to do?
I'm thinking maybe we just shouldn't mess with it.
Maybe we should.
We need to know.
You're not going anywhere, are you?
Come on.
I'll call you right back.
Hey, be safe.
"Welcome to my paranormal realm where psychic
secrets and desires..."
It's me. We talked last night.
Some of the that things you said...
John and I just really want to
know what the hell is going on.
Sorry?
The underground cult that you told John about...
- It was from France wasn't it?
- I don't know what you're talking about.
The judge that lived here, in this house...
...He was a member.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Malcolm Hawks was a member
of the cult that you told John about.
I never told anyone about any...
What?
You're mistaken.
Yes, you did. Last night.
Look, would you like a reading or not?
I have other callers.
Wait a minute. Don't you know who I...?
- Mm mm.
- I'm Rebecca from Collingswood, New Jersey.
The, the receptive one.
You know who I am.
My disclaimer clearly states that
this is for entertainment purposes only.
What?
What are you saying?
It's for entertainment purposes only.
No. We took you serious!
- I can't believe this! So what was it? Some sick joke?
- Goodbye.
And God bless.
What?
Beck, what?
She didn't even remember
me or telling you about anything.
She gave me some line about her disclaimer
about it being for entertainment purposes only.
It was all a sick joke.
- Well, last night, I mean, she was really serious.
- It was all an act.
Beck, she knew about Collingswood.
Well, obviously she digs stuff up once she finds out where
the caller's calling from.
I don't know, it's kind of convincing for some act.
She's sick, John.
Why would she go to so much trouble?
I mean, what does she get out of it?
Some cheap thrill, apparently.
She's messed up.
- I don't know. It's not right.
- I'm so pissed.
Anyway...
...It's been an interesting distraction.
Otherwise I'd be pulling my hair
out with all this fucking homework.
You make a dent?
Still have all day tomorrow
what I don't finish tonight, so...
Huh...
Beck.
Hello?
They're in this book.
What?
Antique post cards, I guess.
Let me see those again.
That thing the ghost is holding. It's one of those.
Didn't Vera tell you they found one of
those in that house on Lee's Lane?
On est pas mort...
At one point during our first conversation
Vera mumbled something in French.
The cult originated in France.
I might be crazy but I think this is...
No. It can't be.
What's going on?
She needs to talk.
No.
What if... Beck, what if they're...
What if they never left this weekend?!
What if they're fucking with you?!
I don't think it's them.
Then it's Vera. I mean, it's gotta be!
John, don't call her! You can't
trust anything she says! John!
Vera!
Vera Madeline!
She's on break or she’s just not answering.
Drop it.
Beck, she's up to something. I'm
not gonna let her get away with that!
I want to forget about her.
Ok, Beck, look.
Just to be on the safe side
I think I should drive down.
Why?
I don't like the idea of you being there
alone. I'd feel a lot better if I was there.
That means you won't get up here until 4:00 am.
You really feel like driving 8 hours tonight?
I already threw some stuff in a book bag.
Look, I can get somebody to
cover for me at work tomorrow.
Look, John, I'm set.
Thanks, though.
Beck.
Do you remember the last
time you told me you were set?
We went fishing and you
got trashed on Jello shots?
You had to carry me all the way down to the car.
And you threw up all over my jacket.
Hey, I just want you to
know that I'm there for you.
I haven't eaten since this morning.
I'm really tired. So, I'm gonna
go out and get something.
Ok.
That sounds like a good idea.
Thanks, John.
Bye.
Hi, John.
Guess it's kind of pointless, but, I figure as
long as I'm out here, Might as well try to find it.
Talking about finding Lee's Lane.
Someone's been having fun.
Wooooo.
Look!
Listen, lady. What the hell are you doing to us?
You... You can not be messing
with me and my girlfriend!
- Alright? What do you think...
- They didn't know what was going on. They didn't know what was happening.
Their father put them in the bathtub.
Put their heads down in the water.
He had to do it.
It was their only escape.
It was their only escape from Alan Tashi.
Tell her to get out.
Her life depends on it.
It's so quiet.
"They're over here."
I don't think I told you this, John.
Supposedly the cult holds meetings here at night.
You have to get her out of there.
Get her out of there now.
- Wait. How come you didn't say this to Beck before.
- She's in danger. I couldn't talk then.
It was too dangerous.
What?
They practice the rites in the attic.
You don't believe me.
There are scars left behind.
You'll find them.
Look, lady, we'll be ok, alright?
I'm definitely driving to Jersey tonight.
She wants me there.
She just thinks it's too late for me to be driving.
She’s just going through
the motions. Don't you see?
She doesn't care for you anymore.
She's got him.
Lee's Lane. I found it!
It's gotta be the next one.
Oh my god!
John!
This is where Alan Tashi lived!
I wonder where the well used to be.
I'm outta here.
Oh my god!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Don't go near her.
What?
Stay away from her.
Stay away from her!
Oh, God!
Hey, it's me.
Bullseye.
Found it.
The house.
It's pretty dark. Let me know if it turns
out. I'll upload them for you in a minute.
They practice rituals in the attic.
Huh?
John, you didn't.
Tell me you...
- Why would you call her again? She's...
- She called me.
To say what?
You know what.
My, God, one minute you don't
believe her and the next minute you do?
Alright, look, Beck, be honest with
me, alright? Don't fuck with me!
Don't talk to me like that. I have
always been honest with you.
I don't need this right now.
John? What's going on here?
- What did she say?
- It's over isn't it?
Beck, she was right. You're
just going through the motions.
You believe some cheap psychic over me?
John, she gets off on
fucking with people's heads.
And you know something?
That's what it feels like
your starting to do with me.
Maybe this whole thing wasn't
such a good idea after all.
Don't let that old bitch get
to you. It's what she wants.
There's too many things that
are right on with what she said.
Too many signs, Beck. It's all proof.
You really think they had the rituals up there?
Ok.
I'll go find the attic and look around.
No, Beck! That's not what I want!
Well, then, what is it that
you want me to do? What?
Tell me.
Just get out of there!
Just for tonight! Go back tomorrow!
- Talk to you in a bit, John.
- Beck!
Ok, John. You there?
Yeah.
Took me forever to find it.
It's above the toilet in the guest bathroom.
I had to plug into a line in their bedroom.
Ok, you know what?
I believe you.
Nothing happened.
Just don't go up there.
I already lugged this
ladder in from the garage.
Beck...
...This is the bathroom
where he put his kids.
Creep me out some more, why don't you?
Be careful.
Can't even stand up in here.
Where are you? I can't see you?
The phone cord is stuck.
Hang on.
If we get disconnected, I'll call you back.
Stay by the phone.
Ok, Beck.
Hey, I'm looking...
...Not seeing any-
Can't even see it.
Beck, what is it?
I think I might've...
It's a door.
What?
Beck.
What's in there?
Hang on.
- Beck, what do you-
- Hang on.
Beck.
What's in there?
John...
What is this?
What's in that thing?
How do I know?
Maybe this is the room where they...
- Beck.
- Hang on.
Don't open that.
Now what are you doing?
I wanna check this out some more.
Just get out of there.
You've been in there long enough.
You don't think it's cool in here?
I don't know...
Hang on.
Beck!
I just, I really think you
should get out of there now.
In a minute!
Beck, what is it?
I don't know.
Oh my god!
Who could be calling?
Beck, see who it is?
- Aren't the scars enough to warn you?
- How did you get my number?
What are you still doing there?
- What do you want from us?
- Get out of the house, Rebecca. Please.
What do you want?
You're crazy, ok? Leave me alone!
I got away.
He loved me too. Look at me.
Be afraid of his love.
Be afraid of it.
He'll cut your eyes out.
Do you see what this is all about now?
Go before it's too late.
You don't know what you're talking about.
- Wait, don't hang up. Listen.
- Please, just leave me alone!
I don't understand what you're-
God...
He'll cut your eyes out!
Who was it?
- Vera?
- Everybody leave me the fuck alone!
What did she say?
I wanna get out of here.
Beck, what?
Jesus, Beck!
What the fuck is going on?!
Someone was up here.
Christ, Beck! Get out of there!
- How do I get out of here?
- What are you waiting for? Get out of there!
How do I get out of here?
I can't-
Rebecca...
Rebecca!
Rebecca.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
- I can't get out!
- Jesus, Beck! You gotta get out of there!
- Is this really happening?
- Just go!
Who is it?
Beck!
I can't see!
Where is he?
Oh my God! What the fuck is going on?!
Where is he?!
Rebecca!
Don't! Please!
Stay where I can see you!
Beck, tell him to stop!
Tell him to stop!