Okay, calm, come on.
Calm down
Who wants to see ghosts?
Who wants to see some ghosts?
Ghosts!
Okay, that's better.
First, hello, welcome.
My name is David Williams,
this is my colleague, Clare McManus.
We archivists at the National Film Archive.
Today will see a series of
films, dating from 1895 to 1905.
It is worth to note
to all who see...
in these films,
are long dead. ..
All these people,
men, women and children...
have disappeared from the face of the earth forever.
So, in a sense, is
and see real ghosts.
Well, well!
Let's watch it and see what you think
.
Thanks.
Do not worry... She'll love.
Hello!
- Hey... I'm glad to see you! How are you?
- I'm glad to see you.
This is my wife Alice.
- Hello!
- Hello! Great meeting you!
Nice to meet you finally. I'm sorry I...
I have come last.
Was... Busy...
No, no, no, no... Not at all!
So... I'm going to let them in,
look for themselves.
I'll be here waiting for you,
take all the time they need.
Okay, thank you.
Come on then!
Come; Your first.
Are you coming?
No. I'm too nervous.
You go, turn around.
- Love it!
- You Sure.
five years later
Alice...
have a message.
Have a message
Who is it?
Mom...
Dad.
Hi honey...
heard a noise and woke
and now I have to go to the bathroom.
I will.
Pa '... Are you afraid of the dark?
No. Of course not.
Why, do you?
No, but it could be something
hidden in the dark.
What?
Monster.
Good night. OK. I love you.
Good night dad, I love you.
Want to tell me
dinosaurs who can name?
Maybe tomorrow.
Can you say goodnight to Mickey
and dragon heads?
Good night!
Is he well?
Yeah, okay.
Who was the message?
Steve.
At work.
Just because you do not have a
life, thinks all...
others should be available
24 hours to be called.
Sorry. I should have turned off before.
I love you.
Good night.
What time do you start work?
What is this?
- What is this?
- Not until 10.
Okay, come on.
Have a nice day, dear.
Goodbye, I love you.
Goodbye. I love you too.
Thanks.
Come on.
Bye guys!
Bye Mommy!
Alosauro, Brontosaurus, T-Rex,
Triceratops, Stegosaurus, that's the best!
Go! God, you're getting so...
intelligent,
that's more than I can name!
Do you think you would be able to swim there?
It can not be... No...
is too deep.
Would you be able to swim there?
No...
No, it's too deep for me
too.
Billy... Billy...
Billy! Billy!
Hey, do not go there, I told you.
A girl in our school saw a ghost there.
Well, I know nothing about ghosts,
but could have rats there.
's Dirty.
Can I throw a stone
and see if a ghost comes?
Want to throw a stone?
Okay, just one.
Then we must go.
Do you have one?
Okay?
Can I throw another?
No! Come, we'll be late.
According .
'll Pick you up later.
Goodbye Dad!
Have a nice day.
hope you feel better than you look
I did not sleep much last night.
No?
Why, I feel so bad?
No worse than usual!
Anyway, I probably
I do not look much better!
I was up until 4 a. m. Displaying
Cat People and the Curse of the...
Cat People? Does passed?
I love that movie!
Yes... I was going to speak, but...
I figured you needed your beauty sleep!
Yes... Very funny.
Listen, do not want to take to lose
day job
but some movies came to the file;
Some from the file
police, could be interesting.
Yes
- Do revisarías for me?
- Claro.
Great. Thank You.
CRIME SCENE 1902
Hey... That's my way.
I had a very strange day today.
Saw a film of 1902,
our house was in it.
There was a murder here. A man...
killed his wife.
It happened in this room.
What?
I would not worry about that.
Horrible things happen in every old house.
Only these dinosaurs govern their...
Williams Looks amazing lady!
Oh! Thank you, Sophie!
This is my husband, David.
- Hello!
- Hi.
Sophie used to be the nanny of Thompson
, two doors down.
Mom, Sophie has not even heard of Stegosaurus
.
Well, not everyone knows
about dinosaurs, you know!
Okay, make yourself at home, and
sírvete any food in the kitchen.
We should get home too late.
Tomorrow. OK?
Sleep well.
Nice to meet you.
Alice!
Hello!
Alex is here. Come on.
'm Sure you remember to David, my husband.
Hello.
You, uh, Librarian?
The... Archivist.
Glad to see you again.
Also.
I'm sure you will not mind if I borrow
your lovely wife
for a few moments, that someone...
I would really like to know.
No, not at all!
I'll get a drink.
Yes, I'm fine.
Can I help you, sir?
Hey can I have another...?
Another gin and tonic?
Hello.
Sorry for that.
What was that all about?
Things work.
He wanted me to meet this customer
, but I did not.
Not tonight.
I thought he was the client.
Yes...
he is.
But he wanted me to meet another.
A colleague.
Come. Let's dance.
I'll just finish this.
I love you.
Sorry! I could not resist.
Are you okay?
- Yes
- You look pale..
No, I'm fine.
Yes?
More paler than usual, even.
I have the last 7 or 8 of those movies donated
,
aligned in the room
projection, you'd miss out?
Yes, of course.
TERRIBLE CRIME DIC. 12, 1902
♪ Twinkle, twinkle, little star, how I wonder
what you ♪
♪ On top of the world so high, like a diamond
the sky... ♪
♪ Twinkle, Twinkle, Little Star ♪
Kiss!
Goodbye child.
Goodbye mom.
Wait till your dad, Billy!
Hey, do not work late tonight.
- Come straight home.
- Why?
What?
It will not be too late, I promise.
Goodbye.
Alice!
Hello?
Dad! I'm still in school
, will you come for me
Dad, did you forget me?
I just lost track of time.
Sorry.
Adam and I were the only ones left
.
Adam said a Gowilla could beat
one Winosaurus in a fight, is it true?
No.
The master wants you
David...
want you to listen...
forgive me... No, God...
I do not want...
David please...
Please... No, no...
do not
I do not want to die
Hi, I'm Alice here, so sorry if I
I missed your call
If you want to leave your name and number
I'll be in...
contact you as soon as I
possible. Thank you
Detective McNamara.
So, when I saw him last?
Eh... Yesterday morning.
We said goodbye, do
Billy, my son, to school.
And she has been out all night
before?
No.
No, never.
Said he'd be working until
late last night, but I asked a...
coworker of Hersand and said...
Alice was about five.
Did you have an argument?
No.
Are you sure?
Yes
Have you been in touch
with family and friends?
Yes
And have not heard of it?
No.
Okay...
Hair Color?
Some of them are a bit old.
That's all I could find.
Dad...
returns when mommy?
I told you... will be in
home soon. Do not worry.
Pretty...
- Hello.
- Hi.
Is there any news?
How is Billy?
Yeah, okay.
I got to bed an hour ago.
He wanted to sleep in her room.
You know there's something black in his hands?
They took my fingerprints digital to eliminate me.
In case there is an inquiry.
Eh... I stuck
Billy in bed an hour ago.
He wanted to sleep in her room.
He's fine. All day.
We get along great!
He's a great guy, I really sympathize
.
Get to know everything about dinosaurs!
I know, yes!
Me I better go.
Yes
Thanks.
See you in the morning.
Si.
Billy... Billy! What are you looking at?
Come here...
I had a dream about Mommy.
I miss.
A man came yesterday saying
be the lover of his wife.
Says
was with her the night she disappeared.
They have been going out together for a year.
Do you know anything about that?
No.
Well, according to him,
was planning to leave.
That's impossible.
She loves me.
Has a lover, David.
He's lying!
Well, several of its
friends have supported him.
In what counts, was
love with the guy, and he with her.
Sorry.
Cursed acid reflux.
Total fucking pain in the ass.
Want one of these?
No.
I have a very weak stomach, David.
Not kill her, right?
No right to be
wondering these things.
I love, love my wife.
Never
I never do anything to hurt her.
Never.
Le asking your lover
these questions, right?
Yes
Do you ask him if he killed her?
He has an alibi.
Your boss called right as he left his house,
listened both insisting on going home alone...
and then the phone went on
for...
Over an hour, so
that is solid, man!
People always suspect the husband.
Do you know why that is?
Because it's always the husband.
Every damn time.
Is this your wife?
Is this your wife, Alice Williams?
Yes
Yes, it's my wife.
There was no evidence of foul play or assault
.
Drowned.
Must have been dropped.
Was it an accident?
Yes
Think so.
One of the heel of his shoe party
it would,
That we think could have caused his downfall.
So, the absence of any evidence to the contrary
,
we have to conclude that it was an accident
yes.
Do you agree?
Did you know she was pregnant?
Therefore entrust your body to the ground
Earth to earth
Ashes to Ashes
Dust to Dust
Sorry for your loss.
Thanks.
Nana.
She loved you.
You knew, right?
Yes?
She loved you.
More than any other thing in the world.
Yes
Oh Billy!
Billy.
Come, go with Clare, okay?
How are you?
Yeah, okay.
Children are strong.
They are stronger than most adults
even.
Of course, they do not really understand
, right?
Maybe I should take him for a while.
It might be good for him.
I think Alice would have liked that.
He should be around another woman.
A mother figure.
Sophie living with us now...
The nanny Billy...
I think it's best if
stays home with me.
Did you hear about Alex?
Alex?
Alice's boyfriend.
Apparently, he has taken
Alice's death very badly.
He is completely devastated.
Say he had to go to a hospital.
To recover.
Yes
I give a shit.
Do you understand me?
No
I could care less, I have my son.
Many people loved her.
I loved her.
I have to go.
I only say goodbye to Billy.
Been a long day.
Are you okay?
Lied.
I, uh, I lied to the police.
I know this Alex guy.
Actually
does not matter now anyway, right?
Was an accident.
The thing is...
on the night she disappeared.
I went to his house,
like that, and went after them...
and saw them in bed together.
I did nothing.
Know, I could have done,
but I did not. I just went.
Not even see me.
On the way home I felt...
so sick
just had to go to the public baths...
canal side and
vomited everywhere,
and remember,
I was feeling sick, and I looked up,
and someone
looking over the cubicle wall to me.
Was a man.
I managed to get to the
door, and just before I passed out.
Swear I saw him with his hands around her throat
,
and he was, he was trying to kill
.
He was killing her, and could not
move, could do nothing.
And then when he did not return
home the next day...
I mean, I've seen
was real... Clare...
was very real.
So you have to tell the police
.
Tell them that what
I said, do not even know,
not even know how the guy looked.
No matter, tell them anyway...
Once you tell them
followed Alice into that house, that would be it.
Okay?
They, they just, they just
thought it was me.
What are you going to do?
I have to find him first.
As I have that.
KILLS WIFE HUSBAND WIFE INFIEL
stabbed 52 TIMES WITH KITCHEN KNIFE
MURDERER'S WIFE ESCAPA, NANA KILLER
,
THEN DROWNING CHILDREN AND HERSELF, IN CHANNEL
WOMAN BODY FOUND IN THE CANAL
then beheaded nanny,
with an ax...
had the opportunity to see
old camera...
David
David!
What?
The old camera.
Eh, no, sorry.
What I do now.
Okay.
Do it in the morning.
What is this?
It's just...
Hey, just...
unsolved crimes.
The killings that occurred in the city around the canal.
I found online.
Just reviewed it.
Let's see if I can find similarities.
David.
You must take time to mourn,
not think about things like this.
I'll find something.
Yes, only
I have to keep looking, that's all.
So what are you going to get ?
- A puppy.
- A puppy
Do you know which receive
So it would not be a surprise
Dad, look what?. we did!
Go! It's great!
I hope you do not mind.
I know how busy you are.
No, of course not.
I had completely forgotten.
Daddy, pick me up, so I
put the angel on top.
Want
put the angel on top, right?
To mere above.
Okay, here we go. Are you ready?
When you want...
1-2-3... Come, stretch!
David, not
Sorry to bother you.
Was thinking we could make a real...
effort with decorations and stuff this year.
I think it would be good for Billy.
What do you think?
I could buy more lights for the stars.
And yes, I thought I could decorate
all the other rooms and stuff...
do, like, very Christmassy.
Yes
Yes That sounds a good idea..
Okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
YOUNG MOTHER
KILLS BABY IN ARSON
Mr. Williams.
Goodnight Sophie.
Want us to move?
Is not good, stay where you are.
Hello...
anybody there?
Sophie?
Sorry!
Sorry.
Sorry...
Look, can you come to my
room for a second?
Why?
Hey, just for a second.
Do not... Listen! He is very weak.
- What would that be?
- Just listen.
Do you hear?
I can not hear anything.
No, he stopped.
There's something behind there.
Maybe it's just a rat.
No, no.
It's not a rat.
I can not hear anything.
What can you hear?
Is someone whispering as if in prayer.
Maybe it's just the house next door.
I do not know...
no, no, no, the walls are very solid.
Dad, what are you doing? He slept.
Billy...
Billy, go to bed.
Okay.
's Nothing.
All is well.
Take him to bed, you do.
Come.
We have to go to bed.
I want to stay.
What does Dad?
What?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Billy, go to your room, get dressed.
You and Sophie will go from here.
I'll just wrap the belt.
That is.
Okay, I'll see you tomorrow.
I love you.
I'm not sure about this.
Sophie, sorry for this.
You're just going to have to trust me
. OK?
It's not safe here,
is not safe for you and Billy.
Everything is paid at the hotel
, they are waiting.
Okay.
Can ask all you want
room service.
'll See you tomorrow.
Thank You.
Yes
Come on... Come on...
Okay, just happens...
Okay, there...
There, you see?
Yes...
I see.
Is anyone there.
Okay, there's more...
Just wait...
And there... There...
Did you see its outline?
Hard to say,
could be just a shadow.
Oh come on, there's someone there.
Maybe. It's really hard to say.
Tell me what you think about this?
Believe what?
This is the man who killed Alice.
This is the same man who
saw on the night he was killed.
What do you mean?
I think there are ghosts in my house.
David...!
I know this sounds crazy, believe me, I know how fucking
crazy this sounds,
but I've seen things, I hear things,
is the only rational explanation.
- I do not think so!
- Yes it is!
Okay, okay,
wait until you hear this.
In the 1930s seances were carried out at home
,
people said they saw a shadow, a shadow.
Is it a coincidence, that's all.
The previous owner,
way, the Realtor...
said it was an old woman who was senile
,
but was not.
We lied.
Was a young woman who tried
burn his house while his family slept.
Now his son died in the fire,
but swore that he did not.
Like me with Alice.
Said it was the devil.
Said a man who could not see
, tried to rape her.
Said he was a demon
living behind walls.
The walls, Clare.
Stop for a moment.
Could you
think what you're saying?
Think I'm having a nervous breakdown is not it?
Well, maybe I have.
No.
- Well, maybe...
- Only these exhausted.
- Right? .
- Yes
Billy?
Sophie?
Billy can you hear me?
Dad, why do not you come to see us today
Sorry.
Wanted, simply
I did not feel very well.
Can you come and see us tomorrow
Yes
Yes, I promise.
What have you eaten?
We ate burgers, fries, ice cream and
Coca-Cola for dinner .
Go...
My belly is big, look how fat
I'm Dad
Sophie Billy does this again
in the room with you?
No, still in the shower .
Billy, I want you to move the laptop around
, okay?
Just move the laptop around for
can see the rest of the room, dale.
Please?
Keep moving...
keeps moving the laptop.
That's it. Good boy.
Keep moving a little more...
that's all...
just had to see...
room.
What is that?
Billy...
Billy!
Billy, leave the room!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Sorry, sorry.
How did you get here so fast?
Mr. Williams?
I'm not sure if
I work here anymore.
I do not know what is happening.
Y...
if it were not for Billy,
think I would go now.
Understand.
Yes, you're right, you gotta go.
I can not guarantee your safety and and...
is not sure
're around.
I do not want to leave behind Billy...
but really do not think it's right, Mr. Williams.
Maybe if you tell me what was happening
, would understand or could help.
Please Sophie,
have to leave tomorrow.
Best
sleeps here with us tonight.
'll Take the floor,
can stay in bed.
No, okay.
I'll be fine.
No. No, no, please.
You will not.
Mr. Williams, I want to talk to you
about this again in the morning.
About me bringing me, I mean.
Yes
Good night.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Come...
- No.
Let me go!
Come...
No...
- No!
- Please.
Come on, get out.
No... What are you doing!?
Just downstairs...
Let me out
Mr. ! Williams
Where is dad, who is in the house?
Do not know...
No.
Mr. Williams, let me out.
Let us leave...
Billy afraid...
've checked everywhere.
Dad!
Me and Billy...
were following someone out...
Okay, then I heard her scream.
're Trying to separate.
Did you see anyone up there?
Did you?
Let Billy!
No, no...
Billy will stay with me.
Sophie...!
Hey Billy...
Have you seen other people in the house?
Billy...
if you see someone, you know
you have to say?
Right?
Are you sure?
Where is Sophie
DEEP WATER HAZARD
STAY AWAY - She left this morning
STAY AWAY. .
- She will not back
Billy... You see that woman?
Where?
There...
's See, he's hiding in the grass?
I can not see anyone.
Are we going to see my teacher today?
No. Not today.
Billy... Billy returns.
- Go.
Back... - What?
Go... Go
hide behind the wall.
Come on...
Turn... Turn, count to 10.
Okay?
One...
two... Forward...
1...
2...
4...
10...!
Is this a game of hide and seek,
can I open my eyes now?
Clare...
David...
Are you okay?
- Hey, Billy!
- Hello!
- I need to disclose this.
- What is it?
's Nothing.
Just let me reveal,
did not take long.
You need to tell me what is first.
Please Clare, do not make me beg.
Really have to see this.
- Please.
- OK.
But it will be a couple of days though.
No. No, I have to see him today...
Well... I need him now.
Is completely full here.
Come on.
Well,
I'll get it done, I promise.
I'll bring  Even when
is done, right?
Look...
I've been thinking...
Maybe you should talk to someone?
Know, maybe...
A grief counselor or something.
Just...
think about it, okay?
I will.
If someone
walk here this evening, will see their footprints.
It Snow!
Can I continue?
Yes!
Now no one can enter without us knowing.
You like me
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
What about all the dust, Dave?
Meal is cooking.
Do not tell me?
What about all the flour,
're making a cake?
What do you want?
Dress.
You come with me.
Found a hammer in the channel,
with your fingerprints on it.
A hammer that belonged to loving your wife.
He says he was lost, the
night she disappeared.
Can you explain that?
There was a murder in my house...
in 1902.
What...?
You can check all this;
And a man killed his entire family.
You understand me...
and I think he was the one who did it.
I have evidence, I caught something on film
.
's A ghost.
We will see in a few days.
As welfare official
senior, I have...
choice but to recommend appropriate to Services...
Social and recommend that the child is taken care.
Is not that a little harsh?
Mr. Williams has just lost his wife.
Its symptoms are clearly part of a process of mourning.
Enclose nannies in closets and hearing voices...?
Behind walls, is
part of the grieving process?
It was just a nanny and
people react...
differently to the death of a loved one...
and, incidentally, is the same nanny
Mr. . Williams...
caught smoking drugs in his room, so...
No way!
Yes
Yes, we can do that.
Wait to return
psychiatrist's report...
and then we'll see what
do after that.
I will not go to a psychiatrist.
There's nothing wrong with me.
You have to.
We agreed on that.
What you were. I do not.
I will not go.
I have to go back to Billy.
Dad...
Who are these men?
Are the police.
Do not look.
Is there anybody out?
No.
Dad...
What?
Never leave me, right?
No. Of course not.
What if you die as
Mommy, what would become of me then?
Never leave you, Billy.
Never.
And always be together, you and me.
Okay?
Now, close your eyes.
REVENGE VIL
- Did you see it?
- No.
Would you...?
Do you want to see me?
I'm afraid to look for myself.
Okay.
Go watch TV, go...
David... Do you remember
call me last night?
Last night? No.
You did.
You were delirious, I hardly recognized your voice.
You were crying.
You said you wanted to tell me something about Alice.
That was not me. I have not called.
Ven. Sit.
If you hurt, if
did, maybe you should...
done with it...
I go to the police.
'll Go with you, if
want it to.
I'll tell you how good a person you are.
I'll help.
Clare, sacrificed children in this room...
do not you know?
David what are you talking about?
The blood of a baby is
more powerful, do you see?
They dragged the bodies through here...
sewers and dumped in the canal.
In the canal!
They... They thought of everything...
David, stop, stop!
Just... Look at me!
You killed Alice?
Just say
did not... Look into my eyes.
Say you did not.
Say you did not, please!
Just tell me!
Whatever you say, I think.
Whatever you say, whatever you say
thing, I believe you.
'll Believe you...
I'll believe you...
Just tell me...
just tell me...
Just look at this.
Then you'll understand.
Yes, we... We will see this.
Okay, there it is... Do not you see?
Moves...
Do you see?
David...
nothing there.
Just wait, wait... there's more.
Okay... there... there!
You see ?, there, look!
What is it there?
Moves to us, do not you see?
What is it?
- Yes... I see something...
- See it?
I see something.
I told you I'm telling the truth...
What is it?
No I'm going crazy!
You understand me...
look there!
What is it?
David...
David, turn it off!
Turn it off, what is it?
David what is it?
David, please turn it off!
Nooo!
To!
What happens then?
Not me.
We saw him enter the house with a woman,
- then we heard her screams.
- What have you done, David?
What have you done?
I did not!
Open the door, David
Mr. Williams...
David! Open the door!
Open the damn door, David
Arriba!
David
Back!
David!
To!
Stop, stop... To...
Look at me...
True, there's .
There! It moves
David...
no, there's nothing there...
No...
It is moving towards us...
Do you see
Watch
I want you to see .
- You can see it! !
- Not there is nothing
Go out there!
The master wants
Give it
- I could not help...
- You a fucking whore
David, I love you
You're a fucking bitch!
That's what you're
I did not mean for this to happen
I have to go, I have to take Billy
me. ..
No, no, David, sorry...
- Thou shalt not take Billy!
- No, no...
Fucking bitch
David...
No, David
Da...
David!
Help
Help!
David
Alice...
David...
Are you okay?
When will the first
review, then?
The next Monday.
- Does that give you enough time?
- Oh, yeah,
the house will be empty next
Fridays. I do not want to waste time.
I just want the
serious people see this house.
Course. I feel the same.
Nana, ¿I can come and bring my book
dinosaur?
Yeah, yeah... Do not delay, because we are now going
.
I have a list of appointments and
in a row next week.
Billy...
Billy, here
Is papi...
I'm here with your mother
We miss you
IS SOLD
You want to stay here us?
You want to stay with us forever
I love Billy
I love you.
Billy!
A translation of TaMaBin
fix Eurogroup_sub