THE PERFUME
OF THE LADY IN BLACK
- Good morning.
Hi, is everything okay?
Yes, pretty good.
I just have to bring it up
to temperature.
- Morning.
- Morning, Miss Hacherman.
- How's it going?
- You were right.
- This compound is positive.
- That's fine.
- It means we're almost ready.
- Yes.
Good.
Well then...
I'm going to see
how Elisabeth is doing.
How's it going?
Are you done yet?
It wasn't as easy as I thought.
Series K didn't work out too well
and I had to do it over.
This material has to be in Berlin!
It's not my fault,
I've been working all night.
I want it ready by tonight.
- Call me if you need anything.
- All right.
- Bye.
- Goodbye.
- Good morning.
- Hi.
Good morning, Mrs Lovati.
Miss Hacherman,
I figured you weren't coming anymore.
Isn't it beautiful?
I hate it here when it rains.
It's so sad.
You're right, it's a lovely day.
- Take the hose if you need it.
- All right.
- I'm sorry...
- Mr Rossetti!
I realized I was out of tea.
And our fellow tenants
are all away on vacation.
Could you help out
an old widower?
- Coffee is like poison to me!
- Of course.
I'll be right back.
Two or three spoonfuls
should be enough.
I hope this is enough.
Mozart...
What a genius!
- It reminds me...
- I don't mean to be rude...
...but I have to go out
and I'm running late.
- Maybe some other time.
- Well, thanks again.
Sorry to have troubled you.
If you need anything...
Thanks.
Goodbye.
We've changed too.
We used to eat our enemies,
now we study engineering.
Unfortunately, it's slow progress.
There's a lot of prejudice.
We have no schools
and the witchdoctor's word rules.
The witchdoctor is Africa.
And you must understand Africa
in order to judge it.
Andy, you've forgotten
Roberto works often in Africa.
I know, Elise.
But he's still a white man.
I remember
an English geologist
in Cameroon with me.
He got the idea of making enemies
with the local witchdoctor.
I heard he was found dead
in his tent after much suffering.
The autopsy revealed
short cat whiskers,
like little needles,
embedded in his stomach wall.
He had evidently ingested them
but no one knows how.
That's a rather uneventful example
of black magic.
A university professor like you
can't believe such things.
In every corner of Africa,
be it jungle,
savannahs, village,
river or even in
the skyscrapers of our modern cities,
a certain fear rides the hot winds.
An ancient fear with many names.
Black magic.
Witchcraft.
Superstitions, rites.
Mysterious deaths.
- Human sacrifice.
- Not just in Africa.
In Europe too.
It's less known,
but it does go on.
But those people aren't normal.
In our country,
there are still cults
who chose victims
without them even knowing it.
By means of potions
or evil rites,
they are driven mad then killed.
It is a challenge
thrown in the face of evil.
The victim suffers a horrible death
by an ancient sacrifice.
But such practices require
time and patience.
They are like a test
of man's mental strength
over his weaknesses.
Did I frighten you?
I was only joking.
You mustn't believe a word of it.
We no longer do such things.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- What time is it?
- 1:30 AM.
1:30?
That's funny,
I thought it was later.
Do you mind if I don't come up?
We have to get up early tomorrow.
Tomorrow's Monday.
You know I can't come.
For Christ's sake,
it's always the same story.
We've known each other four months
and you haven't missed a day of work.
All you think about
is that damn lab!
It's the third time
Andy's asked us to play tennis.
You don't want to offend him,
do you?
I just don't understand you.
It's like you're excluding me
from your life.
You know that's not true.
I just want to check on
the material going to Berlin.
To hell with the material!
You're obsessed.
It's not like you'll win
the Nobel Prize or anything.
You're so upset
over a silly tennis match.
You're right.
Do as you please.
I'll call you when I have time,
goodnight.
Miss!
Wake up, it's late.
Carlotta!
- Is it already time to go to work?
- No, it's much later.
- It's a quarter past three.
- That can't be!
It's a quarter past three.
You've had quite a sleep!
- I didn't even undress.
- It happens when you stay out late.
Why didn't your brother wake me?
We tried.
Luigi rang over and over
and we thought you were out.
Then Francesca told me
you were still in.
- I brought the newspaper.
- Thank you, you can go now.
Don't walk around barefoot,
you might cut yourself.
- The photograph fell and broke.
- I know.
I broke it.
The time is 3.31 pm.
"Music For You" continues.
You must be a witch, Francesca.
How did you know we had an argument?
I saw it from my window.
It's never happened to me,
I fell asleep like that.
Carlotta woke me up an hour ago.
You work too hard,
you should have more fun with Roberto.
You should make up.
I'll take care of it.
- Doesn't he collect butterflies?
- Yes, why?
I have an idea.
Come with me.
Gorgeous creatures!
That's nice.
Is anybody here?
- Is anybody here?
- I've never noticed this store.
Sorry, I couldn't find my glasses.
- Can I help you?
- I'd like to buy a butterfly.
- It's for a collector.
- Right.
I really like this one.
- It's pretty, isn't it?
- Yes.
- I'll take it.
- Okay.
- Can you gift wrap it?
- Of course.
Thank you.
Roberto?
Silvia!
There was a woman there watching me.
What are you talking about?
I saw her.
There is no one there.
A woman was sitting there.
No...
It's an old robe of mine.
I was expecting you,
I thought you'd be coming.
I'm afraid.
Stop acting like a child.
Kiss me.
Or don't you want to...
I love you, Roberto.
Don't serve so hard,
it's my first time!
I'm hardly a champion myself!
I'm glad you invited Francesca.
She's a smart girl.
- And Andy's hard to please.
- Silvia!
I'm worn out,
he's too good for me.
- Your turn.
- Come on, Silvia.
Just one game.
- Don't you want to play?
- No, you go on.
I'll play later
so Andy will be tired and I'll win.
Francesca deserves a nice cold drink.
It sure is hot today.
What happened?
I grabbed the racket
and something stabbed me.
That's strange,
there's a nail in the handle.
- I can't stand the sight of blood.
- Here...
I know what to do.
Silvia's hurt herself.
Don't get angry at me,
any other night...
It's not my fault.
I have a screening of
that geology documentary.
You know I'd rather be with you.
Weren't you going out
with Francesca?
Andy's asked her out to dinner.
They sure made friends fast.
I'll pick you up after work tomorrow
and we'll go out to eat.
I found a nice place
in the country.
Excellent food.
Yes.
Get some sleep.
Goodnight.
Can you give me a light?
SILVIA HACHERMAN
THIRD GRADE
Dear Daddy,
I've now passed the third grade.
I don't want any presents,
just for you to come home.
Mommy said you'll be at sea
for a long time.
Why did you leave us alone?
The man at the animal store
gave me a black cat.
He comes over
and takes us out sometimes.
But he won't take us
to the zoo.
Mommy bawled me out
because I said he scares me.
Mommy!
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
- I called Silvia but no one answered.
- She must be on her way.
- It's almost 11:00.
- Maybe she's ill.
- Someone would have answered.
- Maybe the phone's off the hook.
Good morning!
- There was a vase in the window.
- Which one?
It was pink with
a flower on it.
I'm sorry, there was no vase
like that in the window.
That's impossible,
I've seen it many times.
You must be mistaken,
I do the window myself.
Can I show you something else?
Miss!
- How do you want your steak?
- Same as usual.
Do you really have to leave?
Yes.
- I'm sorry, but I have no choice.
- Where are they sending you?
Cape Town.
There's a new layer,
I can get interesting samples.
I'll only be gone a week.
I don't want you to leave.
Stay with me tonight.
I need to be near you.
I don't want to be alone.
Mr Rossetti!
It's you, Miss Hacherman!
Just one second.
...Fifty-seven, fifty-eight,
fifty-nine, sixty!
- It's beautiful.
- Not bad.
That makes two hundred-twenty.
But the first ones
were out of focus.
You must love animals.
Just hippopotami.
Please, Miss Hacherman...
do you mind taking off
your dark glasses?
It bothers me talking to someone
when I can't see their eyes.
It's unfair
to hide such beautiful eyes.
- Don't you teach anymore?
- I quit a year ago.
I was forced into retirement.
Ever since my wife's death,
my life hasn't been the same.
I know what you mean.
I feel alone too.
How did your mother die?
I don't remember, I was very little.
I'm glad to be here with you.
It reminds me of
the happiest time of my life,
when my father
would take me to the zoo.
We used to come every Sunday
when he was home from sea.
Let's take a walk.
No, don't do that.
Turn around!
I look terrible today!
Stand still, it will be perfect.
One, due, three, four...
Luigi?
Luigi!
Good evening!
I almost forgot.
There's a package for you.
Here.
- Who's it from?
- I don't know.
My sister received it
while I was cleaning the boiler.
Carlotta left it with me
before she went out.
Wait.
I'm coming up too!
- Hello, Mrs Accardini.
- I never have any mail.
No, Chopin!
Miss Hacherman won't hurt you.
She's a friend.
Hello, Luigi.
Here we are.
You're not allergic to cats,
are you?
Do you believe a taxi driver
wouldn't let me in with the cat?
I can't understand why
people don't like animals.
- Who is it?
- It's me, Francesca.
- Hi, can I come in?
- Sure.
- No Roberto?
- He left yesterday.
- You must be lonely.
- Yes.
What a nice vase!
Is it new?
Yes.
My mother had one like it.
- Are they for me?
- Andy sent them to me.
It's odd though.
Twenty-four roses and two lilies.
Funny, isn't it?
I brought some for you,
I know you like them.
Thanks, that's so kind.
I'll put water in straight away.
I'd better run.
I still have to get dressed!
Bye!
Bye and thanks.
Silvia...
- Is my picture ready?
- I don't know what to tell you.
I can't find your picture anywhere.
I've searched the entire store.
That's impossible,
why won't you give it back?
Maybe someone else came
to pick it up.
I want my picture back!
Give it to me!
- There's no use in getting angry...
- Don't touch me!
Just a few friends,
they're all really swell.
You have to be there!
I need your help too,
you won't die without Roberto!
I'm just not in the mood tonight.
- Come on...
- I don't feel like getting ready.
Not tonight...
I'll see you tonight
and make yourself pretty.
It sends shivers up my spine,
she's very good.
I didn't think
you could do it with a photo.
Apart from two or three things,
she guessed everything.
Let's see if she's as good
with Miss Hacherman.
I'd rather not.
You go first, Francesca.
No, I've already done it
so many times
that Orchidea knows me by heart.
Sorry, I'm so tired.
- Let's not waste time.
- It's just a game, Silvia.
Don't be afraid.
Give me your hand.
Your left hand.
Yes.
You're afraid.
I feel you're afraid.
Let yourself go.
That's right.
Clear your mind.
I need an object, anything.
Something that belongs to you,
something that's yours.
- I have nothing here.
- What about that doll?
It's in your handbag.
Mr Rossetti went home to bed,
he's off to the seaside tomorrow.
He said to tell you goodnight.
Have you found it?
Let me see.
Close your eyes.
What is it?
Everything's dark now.
The boat is leaving.
Water.
Nothing but water.
The wind is coming up.
I can see a man.
Struggling against the waves.
He's shouting:
"Silvia! Silvia!"
Now I see him sinking.
Sinking to the depths.
Swallowed up by the ocean.
It's your father.
Your father.
Seaweed is wrapped around his body.
Someone's hurting him.
Why have you opened your eyes?
I know you have,
I can't read your thoughts now.
Not like that.
I want to stop this game.
You can't stop now.
It's not a game.
Close your eyes.
Now I can see
when you were little.
I see a man in your house.
It isn't your father.
You feel threatened by this man.
What is it?
Something strange,
I can't see it!
The man the little girl is afraid of
has vanished.
Now I can see your mother.
Your mother's putting out a flag.
You go up to her...
No, Silvia! Don't do it!
That man will pursue you
for the rest of your life!
Stop!
That's enough!
I hate you! I hate you!
It's later than I thought.
We'd better go,
they're waiting for us.
Who is it?
Where have you been?
I rang and rang.
You can't stay here.
Do you know what time it is?
It's late for a little girl like you.
Your hair's all wet.
- You wanted me to come, Silvia.
- Me?
- How do you know my name?
- Where's the picture?
You probably made mother angry.
You should go home.
Your parents
are probably out worrying.
There's no point in calling anyone.
Go away.
Please go away.
Go away!
It's late, I want to go to sleep.
Go away, do you hear?
It's beautiful.
- Where did you get it?
- It's mine, it's my favourite toy.
I had one just like it.
That's funny,
her arm is broken.
Like mine.
It's mine!
Where did you get it?
Give it to me!
No, you're old now.
What do you want it for, you're old!
Open up!
Mr Rossetti!
Please help me!
What's the matter?
- Make her go away, I'm afraid.
- Who?
Who's there?
A little girl...
A horrible girl, she won't go away.
- A little girl?
- Yes.
Don't worry.
I'll see what I can do.
Not there, in the living room.
There's no one here at all.
Come and see for yourself!
There's nothing to be afraid of,
no sign of a little girl.
That's not possible.
You must have had a bad dream,
because of the storm.
Look, she bit my hand.
If she did, there's no sign of it.
I guess you're right, it was a dream.
But it seemed so real.
I'm sorry I bothered you.
Don't mention it.
Don't even joke of such a thing!
You're like a daughter to me.
Get a good night's sleep
and don't worry about it.
You have a spot on your shoes.
Dear!
Another pair of shoes to clean.
My nose bleeds
when it rains.
Ever since I was a child.
You get some sleep.
- Thank you.
- Goodnight.
Kitty, kitty!
Where are you hiding?
Where have you got to?
I haven't forgotten about you.
...She was such a lovely girl!
She asked me to bring her mail up
but she wasn't answering.
- How did it happen?
- They don't know.
The poor girl must have fallen ill.
- Does her family know?
- She had none.
She told me she was all alone.
- Your sister found her?
- Yes, she was supposed to clean.
She found her in the bathroom.
It was horrible!
It must have been,
what a shock!
- Who are you talking about?
- Miss!
- It's dreadful!
- What happened?
Who could have imagined,
of course it was an accident...
Francesca is dead!
What?
- What?
- She's dead.
They found her in the bathtub.
She was completely naked.
It was awful.
She must have had
too hot of a bath.
Then felt giddy
and her heart wasn't up to it.
She was all alone, poor creature.
What a tragedy!
Miss!
There's no use!
It's locked,
they've taken her body away.
See?
I've come back early.
- Francesca's dead.
- I know.
It's scary.
I didn't know
she had a weak heart.
I'm so afraid,
all these horrible things.
It's all right.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Everything is ready.
Shall we proceed?
"Though she haunts me
phantomwise,
Alice under skies,
never seen by eyes.
Children yet, the tale to hear.
In a wonderland they lie.
Dreaming as the days go by,
dreaming as the summers die.
Ever drifting down the stream,
lingering in the golden gleam.
Life, what is it but a dream?"
Excuse me, do you have
any blackberry jam?
- Yes.
- I'll take all you've got.
All right.
Is that all you've got?
I've got other kinds
but this is all the blackberry.
Wait...
You forgot to pay.
Sorry.
Hello, sorry to bother you.
Were you sleeping?
- No, what do you want?
- Chopin is missing!
Have you seen him around?
- Seen who?
- My black cat.
He ran away last night,
he's in heat.
I couldn't bear him mating
with one of those alley cats!
Sorry, but I haven't seen him.
They've all lost their minds!
Where did you get that box?
It's mine, I had it at home.
Home?
- Where do you live?
- You know very well.
- Via Cavalier D'Arpino.
- What?
Via Cavalier D'Arpino, number 5.
I've brought you a surprise.
Why have you brought them here?
- I've come to live with you.
- No!
I'll be happy here,
you have all that blackberry jam.
Look under the bottom dress
for your surprise.
I want you to be happy too.
You shouldn't have.
I've always wanted
a black cat of my own.
We can have him stuffed
to look like he's alive.
Elisabeth, I'm fine.
I don't need anything.
Can you tell everyone
I've left,
that I'll be back in a week?
Yes.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
She said she'll be back
next week.
But she sounded strange.
Yes, he said that will be fine.
But you'll have to wait
three weeks.
That long?
Couldn't he do it quicker?
It's August and we're backed up.
I'll see what we can do.
But you'll have to leave an advance.
Sorry but we don't accept orders
without a down payment.
I have no money with me,
I left without my purse.
Can you leave your name and address?
Here.
Thanks.
What about your telephone?
We don't have one.
Can you wait a moment?
I'll be right back.
Silvia...
Little Silvia...
Silvia Hacherman.
Don't you remember me?
Yes.
You're Nicola.
Why did you write this address?
You know nobody lives there anymore.
Where are you going?
I don't need you anymore.
Strong north-westerly winds.
Partly sunny skies
except for a few
cloud formations
due to mid-Adriatic rain showers.
Have you made up your mind where?
Via Cavalier D'Arpino, number 5.
Behind the botanical gardens.
Thought you'd be safe
in your old room.
Now your mother's not here
to protect you.
Remember how pretty she was?
You ended all that...
You...
...murdering little bitch!
Remember your mother?
Impaled on the spikes
of the front gate?
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
What are you doing here?
What's your problem?
I don't want to go home.
- Nicola.
- What are you talking about?
I killed him.
- Hold me.
- Another one of your fantasies...
In there, in my old bedroom.
In your old bedroom...
There's no one at all.
Come in, there's nobody here.
See for yourself.
Where is this man?
- Why did you come to this place?
- It's my house.
Listen.
Silvia's back.
- I have to go home.
- Stop it.
That's enough of this.
- I'm taking you home.
- Don't touch me!
I'm not yours!
Hello, Silvia?
Silvia?
Answer me!
Only Silvia's good.
Everyone else is evil
and wants to hurt us.
Only Silvia's good.
Stop it!
You've got to get ready!
Don't leave me,
don't ever leave me.
No one else loves me.
Today is a big holiday.
You must look your best.
The whole city's lit up.
I'm so glad.
Now you must do what I say,
you must obey me.
Yes.
"'The Dormouse is asleep again,'
said the Mad Hatter.
And he poured hot tea on his nose.
The Dormouse
shook his head impatiently
and said without opening his eyes:
'Of course,
I was about to say so myself! '
'Have you solved the riddle? '
Said the Mad Hatter turning to Alice.
'What is the answer? '
'I haven't the faintest idea,'
replied Alice."
We can't play without the Mad Hatter!
Call Roberto.
Is this game that important?
It's a fun game.
Today is a big holiday.
I've invited some friends
and made some tea.
You were the only one missing.
Now we can start.
You'll be the Mad Hatter.
"The Dormouse is asleep again,"
said the Mad Hatter.
And he poured hot tea on his nose.
Where are you going?
Why don't you stay?
Wait for me!
Music!
Do you want to go see the band?