Could you make,
uh, a copy for us as well?
I'll have to figure out how
to do this when it's all done. I'm just...
Jean was not happy, because, boy,
was this thing expensive.
Oh, August. What shall we do?
Don't worry, Mary. He wants me.
He's coming for me and no one else.
Do you understand?
August, I'm frightened.
I know, Mary.
Art thou afraid?
Charlie's doing such a good job.
I am no more.
Yeah, I'm really surprised considering
the last-minute change, but it looks good.
Kiss me.
No, please don't.
Please don't do it, August. Please.
Do you know what they're doing
for the spring play, by any chance?
No, I have no idea. Uh...
They did a great job on the gallows.
For crimes against
the township of Bedford...
including robbery...
perjury...
adultery...
and fraternizing with a noble...
I hereby sentence you...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
August Benjamin Rutherford...
to death...
by hanging on this 29th day...
Charlie? Charlie?
- Charlie.
Oh, my God.
Grab him! Grab him!
Get a doctor!
He's not breathing! Get a doctor!
Lights up.
All right. Let's nail this, guys.
Heh, yeah.
Let's nail this, Mr. Schwendiman.
You got it.
Oh, August, you came.
Oh.
Don't worry, my love.
He's coming for... He wants me.
Project nice and loud
to the back, please.
- Come on, Reese.
- He wants me.
He's coming for me.
Is she gonna throw up?
Dost thou understand?
Thou...
Thou shall be safe here?
Oh, August...
for I am frightened.
Art thou?
Dig deep. Find those tears.
Not anymore.
Oh, what...?
Heh, dude.
August...
just give me one last kiss.
Is he gonna do it this time?
Here it is, bro.
Pucker up for that theater nerd.
- Cut.
- Oh.
- Reese.
- Yeah?
Nice job, dude.
- Pfeifer, great job.
- Thank you.
Everyone else, that was good.
God, she's obnoxious.
- A little more work on the lines, Reese.
- Yeah, you need to work on them.
You need a little bit more work
on them before tomorrow night.
- Yeah, take a moment right now.
- Oh. The play is tomorrow.
Just go over those pages again.
Wow. Jesus.
Oh, Reese,
you're breaking my poor heart.
Oh, this is good.
For those of you watching along at home,
that is why football players do not do drama.
Ryan. You're supposed
to stay in the booth.
No.
Hey, Reese.
Can I borrow your blouse? Heh.
Why, man? I need some clarity, bro.
Help me out here.
Isn't this embarrassing, dude?
Like, you're choking worse
than Charlie did.
Dude, they're gonna tear you apart
in here. Don't do it.
Don't bring the camera in.
This is more booby
than the girl locker room.
This isn't the girls'.
Who brings a camera into the men's room?
Oh, my God. Get that shit out of here.
That's disgusting.
No one wants to see that.
- My boy's gonna be a superstar.
- Yes.
- Look at those tights, Peter Pan.
- Are you serious?
- Why can't you just stay up in the booth?
- The booth camera sucks.
That's why I have my camera.
Besides, I have practice.
Come on. You could have done shop.
You could have done Home Ec.
You're wearing knickers, bro. Come on.
Reese. Knickers, dude.
- Stop walking. I'll find you, Reese.
- Hey, big shot. Get suited up. Let's go.
There's Miss Shannon.
Do you still have a husband,
Miss Shannon?
- Goodbye.
- Love you too.
And another one up.
Cassidy.
Ryan. Come on.
Cassidy. What are you doing?
Told you not to mess with this.
It's not a toy.
Don't "pfft" me.
So, what's it like being a drama techie?
- Such a bitch. Are you kidding?
- Whoa!
What? If I had known
there was a drama requirement...
I love it. I love it.
I get to hang out with the most unattractive
girls. I'm late to practice every day.
- How's drama?
- Oh, how's drama?
- How is it with all your little drama buddies?
- At least I'm not around you.
- Are you trying to defend your drama buddies?
- Well, your mom.
- Hey, big shot.
- Yes, coach?
- Practice? Hello.
- Yeah, Ryan.
Let's go, big shot.
- There they are.
- There's your buddies right there.
They're not my buddies.
Take this. Take this thing, man.
Watch this.
Oh, my God. Oh, no.
It's up. It's up.
Go get the trainer.
- Nailed it.
- Vicious.
Right in the schnoz, dude.
- Yo, David, how you doing?
- Hey, what's happening?
- Working late tonight?
- You know it.
- Time for a vacation, huh?
- You guessed that too.
And here's the 1993 cast.
Just as geeky as now.
And there he is.
Charlie Grimille.
Unbelievably morbid that they still
have a picture of him up here.
Don't forget your costume.
Chris, turn off the cell phones, please.
In the drama room as well
as the theater. That's the rule.
Turn them off or be suspended.
No cell phone, okay?
No cell phones.
All right. Now, listen up.
Eyes forward, everyone.
Tomorrow night is the show.
It's been a long process.
- Not always easy, right, Pfeifer?
- Mm-hm.
Uh, especially not with the school board,
but we got through that.
But, um, I think we're gonna do okay.
Pfeifer, you had a couple of words
you wanted to say.
- Of course she has something to say.
- Thank you, guys.
First off, I would like you guys
to take a peek at the programs.
They're done and they are identical
to the 1993 ones.
- Oh, my God. Thank God.
- So thank you, Brittany, heh.
Thank you guys so much for helping me
make this show possible.
We've worked so hard.
We've had such a great time.
I feel so proud to be
a part of The Gallows. Um...
- I just can't wait to see it finally finished.
- Me neither.
So thank you, guys.
Thank you, Pfeifer.
Our assistant director, Pfeifer Ross,
everyone. And what do we say?
- Break a leg.
- Break a leg, Reese.
Thank you, guys. Let's go.
Backstage.
- Shoos. Mr. BHS.
- What's up, my man?
Oh, look at this.
- What are you doing here?
- My favorite characters.
Peasant Number Five, Hangman.
You guys even have lines?
- I think I clap or something.
- There you go.
If Coach could see you guys now,
you'd be kicked off in a second.
- Yeah, get that camera out of here, man.
- It's a mandatory class, man.
- Thanks for bringing this stuff.
- It's like Halloween down here.
- Yeah, most definitely.
- Yeah, party cen...
What do we have here?
What is this thing?
- That's the old Hangman costume.
- Looks pretty dumb.
- Some kid told us not to touch it.
- Did a little drama nerd tell you not to touch it?
I think he told me too.
But then I didn't listen to him
because I'm such a badass.
Dan and Mark,
can I see you guys up on stage?
- Ryan.
- Yeah?
- What are you doing?
- Nothing.
- I know you don't take any of this seriously.
- I don't.
I'm sorry. No, I will.
- Okay. It's important to a lot of people.
- All right.
- So show a little respect in the theater, okay?
- Got it?
- Yeah.
Thank you.
Yeah, right.
Look at him in those khakis.
What a joke.
- I'm fine.
- What are you doing?
I don't know.
Just trying to get through this thing.
- Heh, what are you doing?
- What?
Oh, I'm Charlie. I'm dead. Oh.
Oh, I got a trick for you guys. Watch.
Watch this.
Ready?
How creepy is that?
God.
Yo, yo, yo. Dude.
Smile for the camera, man.
Oh, come on.
Look, I'm sorry about
hitting you with the football.
You were wide open. Come on.
- Can I at least help you with this stuff?
- No.
And don't touch the fly rigs.
They're dangerous.
Wow. Okay, stage boy.
August is not who he seems he is, Mary.
- To the audience, John.
- Can't you see?
He is pretending to be a noble
that he might win your love.
He should turn himself in.
He must be hanged.
August will not turn himself in.
He loves me.
But, sir, the hangman
will take Mary in his place.
His sentence is death.
- Nerd, heh.
- What shall I do?
What shall I do, Father?
Reese, come on.
- Now, Reese.
- What shall I do, Father?
- Reese.
- There he is.
- Heh, Good timing, Reese.
- Don't come out with the book.
"What shall I do?" And then you come in.
The parents of the nerds.
There they are.
And look at these guys.
Contain your excitement, gentlemen.
I don't even know
if this lady's a parent.
She's here literally every day.
Sits in the same spot.
- Wait, so you were in the old show?
- The original show.
- Like, the original?
- Yep. I was there.
What was that like?
Heh, I don't know if you ever recover
from something like this.
It was...
horrifying.
The students were upset.
The teachers were upset.
- Charlie had a girlfriend.
- A girlfriend?
Oh, I didn't really know her...
but, um, she was devastated.
I've been here and things have happened.
Lights have gone on when there was
no one in the lighting booth.
Doors have been opened and shut
and locked.
There's all kinds of stories
around here, mm-hm.
Oh, heh, no, no, no.
They're patty-caking.
He's slapping hands with another dude.
And zero hot girls.
Oh. And the queen.
Not in a million years.
I hate this class.
Hollywood. What's up, brother?
- Hey.
- What are you doing? Practicing?
- Mm-hm.
- Is it working?
Yeah, I didn't think so, heh.
It makes no sense, dude.
I mean, this is torture.
Why don't you just call out sick?
You know? Put an end to this.
I can't call out sick.
I call out sick two-,
three times a week, minimum. Just do it.
I have a responsibility
to these people. I'm the lead.
To what people?
What are you talking about?
A responsibility to these guys?
Come on.
You're just go...
Let me see.
Holy shi...
Reese? Do you like Pfeifer?
- No, Ryan. No.
- You do.
- Don't you? You like Pfeifer.
- Ryan, seriously, no, I don't.
That's why you're doing this?
- Oh, my God. Does she know?
- Ryan.
- She doesn't know.
- I don't... Ryan.
- Your boy's got this, dude.
- Stop it, Ryan.
Talk to Schwendiman.
I got this one, man, heh.
Hey, drama queen.
Hey, hey, hey. Pfeifer.
- Hey, Ryan.
- Wait a second.
Wait, wait, wait. Hold on.
I need to talk to you about Reese.
What about Reese?
He has a big-ass crush on you.
Like, he wants to be on you.
Pfeifer, please. Talk to me about Reese.
What's going on there?
Um, Reese is gonna do great.
I have complete faith in him.
He knows his lines. He's gonna be fine.
Are you kidding me? Everybody knows
he's gonna choke like Charlie did.
We don't say that name, Ryan.
I've told you that.
- It's bad luck.
- I'm sorry.
I don't get you drama nerds
and your jargon.
It's like "good luck" is bad luck.
- Breaking a leg is supposed to be a good thing?
- Exactly.
And "C'est fini"? What the hell is that?
Oh, my God. Pfeifer, back to the point.
After the show bombs,
how is it gonna affect you and Reese?
The show isn't going to bomb, Ryan, okay?
We're gonna finish the show.
- It's gonna look great.
- Ah.
C'est fi-what? You're from Nebraska.
- Ryan.
- What?
Price needs you.
Who's Price?
The stage manager.
The stage man...?
Stage boy. Yeah.
Hey there, chief.
How you doing, bud?
What can I help you with?
It's Number 28 here.
It's just a little too heavy for me.
- You can do it.
- I probably can, yes.
You just can't, ugh...
It's pretty stuck. Is it this one?
Price got some balls, dude. Ugh.
- You just need it pulled down?
- It's fine if you can't.
- Are you sure it's this one?
- It's this one.
- It's fine if you can't do it.
- I can do it.
It just needs a good pull.
That's gonna leave a mark.
Smile for the camera.
Come here, you sick...
Hey. Stage...
Hey.
Come here, boy.
No, look. Look, it was just a joke.
- We're even.
- It was a joke?
- It was not funny.
- Please don't hurt me. Okay.
- What?
- Stop, Ryan.
- Come on, Price. Come on. Ryan.
- You're lucky, boy.
Ryan, stop.
- We're even.
- No. This isn't over.
Price.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
What?
No way.
Hey, hey, Brooke.
It's Kelly.
Okay. What is up with this door?
It's broken. Everybody knows that.
No.
What?
Reese. Reese.
Dude. Dude, Reese. My man.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- What?
- Do you still wanna do this play?
Do you still wanna do this play?
Are you kidding me?
Okay. Listen. I was talking
to Pfeifer and that stupid stage boy...
and I was chasing him,
but I found this door.
I found a door over here that's unlocked.
It never locks. Always open.
What are you guys talking about?
What'd she say?
- Who?
- Pfeifer.
Oh, my God, heh, Reese.
You like Pfeifer?
Reese, this is your chance.
We break into the school tonight.
We come in through that door,
we ruin the set. Ten minutes.
- You don't have to do the play anymore.
- Heh, that's awesome.
Cassidy, please.
What do you think, Reese?
Heh, you're insane, man.
- Reese, it's a great plan.
- No.
- Why not?
- No. Ryan, this is illegal.
Why would you even want to film this?
...bail on the show. If I bail on this
show, they all hate me.
Especially Pfeifer.
And if you don't bail on the show...
you let everyone down
and they all hate you. Especially Pfeifer.
Dude, I'm done.
I'm done sugarcoating this whole thing.
You suck.
You're a terrible actor,
and you need to do something about it.
Why not do something
that's not your fault?
Tear this mother down.
They're gonna come in, they're gonna be like:
"Oh, my God. The set's broken.
What are we gonna do?"
And who's there for Pfeifer to lean on
in her time of need?
Dude, you are.
- It's a win. I'm a freaking genius.
- You're not a genius.
What time?
You're not coming, Cassidy.
- Yes, I'm coming.
- No, you're not. You're a cheerleader.
What does that have to do with anything?
You're a cheerleader
that likes to do other girl-dance stuff...
not cool, awesome, scary stuff
at the school at night.
Ah, I'll pick you up at 9.
Okay. Dude, are you in?
Do you have tools?
Yes, Reese. Yeah. Yeah, I got tools.
God, Reese.
I can't believe you like Pfeifer.
Shut up. Why did you tell her?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
All right.
Between you and me...
- Ryan?
- Mom, what are you doing?
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- What are you...?
What are you doing?
I told you I needed five minutes.
All right, baby. Stay in here.
In and out, babe. Please.
That's what she said.
Trick or treat, Housers.
This play is... Why is it so important?
You don't understand.
I don't want you doing this play.
Why do you care?
I don't wanna do football.
You should've stayed on the team.
Finish things that you start.
- You don't walk away like a flake.
- Yo. Yo, Reese.
All right, well, I gotta go.
- Damn, man.
- What?
- Rick Houser.
- Evening, Ryan.
How you doing?
Dandy. What's this?
A camera. For the play.
- Play, huh?
- Yep.
- School night, all right?
- Yeah, we're just going to Ryan's.
Don't worry, Mr. Houser.
We'll have him back by bedtime.
- What's up?
- Hi, Reese.
Yeah.
Back seat, babe.
You got it.
Reese, your dad's got a point, man.
I'm not my dad, Ryan.
I know. That would be impossible.
But you didn't need to quit the team.
Well, I quit the team.
- And I'm not getting back on the team.
- Okay.
- Can we talk for...?
- It's like watching an infant on stage.
- You're a wonderful friend.
- Okay, excuse me.
Reese, can you explain what it is about Pfeifer,
because I don't see it. I don't get it.
- I'm pretty sure you don't.
- Here's him on sta...
- Pfeifer. Pf... Pf... Pfeifer.
- Heh.
C... Can I k... Kiss you?
You almost kissed
a real girl once, right?
- Come on. Yes, I've kissed...
- I think I remember.
I've kissed plenty of girls.
She's a nice person. She really is.
- "A nice person"?
- Just talk to her for five minutes.
All right, all right.
- Here we go.
- Dude, I'm so stoked.
I cannot believe
you talked me into this.
No one's gonna believe we did this.
Can I get a "For Pfeifer" on three?
One, two, three.
For Pfeifer!
- I'm not joining in on that.
- You're a...
You're sure it's fine
to park the car there?
Yeah, dude.
It's completely fine, so relax.
Can I get some stealth, please?
Jesus, heh.
Get up, babe. Babe, get up.
- This is so stupid.
- My boy, Reese Houser.
Just lower your voice a bit.
Trading in his baby balls
for some man testes.
Moment of truth.
Do the honors.
Do it, dude. Come on.
Okay.
It opened.
- Let's go.
- Come on.
It's open.
- Where's the light switch?
- Can we find some lights?
Shit.
Find a light switch.
Yeah.
The lights aren't working?
What, is the power out or something?
I cannot see anything at all.
Just ask and you shall receive, man.
Yes.
Whoa, whoa. Hey. Slow down.
There's something I wanna do first.
- We're here to take down the set.
- I know, dude. All right? Let's just...
Come on, please.
- This place is pretty different at night, huh?
- Ryan, can we just get this done?
Yes.
Oh, heh, score.
Stage boy, man,
I told you not to mess with me.
But you did, and now
I got some good stuff up my sleeve.
I have a couple options of what I would like
you to wear at tomorrow night's play.
Here's option number one.
You know? Little booby holes in there.
Number two,
which is my personal favorite.
I hope you enjoy it as well.
Ryan, stop messing around.
- Are you finished?
- Yeah.
Okay.
There's your sign, Cassidy.
Yeah, this place
is super creepy at night.
What do you think, man?
Let's just take this thing down
and get out of here.
Copy that.
Charlie.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Come out and play.
What?
Cassidy, what the hell are you doing?
What I thought we came here to do.
That's my girl.
All right.
I wanna get something.
Yeah.
Felt good. Let me get another one.
...get this one?
Want me to get this one?
- What's up?
- Attaboy.
What is up?
- You gotta like it.
- Bring that light over here.
Will you keep it lit?
- Don't strip it, man.
- Who gives a shit? Are you gonna help me?
- One down, bro.
- Will you take something apart too?
I'm holding the light.
I'd like you to take something apart.
That way I'm not doing this...
"Help me take it apart."
The guy with no screwdriver.
Okay.
For you, sir.
Let's go, Shakespeare.
Come on, my man. Let's hear some lines.
- What?
- Now or never. Let's hear some lines.
What are you doing? Help me
take this apart. It was your idea.
August.
August?
I'm so frightened.
Just do it.
August, speak.
Please.
Don't worry, Mary. He wants me.
He's coming for me.
Oh, my God. What are you doing?
- I'm doing the line.
- Just say them better.
He wants me.
He is coming for me.
No one else.
Dost thou understand?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Thou shall be safe...
Whoa. Get down here.
- Shit, cut the light.
- Lose the tools, dude. Lose the tools.
- Did you see anyone?
- No.
- I heard it over there.
- Is it that janitor, David?
- Who?
- Who else would be in here?
What do we do?
Reese, do you see anything?
Reese.
Okay, let's go out the back.
- Now?
- Yes, right now.
Let's go.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, shit. Pfeifer?
Heh, you're kidding me.
Oh, my God.
Pfeifer.
- This is gonna be really good.
- Reese?
Oh, my gosh.
What are you guys doing here?
What are you doing here?
I saw Reese's car.
I saw your car in the parking lot.
I told you we should've parked
somewhere else.
- No kidding.
- Can I please talk to you?
Yeah. Let's just talk
over here for a second.
- Ryan, let's go.
- Alone, please.
- Ryan.
- Fine.
- Reese.
- What should I say?
- Make something up.
Ryan.
I'm just gonna leave the light
right here for you guys.
Reese, so, what's going on?
What are you guys doing here?
Well, we, uh... Heh.
Heh, what if you guys got caught?
What if it wasn't me that caught you?
- You wouldn't have been able to do the show.
- I know, I know. It's, heh...
It's stupid. I don't know what I was...
What we were thinking.
I'm sorry.
What are you guys doing here?
Uh...
You know, to, uh...
All right. We came to practice
a little bit. You know?
To go over some of the lines and stuff
because tomorrow's the show...
and I don't feel confident.
I don't wanna let you down...
Pfeifer.
I really don't.
Okay.
Promise?
Yeah.
Yeah, of course.
Okay? Okay.
Let's get out of here.
We shouldn't be here.
Let's go.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
What are we gonna do?
Oh, it's so dark.
Night vision app.
I know. I know, heh.
Hit a little snag there with drama queen
coming in and ruining the whole thing...
but Smooth McReese is gonna walk us
out of this so we can we finish this up.
Cassidy, what are you doing?
Fixing the set, babe.
I mean, we just took the set down.
What are you doing?
- But Pfeifer's here. She knows.
- She doesn't know. Look.
Reese is out there coming up
with some lame story.
Pfeifer's gonna leave.
This thing is practically taken apart.
Reese will just call us when he's done...
- and we can finish the job.
- Pfeifer knows.
I don't even have
any service on my phone.
That's weird, but what do you expect
when you're on it 24/7?
- Hey, Ryan, stop being dumb.
- I'm not being dumb.
If you wanna leave, go outside,
call Chelsea, have her come get you...
and you can leave.
But I'm staying.
God. This is so stupid.
It's not stupid, Ryan.
It's over. She knows.
You're stupid.
I told you this was gonna happen.
- I'm not stupid.
- But did I not say:
"If you decide to come, do not back out
because you get scared or..."
- I'm not backing out.
- You're clearly backing out.
Lookit. Where am I going right now?
Right to the door...
What the hell?
Funny, okay?
This thing isn't supposed to lock.
- Ryan.
- What?
- Just open the door.
- Oh, just open the...? Okay.
Let me give it another shot.
I can't unlock it.
- Pfeifer, give me that.
- Excuse me.
I can't unlock it.
- Pfeifer. Gimme that.
- Excuse me.
Is there some kind of trick
to this door, Pfeifer?
No. There's not a trick.
Why isn't it opening?
I don't know.
- What'd you do?
- He doesn't have service either.
He doesn't have it.
We shouldn't be in this situation.
- Find another door.
- What happened to this door?
I have no idea.
How does that not work?
We gotta go try something else.
That should open this door.
They're barred.
- What about the windows in the classroom?
- The classes are locked.
You guys are gonna get in trouble.
Not me.
- Let's go.
- Cassidy, we're trying to go.
Let's just get out, okay?
Yeah, I wanna get out of here.
Thank you. Do you, Ryan?
- Yes, I wanna go.
- You still wanna finish the job?
- You wanna finish it?
- Finish what?
- What do you think?
- Do not do that.
Do not what? I don't care.
We came to break the set, Pfeifer.
We came to break the set.
Reese, Ryan and I came to break the set.
- Are you serious?
- What?
- What is your problem?
- I don't have a problem. I wanna get out.
- Cassidy. Why would you say that?
- We need to get out.
Pfeifer. It was my idea, all right?
Pfeifer, please.
- Will you listen? Pfeifer.
- Pfeifer, it was my...
Will you stop talking for a second?
You've done enough.
- This play is an embarrassment.
- Shut up.
You're gonna embarrass everybody.
This needs to stop.
What?
I took that noose down.
Reese, I took that down.
You saw me take it down, man.
The stairs?
Can you guys please
stop messing with me?
We're not messing with you.
What did you guys do?
- Shut up.
- Don't tell me to shut up.
Stop, Pfeifer.
Practicing?
- You're such a liar.
- I'm sorr...
Reese, what the hell is this?
- Reese.
- I know, I know.
What do we do?
We'll go to the office.
There's a phone there.
Check this.
- Anything?
- This phone's dead. Where's the phone?
No, it's not working.
You're kidding me.
Anything that'll help us. Keys?
I don't know. Just look.
Have you found anything?
Go away. You're making everything worse.
That hurts, man. I'm sorry.
Hey, did you guys see this?
What?
What is that?
Does it open?
No. No, come on,
this is not a good idea.
Reese, we have run
into all locked doors.
Lights don't work.
Where are we?
Oh, my gosh.
Shh.
Reese, can you hear that?
What is that?
Listen.
Just open it.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Tragedy struck BHS last night...
when Charlie Grimille died
in what is now being called a freak accident.
A prop malfunctioned during the
school's presentation of The Gallows.
- Charlie...
- Shit.
Charlie...
BHS say his spirit will live on
in the theater.
It should've never ended like this.
It's just not fair.
That's that lady from the theater.
She was the girlfriend.
Grimille died playing a role
that he was never meant to play.
Charlie had originally been cast
as the hangman.
...department and created
a handmade costume.
Charlie was supposed to be the hangman.
- Charlie. What happened?
- Our leading man.
He called in sick. He called in sick.
Charlie Grimille was the understudy.
What about the hangman, though?
I guess there won't be one.
- Do it.
- Last one.
Here we go. Three, two, one.
What?
What? Do you see this?
Reese. Reese, what did you see?
Who was it?
- There's no tape in here.
- What is going on, dude?
- How do you get it back on?
- I don't know.
Help me. Come on.
- I need to look...
- Reese, hold on.
- Come with me.
- Reese, stop.
- Come on.
- Stop, Reese. Slow down.
I can't see.
- Reese, stop.
- Reese.
- Slow down.
What? Reese, what's going on?
What the hell?
- Take the camera.
- Hold it, Cassidy.
Reese, what's wrong?
What are you doing?
Reese, what?
Talk to us.
What the hell is he doing?
Reese.
Just let me see.
Can I? What is it?
I don't understand.
Who is that?
Who is...?
Reese, is that your dad?
Ryan. Guys, where's Ryan?
Ryan?
Ryan.
Reese, give me the camera back, dude.
Reese.
Guys.
Reese?
Cassidy.
Guys.
Reese.
I don't like this.
Hey, man, you here?
Janitor still here...?
Hello?
David.
What the hell?
Hello?
Shit.
No, I'll do it.
What the...?
What is that?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What...?
Shit.
Cassidy?
Cassidy.
Reese.
Okay.
What the hell?
Is this the wardrobe room?
Reese, where are you?
Damn it. Guys.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What the hell?
God.
- Ryan.
- Ryan?
- Guys! Reese!
- Hey! Ryan!
- Ryan?
- Ryan!
- Guys!
- Ryan?
- Ryan.
- Reese.
What the hell is your problem, dude?
You don't just take the light
and leave me there.
- Sorry. I needed the light.
- Tell him.
- What are you doing?
- It was my dad, dude.
Charlie was supposed to be the hangman.
My dad backed out.
That's why Charlie died.
Where the hell were you?
- Give me the camera.
- Get out, Ryan.
What, it was your dad that backed out?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
The guy that called in sick was my dad.
That's why Charlie died.
Listen.
All I want to do is get out of...
Shh.
Shh. Shh. Shh.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Cassidy.
Just come over...
Cassidy! Cassidy!
Are you okay?
- Hold on a second, all right?
- I couldn't breathe.
- It lifted me off the freaking ground.
- Move out of my way, Pfeifer. Move.
I wanna see it.
I need to get a good look at it.
- You're not seeing it, Ryan.
- I need to.
- Just breathe.
- Ryan, don't touch her.
- Get off of me! She's my girlfriend!
- Ryan, get me out of here! I am done!
- Stop. Let me just see it.
- I am done!
Ryan, you're the reason
we're freaking in here!
- Get the hell out!
- Fine, Cassidy!
And get me out!
- Figure it out yourself!
- You don't give a shit about me!
Let me see.
Reese.
Reese, dude, talk to me.
We need to figure this out.
What is happening?
- I don't know, man.
- What do you mean you don't know?
I mean, what was that with Cassidy?
The TV? What was your dad doing there?
What is that about?
- Stop it.
- What do you mean?
Cassidy's hurt
and you haven't said anything?
Are you serious?
Don't put this on me.
You're the reason we came here.
Yeah, but maybe you're the reason
all this shit's happening to us!
- Don't even do that, okay?
- Why not?
- You brought me here!
- I brought you here to help you!
You were not trying to help me.
- You came here to help yourself.
- That is not true! It was to help you!
- You're the reason this is going bad.
- We're stuck!
Why don't you tell us everything, Reese?
Like how Charlie's dead because
your dad didn't show up.
- I didn't know. He didn't tell me.
- Stop fighting.
- Come on.
- Guys, that's enough.
Guys.
Look at that.
What?
Guys...
look at the vent.
Air conditioning duct.
- It could go outside.
- It goes somewhere.
Ryan? Come on.
What, Reese? One of us has to do
something. I'm not just gonna sit around.
God, Ryan. Please.
- Hold this, Reese.
- What? All right.
- Reese, hold it.
- I got it.
Babe, relax. What are you doing?
What am I doing?
I'm getting us out of here.
- Hey, Charlie!
- Don't say that name, Ryan.
- Please, man.
- Stop.
- Don't say his name.
- Don't say his name?
Charlie, Charlie, Charlie!
Seriously, this is not funny, okay?
- What was that?
- So sick of this!
- Stop! Stop!
- Ryan!
Come on, Charlie. Show yourself.
Show me something, Charlie.
Come on!
- Ryan, please.
- Stop it!
- Stop saying the name.
- Do you not hear what's going on?
Ryan, get down right now!
Goddamn it, Ryan! Stop this!
You're being stupid!
You're gonna get yourself killed!
- Ryan, please, man!
- Stop it.
Okay.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Now, come down. Will you just
come down? Please, stop it.
Reese, I got this.
No!
Cassidy!
Ryan, you're okay. You're okay.
Talk to him.
I'm gonna go get something for you.
I'm gonna go, okay? I'll be right back.
Pfeifer? Pfeifer.
No, don't! No, no, no!
Oh, my God, his leg.
- It's okay.
- It's broken. It's broken.
Reese!
Oh, my God.
- Ryan!
- What happened?
Cassidy.
- Take this.
- Okay, I got it. I got it.
Ryan! Ryan! Ryan!
Why did you leave? I told you to stay.
Ryan! Ryan!
Ryan!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Ryan?
Ryan? Ryan, I'm so sorry.
It's okay. He's okay.
Wait here.
Ryan?
Ryan.
It's okay. He's okay.
He's fine. He's all right.
Ryan.
Ryan, are you there?
No, no, no, no.
Ryan.
- Ryan!
- Where is he?
Oh, my God.
Reese, help her!
Cassidy! Oh, my God.
Reese. Her neck, it's worse.
Cass, come on.
Gotta go, gotta go, gotta go.
Get out. Get out. Get out.
What are we gonna do, Ryan?
Wait, Cassidy.
I don't know what you want me
to do. I don't know what you want me to do.
What do you want?
I don't know what to do.
Cassidy, do something!
Please.
- I can't do anything.
- Please.
- Please, Cassidy!
- I'm so sorry.
Do something.
- I'm gonna get them.
- No, no, no!
Don't leave! Don't leave me here,
Cassidy! Please, come back!
Holy shit.
Shit.
Cassidy?
Cassidy!
Guys!
Guys.
Get out of the way!
Ryan!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Guys!
Guys, there's someone in here!
Reese! Help me, guys!
Guys, please come in here!
Help!
I'm sorry.
Please, don't. Please.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Ryan?
Ryan.
Ryan. Why?
Reese, why?
- Ryan.
- Oh, no, no, no.
Ryan!
Oh, my God. Reese.
Her neck. It's worse.
Okay, stay there.
Reese, hurry. Hurry.
God. What the hell? Come on.
That's locked.
I can get up there.
Oh, no.
Please, no, no, no. Please.
I need a light. I need a light.
Please work. Please work. Please work.
Ryan's phone.
Yes. Yes.
Okay.
- Reese, what's going on?
- I don't know. The light on the camera died.
You think it has to do with the show?
You guys tried to stop it.
Pfeifer, please.
I think I found a way out.
I need you to stay with Cassidy, okay?
Where the hell...?
Dude, no.
No.
God.
Okay.
We're getting out of here.
It can't be.
It can't be. No.
No, where is it? It was right here.
It was just right here.
What the hell is going on?
Where are you?
Don't hang up.
Don't hang up! Come on.
Oh, come on. Please, please, please.
There. Come on, open!
No. No. What?
Come on!
Come on! Come on, don't hang up, Dad.
Don't hang up.
Where's that coming from?
It's my phone. It's in the locker.
It's in the locker. My dad's calling.
We gotta get it open.
Keep ringing. Don't hang up.
Get out of the way. Get out of the way.
- Hello? Dad? Dad.
- Who is it?
Dad. Dad, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm at the school.
He wants me. He's coming for me.
No!
Why?
Why did I do this stupid play?
I'm sorry I asked you to do this.
Oh, Pfeifer. Oh, God.
I'm sorry. It's not...
Do you have your cell phone on you?
Check your cell phone.
See if you have service, okay?
God.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Cassidy.
Cassidy!
Where is she?
Come on, Pfeifer, help me, please.
Cassidy, come on.
The other battery's in.
I think we should...
Oh, my God.
Cassidy.
Wait, the fire alarm.
- Come on, we gotta pull the fire alarm.
- What if he finds us?
- Fire alarm. There's one backstage.
- Stay close behind me.
The fire alarm's right up here.
What if it doesn't work?
It's gonna work.
Okay, pull it.
Pfeif, pull it.
He's gonna find us.
We have to try.
Reese.
Okay. Oh, my God. It worked.
- We're getting out of here.
- It worked.
We're okay, we're okay.
- Oh, Reese.
- We're okay, we're okay.
We're getting out of here.
We're gonna be okay.
We're gonna make it.
We're all gonna make it.
We're gonna be fine.
We're gonna get out of here.
The firemen will be here
any second, okay?
Should we wait on stage?
No. No. No, we're gonna stay right
here, okay? They're gonna find us right here.
Reese. What's that?
Do you not see it?
I don't see anything.
I saw a shadow. I know I saw a shadow.
Pfeifer. Where? I don't see it.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Reese, I'm scared.
There's nothing there, okay?
There's nothing there. You're okay.
- Okay.
- All right?
- Oh, shit!
- Aah!
Run! Go!
Up the ladder, go, go!
Run, run, run! Go, go higher, go!
Go, go! Come on!
Go. Go, go, go.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh, shit. Shit.
Keep climbing, keep climbing,
keep climbing!
Keep climbing, go!
- No! He's coming!
- Keep going!
- Take it, take it, here. Take it.
- Reese...
- Shine the light. I need the light.
- I know!
Just close it!
- Come on.
- Give me the camera.
- Open!
- Go!
- Shit.
- Go, go, go!
Reese.
I don't wanna go any farther.
- Pfeifer, we can't stay here.
- I'm not going.
We can't stay here.
Pfeifer, we gotta move.
I don't know what's back there.
Pfeifer, listen to me.
You have got to move. Please.
Reese.
It stopped.
- I think the police may be here.
- Okay, good.
- Someone turned the alarm off.
- Let's just stay here.
- That means they're here.
- I'm not going down there.
The police are here.
We have to get downstairs.
We're gonna be okay.
- We just gotta get down, okay?
- I don't want to go.
- I'm right here. I'm right here.
- I don't want to.
They turned the alarm off.
The police are down there.
- Come on.
- I hate this.
I'm right here. I'm right here.
I'm right here.
I'm right behind.
Take my hand. I'll get in front of you.
I'll go in front.
Okay?
Stay right here with me. It's okay.
It's all right.
Okay.
Pfeifer, we gotta duck down
under the vents, okay?
Stay with me.
What...?
What the hell? What...?
Oh, no.
It's gonna be okay.
Watch your head.
Do you hear that?
Hear what?
What is that?
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Okay, it's no...
- Oh, my...!
- Oh, my God! Oh, my God! Aah!
Oh, my God.
Pfeifer, don't look. Don't look.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry, guys.
This is all my fault.
Hey.
It's okay.
No.
Hey. Hey, look at me.
Look at me.
I'm gonna get you out of here, okay?
I'm not gonna let anything
happen to you. Okay?
Let's go.
- I got it.
- You got it?
Here, give it to me. All right.
Where is everybody? Where's the police?
Damn it, it's locked.
Why is it locked?
Where is everyone?
It's open.
Reese.
Where is everyone? Why is no one here?
I don't see anybody.
There should be police here.
Okay.
We have to cross the stage.
Yeah, okay. Let's go quickly. Let's go.
We're gonna make it, Pfeif. Let's go.
We got it.
Okay. Yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
We made it.
Oh, we're okay.
Look, Pfeifer...
Pfeifer?
Help me. I can't...
Pfeifer.
- Help!
- Shit.
Where are they?
Pfeifer?
Pfeifer!
Help.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Okay. What's wrong? What's wrong?
You gotta tell me what's wrong.
- I can't breathe.
- What's wrong? Come on.
What shall we do?
Don't worry.
He wants me.
He's coming for me. No one else.
Dost thou understand?
Thou shalt be safe here.
Art thou afraid?
I am no more.
Give me one last kiss.
It's okay.
He'll let you go.
Okay.
It's okay.
Pfeif, you need to go, okay?
You're gonna be fine.
August, don't leave me.
- Hey, you don't have to do this.
- August, don't go, okay?
- You don't have to do that.
- August, for I am frightened.
Why are you saying that?
Stop calling me that. Go.
- August.
- Pfeifer, stop.
Do not leave me.
- Stop calling me that. Listen to me.
- August, please.
Pfeifer, goddamn you.
Why don't you leave?
- Why aren't you leaving?
- August, no.
Goddamn it, Pfeifer, no! No, no, no!
- Pfeifer, please stop!
- August, please don't leave me!
Please, don't go!
Stop!
Pfeifer, don't let him do this! Please!
- August!
- Stop! Don't!
- No!
- Don't let...
It's the police.
If anybody's here, identify yourself.
Kitchen clear. No sign of Pfeifer.
Pfeifer. Mrs. Ross. It's the police.
What the hell?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
1-Paul-21 . 1-Paul-81.
Suspects in the back room to the right.
Lang, do you copy?
Oh, God.
Charlie Grimille?
You shouldn't say that name.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Lang.
I need you back here.
Hold on!
Lang! No.