Subtitles by explosiveskull
We're not getting a bike,
love, not at the moment.
- But, Mum...
- But nothing.
- Please.
- I said not at the moment.
Maybe next year, okay?
Sweetie, I said
maybe next year.
Stewart Macken says our
Jeep looks like something
a fedophile would drive.
Who's Stewart Macken?
In my class.
- Is he your friend?
- He's an ass face.
Hey.
Can I say
"anus face"?
- No.
- But it's a science word.
Mum, look out!
Are you all right?
- Chris, are you all right?
- Yes.
Don't move.
Are you okay?
I didn't see you,
you came out of nowhere.
I'm Chuck, the strongest
soldier in the whole land.
And you're nothing,
buddy...
No,
please, leave me alone.
You finished?
Chris.
It's gone cold.
- Put some more cheese on it.
- I don't like that dust cheese.
Then don't put more cheese on
it, just finish it, please.
Three.
Two.
One!
Mum wins, you know
the rules.
Oh.
Mum!
What is it, sweetie?
Chris?
There's another one.
You're getting far too
big to be scared of them.
What if it comes
back inside?
She won't.
How do you know
it's a girl?
Eight legs
and no willy, see?
Why don't we just
kill it?
What's she ever
do to you?
She croached into
my personal space.
It's "encroached." And I don't
think she did it on purpose.
Dad would
kill it for me.
I'm not Dad.
Why did we move here
without him?
It's not that simple, sweetie.
Why?
It's just not, okay?
Why? You said he'd
be right behind us.
You're a liar.
- Liar!
- Chris.
- Sweetie...
Chris. Wait.
Christopher!
Chris?
Mum?
Never run off on me
like that again, okay?
I'm sorry.
Me too.
I know that
Dad makes you sad.
Love you.
I love you, too.
Mum?
What is that?
Nothing.
Come on, let's go home.
Hooray!
Are you gonna
show me that?
You should sign up.
Might be a good way
of making new friends.
Don't wanna make
new friends.
You know, when I was your
age, I moved town once, too.
I was really scared
about going to this new place
where I've never
been before.
But, when I got there, my mum
signed me up for the Brownies,
and before I knew it, I had
a whole group of new friends.
So maybe that might happen to
you if you sign up for this.
Maybe.
You'll settle in,
sweetie.
We're gonna be
happy living here.
I promise.
Well, no, he had one
of those faces, you know,
you just want to punch over and over again.
You know, like this?
You've never punched
anyone in your entire life.
I punched Tom Drum.
Why, that poor kid who always had
the mustachioed dried snot under his nose?
That's the one, yeah.
Yeah, I punched him square
in the forehead, remember?
Why?
It was years
ago, look, it doesn't matter.
But the thing is,
he gets out of his car.
And he's walking towards me and he's
screaming at me that I cut him off,
- and he's raging...
- You want a bloody degree to open this thing here.
- - That's
you folks, though, isn't it?
Ha! And when do you
planning on graduating?
Jay's a permanent student.
- I'm a lecturer.
- Assistant lecturer.
I am shaping
impressionable minds.
Sarah studied
teaching, too.
Oh, well, I only did
a year, I, uh,
had to drop out.
I got pregnant with Chris
and I took a different path.
Well, I'm glad your path
took you down here,
best employee
I ever had.
How is that junk shop
of yours anyway?
Rob, tell your
brother he's an asshole.
Ow. You're an asshole.
So what happened to the
guy who hit your car then?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. So anyway,
he comes over to the car, right?
And he puts his
hand on the bonnet.
Right, and I swear he's
not gonna budge an inch,
and he's glaring right
at me and you can see...
Sounds like
Walkie-Talkie.
Mmm-hmm.
- Who's that?
Walkie-Talkie, it's
this crazy old lady
lives up on the hills
near here.
Near the bridge
by your house.
You must have
seen her by now.
Oh, yeah, that's the one
you told me murdered a kid.
She didn't murder him.
- No?
- No.
Tell the story.
There's no story.
No, go on.
Her son James was in my class,
used to sit across from me in school.
He was really nice, friendly,
really into nature, I remember.
He used to have, um, ants in
a pencil case under his desk.
Anyway, when we were
around eighth, Noreen,
Noreen Brady
is her name,
she came bursting
into the classroom.
Out of control, screaming
insane things about him.
It took three teachers to drag
her into the principal's office
and lock her in
before the police came.
Nobody knew
what was wrong with her.
He was taken out
of school for a while and
she went away to have
her head fixed.
And then,
a few months later...
She got out,
got a car and mowed
the kid down.
No. No, that's not what
happened, it was an accident.
It was an awful
tragedy.
That poor woman.
Chris?
Sweetie?
What are you
doing down here?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Christopher?
Emergency.
Is this the police?
No, but I can
connect you to the police.
What's the emergency?
It's my son,
he's missing.
What's your address,
please?
Uh... I don't, um...
There's no number
on the house.
Tell me what
town you're in.
No, someone might've
taken him.
You're gonna have to stay calm
and tell me where you live
if you want me
to help you.
Okay?
Hello?
- Hello?
- Mummy?
Hel...
Where were you?
Chris.
- Here.
- No, you weren't.
Are you okay,
Mummy?
How long you been
in the area?
Um, just a few
weeks.
And has it only been since the
move that you felt like this?
Any history of anxiety
disorders in your family?
No.
Have you ever been
on medication before?
- No.
- And how about that scar?
May I see it, please?
That's quite the bump.
Yeah, I was in
an accident.
Not so long ago
by the look of it.
About a year ago, but it just
sometimes gets irritated.
This is
three weeks' worth.
It's not too heavy but
best to take before bed.
Check back in with me then and
we'll see how you're doing, okay?
Sweetie, dinner's ready.
You shall have
diamonds.
Sparkling eyes
of yours.
White diamonds.
- Chris.
- Mummy?
I thought you
were upstairs.
You called me.
- Must be pretty hungry.
- I'm starving.
Good morning, Mummy.
Where'd you get those?
The garden.
You know you're not supposed
to go outside on your own.
I wanted to
surprise you.
Let me see.
They're beautiful.
Thank you.
I can hear
your heart beat.
How does it sound?
Peaceful.
What are your
new friends' names?
Michael and Peter
and Sam and Stewart.
Stewart?
Stewart Macken?
I thought
you didn't like him.
I don't have
to be his friend?
No, no, making new
friends is good, remember?
It's okay, sweetie.
Stay here, okay?
Excuse me?
Can you move
off the road, please?
Mrs. Brady?
It's not your boy.
Noreen?
I'm sorry. She...
She likes to wander.
I told her to keep
to the side, but, uh,
she's not a great listener.
Des.
Sarah.
And what's that's
little man's name, eh?
I should get going.
If you ever
need anything...
Oh, thanks.
He's not your son!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Noreen!
- He's not your son!
Not your son.
Here. Come here.
- Noreen.
- Not...
I'm just gonna
stop for one minute.
Don't move a muscle,
okay?
Noreen?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
"I then
approached the woman.
"She was crouched down on the
ground in front of her house.
"I thought she was looking for
something, maybe something she had lost.
"But when I got closer, I saw that
her head was buried in the ground.
"And I tried to dig it out
"but I was...
I was terrified."
Ms. O'Neill.
Are you happy to sign this?
Ms. O'Neill?
- Ms. O'Neill?
- I'm strong.
Do you want to change anything
I've read back to you?
Morning.
Hey.
I thought I told you
to take a few days.
I know, I'm just not good
at sitting around the house.
Oh, I hear ya, why'd you
think I opened this place?
- So, how was your weekend?
- Fine.
Must've been
quite a shock.
Finding her like that.
Is it true?
The way she was?
Sorry, I don't mean
to probe, sorry.
- It's so bizarre.
- I know.
And how's Chris?
Yeah, he's fine, thanks.
Do you ever look at your
kids and not recognize them?
Yeah, twins are usually
hidden under a layer of shite
or food or both.
And as for Saiorse...
Jesus, it's all about
the eyebrows these days.
Not how they look,
but how they are.
Their personalities.
Of course.
They swing from monsters to angels
and back again in the blink of an eye.
You all right?
Yeah.
Just a funny few days.
Sarah.
Sorry for your loss.
I'm just glad
she's at peace now.
They wanted me
to put a lid on,
but she'll be
in the dark long enough.
Will you join me?
Okay.
Thanks.
James. He, uh...
lost that tooth
playing hurling.
he thought it
a badge of honor.
He's cute.
He was.
I
remember the day he was born.
Noreen said she finally understood
what life was all about.
We both did.
You? Did you get that same feeling
when your little man was born?
And what's his name? I didn't
catch it the last time we met.
Christopher.
Chris.
She didn't mean him
any harm, you know.
Why did she say
he wasn't my son?
That's what Noreen did.
Just after his eighth birthday,
Noreen started to say that
James was different.
She saw tiny, insignificant
things only a mother would notice.
It was like little pebbles
rolling down a hill, you know?
Then you blink
and it becomes a landslide.
A specialist gave some
fancy name for whatever
fuse had popped,
but putting a label on it
didn't make her any better.
She was convinced.
Of what?
That he was
an impostor.
Wasn't her son.
I suppose when
she saw your Chris,
it reminded her
of her James.
What happened to him?
He was hit by a car.
My car.
I didn't see him
dart out on the road.
Well, here I am, eh?
Maudlin as that bunch of
professional mourners
lurking out there.
I almost think it's better to
remember happier times.
Thanks for coming by.
Do you remember those beautiful
flowers you picked for me
in the garden?
Yes.
Have you been going
anywhere else?
No.
Like the forest maybe?
No, Mummy.
So, how's Chuck doing?
Haven't seen you
play with him lately.
Still your
favorite, right?
Are you sure you haven't been
going into the forest on your own?
No, Mummy.
Then how did he
get out there?
No more lies,
Christopher.
- I'm not.
- Tell me the truth.
- I am.
- I am!
Stop lying to me.
I'm not lying!
I'm sorry, Mummy.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Mummy?
Is that you?
Chris.
Where are you?
In bed, why?
Good night, Mummy.
Good night, sweetie.
And in...
And out.
And a big,
deep one.
And out.
It's not the most unusual
thing I've heard of a kid eating.
Yeah, but he usually
is petrified of them.
There's something
not right with him lately.
I can't put my finger on it,
but I know.
I just know
he's not himself.
And how
are you feeling?
Is the medication helping?
May I ask you
a personal question?
Yeah.
Chris' father,
is he around?
And that scar
on your head...
Was it actually
an accident, Sarah?
Hired me,
right there on the spot.
So, which one
of you boys can sing?
What are you doing, Mummy?
Washing.
Morning.
I finished it.
Are you hungry?
Come on.
You know I love you
very much, sweetie.
I'm sorry if I've been acting
little strange lately.
It's just that...
sometimes when
you're a grownup,
life gets
all blocked up with worry.
Then I look at you,
and I remember
what life is really all about.
Chris.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
♪ La, la,
la, la, la, la, la, la, la
♪ La, la, la, la,
la, la, la, la, la
la, la, la, la, la ♪
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Next up,
we have My class.
So please,
put your hands together
for the Rattlin' Boggers!
♪ O-ro the rattlin' bog,
the bog down in the valley-o
♪ Now in that bog
there was a hole
♪ A rare hole,
a rattlin' hole
♪ The hole in the bog,
and the bog down in the valley-
♪ O-ro the rattlin' bog,
the bog down in the valley-o
♪ Now in that hole there was a
tree, a rare tree, a rattlin' tree
♪ The tree in the hole, and the hole in
the bog and the bog down in the valley-
♪ O-ro the rattlin' bog,
the bog down in the valley-o
♪ Now on that branch
there was a limb
♪ A rare limb,
a rattlin' limb
♪ With the limb
on the branch ♪
And the branch on the tree
And the tree
in the hole
And the hole in the bog
And the bog down in...
The valley-o
Sarah.
Are you all right?
He's not my son.
Chris?
Whose son is he?
I don't know, but it's not Chris.
It's not him.
I don't know what you're...
I know I sound crazy, but if
it was yours, you would know.
Okay.
Let's go for a walk.
Sarah.
Let's get some air.
Did you see me?
Mummy?
What's wrong?
Wasn't he brilliant?
Sarah.
You okay, Ms. O'Neill?
Mummy?
I've seen myself
grow old from too many angles.
Even after 30 years,
she still
checked me every day.
Checked you for what?
That I was still me.
The mirror
always tells the truth.
That's what she'd say.
I need to
show you something.
What was wrong with James,
I think it's happening to Chris.
There was nothing
wrong with James.
Please, just look at it.
What are
you doing, Mummy?
Please.
Washing.
Why don't you stay up here
and play with your toys?
Do you see it?
That can't be my son.
Tell me you see him.
Tell me.
I'm sorry.
I can't see anything.
Noreen was right.
- No.
- He wasn't your son!
- Enough.
- Chris isn't Chris, and James wasn't James.
Enough!
Then tell me I'm wrong.
Tell me I'm crazy.
Tell me.
I can't.
Mummy?
Why did you run away
from me at school?
I wasn't feeling too good.
Do you feel better now?
Yeah. Much.
You won't run away
from me again, will you?
No.
I don't like
being left on my own.
You hungry?
I'll make your favorite.
I love you, Mummy.
I love you, too.
Dinner's ready.
Come on,
before it gets cold.
Don't you want some?
You know I don't
like the dust cheese, remember?
You know what
we haven't played in a while?
Our game.
Our favorite.
Three.
Two.
One.
You're not my son.
You're not Chris.
What's
wrong with you, Mummy?
You're not my son.
Get your
hands off me.
Don't, please!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What have you
done with him?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
It's me.
It's Momma Bear.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Chris, wake up.
Chris.
Wake up. Wake up.
Come on.
Chris, wake up.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Okay, okay.
You stay here, okay?
Mummy.
Subtitles by explosiveskull