Planning: Toshiaki Nakazawa
Producers:
Tetsuo Sasho, Hirotsugu Yoshida
Screenplay: Kikumi Yamagishi
Music: Koji Makaino, Koji Endo
Yummy! Let's eat.
My uvula!
Asshole!
Go, go, go!
Got you!
I hit it! Pochi! Fetch!
Around then I started to wonder:
What makes a happy family?
We say 'family',
but we're all individuals.
With our own dreams and problems.
It's said that nature
and nurture influence how we grow up.
With my family,
I know I'll grow up to be really cool.
- You made fun of my divorce.
- Did not.
- You did, just now.
- Did so.
- Don't push!
Grandpa was a department store
shoe salesman.
Working hard, planning his retirement.
Stop it, you two! Act your age!
Then, just like that, he was laid off.
When he was really down,
someone told him,
"They're going to build a major road.
When it's done,
tourists will flock here!"
Sold on the idea, he bought this place.
And practically forced us all
to run it as a guesthouse.
Hey!
He and Grandma Terue
met and married at work.
Sometimes, for the sake
of her husband or children,
an ordinary housewife can do
the most unexpected things.
Ouch! No wonder you're divorced.
It's not like I wanted to come here!
Shizue!
Idiot!
Before I was even born,
Mum was back with her folks.
She falls in and out of love
too easily.
Then the whole family moved here.
But Mum's still waiting for romance.
Uncle Masayuki worked
at a stock company.
It's a long story, but he was fired.
He's got a short fuse,
and goes mad sometimes.
Asshole! Jerk!
Great-grandpa, lives an easy life,
telling lies and being selfish.
I hit him! Pochi, Pochi!
Incredible!
Peak season and not even
a stray cat's come by.
We should never have done it!
Masayuki!
What are you saying?
The sky's blue.
The stars are plentiful,
the air's so pure!
I can't do it. I'm leaving.
Hey, wait.
After all the effort...
Don't say that.
Yes, coming all the way...
...to this wonderful place.
We've worked hard, expecting guests.
Someone had better show up.
You'll pick up the first
handsome guy who comes.
How dare you, you short-arse ex-con!
- Stop it!
- Goody-goody!
Stop it!
I've had it!
I bake cakes, I clean,
and still no guests.
They'll come.
I'm sure they'll come
if we keep this up.
I'm doing nothing until they come.
Masayuki! Shizue! That's enough!
They'll come. I'm sure.
It's great here.
Magnificent guesthouse.
Even got a swing.
You fixed it?
Go on, sit on it.
You have to come here to appreciate it.
The swing feels so good.
It's great. Guests are bound to come.
They'll come!
Hello there.
Welcome.
Hiking?
Some tea on the terrace?
Help!
I'm scared of the dark.
Why did you come here?
Excuse us! Excuse us!
We're on a spiritualist training trip.
Don't mind us.
Excuse us.
Spiritualists have training trips too?
I wonder.
I knew they weren't guests.
People really do come this far.
THE HAPPINESS OF THE KATAKURIS
This is the story of
one summer's events,
for the family that I love.
Kenji Sawada
Keiko Matsuzaka
Shinji Takeda
Naomi Nishida
Kiyoshiro Imawano
Tetsuro Tanba
Directed by Takashi Miike
Thank you, God.
Let's eat.
What looks good?
It's not the season for stews, is it?
Stews are great for leftovers.
If you don't like it, don't eat it.
It'll give you energy.
Full of goodness,
from all the vegetables.
That's why sumo wrestlers eat it.
What happened to the deer's body?
Its body?
Well...
One day...
...some guy with a rifle,
not Grandpa...
Bang bang bang!
...shot it and ate the body.
Did I spit some food?
A pickled plum?
Shit!
Ah, the spit.
OK, OK.
You saw it?
The body is in the wall.
Buried in the wall.
Masayuki.
It's not dead.
Well, if that's what you think,
probably not.
Now, eat some tofu, blow on it.
The other day, he took hours
to fix a hole in the wall.
Dad?
This place is everything to him.
Dad likes tofu, so leave him some.
Not you, Yurie.
So it's not dead.
That's one way to look at it.
At one Karuizawa guesthouse,
cute little animals help out
serving coffee and doing other chores.
This cute animal service
became quite famous,
and now all the rooms are booked up,
from now until next year.
It all started when
the guesthouse's owner
Mr. Sukeyoshi Honnoura
well, he got the idea...
...of cutting labour costs.
Along with his family,
he puts the farm animals to work
at his guesthouse.
Look, a bug.
The pigs thought: 'We can either work
or become sausages'.
So now they carry bags,
and serve coffee.
And that's why...
It's not coming out.
They work like mad.
The animals...
Leave it, don't change the channel.
Oh, let's see that.
Dem bones...
Isn't that actress
the same age as you, mum?
Look at the state of her.
Dem bones...
- A blackout?
- Mum.
White Lovers' Guesthouse
What are you surprised about?
You scared us to death.
Idiot!
Idiot?
Hey.
Someone's outside.
A guest.
Want a room?
Thank you.
Would you care for any dinner?
Just a beer.
We'll bring it up to your room.
Breakfast is from 7:30 to 9:00
in the dining room.
Checkout is 10:00am.
Your room is upstairs.
Hey, sir.
Some of my clothes...
Feel free to use them.
Enjoy your stay.
And when I get there,
it's a dead end.
Darkness creeps up...
in wispy shadows.
Even the slightest warmth,
leaves and deserts me,
and it hurts me.
Even the tears I cry...
dried up and emptied my heart.
At least smile when you go.
Sayonara.
Your beer, sir.
Excuse me.
Thanks.
Squid guts?
- Tomorrow...
- Yes?
If the world was to end...
Huh?
If you were to die tomorrow...
...what would you do tonight?
Huh?
Masayuki, it's your turn to mop.
Well?
I'm off.
See you.
- Take care.
- I will.
Hey, Shizue.
That really suits you.
Thank you.
As always.
Well, she likes it.
Shouldn't we wake up the guest now?
You're right.
Good morning.
Breakfast is ready.
Excuse me, sir?
Sir? Sir!
Masayuki, get the key!
Dad!
Suicide?
Is that our key?
- Oh my god
- Dad!
Should we call the police, dear?
Calm down.
Where's the will?
He brought a knife.
Why didn't he use it?
Probably too depressed.
Why?
Why did he have to die?
Why do it in our guesthouse?
Where's the will?
At least leave a will, you bastard.
A Will. A Will.
Come on. You must have a will.
Why did you have to die here?
There's something written here.
Peach?
A wallet. He had a wallet.
- Maybe there's something in it.
- His wallet!
- Not here.
- Or here.
What are you looking at me for?
We didn't say anything.
But you look at me like that.
You used to collect wallets.
That was long ago.
You think I killed him for his wallet?
No one said that.
Might as well have.
- Masayuki.
- What?
Bring some plastic sheet and rope.
Just do as I say.
We have to call the police.
Don't! Wait.
Say the police let it out that
our first guest committed suicide.
No one will ever come and stay here!
If I lose this,
I don't know what I'll do!
This is the end for me.
Just look...
Does it look like a regular suicide?
Look at it.
Masayuki.
Bring the plastic sheet and rope.
Maybe it's better
if we stop this, Masao?
I had nothing to do with it.
It has to be done. For everyone's sake.
What in the world...
are you doing?
My time will come soon too,
but I pray I don't see you lot there.
On my own, I remember,
the days when I was in love.
La la la, la vie en rose.
The colour of love.
La la la, my unruly heart,
beating fast.
La la la, just one more,
just one more time.
La la la, even though...
...it hurts.
Cast your magic spell on me.
The magic of your love.
Cast your magic love spell on me.
Yurie.
Yes?
Would you be happy,
if you had a new daddy?
A bug?
The feeling of love.
The wonderful moment that comes to all.
When god whispers...
I love you!
In the busiest moment,
a feeling of joy.
No more pain.
Just longing to hear your voice.
Desire.
All I need, are your words.
The magic of love envelops me.
When you fall in love,
everything shines brighter.
When God sings...
I love you!
These long nights I sleep alone.
At twilight, I wait for you,
it's all so delightfully...
Heartrending!
I want to hold your smiling face.
I'm so thankful I fell in love.
The magic of love envelops me.
Hello? Hello?
Are you a serviceman?
I'm with the US Navy.
To be more precise,
Britain's Royal Navy.
Really? Your Japanese is excellent.
Yes, my father was Japanese.
Are you here on duty?
Yesterday...
I took up my post in Morioka.
I wanted a break so I came here.
I'm happy to have met someone like you.
What an adorable little girl.
Your mum is beautiful.
Your husband, I envy him.
Actually, I'm single.
Dad had an affair with
a high school girl.
Yeah!
Well, just between you and me,
I'm also a British secret agent.
By order of Queen Elizabeth,
give me your mobile number.
Mobile phones don't work where I live.
Oh... I'll... I'll be here.
My name is Shizue Katakuri.
What's your name?
I almost forgot
the most important thing.
I'm Richard Sagawa.
Richard Sagawa...
Who is it?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
A few more days passed
without any arrivals.
But no one said a word.
Let's go.
Ah, this looks delicious, see.
Look, mmm, oh yes.
How are the noodles?
Masao, you have to eat something.
Delicious!
You have to eat to keep
your strength up, to be happy.
This is good. Really good.
How can it be so good?
Maybe because I'm hungry.
Maybe the dog wants some?
Hey, this is really good.
You want the fermented beans too?
You gourmet.
Pochi! Pochi!
Hey, know what this is?
Do you know what that is?
What is it, then?
Good, eh?
- Rough noodles.
- Right! You got it.
- Why?
- Well, how do dogs bark?
Ruff!
And what's he eating?
Noodles.
So, ruff noodles!
I'm done.
Huh?
Keep going.
Wow. Our first famous guest.
Wasn't he on
"Athletes' Singing Contest"?
This is your room.
We've found a really nice place.
No one will find us.
Darling.
Still suspicious?
Aren't you?
Me?
How many times has he deceived us?
He was the last one to see the guy,
when he took up the beer.
The guy's wallet is missing.
If the police came
and started investigating,
his past would come out,
it would complicate everything.
But he's such an honest, gentle soul.
You said you'd disown him,
but when he came back from jail,
you said, 'Let's all work together
for the guesthouse'.
It's only natural!
When his only son is down,
what father wouldn't
lend a helping hand?
See, you two are so alike.
He's too nice, that's why
he's popular. Just like you.
Hello, White...
Hello?
Hello, this is...
Yes? Yes?
I can hardly hear you.
Ah, well... Shizue?
Hold on a minute.
Go over there.
- Shizue?
- Oh, Richard!
Yes, it's me, Richard.
I just wanted to hear your voice.
I'm currently flying over Iraq.
- Johnnie!
- Who's Johnnie?
This call is being bounced
via the Yokota Airbase in Japan.
- Yokota?
- Look out!
Be careful! I'll be waiting.
Shizue, I love you!
Oh, me too!
Richard?
Looking at him like this,
he seems even bigger.
He's inflating.
Where's the girl?
She's disappeared.
Maybe she ran off.
P... police.
What?
We have to call the police.
There's no need.
What are you doing?
Masayuki! Sheet and rope!
We should call the police...
this won't work.
We'll never get him through the hall.
Maybe lower him down from here?
Chop him up?
What do you think?
Do you realise what you're about to do?
Let's not.
It could expose the other one.
- What?
- This isn't over!
Just do as I say.
How come we only get guests like this!
What's the deal with these dead bodies?
Listen!
We must save the guesthouse.
You're acting strangely, what...
Guesthouse, bullshit!
This place has no future.
Masayuki! Stop it.
I started this
so we could all work together.
I'm not going to let this ruin it.
You always say 'for everyone's sake'.
But your selfishness
dragged us all up here.
Don't you feel any responsibility?
I didn't drag you here.
You don't know how I feel!
If you want to leave, then go.
Masao!
Stop!
There's no going back!
Nonsense, idiot!
Masayuki! Apologise!
Asshole! I have thought about it!
We have to do this for everyone's sake!
If you're going to do it, do it fast!
Are you doing it?
This one's stiffer than he looks.
And heavier, too.
Popped Out!
It's... popped out!
What do you mean?
What are you talking about?
See?
What's going on?
Why is this happening?
Why do you all come out here to die?
What's wrong with you?
Anyone home?
This is Officer Miyake.
Hello?
Mr. Katakuri of
"White Lovers' Guesthouse"?
Coming!
You go!
I'm Officer Miyake.
Welcome...
...to our remote area.
I just came up the mountain on my bike.
Thank you.
A little one too!
- Hi.
I'm Officer Miyake.
Would you mind filling out this form?
I'll do it.
Thank you.
Er...
Yes?
- Um...
- Shizue.
Truth is...
I had a very difficult birth
with her...
Thankfully she's grown up all right.
Hurry up and fill it out.
A difficult birth, eh?
She's popped out!
A guest?
- Yes!
- No!
What was that noise?
We were just about to tidy up.
Who should do what...
Something fell over.
How many guests have you had?
Oh, maybe I shouldn't have asked.
But some people like
these quiet places.
Yeah, can't complain.
Great to see a family pulling together.
Oh, there's this too...
A wanted poster.
I'll leave it here.
Thank you.
Pochi? That's your dog?
Yes.
Well, goodbye.
Thank you, bye.
Keep it up!
This'll do.
I've never done this kind of thing.
Hey, he's massive! OK.
- Shizue!
- Yes!
Darling!
What?
It's not like he's breakable.
The poor thing.
Hello?
Are you from the guesthouse?
Yes.
Do you have any cake?
Can we get something to eat?
Yes!
Ordinary people.
Ordinary people!
Really ordinary.
Mum, Mum... where's the sugar?
In the cupboard.
OK, hold this.
Hurry! Hurry!
You've got something on your face!
That's alright, I'll eat it.
Here you go.
It's all home-made.
Here's the sugar.
Enjoy!
Under one roof and sky,
laughing and sleeping...
My dream of living together.
If you want to go, just go.
When you get lonely, just come back.
Let's live here.
Let's start here.
In this new place.
There's a big new road coming.
Will it bring happiness?
Happiness is made by all.
That's right. By the whole family.
Let's live here. Start here together.
On this road to happiness and health.
Let's live here. Start together here.
What?
Is that so?
Thank you.
Near the lake.
We look forward to it.
We've been praying for a big road.
We're jumping for joy.
Yes, thank you.
Don't do that!
What is it?
That road construction.
The date isn't decided yet,
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
but they're digging
the whole lake area.
So...
We'll move them.
Dem bones...
Richard.
Shizue,
I've thought about you every day.
What are you up to?
I was on the phone.
Someone was making an enquiry.
Welcome. I'm so happy that you're safe.
I missed you.
Are you thirsty? A drink?
Or something to eat?
I want to eat you.
Stinks of disinfectant.
White Lovers' Guesthouse
2,212 Yen!
How lucky!
After shampooing, I cut my hair.
Maybe I messed up.
We should have marked the location.
When did you make that thing?
Just now.
You planned to put it here?
Otherwise we'll forget where they are.
I thought we'd need this.
Everyone who comes by will see it.
Maybe not, then.
But then again, it is a work of art.
Uh, about here...
Well?
Over here wasn't it?
There?
Where the road will be?
Please join us.
Everyone, sing along.
I got this far
because of your smiling face.
No,
I simply followed you, ace.
Together,
how far have we come?
Before I knew it, I was happy.
That sounds snappy.
All the hardships...
Are long forgotten.
Dreams and joys...
and so much more.
But your gentle, true heart...
is my solace.
Our true gentle hearts...
...are our solace.
No promotion, no money,
all I have is my health.
Yes,
you have energy and strength.
You always...
gave me a helping hand.
Sometimes even a helping kick.
I'd be hopeless without it.
I have no regrets.
Dreams and joys...
and so much more.
But your gentle, true heart...
is my solace.
Our true gentle hearts...
are our solace.
We have to dig them out.
We have to rebury them.
Your job is so demanding.
Well...
There's something I should tell you.
My mother is in fact...
...Queen Elizabeth's youngest sister.
But they're half sisters,
so it's not officially admitted.
It's very tiring, the royal family.
The royal family!
But when I was little,
I remember being cuddled
by Aunt Elizabeth.
Diana! If only I'd been there!
She often called me for advice.
I said to Charles:
'You must treasure your wife'.
The crash happened
when I was away on duty.
So sad.
I can't forgive the paparazzi.
Mother came to Japan to study,
and fell in love with my father.
Father was a student
at Tokyo Imperial University.
That's amazing.
Not at all.
Father wanted to be a painter,
but as a doctor's son,
he had to go and study.
So that's where you get
your artistic talent.
I wanted to paint too,
but Aunt Elizabeth objected.
Oh dear.
Shizue.
I'd like to paint you.
Shizue, you are very beautiful.
Father used to say
Japanese women are wonderful.
Now I've met you, I really think so.
No Parisian girl nor Russian ballerina
is a match for a Japanese woman.
I've never met anyone like you, Shizue.
I want to go to Paris
and live there with you,
painting pictures.
It's like a dream.
I must go to England
to explain to Aunt Elizabeth.
But my funds are strictly
limited to official duties.
If I return to England...
It's so embarrassing.
If you just lend me the airfare,
I can come back rich!
But what am I saying!
Don't worry...
So that's his plan.
I'll take care.
Aren't the stars beautiful?
Ah!
Oh dear, your nose!
My nose isn't bleeding
because I'm horny.
The blood is rushing
to enhance my critical faculties.
And as I have much
more blood than a Japanese,
it surges uncontrollably.
Beyond all reason.
Uncontrollable!
Asshole!
Richard!
Our ashtray?
You cheapskate asshole!
Bastard!
Want a fight? Come on!
Hold on.
Hit an old man, would you?
Hold it.
You bastard.
You old fart.
Richard!
What? Keep out of it.
I know, it hurts, I know.
Let's forget it.
Die, old geezer.
Richard!
What?
Here, take it.
Die!
My eyes are spinning...
Grandpa!
Wow, we're so high up.
Are you OK, Grandpa?
Hey...
Stop it.
Look out!
Asshole!
Richard!
Shizue.
This will be our little secret.
OK?
Grandpa.
All men are assholes.
Mum, why did you marry Dad?
Well...
The first time your dad stayed
with me, the next morning...
he got all my shoes out of the closet
and polished them in his underwear.
At that moment I decided,
I wanted to cook for him forever.
I'm jealous.
Dad would probably eat poison
if you cooked it.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
He'd be easy to kill.
Really!
Sachiko, I'm sorry, forgive me.
Michiko, Yoshie,
I never meant to make you unhappy.
It's all my fault.
Kimiyo, Yuka, Kazue, forgive me.
Sachiko, Yuko,
Miyuki, sorry.
Shi... Shi...
Shimizu Yoko!
Is he dead?
What's wrong now?
An actor?
He's a member
of the British royal family,
and a pilot with the US Air Force.
No way.
The bastard! Look what he's holding!
Tissues from the dial-a-date club
at the station!
You think a real pilot
would carry this?
What's this?
Shochiku Film Studio Rental Costume...
He's not a foreigner?
No way.
Darling...
Not another one.
Hey, look, hey.
A wallet.
What?
See, I told you it wasn't me.
The bastard!
He stole our ashtray too.
But why did he have to die here'?
And after falling down that
gully so well too, asshole!
Yes, Officer Miyake.
Yes.
What!
A dead body?
A typhoon is approaching,
moving slowly, gaining intensity.
After midnight, the whole area...
- Here you are.
- Thank you.
The picture's gone funny.
It's the aerial.
A guest?
Maybe.
What will it be this time?
Do you have a room available?
Would you like two rooms?
Just one, the cheapest.
Thank you.
Welcome, this way please.
Please, as you are.
Don't you have a bad feeling
about this?
Excuse me.
Do you have some strong cord
I could borrow?
Cord?
I need some, if you have any.
I'll find some and bring it right up.
Please.
Maybe we should prepare ourselves
for the worst.
Yes.
This wet ground...
...really gives you back ache.
Well, Grandpa?
What?
Oh, that'll do, that's fine.
I can hear something.
A flute.
The cord.
Er...
What's the hole for?
It's for the garbage.
Hard work.
Thanks for everything.
What's this?
What are you burying him for?
Look on the bright side.
OK!
- Always be positive.
- OK!
Oh, you can look away.
Really?
You can even stop.
Go on, go on!
But always get moving again.
Even if no one is waiting for you.
- Looking good.
- Let's go.
Let's go slowly.
With chins up high.
Are we losers
looking back to the past?
Don't try too hard to forget.
In the end, it's just a memory.
Let's go together.
Take me with you!
Let's hold hands.
Man is a weak...
and lonely thing.
So until we finally close our eyes,
let's live to laugh and dance.
Where am I? Shit!
What the hell!
What is this! Damn.
Good morning!
Morning.
Shit... Shit...
What?
What is it?
Dad.
- It can't be.
- They found out?
What shall I do? What?
Look! Look at this! Shit!
Damn.
Terue, look inside.
Please.
OK.
Masao.
I shall go.
Don't be stupid.
I did it.
I'm guilty of... everything.
Too incredible!
Nobody would believe it.
Don't think about it.
Masao, you did your best.
Dad.
I shall go.
As long as you're here,
the Katakuri family will be OK.
Don't worry.
I gave up my life once during the war.
Grandpa, wait,
I'll go!
Masayuki, good for you.
Spoken like a real Japanese.
But it's times like these,
when luck's run out,
that old coots like me should go.
No, it should be me.
I suggested we bury them.
Fact is, I dragged everyone here.
I was wrong and I'm sorry.
That's not true.
That is true.
No it's not.
Yes it is.
What is happiness?
In all these years,
I've learnt just one thing.
No one should die in a way
that saddens anyone.
People should laugh at funerals:
'He did well to live this long'!
How you die
is all down to how you live.
Grandpa.
Don't worry. God's kind to fools.
Shit! They followed me! Shit!
They're all following me!
These are detectives
with the county police.
Mr Katakuri,
there's been a homicide.
Hello!
Down at the foot of the mountain
a woman was killed at a guesthouse.
We believe her lover did it,
but we lost track of him.
Had any suspicious guests lately?
This is Grandpa's.
Dad.
Could we see your guest register?
And look in the grove out back?
- Asshole!
- Asshole?
You bastard! Damn you!
It's coming! Coming!
A hit!
You bastard!
Terue!
Damn you all!
- Let her go!
- Don't move.
Shut up! Shoot, go on and shoot.
Come on! Shoot, damn you.
OK, OK, calm down.
- Darling!
- Let her go.
- Let her go!
- Don't move.
Calm down.
You killed the woman down
at the guesthouse!
You killed your wife!
Yes! Shut up, bastard!
It's Nobuko's fault. It's her fault.
Let go of her!
Darling!
Please stop.
Why did you do it?
Was it so unforgivable?
Or was it unforgivable
because you loved her?
- Shut up!
- Easy.
I killed her because I loved her.
What do you know, you bastard?
How can you understand Nobuko and me'?
Stand up!
Nobuko!
Nobuko, I'm sorry.
Hey,
did you love Nobuko that much?
Me too.
I love Terue more than
anything in the world.
I can understand your love.
So you have to understand
how I feel too.
So please let her go.
I beg you.
The woman you're holding on to
so tightly now,
isn't your wife.
She's my beloved wife.
Please understand.
I beg you.
Shut up!
OK, then take me hostage instead.
Take me instead.
Shut up!
I beg you.
Never.
Please!
I beg you.
Please.
I beg you!
Terue!
Alright.
Hey!
Let go, you asshole!
Masayuki!
Nobuko!
Mum.
Be brave!
How precious... our son is!
Masayuki.
Mum.
Are you all right?
I'm all right.
I'm right here.
Dad.
I'm sorry.
I wasn't a good son.
Nonsense.
But I'm proud to be your son.
It hurts! It hurts!
Be brave.
Sis.
You're quite a babe.
So, keep trying.
Don't die!
Masayuki!
Is that it?
- It's this big.
- This big?
- A graze?
Just a scratch!
That's good.
Hey, wait!
Where's Pochi?
Find Pochi!
Pochi!
- Where are you going?
- Darling!
- Impossible!
Masao!
Pochi.
Give me your paw.
Give Dad your paw.
Incredible.
You OK?
- Darling!
- Pochi.
Pochi, that was dose.
- Right, that's it, it's OK.
- Sorry.
Here it comes.
Everyone, stick together!
Right.
Hold hands.
Yes.
Hold my hand tight, Yurie.
- Mum, Pochi!
- Grandpa!
Everyone!
Hold hands!
Go for it, everyone!
Grandpa's gone.
There's Grandpa!
Grandpa laughed and said,
"Never give up saying 'that's life'.
Remember,
anything can happen in life".
The human race has survived
thousands and millions of years,
living bravely and tenaciously.
Darling.
He's awake.
Hey, hey.
Can you see us?
You OK?
Survived.
Thank God.
Pochi.
Wait.
Look over here.
It's beautiful.
So, let's go! Let's go!
The sun is watching with a smile.
Let's sing!
Like the birds, aim for the sky.
Let's laugh!
Leave your sadness to the wind.
Tomorrow will be fine, we're all well.
Let's laugh together, that's happiness!
Let's laugh.
Leave your sadness to the wind.
Tomorrow will be fine, we're all well.
Let's laugh together, that's happiness.
The following year,
Great-grandpa Nihei dropped dead.
Man is just one of nature's creatures
and one day mankind will probably...
...lose the game of natural selection.
But until that time,
man goes on living,
earnestly, touchingly.
That's...
...life.
Yeah!
Directed by Takashi Miike