Will.
Will. Hey. I asked if you were okay.
Sorry.
You know, we don't have to do this.
We can just go home.
I'll be fine.
God, this thing is so...
thick...
Official.
Maybe they're overcompensating.
It's kind of hard to call everybody up
out of the blue after two years.
- Nobody's seen her?
- I ran into her and David at a supermarket,
and a little bit after that,
I heard they disappeared.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
And they met in the grief group?
While we were still married.
Yeah, I guess you could have
put odds on our divorce.
- No, people don't think like that.
- Yes, they do.
- No, they don't.
- Yes, they...
Oh, my God.
- Jesus.
- What was that?
A coyote, I think.
Just stay here.
Oh, man.
You should go back in the car.
Okay, okay.
Oh, my God.
Jesus.
This was your house?
A lot of money in Eden's family.
Wasn't ever mine.
Come on, Ty.
Dinner's ready.
Hey, you're here.
Fucking A. I win, see? Hi!
- Was there a betting pool?
- For entertainment purposes only.
- Hey.
- Hey, buddy.
- I am Gina. We met at their...
- Yes.
- Nice to see you.
- Good to see you.
Kira, you look so fucking hot right now.
Will you bear a child for us, right now?
- We're not kidding.
- And, you...
I see you've almost shed that dirty
dishrag look that's so concerning.
- What? I have a dirty dishrag look?
- Less so now.
- It's just...
- What? Come on.
How are you?
- Is this Kira?
- That's me.
- Hi. I'm Claire.
- Hi. Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you, too.
- Hey, Will.
I'm Ben. Remember me? We drove
a thriving business into the ground together.
Never thrived.
It was thriving like a motherfucker
for three months, and you know it.
Hey, wait. Where's Choi?
Late as usual, and I can't get
any reception up here either.
- Is Eden and...
- I'm here.
Let me look at you, Will.
- I missed you.
- Me too.
House doesn't look
very different, does it?
No, not... not really.
Well, we're glad you're here.
You're a mess.
And you must be Kira.
Hi. Thank you for having me.
Will, you remember David.
Of course. Sure.
Will, come here. Hey.
I'm so glad you're here.
I'm really glad, man.
Hey, how are you?
Oh, I'm brilliant. I mean,
we've got a lot to talk about,
so much to celebrate tonight.
- Kira.
- Yes.
Okay.
Beautiful.
- What can I get you to drink?
- No, I'm good.
I'd go with the wine.
It's an '85 Rothschild.
- Are you shitting me?
- Okay, what does that mean?
- Oh, Will, you're adorable.
- It's, like, $8 million a bottle, cro-mag.
Well, this night is special.
We shouldn't save these things.
We shouldn't put off enjoying...
what we have.
- You sure?
- I'm good.
Yes. Thank you.
- Well, since everybody's here...
- Except Choi.
- Oh, fucking Choi, man.
- All right.
Except Choi, but, you know, I guess
we'll just have to start without him.
First of all, welcome to our
little reunion of sorts.
You guys are all very special to Eden,
which means you're very special to me,
and we really missed you, and we love you.
You know, each and every one
of us is on a journey,
and we feel that it's important...
We want to open up the house again,
give it and us a new start, so...
Let's raise this ridiculously
expensive glass of wine
- to new beginnings.
- Yeah.
- To new beginnings.
- Cheers.
Salud.
Hey! Save a glass for me.
This is Sadie. Sadie, meet my friends.
- Hey.
- Hi.
So...
How do you guys know each other?
Just friends in common, I guess.
We met in Mexico.
Sadie's staying here with us
and helping us out.
Yeah. It's fun. We have fun.
Hope you don't mind me crashing
the party. It's awesome.
They've told me so much about you.
- We hit a coyote on the way up here.
- What?
It just came out of nowhere.
I mean, there was nothing we could do.
It was in horrible shape.
He had to kill it.
What? How did you not
tell us this, like, immediately?
You killed it with, like, what?
- Tire iron.
- Oh, God. What?
I don't know how you did it, man.
That's pretty butch.
No, it was a good thing. That was mercy.
Would you mind
if I looked around for a little bit?
Of course not.
Thank you.
See you in a bit.
Can't believe it.
A tire iron requires a lot of...
No, you don't. No, you don't.
No, you don't. No. No. No!
Will.
Jesus.
Sorry. You scared me.
No harm done.
You're so handsome tonight.
You're shining.
And, Kira,
you're both really beautiful.
Thank you.
Could you help me
get those glasses, please?
Bars on windows are new.
Well, I was here alone for a while.
It's security, safer.
It's nice.
Thank you. We got them in Mexico.
Is that where you've been
for the last two years?
Some of the time.
Did you worry about me?
Did you think about me?
Yeah.
I did.
Well, I'm fantastic.
I've never been better.
You don't have to worry about me anymore.
You don't find it hard
to be in this house again?
No, not at all. It doesn't have to be.
That's what's so incredible.
- You look different, Edie.
- I am different.
I'm free. All that useless pain...
it's gone.
It's something anyone can have, Will,
and I want you to have it, too.
Eden looks hot. I can say that, right?
We're all consenting adults.
- It's good to see you again, Ben.
- You, too.
It's been way too long.
I'm just here for the food.
What were you guys talking about?
Not my business.
I was just telling Will
that pain is optional.
It is? Why didn't anyone
tell me that before now?
I know. But it's actually really simple.
All those negative emotions,
grief, anger, depression,
is all just chemical reactions.
It's entirely physical,
and it's completely changeable.
Kind of sound like a pamphlet there, Eden.
You can actually expel
those emotions from your body
and live the life you want to live.
So you're shitting out your pain?
I can see you're not interested.
I'm sorry, Eden.
It just sounds fucking crazy.
Eden, what the fuck?
Until you stop making a joke out of
everything, you'll never learn a thing.
That's why nobody cares what you think.
Yeah. Okay.
She fucking gored me, man.
That was loud.
- Oh, it's not...
- For the vegetarians.
- Has she been acting like this all night?
- Yeah. David, too.
Look, I'm all for whatever
you gotta do to get by,
especially you two, with what you went
through, but you didn't lose your mind.
Oh, I didn't?
Not like that.
How are you?
I don't know.
I don't really know how to act.
Well, it's not like the good old days
anymore, you know.
No. No, it isn't.
- Wait. Where's Amanda?
- Home with the kids.
- Yeah?
- Pissed.
What? What's up?
Think we hate each other.
- That's not good.
- Yeah. I know.
But the sex is... it's so...
angry.
I can't get away from it, man.
- It's good to see you.
- You, too.
- Hey, no one cares what I think?
- No.
- Come on? Really?
Ben, have a glass of wine.
I've let it go already, and so should you.
- I'll always have a drink.
- See? It's gone already.
- We'll be here.
- Come. Sit with me.
Ask me a question.
Okay.
- Seriously, ask me a question.
- Okay. Sorry.
- Wait. You're up for tenure, aren't you?
- Yeah. I got it.
- Come on.
- A year ago.
Year ago? Really?
I had a party and everything.
I'm... sorry.
You don't have to be sorry.
You're here now.
It's weird to be here, isn't it?
Maybe that's Choi, our hero.
Fucking Choi.
- I'm finally here.
- Yeah.
Who's that?
Hey.
Everybody.
- It's you.
- Oh, darlin'.
- I can't believe you're really here.
- This is my friend Pruitt.
- Hey.
Evening.
- Eden.
- How are you?
Hey. I'm Ben.
Nice to meet you. I'm gonna grab
a whiskey. Did you want anything?
- Anything diet is fine, thanks.
- Okay.
Hey. I'm Tommy. Miguel, Kira, Gina.
Nice to meet you.
I have no idea.
I'm glad you're here,
but frankly where the hell is Choi?
Choi?
Is my asshole boyfriend.
Said he was gonna be early for once.
He didn't call you guys,
say he was gonna be late?
No. Come on. I thought
he was gonna come with you.
- Yeah, I...
- We haven't seen him.
All right, that's it. I'm gonna try again.
Do you guys have service up here?
- Sorry.
- Horrible.
And the bills fell through the cracks
while we were away.
We have to get them up here and reconnect
the landline. I'm sorry, Gina.
Well, he usually calls at least once.
You know what? Your best bet
is gonna be in the back actually.
Good luck, though.
Is everything okay, Will?
Yeah. Yeah, why didn't you leave
the key in the door, though?
There was a home invasion
up in the canyon about a month ago.
This couple got terrorized.
It was really sick.
Just kinda freaked us out.
- I didn't hear about it.
- Then I'm sure it never happened.
Yeah, come on, Will. Can't a man
put himself in lockdown if he wants?
This is America.
Okay, what if there was a fire?
Okay.
There you go.
Better? I just keep the house
a little differently. That's all.
It's my house.
Will, could you do me a favor
and go get some more firewood?
You know where we keep it.
Has he been like this a lot, so agitated?
Sometimes.
Well, I'm glad he has you.
It comforts me.
I know he wants the best for you, too.
I'm glad you're here, Kira.
I think it's important.
Can I ask you something?
How has he been handling things?
He can be self-destructive.
I think he's doing the best he can.
You're it. You're it! Come on!
Come back to us when you're ready.
- I'm telling you.
- Why are you doing it?
Because it's... you're very dirty here.
- Am I?
- Yes.
And it's attention to detail
that is incredibly important.
- It's my credo.
- It's your credo?
It's a new...
I came up with it last night. Hey.
Why don't you go back to bed, okay?
- We'll keep... we'll keep it down.
- Okay.
Okay. I love you.
- Good night, baby.
- Good night.
- I love you, too. Night.
- Good night, hon.
And that'll be the time he saw
his gross parents having sex.
We are gross.
Do you think he needs a brother?
No! Oh, my...
- They're in a cult.
- No, no, stop. We're not in a cult.
I know plenty of people
who do the invitation.
- You do?
- Yeah.
- Eden, you guys really in this?
- We are.
So that's why you were in Mexico?
Did you get all naked
down there in the jungle?
Sometimes.
Well, I did.
Yeah, you did. But, you know, it's just...
it's just a group of people
coming together.
You know, they all have lost someone,
and then they help each other.
You know, it's really a science
rather than, like, some weird
religious cult or anything.
You know, it's smart people
like... like us,
here in L.A., New York,
thousands of people. You'd be surprised.
Yeah, my boss is into it.
It's like a new est or something, right?
Yeah, no...
I think it's a little more grounded
than that, you know, more practical.
And at the same time, it's very spiritual,
you know, however you define that.
Seriously, what goes on down there?
I mean, is it like
a self-help group thing or...
Well...
since you asked, we have something
that we'd like to show you.
- David.
- Oh, no. Oh, no. No, no.
- Perfect. Just perfect.
- Now I understand why the doors are locked.
You're gonna convert us.
This is a conversion thing, right?
Oh, my God. No, this is the real reason?
I know it sounds a little weird,
but it's actually, it's pretty amazing stuff.
Indulge us, okay.
Is this some kind of a recruitment video?
I really don't want to...
- I do. Convert me. I am weak.
- Yeah, you are.
It's nothing like that. Promise.
All right, let's do this.
This is our home in Sonora, Mexico,
and it is your home, too,
if you choose it to be.
Our home and our family is open to anyone
with the desire to help themselves.
The human brain has
a remarkable ability to heal.
My life's work has been to discover
new ways to rewire, to rewrite
our experiences with trauma.
I mean, trauma has visited...
all of us.
We invite you to a conscious existence,
to a connected existence.
But we take this journey,
all journeys side by side.
You are not alone.
Wherever you are...
we... we transcend.
How do you feel, Annie?
I feel loved.
You are loved.
You are deeply loved.
Who are you going to see, dear?
My husband...
James.
My father.
It's all right.
They will all be there.
- I...
- Soon, Annie. Soon.
Over soon.
All of the pain and all of the grief,
you renounced it, haven't you?
You've made a choice.
You're ready to go, aren't you, honey?
Come. Come. Breathe in.
Breathe in. Breathe deeply.
- You feel her spirit?
- I can feel it.
I can feel it.
She's with all of us now...
And your father...
And your wife... and your son.
Don't cry.
There's no darkness, just reunion.
Annie is safe now.
This is what it's about.
We did not just watch somebody die.
- That was real?
- Yes, it was.
Why would anyone want to watch that?
She just wanted to show everyone
that there's nothing to be afraid of.
That was the point. She was very sick.
With what? She barely looked 30.
Cancer.
Look, I get it. If you gotta go
at 30, it's not a bad way,
- surrounded by people who love you.
- On video?
It's beautiful.
It's a little grim.
She looked at peace to me.
I'm not judging her.
- No, I know, babe.
- Yeah, no one's judging her.
I just don't understand why you'd show
something like that at a dinner party, David.
You don't get it?
I guess this is not really
being taken the way we meant it.
I mean, it is a pretty heavy thing
to drop on us, David.
But it's not heavy. For us, it's not.
- No.
- It's okay. Not everybody gets it.
It's not about the fact that she died.
We all die.
- What's it about?
- It's about communion.
Right, like Eden said,
she's just trying to show you
that there's nothing to be afraid of.
Look at me. My pain had turned me
into some walking cliché.
I was a coked-up, out-of-control
record producer, for God's sake.
I was a slave to my own grief...
but not anymore.
Dr. Joseph freed me from that.
I just...
He gave me back my center, you know?
- I don't have to be afraid anymore.
- Amen, brother.
You know, we've all been
through horrible things,
but those things don't have to define us.
- What happened to Eden and Will...
- No, don't. Don't! David, don't.
Finding this saved my life.
I almost died after.
I almost couldn't keep on living.
You know that, Will.
But look at me now. I'm great. I'm happy.
I'm not angry anymore.
And if anyone is gonna try
to take that away from me...
My God, look at the way
you're looking at me.
If anyone is gonna try
to say that this isn't...
Edie, I... Edie...
it's just you don't think I know?
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
- I know!
- Let's get a drink.
- It's just that easy for you?
Come on. Come on. Let's get a drink.
Yeah, we all are lost.
We can agree on that, right?
It's just...
It's too big.
It's too big for any of us alone.
You got to...
- That better be...
- No, I've got it. I've got it. I got it.
David.
Sorry.
Excuse me for a second.
Hi there.
- Hey.
- Are you okay?
- I'm sorry.
No, not you.
I mean, I knew it was
gonna be heavy, but...
I was just... why Choi and I were
supposed to be here together for you.
We have to make a better effort.
It's on us, and...
I was trying to give you space,
and I don't know if that came across
like I was checked out. It's...
Okay, hello. I don't...
- You haven't heard a word I said, have you?
- I'm sorry, Gina.
Just a couple people
looking for a party... on foot.
- Good luck. They'll die of dehydration.
- Yeah.
Anyway, we can talk later.
I just... I wanted you to know that...
I have been thinking about you.
- Yeah.
- All right?
- I love you...
- I love you, too.
- I miss you.
- I miss you, too.
- I'm gonna get a refill.
- Get a... get a drink.
I feel like you guys
have to come to my house...
Are you gonna come
and join us at some point?
Will?
Can you tell me what that is?
It is a pill, Will.
I found a bunch of it
in Eden's bedroom unlabeled...
- Wait. What are you...
- Please just look at it.
- It's Phenobarbital, I think.
- Is that dangerous?
Anything is dangerous
if you take too much of it.
It's a barbiturate. I mean,
it's old-school, but it's...
not unusual to find it if you're rifling
through somebody's medicine cabinet.
Hey, hey, break up your little clique.
Come talk to us.
Come on. Let's go.
Apparently V.I.P. room is in the kitchen.
Guys, guys, guys, join us, please.
Just opened another bottle.
- Oh, yes.
- Probably needs a little more air.
I mean it, Miguel.
Just keep it between us.
Okay, Snoopy.
- Oh, man.
- Can you give this one to Miguel?
- Yeah.
- Gracias.
De nada.
Smell that.
Okay.
- Salud.
Will thinks you guys are on pills.
Figuratively.
- You think we're crazy?
- I never said that.
That's okay. I'm not offended.
A lot of people think we're crazy.
But I doubt they're as happy as we are.
Where's the diet again?
- Why?
- No comprendo inglés.
- Thank you.
- De nada.
Don't you guys think
this is a little bit weird?
Look, Will, there is no way that tonight
wasn't gonna feel a little strange...
Or sad.
Look, this is just a long-overdue reunion
between old friends...
with a couple of totally
frickin' friend weirdoes.
- They're a little Mansony.
- "Mansonian"?
- And that skinny girl...
- Look, I'm not kidding. Come on.
I got you. Look at me.
Yeah, they're a little weird,
but this is L.A. They're harmless.
Let's just get through this night, give them
a break. Let's steal some more of this wine.
Now, that is something
I can get behind. Come on.
Hey, guys, listen! I...
I realize that some of you might have found
that video a little disturbing or off-putting,
- and I apologize for that.
- It's cool.
No, Gina, it's not.
Last thing I want you guys to think is
that I'm trying to force my ideas on you.
Welcome back.
You know, it's just
I want you guys to know me.
There's this game we used to play
in Mexico at the end of group,
and I think we should try it.
- What kind of game are we talking about?
- Like charades or something?
It'll be fun, and it'll give you
a sense of what we learned, right?
- I'm in. What is it?
- Okay.
It's kind of like that game
we played in college, "I never."
- I always lose that game.
- Oh, I never do.
Except this time, it's "I want,"
so we take turns, and everybody
gets to say what they want.
- I want to hear what Gina did in college.
- You mean who she did.
But the point is to be honest.
All right? To admit your desires.
You know, because anything is possible
once you strip away
social constraints and embarrassment
and those negative emotions that,
you know, the things that hold us down.
So honesty, okay? That's what it's about.
Want to give it a shot?
- I'll go first.
- Wonderful.
Okay.
I want...
to tell you, Eden, and David...
Will and Kira and Gina...
- Miguel...
- Pack a lunch.
And Tommy... there are so many.
Ben, Claire, Pruitt...
I want to tell you all that I love you.
I know I haven't known
some of you for very long, but...
tonight I feel love.
I do.
And a lot of people don't say that.
They're afraid.
But... so...
I love you.
- Oh, shit.
- Oh, my.
Oh, my gosh.
This is...
Hi there.
You get it?
All right.
I want...
some of that coke you used to do.
Done. I think I might have some more.
You keep it in the house?
You're the worst rehabber in the world.
- No, David, don't. I was kidding.
- No, you weren't.
That's okay. That's the point of the game.
Okay. I wasn't kidding.
Bust that shit out.
- There you go.
- I like this game.
I want to tell you about my wife Margaret.
We were married eight years...
would have been 15 next month.
She was a painter, oils.
First saw her work
at this artists retreat in Minneapolis.
I was in love with her
before I even met her.
These...
abstract, energetic landscapes...
and then I saw her.
It was like I'd hit the jackpot.
She was the most
generous spirit I'd ever seen,
and she was as bright and gorgeous as...
the morning.
When you surprised her,
she had this laugh, this...
joyous, guttural rumble that came
from way down deep inside.
You knew you'd done something good.
She was all light, all light.
During times like this,
nights like this night...
I think of her quite a bit.
Did she... pass away?
Yes, she did.
We had been drinking.
I had been drinking.
We had just come home from a dinner,
and we were in the kitchen.
We'd fell into one of those arguments,
you know, one of those...
stupid fights that last
your whole marriage.
It was about the dishes.
Somebody started yelling.
I don't remember who.
I went to pour myself another drink.
She tried to stop me, and...
something just gave.
I turned and hit her as hard as I could.
Her knees buckled. She hit her head.
Think she was trying to get back up.
You know, she had her hand out...
was staring at me.
And then...
she collapsed, and she was gone.
What the fuck?
It was a terrible, terrible mistake.
It was seven years ago.
I went to prison. I paid that way...
but I was still the same person.
Finally, by...
accepting the invitation...
And looking only ahead...
destroying that horrible part of me
that made that moment possible...
I'm cured.
And I miss her.
Not a day goes by I don't think of her.
But I don't grieve,
and I don't feel guilty anymore.
I've chosen to let that go.
Those emotions are useless, because...
I'm gonna be seeing her again
in a better place than this.
That's what we believe. That's what
most people have believed for centuries.
I, for one, can't wait to get there.
But forgiveness doesn't have to wait.
I'm free to forgive myself,
and so are you.
It's a beautiful thing.
It really is.
What's more honorable, facing
the truth or hiding it to be accepted?
And people change.
I don't know.
This... doesn't seem very honest.
It feels like you're selling us something.
- No, we aren't.
- I want...
- Are we really gonna keep doing this?
- This better be good.
- I want to kiss Ben.
I always have.
Why the hell not? Bring it, sister.
Oh, my God.
- I want to kiss Ben.
- One per party.
- Boom. No?
- No.
Yeah!
Get it, girl.
Go!
Jeez.
I don't know if I approve that.
And nobody tells Amanda.
- I want a blow job...
- Oh, you're ridiculous.
- From somebody.
- Oh, I know.
- What? I'm not joking.
- I have to go.
Come on. We're just having fun.
It's all right.
This is all making me
a little uncomfortable. I'm sorry.
Come on. Have a seat. I'll get you a drink.
We'll do something else.
No, no, no. I don't want to spoil
anyone's fun. This just isn't my thing.
- Claire, please.
- Just... just let her go, David.
Why can't she just leave?
Will, I just want her to stay
and have a good time...
and Eden has planned this night for
a long time. We'll be very disappointed.
Well, just let her do
what she wants, okay?
I'm gonna leave.
- Of course.
- Bye.
I'm sorry if I've made you
feel uncomfortable.
It's... it's okay. I'm tired.
Claire, why don't you
just stay a little longer?
I'll see you again soon, okay?
I'm really sorry.
Okay, Claire.
Eden, it's okay.
I know.
- Do you want me to walk you to your car?
- It's, like, 40 feet, Will.
- Bye.
- Bye, Claire.
- Are you in the Prius?
- Yeah.
I parked behind you.
Thank you, guys.
Hey, Will, come over here, and talk to me.
Just give me a sec.
Careful on the right.
Okay.
Straight out. You're all set.
Oh, Claire.
Will, come on.
Can you and I talk alone for a minute?
It's important.
Yeah. Yeah.
Come on.
I'm very happy you're here.
It's so important to Eden and me.
I mean, we chose you
because you matter to us.
- You chose me?
- To be here tonight.
But I don't know, man.
You've been acting so...
suspicious of our hospitality.
Frankly, it upsets me a little.
I lock the door,
and you have a fit about it.
Just now, my friend wants to move his car,
and you're standing by the window like
you're gonna catch him stealing something.
You seem very distant, very...
just off somehow.
I'm sorry.
Maybe I wasn't prepared
to be here tonight.
Okay. Okay.
I appreciate your honesty.
Look, I...
I understand that you feel
like you have to be on the lookout.
I know, because that's how I felt.
The world is unsafe and chaotic,
and, you know, it happened before.
It can always happen again. David, please.
I don't pretend to know
what you went through with your wife...
and you don't know me. You can't.
- Hey.
- Hi.
I tried to convince Claire to stay.
I felt bad about, my story scaring her.
She seemed to understand.
I swear to God, every day I get
an email, and it's just I'm going,
"what is this? Is this, like,
gonna kill my hard drive?"
And it's usually some stupid
fricking video of, like...
How many cat videos has Claire sent you?
- Claire has sent me cat videos so...
- Every day, it's a cat video.
I mean, I got a cat video.
I got a penguin video.
- Penguins. Penguins are overrated.
- Overrated?
- Yeah. Yeah. They are.
- Here we go...
You're it.
Kira.
So things aren't great with Kira?
What... why would you say that?
Just seems like that to me.
Seems like she's real distant.
No.
No, she's great.
- Should we go back inside?
- No. I'm gonna make a call.
Oh, good luck. There's no service up here.
No, it goes in and out.
I could hang with you.
- You could fuck me right here.
- What?
Why should we deny ourselves ever?
It's what it was like in Mexico.
Man, everyone was just going for it.
It was awesome.
I think you need to go back inside.
You don't like me?
I don't know you.
I could make you like me so much.
I could make you beg me.
Could do it without even touching you...
just with my voice...
- my breath.
- Sadie.
You can hurt me if you want.
I don't want to hurt you.
I don't believe you.
Hey. What are you doing out here?
I needed a break.
Oh, really? From what?
Tommy, there's something wrong here.
- Will...
- Something bad is happening here.
You're wrong. Look, and I know
what you're gonna say,
but Claire left because that poor girl
is sexually awkward.
Choi is the most unreliable Korean
in Los Angeles. He could be anywhere.
And Eden...
I haven't seen her for two years.
It's crazy.
But we're all trying to figure out
how to go on, you know.
- This is how they do it.
- Something doesn't feel safe here.
Of course it doesn't feel safe. Took a lot
of courage for you to come here tonight,
but you're letting your mind
run away with things.
Hey...
I love you, Will.
But you gotta stop acting so fucking weird.
It's freaking people out.
You're safe, okay?
I'll see you back inside.
Will, Choi. What's up?
Listen, it's about 7:00,
and I'm pulling up to Eden's house.
I forgot to pick up dessert like I said
I would, and I can't get ahold of Gina.
Could you get some on your way? I...
Look, I'm early, dude.
I'm actually early, but honestly
I don't want to go back down the hill
and look for a fucking patisserie.
I hope you get this.
See you here in a few, I guess.
I'm goin' in. Okay, bye.
There he is.
- See?
- Hey, buddy.
- I want to play "I want." I want...
- No more blow jobs.
I like this game.
Was it obvious that I like the game?
- I have room. I could do it.
- He has room for everything.
- We both enjoyed that game.
- We did.
I think this is a new game.
- All right, I'm scared.
- This is the next game.
Maybe this is one of those guess who...
So pretty. So purty.
- It is lovely.
- Stop it right now.
What is going on here?
- Happy birthday.
- What is this about?
- It's not for another week.
- It's close enough.
Okay, please, please. But no singing.
Please? Please? Please?
Thank you. It's wish time.
- Make it good. Make it good.
- Yeah.
You attacked that one.
- Bastard.
- Well done.
- Where's Choi?
- Excuse me?
Where's Choi?
I mean, where the fuck is Choi?
- What are you talking about, Will?
- I got a message from him.
He said he was here,
that he had gotten here at 7:00.
- What?
- He said he was here.
- Eden, is that true?
- I haven't seen Choi tonight.
- Edie, where is he?
- Will, stop, please. Just...
No. No. I just got a message from him.
He said he was here.
- He made the call from right outside.
- We haven't seen him.
Don't fucking lie to me. He called
from right outside your front door.
David is not lying to you.
Choi never got here.
- Maybe he turned around, man.
- He might have forgotten something, Will.
Yeah, why is everyone
acting so fucking polite?
- Where's Choi?
- Hey, Eden, what's going on?
I have not seen Choi tonight,
Gina, I swear.
Something isn't right here.
There is something
very strange going on here,
and no one is saying anything.
- What do you think is happening, Will?
- Hey, who are you?
See, see, I don't get
why you two are here.
- Hey, these are my guests.
- Yeah.
Two years.
We don't see you for two years,
and then all of a sudden,
we get invited to this lavish dinner.
You're all smiles, spewing out all
this jargon with these two in tow.
Don't tell me that this is normal...
the invitation.
- It helps people.
- Will, everybody's allowed...
No, it's a fucking cult, Miguel!
It's a fucking cult!
- Will, sit down!
- No! No, look at the video, okay?
It's not about communion. It's not
about family. It's about fucking denial.
- You are out of line.
- All right, no, it's about denial.
You know what it is?
It's a fucking brainwash.
Our son died, Edie,
and you're trying to ignore it.
It meant something when he died,
and don't you try to erase that.
Ty was real. It was rea... it is real.
Please, please, Edie.
- Where's Choi?
- Will, she said she doesn't know.
I think this is
just a big misunderstanding.
Don't fucking patronize me, David.
Why don't you tell me something?
Why are all the doors locked?
Okay, why are all the bars on the windows?
Why is there a big fucking bottle
of phenobarbital stashed in your bedroom?
- Jesus Christ, Will.
- Did you go through our things?
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry. We should go.
- No. No. No.
Something very dangerous is going on here,
and nobody's talking about it.
We're all just ignoring it because
David brought out some good wine!
- We are going, Will. We are going.
- No, I'm not going anywhere!
We are going right now, Will.
It's all right.
What's up?
Choi?
I'm so sorry.
I was right here, and then work called,
and it's so fucked up,
'cause they can't do anything without me.
- I called you.
- I didn't get it.
You okay?
Hi, love. Did I miss dinner?
- You missed more than that, bud.
- We have plenty. I'll get you something.
- I'll fix him a plate.
- Thank you, Pruitt.
What's going on?
David...
It's okay.
- We really should go now, Will.
- Just give him a minute, Kira.
I'm... I'm sorry, Eden.
I know it's hard, Will...
but you can't criticize us
for finding our own way through this.
I've never done that to you.
I know. I know. It's none of my business.
I know...
and I'm very sorry.
It's okay.
You're part of our family, Will.
All of you are.
Will you... will you
excuse me for a second?
Choi, eat.
You... you got any more of that wine?
Just gotta lather it up.
Keep washing.
10 seconds, at least.
We should go.
Let's go, then. Let's just...
let's just get out of here.
I can't.
Kira, I'm not okay.
My son is dead. Where do I put that?
I don't know.
It's like a scream trapped inside me.
And... nothing changes the fact
that I should have... I should have
been watching more closely that day.
Now, look, you couldn't have known, Will.
You could not have been looking out for that.
It's another kid.
And Ty loved him.
And they were just playing.
They were just messing around.
- I shouldn't have let them have the bat.
- What happened to your son
wasn't anything that could be
predicted or changed or...
I've been waiting to die
since the moment it happened.
Moving forward is not a betrayal, Will.
Look at Eden.
That's what letting go looks like.
You're not letting go of him.
I would never ask you to. You know that.
We can help each other, Will.
That's the only way.
I love you, Kira...
but I don't think you can help me.
- I'm sorry.
- Yeah, you are.
Red velvet.
- Miguel, you get the first piece.
- I'm excited.
Hi, Will.
Can I see his room?
Of course.
I know you have doubts.
Skepticism can be contagious.
I wouldn't have known either
before I saw the new truth
and shared it with you.
I wouldn't have believed,
but it was revealed so clearly.
Remember the reward.
This beautiful moment is upon us.
Tonight is the night
our faith is made real.
The hardest thing is to start.
Just take the step.
Believe...
and give yourself over.
Will, let's go. Everybody's waiting.
I love you.
I love you so much, my heart is breaking.
I'm waiting for you.
Okay.
Kira.
Look at these people.
They're so happy to be here with you.
I think we should take a moment
to look at each other and really look.
Please raise your glass.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
To a better world.
To peace.
- Cheers.
Don't drink it! Don't fucking touch it!
- Will!
- No, don't drink! Don't drink!
- Calm down, Will.
- No. No. We are leaving now!
- Will, you do not want to go this way.
- Let's go, Kira. We're leaving right now!
- Calm down.
- No, we are leaving now!
You ruined it! You ruined everything!
Oh, my God.
Sadie.
- Sadie.
- Oh, my God. Will, what did you do?
Don't move her.
- Sadie. Somebody call 911.
- I'm on it.
Sadie. Sadie, can you hear me?
Do you have a first-aid kit?
Sadie, can you hear me?
- It's okay, Sadie.
- She's not breathing.
- No, she's breathing.
- Not Sadie, Gina.
What? Gina?
All right, get her on the floor.
What's going on? Gina!
- Baby?
- Gina!
- Can you hear me? Starting CPR.
- Baby?
Baby, it's gonna be okay.
What's happening, Miguel?
- Somebody get 911?
- I'm not getting any reception.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- I'm not getting a pulse, Miguel.
- Fucking door's locked.
- Gina, can you hear me?
- Come on, Gina.
Come on. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go.
- Tommy. Tom... Tommy.
- Come on! Let's go!
Tommy!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Kira! Kira! This way.
- What?!
Ben, this way!
Go left. Left!
- It's locked. Will, it's locked.
- Okay, okay. This way. This way.
Will! Will!
The door. The door.
Fuck. It's locked.
We're gonna have to break it.
Kira.
- No.
- Please, no.
- Will, why is this happening?
- Listen to me. We are gonna get ready.
We're gonna do whatever it takes.
Do you hear me?
- They are just people.
- Right.
- Okay?
- Okay.
- Come on.
Okay.
You weren't supposed to hurt
anybody like that.
I know.
- Oh, God.
- How could you do that?
- Why would you do that?
- Don't do this.
We were supposed to just go
to sleep and go there together.
- It was supposed to be beautiful.
- It's gonna be quiet in a minute.
- We'll be there soon.
- It wasn't supposed to be like this.
- That's not what he said.
- No, I know. It's just...
We just have to finish now. Hey.
Listen to me. We take it
one step at a time. We finish.
- No. I can't.
- It'll be quiet and we can rest. Yes, you can.
Eden, you gotta help me.
- You have to help me. You can't leave me.
- No, this is wrong.
Dr. Joseph said it was gonna be hard,
but we'll have to finish it now.
- This is wrong.
- We were chosen, remember?
We were chosen. This is the only way
we can leave this hurting.
This is right.
This is the only way we can stop hurting.
We can leave all this... all this pain,
all this shit behind.
You can do this.
Hey...
we can still get there.
Come on.
There's a door to the garage upstairs.
- Okay.
- We're going there.
Okay.
Dr. Joseph...
- Oh, my God.
- Choi.
Oh, my God.
Oh, God.
- No.
- What?
No. No. There was a door here.
- Oh, fuck.
- We had a door here when we lived here.
Fuck. Okay. Okay.
Maybe... maybe we can
signal someone outside.
Maybe I can signal someone outside.
- Come on.
- Kira.
Kira.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Don't be afraid.
There is a plan for us, man.
Will.
Just let go. Just...
We'll be there soon.
I promise.
Come on. Let's get out of here.
Eden.
I'm sorry, Will.
I'm sorry, Will. I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- Eden.
Stop it. Stop it. Stop it.
Okay.
Will.
We are not gonna die like this.
Hey, lis...
I'm okay.
Eden?
Get the gun.
She shot herself, David.
That's good.
She's with them now.
It's empty.
We have a gun.
That's okay.
It's time.
Don't do this, David.
Will.
I miss him.
I miss him so much.
I wanted to leave.
I'm sorry.
Will you take me outside?
I hope...
I hope we...
I...
I gotta go get Miguel.
Tommy.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
Kira.
I might be a part of this
Ripple on water from a lonesome drip
A fallen tree that witnessed me
Him alone, him and me
And that life itself could not aspire
to have someone be so admired
I threw creation to my kin
with a silence broken by a whispered wind
All of this can be broken
Hold your devil by his spoke
and spin him to the ground
And root to root and tip to tip
I look at him my country drip
Leathered up by all his fears
but someone brought you close to tears
Many trains and many miles
brought you to me on this sunny isle
And what of which you wish to speak
Have you come here to rescue me?
All of this can be broken
Hold your devil by his spoke
and spin him to the ground
But the love of your life lives
but lies no more than where she lay
Your flower grows
The arms that fed and the babes that wed
The backs that bled keeping her in tow
But I am your keeper
And I hold your face away from light
I am yours till they come
Eye to eye, nose to nose
Ripping off each other's clothes
in a most peculiar way
Eye to eye, nose to nose
Ripping off each other's clothes
in a most peculiar way