- Do you have
to film everything?
- Yup.
- Describing...
You're filming everything,
you're describing.
- That's his journal. I want him
to remember everything.
- His journal.
You don't even know
if it's a boy
or a girl yet.
- Yeah. But, you know,
we trust the first
ultrason, it's a boy.
So tell us.
- Where are we going?
- Yup.
- We're going to the hospital
to get our second ultrason
and confirm the sex of the baby.
This little guy.
- Yeah, little guy.
- And we're happy,
we're excited.
Hi.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hi. You're gonna be
editing all this, right?
- Of course.
- All right, so your turn now.
Tell me how you feel,
future dad.
- I'm just really grateful
that our kid
is gonna be healthy.
- Matt! Watch out!
- Oh my god!
Oh! Jess!
Jess! Oh my god!
- Matt!
- Oh my god!
You got the phone?
Where's the phone?
Call 911! Call 911!
Oh my god!
- Oh, my baby.
You're gonna be
editing all this, right?
-  Of course.
- I hate night shifts.
Did your boss say how much he's
charging us for the weekend?
- Free. Yeah, we have
the cabin to ourselves
for the entire
weekend. Yeah.
He want us to have a good
time before I get back to work.
- That's nice.
I can't believe we're leaving
for a whole weekend.
- It's been so long.
- I want us to have fun
and laugh and party.
- Party.
- And be ourselves again.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- You didn't tell anyone
about this, did you?
- No. Why?
- Okay.
I want to make a little surprise
video for Joe's birthday.
- Oh. You gonna have
enough time
to put it together
before we leave?
- Yeah, if I work
all night on it.
- Okay, well don't work
too hard
'cause I need you to have
your energy this weekend.
- Oh, yeah?
- I got the news from Joe.
All is in order, we can start
trying to have a baby again.
Okay? So, I need you
to have your energy,
all of your energy.
I gotta go to work. Bye.
Oh, don't forget, you're
picking us up at 11:00, okay?
- Okay.
- Love you!
- Good morning,
you're listening
to the morning show
with me, Dan Hitchcock.
Okay, the weather.
Now, temperatures will today
move into the low 80s
and we'll have sunshine
and a few clouds
for most of the day.
With wind from
10 to 20 miles an hour.
Now, as for
the long weekend ahead,
well, sunny with a few clouds
and temperatures are going to
move down into the lower 70s.
But still,
a perfect weekend to get away.
Now, after the break, we'll
talk about why there's a...
... you should be taking
an evening stroll
over the long weekend.
- Earlier this morning
an American satellite
was destroyed by what
authorities are calling
an unidentified object.
Images taken by the satellite
itself moments
before it was destroyed seem
to indicate that a collision
between the satellite
and the object was the cause.
Mainly over the province
of Quebec, Canada...
- Ready Teddy?
All right, let's go!
We're running late,
buddy.
- ... and to report
any unusual sightings.
- Hey Joe!
-  You're late Matt.
- I know, it's Teddy's fault.
- I think he disagrees
with you.
- I'll be there in a minute.
-  Yeah, right.
- What's up, birthday boy?
- A weekend away from the
hospital, that's what's up.
Keep your eyes
on the road, man.
- Nice haircut, doc.
- I hate it!
When we get back
to the hospital,
I'm gonna show you
something real sweet.
Check it out!
- What is it?
- Hold on, hold on.
- Come on, what is it?
- Check it out!
- Holy shit!
- Yeah baby.
- No way!
Are you kidding me?
You finally bought it?
- Yeah. It costs me
a small fortune,
but I got everything
i wanted. I got lights
for the night shots,
i got everything man.
- Wow! Check it out!
Is it recording right now?
- Yup.
Matt, I'm telling you,
I'm ready for
any eventuality now.
- Hold on.
Hi, honey!
- Who's the girl your brother's
bringing, Jess?
His new girlfriend?
- Yeah, I think so.
I don't know much about her,
she's going to school with him.
- Wait. Wow.
- Are you gonna film like that
on the weekend?
- I'm just trying
to make a souvenir here.
- Of my ass?
- You know your nurse outfit
excites me.
- You know you're not bringing
that thing into the bedroom.
- Come on!
- Where's your brother?
Did you tell him
to meet us here?
- Yeah, I did.
- Your brother is a mess.
- What? Is that Trey
and his new girlfriend?
- What do you think
you're doing?
Give me that.
- Hey.
- Hi, I'm Jess.
- Julia.
- This is my husband Matt.
- Hey, nice meeting you.
- Nice to meet you.
- What up, Trey?
- What's up, Matt?
Hey, nice to see you, Joe.
- Yeah, it's been a while.
- Stop, my god.
- Matt, how long will
it take us to get there?
- Gracefield is about
five hours.
- Five hours? I thought
it was closer than that!
- Five hours? You know what?
Just wake me up
when we get there, tron.
- Why are you
calling him like that?
- He called him that because
Matt's a video game editor.
- Oh, okay.
- That's not really why.
Come on,
show it to her, tron.
- Trey! He's driving.
- Come on, man.
You can't see anything...
- I'm not doing it.
I'm not doing it.
- She'll like it, man.
I'm telling you.
- Don't do it, Matt.
- You really want to see it?
You really want to see it?
All right, I'm doing it.
- You know, Trey,
this is all your fault.
- What is it?
- I'm filming this.
I got this. Oh god!
- Oh my god!
This is disgusting!
- She dropped it in the trunk.
- What? What?
What's going on?
- Shit!
- Teddy's licking it.
- What do you mean
she dropped my eye?
- Teddy's licking it.
- Wow!
- Oh, man!
- Matt's prosthetic eye.
- Trey,
can I have it back, now?
- Teddy, don't swallow it!
- Yo, does anyone have
any reception?
- Nope!
- Negative.
- I lost reception
like an hour ago.
- Me too.
- God, Matt.
Why is it taking so long?
Are you lost?
- No. I'm not lost.
We'll be there soon, okay?
- Relax.
- Matt, whose cabin is this,
by the way?
- My boss.
- Please ask him why
he bought a cabin that far.
- 'Cause he traps, Trey.
- He what?
- He's a trapper.
He captures animals.
- No, no, Matt,
tell him the real reason
why your boss bought
a cabin out here.
- That's a good story.
- Why?
'Cause my boss has been
trying to capture bigfoot.
- What did he just say?
- Sasquatch!
- Your boss
is a kooky little man.
- It's a hoax, that's what
it is. But it's cool.
- You'd be surprise how many
people believe in that shit.
And he does! And he's been
trying to capture it.
- Nobody believes in that stuff.
Your boss, he freaks me out.
- Hey guys,
i think we're here.
- Ah, finally!
- What kind of cabin
has a gate like this?
- I was expecting a shack
with one room and no toilet.
- Well, if it's true,
I'm sleeping in the car.
- Come on, Liz!
- Shotgun!
- "No trespassing"?
- Are we sure this is it?
- I hope so.
'Cause if it's not,
we're definitely lost.
- That's reassuring.
- Did he say we were lost?
- Yeah, probably.
- Matt, you do realize
how crazy your boss is for
believing in this shit, right?
- You got that right.
- A bigfoot, come on!
- Yeah, man, he even told me
he heard one a while back.
- Yeah, your boss is definitely
out of his mind.
Oh, and paranoid too!
- So, Julia and i
are getting
the biggest room,
that's just for sure.
- You guys are getting
the couch.
- No way, man! Are you serious?
- Hell yeah, I am.
- Man, I'm not getting
the couch.
- Yo! Guys!
Check this out!
- That is sick!
- This place looks amazing!
- Yeah. You're still getting
the couch, Trey.
- That's bullshit. Come on!
Don't do that.
- You're so getting the couch.
- - No, no, no.
- No, I'm gonna go there before
you. You know it.
- You're the youngest,
that's why you get the couch.
- Matt, why are you
locking the doors?
- Give a head start to my wife.
- What?
- Ready? Go, go, go!
Grab the best room!
- Go, go, go. Go, Liz!
Go, go, go.
- That's not cool,
Matt, come on!
- Hey, oh, slow down!
- Looks like you got
the couch to me, Trey.
Go, go, go.
- Catch up, Teddy,
come on!
- Wow!
This place is huge!
- Bring you ass, quick!
- Holy shit!
Look at this place.
This is unbelievable.
- What's wrong with this guy?
There's a surveillance room.
- Matt, I got it!
- Jess, where are you?
- Right here.
- Right where?
- Upstairs.
- No, no, two separate beds?
Definitely not.
- You guys are too young
to sleep together anyway.
- Yeah, yeah,
really funny, Matt.
You should be a comedian.
- We need a double bed.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Jess?
Oh, oh, oh, tell me
this is our room.
- Hey, Trey, how's the couch?
- Shut up, man.
- Oh, shit!
You have to stop doing that.
- You want me
to stop doing...
- Whoa, whoa. No, no.
- ... that?
- That, you can keep
doing all weekend.
- Yeah? You like that?
- Yeah. I've been waiting for
this weekend for a long time.
- I know, me too.
It's gonna be nice.
- Guys! Come outside!
- Hey, Joe? Heads up.
- Guys, check this out.
- There's a hot tub. Yes!
- Crazy.
- It doesn't get
any better than this.
- I think I can die, now.
Man, I'm telling you,
this is exactly what I needed.
No worries, eating,
drinking, and...
- And what?
- And eating again, baby.
Just eating again.
- Like the sound of that.
- Yeah.
- No cameras allowed, tough.
- Dinner's ready.
- Oh, man, I'm so hungry.
Thanks, babe.
- To an amazing weekend...
With my best friends!
- Cheers!
- I'm getting drunk.
- Cheers, love.
- It's yours, right there.
Ready?
- Come on, Matt.
- Way to go, way to go!
Come on, buddy, drink it.
Drink it.
- Chug, chug, chug!
- And there we have Jess,
the luckiest poker player
in gracefield.
- She's always winning.
- And here is my wife
and her sexy poker face.
Oh, what a lucky bastard.
- That's how
they study biology today.
- At least he got the couch.
- Leave him alone.
- Julia. Julia?
Come on in, baby, the water's
so good. And, well...
You know,
i have a surprise.
- Really?
- All right, I'm coming.
- Trey, your sister
is gonna come out.
- Joe! Who cares?
- Sorry, everybody, but I'm not
getting my bathing suit.
- Don't be sorry.
- Did you see that?
- Yeah. Is she for real?
- Whoa!
- What? I... I mean, I didn't...
- Look.
- What?
- Whoa. What is that?
- What is what?
- That!
- Whoa.
- Guys, are you seeing this?
- Yeah.
- What is it?
- This thing is getting
bigger and bigger.
- Yo, what is that?
- It's coming
straight at us!
- Watch out!
- Whoa!
- Oh my god!
- Shit.
- Are you all right?
- Did you feel that?
- It crashed right behind the
house. Guys, are you all right?
- Fine!
- Jess, are you okay?
- That was...
- Joe, grab your camera!
- Yeah, I'll meet you
in the front.
- No, guys, no. Matt, no!
- We'll be right back!
- Wait up!
- This is so cool!
- This is insane!
- I'm so glad
i brought the light.
- This is unreal. Make sure
you record everything
because nobody
is gonna believe us.
- Yeah, I got this. Hold on.
Let me just set up here.
- I'm recording
with my camera too.
- What camera?
- Never mind, never mind.
- That's what the red light in
your eye is all about, isn't it?
- No. No, it's not.
Come on, let's go!
- Yo, where is it?
- Come on!
Just put some clothes on!
- What is it? I wanna see it!
- Let's go, he's drunk.
- Where are we going?
- You stay here, all right?
Get you clothes on
and make sure you don't
lose sight of us.
- Let's go! He's just trying
to impress his girlfriend.
- I wanna go with you!
- It has to be somewhere close.
- We should see lights
or something, right?
- Talk about a satellite that
was destroyed this morning.
- You think this could be
a part of it?
- Maybe. We should
found out pretty soon.
They said they were
expecting some debris
to fall back to earth.
- Best birthday weekend ever!
Which way do you want to go?
- Let's try this way.
Follow me.
Watch you steps.
My boss might have set
some traps around here.
- Seriously? Your boss
and his hunt for bigfoot?
That's pretty sick, too.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
- What?
- Where is Trey?
Trey?
- Trey?
Why doesn't he answer?
- Yo, Matt,
we went way too far.
- Trey?
Trey? Trey?
- Yeah, yeah, I'm right here.
- What's wrong with you?
Answer us.
Hey, Joe! You know what?
You stay here, I'm gonna-
- whoa, hold on, hold on.
What are you saying?
- You stay here,
I'm gonna go check it out
a little bit further in.
It has to be somewhere.
Keep your light on
so I can see you.
- Just don't go too deep.
- We have to find this thing.
- Just don't go too far.
All right Matt?
- Yeah.
- What was that?
What was that?
Oh, come on.
Matt! Come on!
Look, man.
I can't see you anymore.
You should backtrack, come on!
We'll come back tomorrow.
- Hold on,
just a little bit more.
Oh my god!
Joe! I see something!
There's a light,
about 50 feet in front of me.
- Hold on.
Hold on.
Trey! Trey! Are you there?
- Yeah, yeah,
I'm right here.
- Matt thinks he's got it.
Really? No way!
No, no, listen to me.
You stay there, I'm gonna go
check it out.
- Are you kidding me, Joe?
Holy shit!
Joe!
I found it!
- Really?
I'm coming!
- Oh my god.
- Matt, where are you?
- Hurry up, Joe!
You won't believe this!
- Keep talking.
Where are you?
- Right here.
Right here, Joe.
I told you! I told you
we were gonna find this thing.
- Oh, what... what is this?
- Look at the size of it!
- Can you see what it is?
- No, it's too deep.
It's really down there.
- Really?
- Yeah, hold on.
Let me try to get it,
all right?
- What? You don't know
what's in there.
- Stop it.
You're such a pussy.
It's kind of cold.
I feel something.
- Ah!
- What are you doing?
Why are you backing up?
- I don't know, you said
you felt something, I...
- Come on, you're scaring me.
Give me some light.
Come on, Joe!
I think I got it.
It's pretty big too.
- Holy shit!
I've never seen
anything like it!
- Look at this, man!
- What the hell is it?
- Looks like some kind
of meteorite.
- That has nothing to do with
the satellite. Is it hot?
- No, it's freezing.
- Is it heavy?
- Do you want to hold it?
- No.
- Why are you scare?
- No, it's all right.
I just don't want to touch it.
- Come on, Joe. It's a rock.
It's like lava.
Holy shit!
- Hey!
What are you doing here?
We told you--
- you gotta let me touch it.
- What the hell is wrong
with you? You have amnesia?
- Dude, you're not the one
standing alone in the dark.
I was freezing
my balls out there.
- How are we gonna get back
to the cabin now, huh?
- Relax, it's okay, the house
is like right... there.
Oh, shit.
- Yeah. Right, where?
- It was more
or less right there.
- What were you
thinking, Trey?
- The house moved, jackass.
- What a stupid move!
- Come on, let's try this way.
- I'm sure it's that way, okay?
- Yeah, you better be right.
Jess!
- Liz!
We're definitely close,
i can feel it.
- Ah, shit! I think I dropped
my phone out there.
- Sorry, but we're not
going back.
- Oh, shit.
- Guys, guys.
Stop, stop, stop.
- What? What is it?
- You know what? I think
we should just wait here.
I mean, we don't
wanna go too deep.
I'm sure in a few minutes,
the girls gonna come
and look for us, right?
- Yeah, you're probably right.
'Cause if we're going
in the wrong direction,
we are not gonna hear
the girls yelling.
- Exactly.
So, let's wait here.
- Yeah.
Liz!
- Whoa!
What was that, Matt?
- What the hell was that?
- Dude, I don't know.
- I'm not--
- shhh! Shhh!
- I heard something--
- shhh!
- You guys
see anything?
I can't see anything.
- What kind of animal
sounds like that?
- Matt!
- Jess!
- I think it was Jess.
- That scream didn't
sound like Jess to me!
- Joe. Joe!
- What?
- I'm gonna go check it out.
- Matt, no!
- Give me your camera,
I'll use the light.
- Just stick to the plan
and stay here.
- I think the girls
are looking for us.
I'll be right back.
You guys stay here, okay?
- Come on!
Are you out of your mind?
Let's just wait here.
Matt! Matt!
- Jess!
No, no, stay on!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Matt! What happened?
Matt!
- Joe!
- Trey, follow me. Come on.
Matt, where are you?
- I need some help!
- Matt!
- Joe, over here.
- Holy shit, what happened?
- I got caught in one
of his frickin' traps.
- Hold on, hold on. Trey?
- Right here.
- Matt?
What was it?
- I didn't see it but it got
really close to me.
It was walking all around me.
- What was walking around?
- It was probably hungry
or something.
- What? Hungry?
What the hell are we dealing
with here?
- Listen!
- What?
- Listen.
- It sounds like my dog.
Teddy!
- Matt.
That wasn't Teddy!
- Ted!
Get over here, Teddy!
- Sounds like he's hurt.
Shit. Trey, hold this.
Hold this.
- What? What are you doing?
- We're gonna go get him.
- Get him?
- What? You gotta be kidding me.
What about that sound
we just heard?
- Every noise gets amplified,
we're in the woods.
- You want me to believe
that that shit we heard
was some kind of little
squirrel screaming?
- You want me to leave Teddy?
He might get struck
in one of those traps.
You stay here.
Joe, come with me.
- Matt, where are we going?
- Keep shining the light.
- Matt, you gotta slow down.
- Teddy!
- You gotta slow down.
- Teddy, where are you?
- Matt, slow down!
Matt! I can't keep up with you.
Holy shit!
No way,
he's not in there!
- Teddy!
Why the hell
did he go in there?
- I'm not sure
i wanna find out.
- Teddy!
- Was is wrong with him?
- He sounds scared.
- Scared of what?
- I don't know.
- Where are you going?
- I'm going in.
- I'm not going in there.
- Hey, I'm not leaving
Teddy here. Okay?
You brought that camera and
that light here for something.
- Oh, great, now the night
vision's on.
- Are you coming?
Teddy!
It's sounds like
he's crying.
- Dogs don't cry like that.
Matt, let's go!
- Shhh.
- What?
- Teddy?
Teddy!
- Matt, hold on.
What is that?
- Matt, I say we go.
- Hold on.
- Let's go!
- Teddy!
- What is that?
What is that?
- What the hell is this?
What is it?
- It's Trey's cell phone.
- What?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Yeah.
I'm pretty sure it's his.
How the hell
did it get here?
- Oh my god.
Oh, shit!
- Go, go, go!
Come, come, come.
- What was that?
We gotta go.
We gotta go!
Let's get out of here.
- Wait, wait, wait.
- Is it gone?
- Can you see it?
Can you see it?
- No.
- I think it's safe to go.
- Let's go.
- Joe!
Joe, what are you doing?
Come on, let's go!
Don't move.
Shhh, shhh.
- Is it following us?
- I don't know!
Keep going. Keep going.
- Joe!
- Wait, wait, wait.
- Matt! We're here!
- Julia?
- It's the girls.
- Liz?
- Joe, are you okay?
- Hey! Don't say anything
to the girls.
You have to stay calm,
we don't want them to panic.
- Okay, sure, whatever.
- Joe, are you okay?
- Over here!
- Wait, wait, wait.
- Where have you been?
- What's going on?
- Stop it. Stop screaming!
- What?
- Are you all right?
- Matt?
- I think I just shit my pants.
- Is Matt okay?
- Trey, hold on.
- Yeah, yeah, he's good.
- Did you guys find it?
- Yeah, we did.
But we should probably
get back to the cabin now.
- Why?
- I'm not staying here.
- What's going on?
- There's something...
In the woods.
- Like an animal? What's...
- We're in the woods,
what did you expect?
- Yeah, but don't worry.
It was just a little scream.
- A scream?
- Yeah, bigfoot in a cave.
- Is this a joke?
- No, this is serious.
We gotta get our stuff,
we gotta back up and leave now.
- We're leaving tonight?
We just got here.
- I think it's safer not
to hit the roads tonight.
- What are you talking about?
- Everybody stays in the cabin.
I'm sure everything
will be fine.
- I agree with Matt,
we shouldn't leave if it's dark.
- What the hell?
No, we leave now!
- Joe, can you calm down?
Nobody's hurt and
you're overreacting as usual.
- Whatever!
- Teddy ran away, Jess.
- I know, he was acting weird.
My phone
won't stop recording.
- Trey's cell phone
was doing the same thing.
It's probably
because of this.
- Look at this thing.
- It's crazy, isn't it?
- Matt, can I talk
to you, please?
- Yeah, give me a minute.
- Should I be worried?
- No, I'm sure there's
nothing to worry about
but let me try to find out
what happened back there.
- Okay.
I'll get the bath ready.
Hey, girls!
Check this out!
- What's wrong with you?
Why aren't we leaving tonight?
- Why do you think it took
so long to get here? I got lost.
- What?
- Yes. We only have enough gas
to make it to the first
gas station and I'm not sure
I can find my way in the middle
of the night. If we leave
and we get lost, then we are all
stuck in the woods.
I'm not risking it.
- Why didn't you say it before?
- I didn't think it was
a big deal until now.
We lock ourselves in,
and we'll be fine.
Nobody gets out tonight.
- Shit.
- Let's get inside.
- There it is.
I told you I got it.
- Joe? What the hell
is that?
I mean, look at the size of it
compared to the trees.
- I'm starting to think that
your boss isn't that crazy.
- A big foot?
- Yeah!
- Joe, are you talking
about a bigfoot?
- What else could it be? Huh?
It lives in a cave
in the middle of nowhere.
It's huge and
it's hungry for flesh.
What do you think
it could be then? Huh?
- I'm not sure what to think,
I'll be honest with you.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure
it's his.
What's wrong with it?
- All right,
that's enough for me.
- Are you coming, Matt?
- Yeah, I'll be there
in a minute.
- Hey. Are you okay?
- Yeah. I'm all right.
- Did you find out
what it was?
- No.
Joe thinks it might be
a bigfoot.
- A bigfoot?
- Yeah.
- Whoa. That's funny.
- I know, it's hard
to believe, right?
- It's hard to believe.
- I'm more concerned
about Teddy.
- I'm sure he's okay.
It's not his first time running
away. He'll be back.
- I don't think so.
He's gone.
Jess.
- Hmm?
- I'm tired.
I'm really tired...
Of losing people I love.
The baby, Teddy.
- Matt.
- I'm tired of this.
- Are you trying
to tell me something here?
- I don't think I can go
through this again.
I can't.
I know you wanna have a baby,
but I can't.
I don't think I can.
- Having a family is the most
important thing for me.
And a baby is a gift.
I'll understand
if you don't want to have one
but you better make
your mind up soon.
You might lose someone else
you love.
- Jess.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Damnit.
- What was that?
- Jess? Jess?
- Oh, shit.
- What happened?
Holy shit!
Are you all right?
- What was that?
- Matt?
- Jess?
- Guys, what happened?
- We heard a scream.
- Everything's fine.
I think a bird just went
kamikaze into our window.
- A bird? Jeeze,
i thought it was the...
- No. No, it's not.
Jess, you're sure
you're all right?
- I'm fine.
- Okay.
Joe, come with me.
- Man, that bird
scare the shit out of me.
I thought
it was that bigfoot.
Or whatever it was, you know,
that followed us back here.
- Not the birthday you expected,
isn't it?
- Yo, no. Not at all.
- To your birthday, man.
- Matt, as your best friend
and as your doctor,
don't you think you've been
drinking a lot lately?
I mean, I...
I know you've had
a rough couple of months,
but you got--
- but what, Joe?
But what?
- You need to move on.
You're not the only person
that has lost a baby
and at least,
you can try again.
- And what?
Losing another one?
Take the chance
to lose another one?
- Come on, Matt.
- I'm not gonna have this
conservation with you. I'm not.
- Matt, don't be like this.
- I'm going to bed.
- That's right. Just go.
Walk away.
- Happy birthday, buddy.
- Hide.
- And by the way,
birds don't fly at night.
- I knew it.
I knew it. Goddamm it!
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
- Stupid phone.
Why won't you stop--
- what the hell's going on?
What the hell?
What...
What the hell
is going on here?
Shut up, shut up.
What the hell was that?
Hey!
Who's up?
Hey. Who's down there?
- Die.
Die.
Die. Die.
Die... die...
It's too late.
Die...
- Trey?
What are you doing?
Who are you talking to?
Die? Who's going to die?
You said it was too late.
Too late for what?
What's wrong with you, man?
What the hell is this?
We have to leave this place.
That's right.
Oh god.
Holy shit! You scared
the shit out of me, Julia!
- Who are you screaming at?
- This... creature
was in the cabin.
We're leaving now.
Grab your stuff.
- Have you seen Trey
anywhere?
- Yeah, he's in your room.
- No, he's not.
- What?
I put him to bed
a few minutes ago.
- Not in my bed.
- Julia, what are
you talking about?
- I woke up
and he wasn't there.
- See? Right there.
This is right after
i put him to bed.
What?
- I told you
he didn't go to bed.
Why is he walking
like that?
- Oh, shit.
Where is he going?
Whoa, whoa!
Can you see him?
- Hmm, there.
- No. No, no.
Don't go outside, Trey.
- Why is he going out?
Where is he?
Matt, where is he?
- Over there.
No.
- Trey, where are you going?
- The forest.
- Trey...
- No. No.
- What the hell
is wrong with him?
- Do you have signal?
- No. I don't.
- Trey!
- What's going on?
- Shhh!
Your brother went
for a midnight stroll.
- What?
- That's what's going on.
- Trey!
- Why would he do that?
- You tell me!
- Oh, no.
I told him
not to go outside.
- Trey!
- Stop screaming!
- Trey! Answer me!
Trey, come on...
- Shhh, listen. Listen.
- We need
to get back inside. Now.
- Trey?
Trey, is that you?
- We shouldn't be out here.
- Trey...
Ah, screw this!
I'm going to get him!
- Hey, hey, no!
- What?
- I told you
it was too dangerous.
- Matt,
we gotta do something.
- You and
your stupid monster!
- All right, that's it!
I'm gonna go wake up Joe.
Jess, make sure
she doesn't go in there.
- Okay.
- What's going on?
Trey!
- Julia!
- Jess! Where's Julia?
- She just went in there.
- I told you to keep her here.
- Yeah, I know. She went in,
what do you want me to do?
- Shit!
- What's going on?
- Julia's in the forest.
- What?
You're kidding me right?
- I wish.
- Ah, shit.
I knew we should have left
last night.
- You guys,
get back in the cabin
and try to call for help.
Let's go, Joe.
- What the hell
is going on here?
- Trey?
- I gotta be the dumbest idiot
to follow you.
If I die here, you better tell
my mom it was your fault.
- Hey! I'm not losing
anyone else.
- I'm sorry, Matt.
I'm sorry.
- Julia?
Trey?
Julia?
- I can't believe
we're back in these woods
'cause of that little brat.
- Trey?
- I just don't
understand why he had
to come back.
It doesn't make sense.
- Look, I don't think Trey
knew what he was doing.
- What? Tell me
what's going on here then!
- Trey walked in the forest
like a frickin' zombie.
Like some kind of force
was dragging him in.
He looked like
he was hypnotized.
- What do you mean,
"hypnotized"?
- When I went downstairs,
he kept repeating 'die, die'.
Something was going to die.
Or someone.
- Die?
- I don't know if--
- who's gonna die?
- I don't know!
But there's one thing I know.
This thing, this creature,
whatever it is, was in the cabin
after Trey disappeared.
- What?
- I didn't say anything.
I didn't want
to scare the girls.
- That's great of you.
That's real sweet of you
'cause you scare
the shit out of me now!
- Hey!
- Matt! Don't!
- What do you want from us?
- Look.
- What could they want?
- They're leaving.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Oh, shit, Matt!
Oh! Oh!
Oh my god! Oh my god!
Go, go, go!
Oh! Oh! Oh my god!
- Turn off the light. Turn off
the light! Turn it off!
No, I don't think so.
- Let's get back now.
Let's go!
- No! Not without Trey
and Julia!
- I...
I can't place a call,
my phone
is still recording.
- Try mine.
It might work.
-  911,
what's your emergency?
- Yes, 911!
Yeah, hi!
My name is Jessica Donovan,
we're staying at a cottage
in gracefield, Quebec.
And the address is 11...
1111 ranger lake.
Can you hear me?
Hello? Can you hear?
My brother and his girlfriend
disappeared in the forest
after deciding--
-  I triangulate your location.
- Hello?
Shit! Hello, can you hear?
If you can hear me,
can you just please send help?
-  Madam?
- The call dropped.
The call dropped!
There's no...
There's no signal.
- Oh my god!
Look what I've found.
- Bigfoot sightings?
What the hell is this?
- That's the cabin.
- And...
The cave they went to.
Cornfield.
- Farmer blackburn's property.
- This is insane!
Okay. Matt's boss is a lot
crazier then I thought.
- That's not gonna work.
- Yes, it is gonna work.
The balloons are gonna
track us back to the cabin.
- This is so ridiculous!
- Hey, do you have
a better plan?
'Cause I'm not getting
lost in these woods again.
Let's go. Let's find Trey
and Julia and get out of here.
- Trey?
Where are you?
Trey!
Look,
you don't need to try
and impress me anymore, okay?
I can't even see
the cabin from here!
There you are.
Why did you come back here?
Trey! Can you please answer me?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Trey?
Where the hell did you go?
- Julia! Julia!
Julia!
- Julia!
Where is she?
- You see anything?
- No!
- Julia!
- Where the hell is she?
- She can't be that far.
- I think our minds'
are playing tricks on us.
Let's get out of here.
- No!
No, no. We can't.
- Come on.
Julia!
Joe. Joe...
- Is that Julia's?
- Yeah.
- Julia!
- Oh... my... god...
- What?
- Oh, Matt!
- Holy shit.
What the hell did
they do to her?
- How did her clothes
get up there?
Matt, what's going on?
What happened to her?
- I don't know.
- What the hell was that?
- Trey! Trey!
- No, no, Matt!
- Trey! Where are you?
- Matt!
Matt! Where are you?
- Trey!
- What the hell
happened here?
- He's not here.
Where the hell is he?
- Matt. Let's get
out of here! Now!
- No! I'm not leaving
anybody behind.
- I don't like
this place, man.
I don't think we're gonna
find Trey or Julia here.
- Guys!
- Stop, Matt.
Stop.
- Hey! We can't leave them here.
- No, Matt. But look around you.
Look around here.
The corn is twelve feet tall.
Everywhere you look,
it's the same damn thing!
The only way you're gonna find
someone here,
is with a helicopter.
- What did you say?
- I said that the only way
you're gonna find someone here
is through the air
unless you learned how to fly--
- that's it. That's it.
- What "it"?
- Gimme your phone.
Gimme your phone.
- Matt, it has no reception.
- It doesn't matter.
You just said it,
if we can tie this
to the balloons, right,
and we can get it airborne.
- And then you'll have a whole
perspective on this place.
- Exactly!
- Yes!
- How many balloons
do we have left? Come on.
- We only have two.
- Oh shit!
- What?
- Joe.
- What? What is it?
- Our balloons.
- What the...
- Those are the balloons
we used in the forest.
- Are they doing this to us?
- Who else can it be?
- Why?
- Grab them.
- Yeah, but, how are--
- it doesn't matter.
- How are we gonna get back?
- Just pick them up!
Is it recording?
- Yeah.
- Perfect.
All right, let it go.
- All right.
You really think
this is gonna work?
- Yes. I do.
Don't drop it.
- I'm not gonna drop it.
- Come on. Higher.
- It's working. It's working!
- Holy shit!
- What is that?
- This... this symbol.
- What is it? What?
- I saw this symbol
last night on TV.
Just before Trey disappeared.
- You saw this before?
- Yeah.
- And you're telling
me this now?
- Yeah.
- What does it mean?
- How should I know
what it means, Joe?
What the hell are we
dealing with here?
- Maybe they're trying
to communicate with us.
- They? Who's they?
And what the hell
do they want from us?
- Trey?
- What?
- Trey!
- Where?
- There.
- Trey! Trey!
- Matt!
- Where are you?
- Shit. Matt, hold on!
- Hurry!
- Wait for me!
Shit! Shit!
- Where are you, kid?
- Wait!
Matt, wait up!
- Oh no! Oh no!
Trey!
- Matt!
- Oh god.
Oh god.
- Oh shit.
Oh shit.
- Trey is gone, man.
Can you believe...
- Matt, Matt. Shhh! Shhh!
- Go, go, go!
Ah! Ah!
- Matt! Matt!
Oh shit!
Oh no! Oh no!
- Stop, stop, stop.
Those things
are looking for us.
- Holy shit.
You think we lost them?
- No, I don't think so, Joe.
We can't stay here.
We have to go.
- What's going on?
What just happened?
Where's Trey? Where's Julia?
- I don't know, Joe!
I don't have the answer to that!
But I have
a really weird feeling
that they used
Trey as a messenger.
- A messenger?
- Yes!
When I went downstairs last
night, he wasn't feeling well.
Why? Because they did
something to him.
They gave him a message.
- A message?
- Yes! About this...
This someone, something,
that was going to die.
All this nonsense that he kept
repeating in the basement.
- Why would they use Trey?
- Why?
Because these things are
trying to communicate with us!
You were right about this. They
were listening to us out there.
There's a reason why they gave
us back our balloons
when we needed them.
They wanted us to
see that symbol.
- Yeah but what does
it mean, huh?
- I don't know
what it means.
But it's not important
for now.
- Yes, it is!
Come on, Matt. Think about it.
These things are getting more
and more aggressive
and impatient with us.
We gotta figure it out.
- We will but right now, we just
have to get to the cabin,
get the girls
and get some help.
- And how are we supposed
to do that, huh? Huh?
We have no guide, we have no way
to get back. We're lost.
- Shit.
We can't stay here.
- Oh shit! Shit! Shit!
- What? What?
- The balloons.
They weren't there
a second ago.
- Maybe they'll lead us back
to the cabin.
- No. No!
- Look, Joe.
There's no other option.
I say we go.
- Huh, huh.
- Right?
Let's go before these
things come back.
- No, no, no,
think about it.
- There's no other option.
I'm not staying here.
- They're probably
around us right now.
- I'm not staying here.
I'm going.
- Wait, no, no, no!
Wait, wait!
They are probably
watching us right now!
- Oh shit!
- What's going on?
- I dropped my eye.
- Matt, forget it!
We can't lose time with this.
Let's go!
- It must be here, I need it.
It recorded the whole thing.
- What? I knew it! That's what
the red light was all about.
There it is.
Good. All right.
Okay, let's go!
- We made it.
- Come on!
Liz!
- Joe?
In here.
- Thank god.
- Where we you guys?
- Where's Trey?
- And Julia?
- We couldn't find them.
- What do you mean
you couldn't find them?
- They have to be somewhere.
- We looked everywhere,
we couldn't find them.
Drop it.
- Oh my god. Oh my god.
- I'm sorry, baby.
Jess, calm down.
We did everything we could...
- Tell me this is not happening.
- We have to get out of here.
We have to go get some help.
- I'm not leaving my brother
here. Are you crazy?
- Listen, we can't stay here!
Do you understand me?
- I'm not leaving him.
They might come back.
- Matt, you can't stay here.
- I know but Jess
won't leave her brother.
- Take the camera,
you might need the light.
- Okay, thanks.
I think the gas station
is about 25 miles from here
but I'm not sure where exactly.
- We'll be back soon.
It shouldn't take us too long.
- Yeah, the sooner, the better.
- Yeah.
- Be careful!
- I'm sure Trey and Julia
are gonna be fine.
- That's not reassuring.
- No.
- It doesn't want to start.
- You gotta be kidding me.
- No.
Oh shit!
- What's wrong with it?
- The fuse box fried.
- Shit!
- It's probably another surge.
- But we haven't used this
since we got here.
- It's probably
the same frequency
that fried the fuse box
inside the house.
- So it was caused
by the power surge we got?
- Maybe. Maybe not.
- Can you fix it, baby?
- Yeah,
with my eyes closed.
If I had an other fuse
but I don't.
We truck here, we're not going
anywhere the way it is.
- Shit.
- What do we do now?
- I got an idea.
- You wanna use the bikes?
Come on, Joe!
- What time is it?
- Shit! My watch
is still messed up.
- Look, we got about
five hours before sunset.
Liz and I can make it to
the gas station within three--
- Joe, I don't think
this is a good--
- Matt! We have no choice.
- Liz! I think
you should stay with us.
- Hey, I'm not gonna
let him go by himself
with these things around.
Plus he needs me
to cover his ass.
- Guys, we'll be back in a
couple hours with some help.
- Joe, you stay on the road,
no matter what you stay
on the road, okay?
- Don't worry, man.
We'll be back in a couple hours.
Come on, Liz. Let's go!
- Joe?
Joe?
- Whoa. Oh, there.
Press stop.
- Whoa.
- Oh my god!
- I knew I heard something.
What happened to Liz and Joe?
- I'm not sure.
- And what happened
to my brother and Julia?
- I don't know. I mean, look,
Jess, we... we found them
in this cornfield.
- What?
- After we discovered
that symbol.
- No, no, no. No, no!
What happened to him?
What was this symbol? What does
it have to do with anything?
- I don't know.
- Matt! What's going on!
- I don't know! Okay?
So can you calm down
and help me find some clues.
I would really
appreciate it.
-  Matt! Watch out!
- Shit!
I thought I deleted this.
Ah, oh my god.
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- I'll see if I can find
anything on Joe's camera.
- Early this morning
an American satellite
was destroyed by what
authorities are calling
an unidentified object.
- Hold on!
- Images taken by
the satellite itself...
- This?
- Yeah. Play it again.
- ... authorities are calling
an unidentified object.
Images taken by the satellite
itself moments before
it was destroyed seems
to indicate that a collision
between the satellite
and the object was the cause.
- Stop!
Holy shit.
- Oh my god!
Ah! Oh my god!
It tried to grab you!
- Shit.
It wasn't trying to grab me.
- Matt!
Matt, open the door!
Matt, please.
What are you doing in there?
Why did you lock yourself in?
I'm really worried
so open the door.
Matt? Tell me
what's going on.
Tell me what's going on.
- The symbol.
- Matt, you're really,
really scaring me right now.
Open the door! Open up!
Matt! Open the door!
What are you doing in there?
- We're leaving
this place in 30 seconds!
- What? Can you tell
me what's going on?
- It has been looking
for this rock the whole time.
- Holy shit!
What do you think it is?
- Maybe some kind of
radio transmitting device
or something.
Yeah.
Look, there's only one way
out of this.
We're gonna give them
this rock
but only if they give us back
our friends.
Otherwise, we're not giving
them anything.
Wait! Wait!
- What?
- No. Not that way.
We'll take the basement.
- No.
- They might be right outside.
I think it's safer.
- Okay, let's go.
Oh I don't wanna go.
- Let me go first. Here.
Grab the camera.
Let's go, follow me.
We saw these creatures today,
in a cornfield.
We have to find a way to make it
there without them seeing us.
I think that's why they have
your brother and Julia.
Turn off the light.
- What's your plan?
- The cornfield is about
a quarter mile from here.
There's a farm
on the edge it.
We have to find a way to make it
there and call for help.
- Come on, are you sure? Okay.
- Yes.
- What?
What are you doing?
- Oh my god.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- We have to go.
Matt, what the hell
are you doing?
What's the matter, Matt?
- They're here.
Go, go, go!
Let's get out of here.
Go upstairs!
Run, run, run!
- Oh my god! Oh my god!
Oh my god!
- Holy shit!
- What the hell
is going on?
- Holy shit!
- What's going on?
What the...
- Oh my god!
Take cover, Jess!
- We're gonna die!
Ah! Make it stop! Please!
Ah! Make it stop!
Make it stop!
- Jess! Jess!
Oh shit!
Are you all right? Hey!
- I wanna go.
Let's go! Let's go!
- We gotta go.
We gotta go!
We're good.
What? What?
What's going on?
Holy shit.
- What happened? Matt,
what happened to Liz and Joe?
- We need to get into
that forest. Let's go, now!
Run! Run!
- Oh shit! Oh shit!
- Go, go, go!
- Oh my god.
- Shit. What? What?
We can't stay.
- I can't breathe.
I can't.
I can't breathe.
Matt!
Let him go.
Let him go!
Matt!
No!
- No, no, no!
- Run!
Quick! Quick!
- Oh shit!
Keep going!
Go! Go, go, go!
Go, go!
- Matt!
Get up! Get up!
Let's go! Matt!
Give them the rock.
- No. They have to give us
our friends first.
- Shhh! Shhh! Jess!
Shhh! Shhh!
Jess, please.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I'm not gonna lose you.
I'm not gonna lose you too.
Jess! Jess! Jess!
Jess!
Jess! Jess!
Jess! Jess! Jess!
Where is my wife?
Where are my friends?
I'm not giving you this rock
until you give me my wife.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I lost you baby.
I'm... I'm sorry we...
We didn't know.
- Matt? Matt?
- Liz!
- Joe!
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, yeah, I'm fine.
- You're alive!
You're alive!
- Joe, is that you?
- Trey?
- Julia?
- What happened to us?
- I don't remember.
-  This is lieutenant Stewart
from the Canadian air force.
We got a 911 emergency call
from Jessica Donovan.
Please follow our light
and regroup all
to the same location
until further instructions.
I repeat: Follow our light and
regroup at the same location
and wait until further
instructions.
We are going to find a place
to land and come and get you.
You're safe now.
You're going home.
- Hey.
Closed captioning pmt