All units, be on the lookout
for a missing person.
Female, 18, about 5'7".
Last seen wearing a white dress.
She is considered unstable
and possibly dangerous.
What the hell?
Must be that girl.
Come on.
Alright, little girl...
No! Get your...!
Get off me! No! No! No!
Careful.
Get her in!
No! No! No!
No! No!
Sweetheart, behave.
You're going...
Watch her head.
Get the door.
No!
Cuff her.
Get off me! No!
Get the cuffs on her.
No! Get off! Let me go!
Let me go!
What's your name?
Kristen.
She belongs in jail,
not here.
They're taking her to
the ward. She can't hurt anyone there.
I'm Roy.
Welcome to paradise.
So, I can be your buddy
or I can be a thorn in your side.
It all depends on whether
you're willing to follow the rules.
Come to visit me.
This is the ward, your new home.
Come on.
OK. Kristen, huh?
Alright, come with me.
You're free to use the recreation room
and the courtyard
any time 8 a.m. to 10 p.m.
But at night we're locked down
and you'll be confined to your room.
This will be your room.
Get some rest.
Kristen?
Most patients prefer the bed.
I'm Dr. Gerald Stringer.
I'll be treating you
while you're here.
Good morning. How did you sleep?
Who came in here last night?
What do you mean?
Somebody came in here
and hid my blanket.
The door was locked all night,
wasn't it, Nurse?
Yes, Doctor, always.
Here, take these.
No.
It's not a request.
What are they?
Something to help you get better.
You're right... I feel better already.
You'd do well to follow the rules
around here, young lady.
That'll be all for now,
Nurse Lundt.
Yes, Doctor.
Why am I here?
That's the $64,000 question.
I am ready.
Are you a member
of the theatrical profession?
Yes.
Who's the new girl?
Some runaway.
Let's see how long this one lasts.
Who are you?
I'm no one.
Well, why are you here?
I'm not. I'm leaving.
Are you gonna save us?
From what?
Whoo-hoo-hoo.
Come on, Emily, knock it off.
Let's not scare off the new girl
on her first day.
Hi.
My name's Iris.
It's Kristen, right?
I saw your name on the door.
Looks like Iris has herself
a new girlfriend.
Jealous?
Please.
Don't make me throw up.
You two are disgusting.
Looks like it's time
to see the doctor.
Right this way.
How are you feeling?
Have you met the others yet?
Why am I here?
I'm hoping we can get to the bottom
of that mystery together.
Let's discuss what happened
yesterday, Kristen.
What's the first thing you remember?
Fire.
And before that?
Tell me about this farmhouse,
the one you burned down.
Why do you think you went there?
You had the address for the place
written on the palm of your hand.
It must have some significance.
No.
Do you think
you'd been there before?
I...
I don't know.
Burning down that house
won't destroy those memories.
You've got to deal with them.
Let's deal with them together, OK?
No. No!
Often the root of a problem like this
lies with an emotional trauma.
There is no emotional trauma.
How do you know?
Look, why don't you just let me go?
I'll stay out of trouble.
And then you never
have to think of me again.
I'm trying to help you.
I don't need your help!
Yet, here you are...
confused and disturbed.
I'm not crazy.
We don't like to use that word here.
Who's we? Your friends
behind the mirror over there?
Thatta girl.
Make you feel good.
Nighty-night.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Going somewhere, darling?
We can do this all night long.
Let go of me!
Get off me!
Got some clothes for you.
What is her story?
Oh, she's just crazy.
Like me. And you.
And like all of us.
¤ Boom-boom,
ain't it great to be crazy? ¤
Speak for yourself, lunatic.
¤ Boom-boom,
ain't it great to be crazy?! ¤
Stop it. You're gonna
make my ears bleed.
¤ BOOM-BOOM, AIN'T IT... ¤
Ow! You...! You bitch!
Oh, I'm sorry,
did I hurt you?
Did I hurt your little hand?
Don't!
You'll get us all in trouble.
Come on, now,
don't you think that'd be fun?
If you and I went
and saw a movie together,
we could snuggle up
real close in the dark.
We'd just be by ourselves.
I wanna draw you.
Come on. It'll be fun.
Just... Just act natural.
Look up.
They've been here before.
Who are they?
Those are the sad people.
Always so sad.
He's a great doctor.
I overheard the staff
talking about him.
Apparently the way
he's dealing with us
is some sort of
experimental therapy.
Futuristic kind of stuff.
And what do I need to say to this guy
to get out of lockdown?
I mean, you know,
to get night privileges.
No one has night privileges.
I just saw this girl walking around
in the halls last night.
That's impossible.
And someone came into my room
the other night.
¤ Someone came
into my room... ¤
Just ignore her.
She never makes any sense.
¤ Someone
¤ Someone... ¤
Listen, don't let this place
get to you.
¤ Someone... ¤
You stay locked up long enough
and you start to believe
that you're nuts.
¤ Run
¤ Run, baby, run
¤ Oh, come back to me
¤ Bring your kisses to me
¤ Run, baby, run
¤ Back into my arms
¤ I need you, baby
¤ Run, baby, run
¤ I don't mean maybe
¤ Back into my arms
¤ And even though you hurt me
¤ I still love you
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
¤ It's true even though I know... ¤
It's OK. I've got you.
I don't like the dark.
Shhh.
Bad things happen in the dark.
See, it's OK.
It's alright.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Ah!
Did you need some help?
Just keep a lookout.
Why are they giving us
all this stuff?
They don't know what they're doing.
Thorazine, Mellaril.
Now they give us this.
It's tasty.
Got anything for me?
You're not supposed
to be in here.
Shut up.
You seem to be getting
in the middle of things, new girl.
If I were you, I'd watch out.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
What is it? What's the matter?
Something was in here.
Listen to me, something was in there.
Something not... not right,
not... not human.
It's going to be OK.
We just need to calm you down.
Please, you've got to believe me.
Please, wait, please...
Wait, please...
Please don't do this to me.
Relax. It won't hurt you.
Call Dr. Stringer, please.
I'm right here, I'm right here.
Please... Please...
This is a bit. Bite down on it
or you'll bite your tongue off.
No, please...
The medications
aren't working as I'd hope.
This treatment should be beneficial.
I thought they stopped
using electroshock.
Just look at her.
She was all riled up before,
now she's docile as a lamb.
Hell, I wish they'd do it
to all the patients here,
just fry the crazy
right out of them.
Come on, sleepyhead.
It's time to wake up. Come on.
Come on.
So, since we have a new member,
let's go over the rules.
Everyone gets a chance to talk.
No interrupting.
Just say what's on your minds.
Who'd like to begin?
Emily?
What did you do to Kristen?
We had to have a little unscheduled
therapy last night.
Is that what you call it?
It's nothing to be
alarmed about, Emily.
Sometimes when you take people away,
they don't come back.
Tammy didn't come back.
Who's Tammy?
She's the last one that got out.
What did you say?
Iris, you know we don't discuss
people who aren't present.
Wait. Why can't we talk
about Tammy?
Who's Tammy?
Zoey, how do you feel
about all this?
Zoey?
OK.
Let's discuss what happened yesterday,
shall we, in the showers?
Kristen?
Well... I didn't see a thing.
I believe her.
Great. That's someone
you want on your side.
Are you OK?
I don't know what's going on
in this place.
It'll be OK.
I can tell you are strong.
See you later, alligators.
I'm off to what should be
my last session with Stringer.
What do you mean?
I mean, I'm being released.
That's impossible.
I've been here longer than you.
Stringer told you
he was releasing you?
Not in those words, but he said
I'm making great progress.
You're not going anywhere.
Yes, I am.
How did you get him
to release you, though?
How did you act? What did you say?
I didn't act cured, Kristen,
if that's what you're getting at.
I am cured.
I'm ready.
Do you really think
she's getting outta here?
How have you been feeling?
Better.
I've been drawing a lot.
And I'm getting along with everybody,
even the new girl.
I have some of
your latest work here.
Where did you get those?
You really managed
to capture her essence.
I was just fooling around.
You're really quite talented, Iris.
I'm practically cured,
don't you think?
That's an old one.
I'm not like that anymore, really.
You're making considerable progress.
So I can go?
Let's see how things go today, hmm?
The others didn't believe me.
They don't think that I'm better.
Why are you doing that?
I'd like to try something
a little different this time.
What is that?
It's a metronome.
Listen to the rhythm.
It'll help you to relax.
OK, close your eyes.
I haven't had any problems
in a while.
I'm feeling better. Healthier.
Focus on your home.
Imagine it.
Imagine your parents there
waiting for you.
I'm starting to get sleepy.
Can you describe your home for me?
What color is your house?
We live... in a little white house.
I have to... go to sleep.
It's September 3, 1958.
It's night time.
You are asleep in your bedroom.
She's asleep in my office.
Where did she go?
Find her.
Where are we going?
No.
This isn't right.
No! No! No! No!
No! No!
Oh, please don't.
Please don't hurt me, please.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
I just wanna go home.
No! Oh, my God, No! Please!
Please don't do this!
Please! Please!
No. Help!
No! No!
It's alright.
Where's Iris?
She's not back yet?
OK, time for bed.
Where's Iris?
Come on, time for bed.
Go to sleep.
Anyone see Iris today?
Maybe they let her go home.
No way.
Nurse Lundt.
Please, Nurse Lundt.
Where's Iris?
If she went home, why didn't
she take her sketchbook?
You can't get them to tell you anything
around here.
Trust me, I've tried.
Kristen, tell me
what's bothering you.
Did you treat a girl named Alice?
Where did you hear that name?
That's who attacked me
in the showers.
You're not gonna answer me, are you?
What happened to Iris?
How many girls have disappeared
at this hospital?
Nurse Lundt was wiping someone's
name off the door when I got here.
Well, you were heavily sedated.
I'm sure you believe
you saw what you say.
It happened.
What happened to them?
To whom?
To Iris, Alice, Tammy.
Are they dead?
Why would you think they're dead?
There's a ghost in here.
A ghost?
What does it look like?
A girl.
The girl that attacked me
in the shower.
The one I see in the halls.
Same with the other girls.
I know they've seen her too.
So, please, tell me
what's going on here.
Please.
I can't give you the answers, Kristen.
You have to find them for yourself.
Goddammit! Tell me!
Take Kristen back to her room.
You just don't give up, do you?
Let go of me!
Who's Alice?
You all know she's here,
so why won't you answer me?
Look at me!
Sorry, I don't converse
with loonies.
Don't you ever call me that!
Don't do this.
Tell me who Alice is.
Alice Hudson was here. She was
one of us but she's gone now.
Gone?
Where?
She got out, they let her out.
I'm getting outta here.
Tonight.
I'm gonna find Iris.
Really?
Really.
You can't get out.
Watch me.
You coming with me?
How?
Zoey, give me your penny.
She won't let us leave.
Hello?
Leonard! Yes,
thanks for calling me back.
I need a consult.
Still the same lost causes, yes.
The problem is that
things have begun to escalate.
Alright. Let's see.
I need you to shove this in here like this
so it seems locked but you can
still open it from the outside.
OK.
And then you're gonna get into bed.
Make sure you have all your clothes on,
but hide it with the covers.
And then I'm gonna come
and get you after bed check.
Then what?
Then we get Iris and get outta here.
Why do you care so much about Iris?
I care about getting us all
out of here alive.
Open.
Alright, we gotta go now. Come on.
I don't think this is the right way.
Ah, in here.
It's a morgue.
Hide!
Someone's been in there.
Come on,
let's take a look around.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Do you see anything?
No.
Emily?
Is that you?
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Alice?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Nice try.
Kristen!
Emily! What happened?
Those orderlies caught me.
And they hurt my arms.
Did you find Iris?
No.
She's gone.
She's not coming back.
Look, if we don't get out of here,
we're next.
We're not getting out.
We have to try again.
Nobody... gets out.
Hello!
So... Roy...
Not interested.
You didn't even hear me out.
Fine. Shoot.
Well, I know you said you wouldn't
date any of us inside the ward.
But I just know I'm getting out soon
and I thought maybe you could
call me some time.
There is no way I will
ever, ever date you.
Got it?
But I...
No! Not ever.
Now, leave me alone. I'm swamped
here and I don't have time for this.
Tom Stewart killed me.
Tom Stewart killed me!
So, you and cuckoo bird have fun
sneaking out last night?
Go away.
You could have gotten us
all in trouble.
We were looking for Iris.
And?
We couldn't find her.
Well, you probably weren't
looking in the right places.
Not with Magellan over there.
What are you saying?
Nothing.
I saw the two of you
sneaking around last night.
Shut up.
They're watching.
Well, can you blame them?
Just because I was brave enough
to go through with it...
Well, maybe next time
you'll do us all a favor and get it right.
Boo-hoo. Timid little Zoey.
Why don't you crawl into your shell
and hide, just like a little turtle?
Why don't you leave her alone?
What's the matter... Daddy didn't
pay enough attention to you?
Mind your own business.
Why don't you leave us all alone?
I mean, nobody likes you.
Well, you're just jealous.
Of what?
Of me.
You've been jealous of me
since I got here.
I am tired of putting up with
your pathetic behavior, and...
I can't hear you!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
They're all just jealous of me.
Let's see Roy say no to this.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
No! Ah, no!
Please let me go.
Please let me out of here!
Alice, it wasn't my idea, I swear!
They made me do...
No, stop! No!
No, please don't do this! No!
Just let me go! Alice!
No, please don't do this!
No! Please don't do this!
No! No!
Where's Sarah?
Sarah? No!
If Alice got Sarah,
she'll get us all.
No! No, no, no, no!
Alice Hudson.
This was hers?
I didn't touch her!
It was Sarah and... the other girls!
What did you do to her?
I don't know what she's talking about.
Yes, you do.
You shut up, Zoey!
This isn't a game!
What did you do to her?
Why does she want to kill us?
What did they do to her?
Zoey...
Look, please, Zoey...
I need to know.
A-Alice was bad.
She hurt us.
She hurt us all the time.
Tammy told us what to do.
Tammy was here before you.
She said she could make it stop.
It was her idea.
So... we got rid of her.
Alice?
What?
I know where your bunny is.
You found it?
Yeah.
It's in Tammy's room.
That's mine. You can't have it!
We all helped.
And now she's going to kill us all.
We had to.
She was horrible.
Then why is she after me?
What's it matter? We're all dead.
Emily... Emily!
Emily!
We have to get out of here. OK?
But what about Emily?
We'll get her.
Alright?
Come on.
Emily, what are you doing?
I'm not strong like you.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Put the knife down.
I can't!
We're gonna get out of here.
Emily!
No, no, no, no! This can't be happening.
Please don't let her get me!
I don't wanna die!
Zoey...
Do you trust me?
Open the door.
Where did you get that?
Open the door now.
Calm down. Don't do
anything you'll regret.
We have an incident in progress.
Open the goddamn door!
Hey...
Hey, back up!
Easy...
Back up!
Calm down.
Back up.
Go to the wall.
Back up! Against the wall.
Come on.
Back up!
Back up. Back up!
You can't do this.
Watch me!
You're only hurting yourself.
What are you gonna do, Kristen?
Where are you gonna go?
Away from here.
C'mon, drop the knife.
No! No, let me go! You don't get it!
You don't get it!
Alice Hudson is trying to kill us!
Enough.
You can't be serious.
No, please!
Alright, Kristen. Kristen, Kristen...
I need you to calm down.
That girl is a hopeless case
and you know it.
Luckily that's not your call to make.
You honestly think you can cure her?
I have to try.
I need more time with her, that's all.
You're as hopeless as she is.
You could spend 100 years with her...
Ahh!
No! No!
Please... please listen to me!
Get her in a straitjacket
and lock her in her room.
Doctor.
You don't understand...
No... we...
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
You need to get some rest.
Come on.
Mmm. Mmm!
Down the hatch.
There. Now, that wasn't so bad, was it?
Sleep tight, sugar.
Where are we going?
We're getting out of here.
Open this door now!
Stop!
Son of a bitch! Don't you close that...!
Don't you close that goddamn...!
He's really mad.
Hey! Get back here!
Wait!
We're trapped!
Maybe not. Here, come on.
Come on!
Zoey, take this.
Come on.
Maybe this goes to the first floor, right?
I'll go first.
Alright. Come on.
Send it back as fast as you can, alright?
I will.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hey!
Open this door!
Fuck.
Come on.
Zoey?
Zoey!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What's going on?
What?!
Answers. No lies this time
or I swear to God...
Now!
The truth.
Your name...
...is Alice Lee Hudson.
May I?
You were abducted from your home
the night of September 3, 1958.
I'm Kristen,
not Alice.
I'm Kristen!
You were left chained up in the
basement of an abandoned farmhouse
for nearly two months...
the same farmhouse you burned down.
You were only 11 years old.
Half starved, sick with fever,
trapped in the darkness,
it was a waking nightmare.
Your only escape was into delusion.
In order to survive the trauma,
your psyche fractured.
You suffer from multiple
personality disorder.
Each personality took
a piece of this nightmare
and locked it away from you
for your own protection.
But the new personalities
became so... dominant
they completely overwhelmed
Alice's personality.
I know it hasn't been pleasant.
But my techniques are helping you.
After several years of therapy,
we've been able to isolate
your different identities.
We'd just begun to single them out
and eliminate them
through some experimental techniques
when you, Kristen, appeared.
I didn't just appear!
Your psyche invented Kristen
to protect itself
from having to relive this trauma.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
And now it's time to say goodbye.
Please don't kill me.
Don't move. It's OK.
She's the last one who got out.
What did you say?
Iris, you know we don't
discuss people who aren't present.
She can't remember the rules
because she's the crazy one
around here, you know?
That's enough.
Is she cured?
She'll probably need
a lifetime of therapy,
but she's no longer a danger to herself.
She is, essentially...
your daughter again.
Can we please see her now?
Alice?
Honey, are you OK?
We love you, sweetheart.
Mom?
Dad?
Oh, honey...
I figured you'd... want
your things around you.
And I put this one
back together for you too.
Thank you.
I think I remember...
What do you remember?
Everything.
The old farmhouse.
This place.
The others.
Emily, Sarah, Iris,
Kristen...
You can forget all about them now.
When can I get out of here?
I really just wanna go home.
Dr. Stringer says two, maybe three days.
I think that's enough
visiting for today.
We'll let you get some rest.
Couldn't we stay just a little bit longer?
You'll have her all to yourself
in no time.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
SUBTITLES BY : manishpk2007