Close your eyes...
...and place your attention on your breath.
Breathe in...
and out.
Just put your attention on the breath
coming into your body as you inhale.
It's clear.
Nothing.
And as you breathe out...
...the air
that comes out of you is black.
And that black is any anxiety, stress,
any worries that you carry.
And as you breathe out,
feel it leave your body.
Breathe in clear air
and breathe out the black.
Breathe in clear air.
Breathe out...
There I am standing
in front of this old
nothing house, staring at it,
and this bloke comes over.
And I recognize him, you know?
Older, but I recognize him.
I said, "It's me, Paul Emery.
I used to live in that house."
And he goes, "No. No, you didn't."
I said, "You're Chris."
"Chris. You had that German Shepherd."
He says, "How did you know that?"
"We lived in this house for years."
- This old fellow...
- You heading to WA for work?
No.
Never actually been there before.
Yourself?
Home. Headed home.
No, I just had to, uh, clear out...
Clear out of Queensland.
Sort myself a car.
Some place to stay and that.
I'm Paul.
Henry.
Turn her off again.
And again.
Yeah. Let's hear her, mate.
I need an address for
the transfer of ownership.
Yeah.
- I can put down a motel?
- I don't know about that.
- That's where I'm living. A motel.
- Can't put down a motel.
I've got a PO box you can use,
put that down while he sorts himself out.
- Okay.
- Thanks.
Thanks, Henry.
All right.
$1,600.
- Here, mate. That's for you.
- Nah.
Come on, mate.
I mean, you really helped me out.
No.
What do you do for work, Henry?
Everything I know is in my hands.
Can't hardly work now though.
I'll be fucked in a few years' time.
And why's that?
Can't fuckin' breathe, mate.
I know what it's like to be
on the other side of things.
You got your last few fuckin' dollars
in an envelope there.
I see it all over you.
Paul Emery?
I can't, uh,
take your call at the moment.
If you leave me a message,
I'll endeavor to call you back later.
Henry, it's Paul.
I need to talk to you about something.
I might need to shift out of the motel.
So give us a ring back when you get this.
Okay. Talk soon.
So it's just a bit further up here.
There's a house. You can drop me off.
All right, I have to tell you, Henry...
I came out here
to do a job for some people.
And there's a mate of mine.
Mark. He asked me if I knew anyone
who could handle a bit of work.
I talked to him about you.
Yeah, just here is good.
Yeah, this is good. Just here.
What kind of work?
I have to let him tell ya.
I don't do violence.
No, Henry, come on. It's not like that.
We'll meet him tomorrow.
He'll tell you all about it.
Have you dyed your hair?
What?
Yeah, I just went a bit darker.
It looks good.
Thanks.
Tell him we're on.
Yep.
Great. I'll see you tomorrow.
Thanks for the lift.
- Where's Paul?
- He couldn't make it.
Get in.
Put your seat belt on.
I don't do violence.
No. I've heard.
Fat cunt.
What are we doing here?
Wait here.
How you doin', Mark? Good?
Why'd you call me?
Look, I've got your passports ready.
They're all clean and unmarked.
And I'm so sorry I couldn't get the money.
- I'm sorry.
- Don't be sorry. Why?
I tried everything I could.
- But...
- I'll get it for you Tuesday.
By the way,
there's a girl shifting gear around
out of Central Massage.
Who?
You remember Letessia?
- Who?
- Letessia.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
She's dealing out of the rooms.
- Next week, Ken.
- 12:00 sharp?
- What will you do? Thank you.
- Get your money.
No car parks from now on. Fuck.
Shift around gear. Is that it?
No, we don't fuckin' touch it.
You don't use when you work with us, okay?
I've heard that you don't have
many acquaintances, which is good for us.
Works well.
'Cause you don't discuss
this work with anyone.
Open that.
It's blank.
It's just here.
You know,
he's in, uh, trouble. Old mate. Paul.
That's why they had to bring him out here.
What's wrong?
If he contacts you and it's not
through me, just let me know.
Don't you go tell Paul
what I said about him.
Where's your place?
Little piece of fluff.
Thanks.
One, two, three, four, five.
I'm a sworn member
of the Western Australian Police,
conducting duties
at the Undercover Crimes Unit
in the investigation into
the abduction and murder
of James Liston on the 12th of May, 2002.
Today's date is May 6, 2010.
My CO number is 452
and I'm using the assumed name
of Mark Frame.
Old mate, he called me last night.
I let it go to voicemail
like... like you said.
Uh, he wanted me to, uh,
to collect this, though.
Yeah, I'll take that.
He's at a property
out of town for a while.
What?
I thought I saw a car.
What'd it look like?
Ah, it's a van. It's turned off now.
Hey, just hold on a sec.
All right, Henry?
Have you seen the sea?
Hey.
Hey, Gary.
This, um, came for Paul yesterday.
Henry.
Come here.
This is Henry Teague.
That's Gary.
You can't come in here dressed like that.
Get yourself some proper clothes.
You look like a fuckin' criminal.
Seriously, sort it out. Sit down.
About Paul.
He has issues in the past
and we have to resettle him.
That creates an opening.
We're a closed group.
We don't often let people in,
and when we do, we take care of our own.
How's that sound to you, Henry?
Yeah, why... Yeah, why not?
Look, Mark. I don't have enough money
to buy new clothes, mate.
- I can't fuckin' afford that, you know...
- Ah, mate. Mate, shh, listen. Here. Look.
Yeah, don't worry about it.
I'll look after you.
See?
Wait. I've gotta ask you something.
That fella up there, Gary,
all right, he's the head here, okay?
But there are people who he answers to
and they answer to people above them.
But he told me to ask you
if you'd done time before.
Yeah, I have, yeah.
Mm-hmm. What for?
Been in and out
a few times, nothing serious.
So no longer stints then?
I did time for an assault
up in the NT, okay?
That's why no fucking violence, you know,
because of the time for repeat offenders.
If you've done longer stints,
just fuckin' tell me, okay?
Don't wait for me to ask you.
How long for?
Two years.
It was at a family crisis center
and there was this fella
who kept chattin' about my
fuckin' missus all the time.
I went for him.
He ran off into the trees,
I went after him.
Yeah, I don't fuck...
I don't care what you done, okay?
What I care about is
you being honest with me.
Yeah. Be honest with me.
That's all I ask, mate, serious. Here.
Cheers.
What?
Just... Nothin', man. All right.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Oi!
What did you do?
Get off the fuckin' table. Get...
Here. Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Come here. Sit on the... Stand there.
You've got bare feet.
- What did you do that for?
- I didn't mean it.
Fuckin' hell.
Can you just pay attention?
All right?
If I cut myself, whose fault is it?
Fuck.
What are you gonna do next time?
- Clean it up.
- No, pay attention.
All right. Come here.
Listen. Look at me.
Sorry I sweared at you, all right?
Go put your shoes on.
Hey, you want me to
teach you something I learned at work?
Okay, you gotta close your eyes, yeah?
Close your eyes and you gotta breathe in,
and when you breathe in,
you're gonna imagine that
you're breathing in really clear air.
You gonna get out in a sec?
And then when you breathe out, you're...
you're gonna breathe out all the black...
Did you know...
...dark, bad air.
What?
That there's a frog that makes this sound?
And that's all the things
you don't like.
Up top. Oh, don't hurt me.
- I'm not trying to hurt you.
- Like when you're angry...
You're getting it in my beard!
...or when you're scared and stuff.
- Close your eyes. Trust me.
- No.
Things you don't like
and then you breathe in the clear air...
...and out the blackness.
There you go.
Your whole body's gonna relax
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
from your feet, your knees,
your hips,
your stomach, your chest.
In the clear air...
...out the black...
Do you need a hand?
Sorry.
Ah, I'm just fucking with you.
You look good. Come on.
Now he's gonna make me go shopping.
Hey.
Shut the fuckin' door.
- What's going on here?
- Sit down.
Hand over your phones.
What do you need our phones for?
Unlock them.
What do you need them for?
We're deleting all of Paul's contacts.
He's downstairs. Give him this.
John's taken care of everything.
Have a drink with Paul
and then we're taking him to the airport.
And you, do whatever Mark tells you to do.
There you fuckin' are.
Sit down.
- Hey, Henry.
- How you doing?
All right, there's ten grand in there.
Passport's been issued.
Ticket to the UK as well.
And your visa's good for a year.
Listen, mate, whatever this is about,
I don't want to know about it.
We don't need to know.
You told John and that's all that matters.
Okay?
And he reckons it'll all be over
by the time you get back.
We've all got a history, mate.
We've all got a past.
And now you're nobody. Woo-hoo.
Cheer up, man.
I'm gonna get us a drink.
Henry...
Trust Mark.
Trust Mark. Yeah?
If you're honest...
If you're honest with these guys,
you'll be looked after, mate.
You'll be looked after.
What are we doing out here?
We're making sure that Paul's clean.
Who's John?
He's your employer.
Sorry, I can be a bit of a cunt.
I've had issues myself in the past.
This is the only family I've ever had.
So, listen, if you have any issues,
if you need help or what have you,
just come out here and you wait,
and I'll find you, brother.
After the child
was abducted from the underpass,
he was questioned several times
due to his record.
He refused psychological testing.
He stated he had a history
of violent of fences.
There's an assault in the NT.
Details aren't listed.
We've been tasked P28
to reassess for the coronial inquest.
At the time of the abduction,
P28's file was closed
after detectives found
insufficient time or evidence
for him to be considered
a person of interest.
He has since relocated
to Western Australia.
We've been tasked with P27.
He has a history of assault
and sexual violence.
His movements place him
in the region, the bypass road
on the morning of the 12th of May, 2002.
We're tasked with P26.
He has a lengthy history
of domestic assault charges.
There are currently four AVOs
ascribed to him.
Mark.
Thank you for everything
you've done on this case.
It's your groundwork got us to this point,
so you should be proud of that.
See you on the other side.
Flying back to Queensland?
Hey!
We burnt your car.
The decision is we can't have him
in densely populated areas,
so isolate him further.
Downside is we can't have
physical surveillance in remote areas,
which means you'll be
unprotected and unobserved
apart from the recording equipment.
The whole operation hinges
on you getting closer with him.
I know you fuckin' know this.
Don't find yourself in terrain
that you're unfamiliar with.
Weigh the balance of the closeness you
could form against your own vulnerability.
Fuck!
I said wait in the car.
You were taking ages.
Could've been one of those silent alarms.
Ah, I sorted that ages ago.
Here. I forgot your brand.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Here you go.
- Thanks, mate.
- Do you want a smoke?
- Nah. I quit.
Do you want a smoke?
Nah. I quit.
I couldn't find a job
anywhere before this.
You got a criminal record,
you're fucked these days.
My dad was in the Army.
Thought about joining the Reserves myself.
I did all the tests.
I failed the psych
'cause I fuckin' sleepwalk.
Do I look like a monster?
What?
I can taste with my feet
and hear with my fur.
- What am I?
- What?
A moth.
You're a pain in the arse,
that's what you are.
No, here, here. Here.
All right, mate. See you Thursday.
This is Detective Senior Constable
Kate Rylett
in the presence of Detective
Senior Constable Graham Ikin.
We are carrying out a timing
of the movements
of POI 28, Henry Teague,
on the 12th May, 2002.
P28 claims to have left
his home at 2:50 p.m.
and returned at 5:30 p.m.
He drove along the bypass
towards a relative's house,
he parked and collected an engine part.
He returned along the same road,
passing the bus stop at the underpass,
where the victim was last seen
between 4:05 and 4:10 p.m.
He claims not to have seen the child,
but places himself driving past
at the same time the child was
observed by other witnesses,
including those on a passing bus.
That bus wasn't taking passengers.
It drives through
the underpass at 4:15 p.m.
A number of witnesses
on that bus saw the boy.
He was waiting by the side of the road
with a man standing behind him,
leaning against a pillar of the underpass,
his leg bent behind him like a stork.
A second bus passes at 4:18 p.m.
There are no sightings of either the boy
or the man from that last bus
which means in those three minutes,
between 4:15 to 4:18 p.m., he's taken.
He claimed that a camera,
angled at the road,
would've seen his car
driving through the site.
That camera was not operational.
He... He's only placed himself at the scene
because he thinks
he was recorded passing through it.
P28 claimed he drove
through the site without stopping,
proceeding directly to
the home of an elderly friend
with whom he spent the next half hour.
The alibi no longer resides
at her home address.
When asked why
he hadn't raised the alibi earlier,
P28 stated it was because
he did not want to upset her.
Hello, Mari.
How are you today?
What was the period of time
you were hoping to talk to her about?
We can't discuss that.
He claimed to have been with her
between 4:10 and 4:45 p.m.,
however, she's unable to confirm that.
Forensic investigators
attended his property
in the days following
and conducted an examination
of his vehicle.
Tape lifts were taken through
the interior of the car.
There's no record of the results here.
Senior police considered him
an unlikely suspect regardless,
as he did not drive
the "boxy black vehicle"
sighted by multiple witnesses
at the scene.
The conclusions were a lack of evidence
and insufficient time for him
to have abducted the child
and returned home by 5:30
to what he stated he'd been doing.
Which was what?
Cleaning.
You know, when I was a kid, I used to ride
the cane trains all the fuckin' time.
Out of my fuckin' head, I was.
I never felt more free until now, mate.
I reckon this is what
fuckin' real dreams are made of.
You know Paul?
When I first met him, I...
I didn't even fuckin' trust him.
I thought he was a fuckin'
reporter or something, you know?
With all the fuckin' questions
he was asking.
That cunt couldn't be a reporter.
He can hardly fuckin' read.
It's true.
He's a fuckin' dumb dummy.
- Done?
- No, not yet.
Hey.
This is Henry.
Here you go.
Good?
- Yeah, you'll let me know?
- Yep.
So...
Meeting him is a marker of trust.
It means you've been brought further in.
He's a detective senior sergeant.
His influence goes right up
through the ranks.
If you ever see him out,
don't approach him,
don't talk to him.
He's hooked us up with an arms contact.
We've got to go and meet him out of town.
Two 1911s,
two Berettas, three Glocks.
I can do the lot for, like, 12...
I like firearms.
I used to collect them.
Now it's antiques,
little trinkets like this.
Oh.
Who's Rylett?
- Rylett?
- Mm.
Oh. Rylett Holdings. Yeah,
I used to work for them back east.
This is Kate Rylett.
I'm after any archival video material
related to P28, Henry Teague.
What was your relationship?
We met through church.
Why have you come forward?
Well, I don't...
I don't know about this case, but, um...
but if a child's gone missing
and he was in the area, then I...
think that...
You think he was involved?
Yeah.
He drove us into the forest
this one night, um...
And told me to get out
and pretend that I didn't know him.
And... and then he's...
He's just driven off,
and he's just left me there. Uh...
Then he's... He circled back round,
he's pulled over to talk me into the car,
and then when I climbed in, he's...
Ugh.
He said, "You should...
You should be more careful who you trust."
And then what happened?
I used to be
a tow-truck driver, you know?
Take the wrecks to... to be destroyed
down at the shredding yard.
If you ever needed to,
that would be a very good place
to get rid of a body, you know.
If you ever needed to.
They don't check the cars?
Nah.
A lot of fuckin' crosses out here, mate.
I used to be a member of
the church, back east. Yeah.
A charismatic revival.
Do you know the type?
Yeah.
You shake and you flap about.
Then they go into fucking convulsions.
Eh.
I had a falling out
with the pastor, though.
He said there was
no such thing as an unforgivable sin.
All sins could be forgiven.
"That's not what it says in the Bible,"
I fuckin' told him.
Standing up there,
preaching things that aren't fuckin' true.
Fuckin' lying.
When we get there,
I'll need to go off and meet our contact.
You just hold there at the caravan park
till I come back for you.
Your recording device failed.
Take this one and hand me yours.
You guys, you, you need to
back off further, all right?
You're following way too close.
All right. You all right?
You just...
Just... just run me through
the fuckin' scenario.
There's no scenario, mate.
Local police were alerted to activity
at the warehouse we planned to use.
We had to clear out.
Fuck.
Henry!
- Buddy.
- Henry!
Got to move out, mate.
Hurry up. Get your shit. Serious.
- Quick! Anything else here?
- Yeah.
- No.
- All right.
Do you, um...
Do you want to come up to the house?
The missus is out of town at the moment.
Nice.
Back in a sec.
What does your missus do?
Oh, she...
She suffers with anxiety and depression.
She doesn't really leave
the house that much.
Oh, yeah?
Bought that with the money
you paid me for the work last week.
Where did you grow up?
A lot of army bases.
I'm the black sheep of the family, mate.
They're ashamed of me.
Can't fuckin' stand me.
Why's that?
I don't know.
How old are you, Mark?
Forty-six.
- Nearly 50, eh?
- Yeah.
Old man.
Huh.
What kind of music do you listen to, Mark?
I don't really... listen to music.
How do you mean?
Well, I'm not really a song person.
Yeah.
Hey, listen, um,
there's preparations
for something that's happening,
and I've talked about bringing you in.
But it would mean travelling out of town,
like, interstate, if you're up for it.
I'm there, mate. I'm there.
Brilliant. All right.
I'll let 'em know.
It's good to have a friend, Mark,
you know.
Someone you can chat to.
- Yeah.
- It's been a while.
We see through to the other side,
you and me.
That's why we get on so well.
Yeah. You're doin' good.
Oh, fuck, I'm tired, man.
I have a long drive back.
I'm going to have to head off.
Sorry.
Um... It's a nice place.
Mark, wait.
Hey. What are you fuckin' doing?
All right, enough.
All right, one time. That's it, all right?
Hey, wait, wait, wait. Shake my hand.
- Promise.
- All right. okay.
I'm gonna... How much do I gotta count?
Uh...
- Forty.
Thirty? Thirty. I'll count to 30.
One, two, three,
four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine,
ten, eleven...
You in here? Huh?
Buddy?
I'm gonna tickle ya.
I'm gonna getcha!
Fuck are you?
Fuck.
Mate?
Mate, I'm fucking serious!
Call out now if you can hear me.
Mate!
Hey, where are you? Mate!
- Mate!
- I'm here!
- What are you doing out here?
- You said hide.
You cannot come out here.
You don't go out here. What did I say?
- Come here.
- You told me to hide.
What did I say?
You don't go outside. Get in the house.
Fucking feel this, cunt.
Feel the wind in me hair.
I can feel the wind in me hair.
What is this fuckin' person doing?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What's the matter with you, you fuck?
Get out there, you fuckin' idiot.
What the fucking matter with you?
Oi! Get the fuck out!
Fuckin' drive, cunt!
Fuck!
Fuck.
Fuckin' hell.
- Police, fire or ambulance?
- Ambulance.
What's the situation there, sir?
Can you describe it for me?
Uh, car crash.
Uh, corner of Ellery and...
Fuck, I don't know.
All right, sir.
Can I have your name
and a contact number please?
Fuck.
- Henry!
- Sit down here. Sit down.
Yeah.
Henry, come on. We've got to go.
Henry!
Do you want to come up to the house?
No, no, no.
They're... they're putting
the final pieces in place
to fly us across to Victoria.
- What?
- What's that noise?
They're putting the final...
I've never been to Victoria.
Okay, I'm just gonna
need you to lay low.
That's all...
I'm fuckin' tired, man.
All right? I'll call you later
with the details, okay?
No, no.
I'm just fuckin' with you.
I know.
Are you, um,
dealing with any increased irritability?
- Stress?
- Nah.
Nothing that
you've perceived in yourself?
No.
Okay.
Any physical discomfort,
anything likewise?
No.
Any symptoms of depression?
How about anxiety?
- Are you feeling anxious?
- No. No.
And, um, how about any...
any thoughts of self-harm?
No.
Look, um, I do have, um, it noted
that you are dealing
with some sleep issues.
Might it be linked to
your work with WA Police,
or is that more personal?
Nah.
More to do with WA Police
or more personal?
Neither.
Mark, look, the reason that you're here
is I've been told you're being placed
in a difficult work situation.
I've been asked to discuss that with you.
You know, a person in this profession
goes through enough...
goes through enough trauma
that the aggregation of that trauma,
- the amount of it, is overwhelming.
- Mm-hmm.
There's not always an isolated incident
or a situation that...
I don't know what you're talking about.
If you need to take some time off work,
there will be other people
that can take your shifts.
Look, I need to talk to you
about the other night
outside the front of my house.
- Uh, no, Henry, listen...
- No, Mark, please.
I used to watch a lot of porn, you know?
Uh, amputees.
That was my thing.
You know, people with no...
no arms, no fuckin' legs.
I don't know what it is about you, Mark.
You... you remind me of an amputee.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
You keep talking like that,
I'll have to take you down
to the fuckin' watch house.
What was that?
Uh... Uh...
I've got a black lake in my eye!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
You need to know that
I've told them that we cannot replace you.
You've been on for five and a half months.
We can't replicate that
and we can't undo that work.
Flying you down to Melbourne
in the coming days.
Victoria are providing coverts.
That'll take the pressure off.
We've heard nothing
about the assault in the NT
and Forensics have come back
with the test results from his vehicle.
The tape lifts they took
were never tested.
They were submitted to the lab
where they were set aside.
They tested them yesterday.
Testing confirms no physical evidence
of any other presence
in the fucking vehicle.
- Sorry.
- It's all right.
They noted that this,
in and of itself, is not conclusive
and that at the time
the tape lifts were taken
the person of interest was compliant,
cooperative and understanding
of the process.
We have absolutely nothing on him.
How's, uh... How's your mum?
She said to not talk about it.
Talk about what?
How she is.
- Hey, mate.
- Yeah?
I'm not gonna be able to
take you for a few days, okay?
Okay.
- So you tell your mum?
- Okay.
There's a boy out there.
Alone.
Waiting to be found.
And you know what he's saying?
"Where am I?"
"Where the fuck am I?"
Henry.
I heard this is
your first time in Victoria.
Must've done something right
to be sent interstate.
We're making a collection from a contact.
You're taking it back with you to WA,
that's why you're here.
Mark.
Mark!
John's here in town.
Take this.
- You wait here.
- Hey, Mark.
Follow me through here.
What the fuck's happened to this shit?
Through here, mate. You all right?
Yep.
Victoria have provided John.
He'll be leading
the final part of the operation.
But my concern is that
he's too direct for Henry.
I need you to talk to him
about Henry's anxiety.
So we've gone after him
and we're racing down this corridor
and he's locked himself in
so we thought, "Well, all right."
"Wait for you to ask
to be nicely let out."
John.
- Do you have a minute?
- Yeah.
Uh, Mark here's been
leading the operation in WA.
Be good to talk to him about...
Sorry, what was your name again?
Mark.
Yeah, but that's not
your actual name, is it?
I mean they did tell you
not to use your actual name?
Yeah.
So what's your real name?
What's your name?
Well, it's not Mark. That's taken.
Sorry. I'm just fucking around with you.
I'm sorry.
I'll be with you in a sec.
I've just got to...
So...
He's a fuckin' arsehole.
We've got him here.
We picked him up,
take him down the hallway...
We've been taking out insurance policies,
putting it through our claims officer.
Which puts it in our system...
Mark.
What do you reckon is in the case?
You just have to trust him.
Where is my water?
Where's my water?
Bloody hell!
No, no, no, no!
- It's him.
- Who?
John.
- You all right, Mark?
- Yeah.
- Flight sorted?
- Yep.
How are you, Henry?
Yeah.
It's really... nice to meet you,
John, yeah. Thanks...
I'm not John.
He's over there.
He wants you to write down
your name and date of birth.
Um, yeah.
He said to write down your other name.
- My other name?
- Yeah. Your other name.
- I changed the name years ago.
- Why didn't you fuckin' tell me?
What's he want to know the name for?
Why didn't you fuckin' tell me?
They'll give your name
to a police contact,
run a background check on you.
We all have to get cleared.
Make sure we won't draw attention.
Yeah, yeah,
don't fuckin' worry about it.
I remember sitting where you are,
thinking I'd never be let in
with the shit I'd done.
- John wants to see you.
- What?
John. He wants to talk to you now.
I heard about you. Henry.
Whatever your name is.
You've got to be honest with us,
all right?
I... Yeah.
I changed... I changed the name years...
I don't give a fuck.
No.
- What are you staring at?
- Nothin'.
Then why are you still standing there?
Thanks.
Right. They've got us in different places.
Don't leave the hotel.
There's nothing else I haven't told you,
apart from the name.
- Nothing else I know about, at least.
- All right.
Don't leave the hotel, Henry.
I met this woman down
in the hotel bar last night.
Brought her back to the room.
You know what she told me before she left?
Hm.
"I'll never forget you, Henry."
Fuckin' hope they've got enough ink
in the printer to print out my record.
Eh, you don't need to worry about it.
Ah, there's been nothing
in 20 years, mate.
There were no records
of an assault in the NT
under Henry Teague.
They were filed under his
former name, Peter Morley.
I provided them with the information,
but it was misfiled.
Jesus Christ.
I can't, uh,
take your call at the moment.
If you leave me a message,
I'll endeavor to call you back later.
Henry?
Fuck.
- I've lost him.
- What?
- I've fuckin' lost him.
- Did he follow you back?
Uh, no, I don't know,
but I don't think so.
Fuck!
Uh... Listen, Mark.
We can't put out an alert. You know that.
There... there can't be a follow vehicle.
I can't put out an alert.
You have to try and find him.
What?
You're gonna have to
try to find him, mate.
Only issue is the alibi.
Her daughter worked at a local RSL
at the time of the abduction.
She said her mum was often there,
playing the machines.
Don't have security camera
footage dating back to 2002?
Not back that far.
Do you keep records of your sign-in books?
If she was a regular,
she wouldn't have to sign.
What do you do for the regulars?
We used to have a loyalty program
where members could scan their cards
and the machine
would record their numbers.
How would we track down...
Sorry.
They shall not
grow old, as we who are left grow old.
Age shall not weary them,
nor the years condemn.
At the going down of the sun
and in the morning,
we shall remember them.
We shall remember them.
- We shall remember them.
- Lest we forget.
- We'll have her number on file,
- but the machines have been out of use...
- Where are they?
What's the date you're after?
The 12th May, 2002.
I'm sittin' here with
the missus and just had ourselves a roast.
She says hello, by the way.
"Hello, Mark," she's saying,
"Hello, Mark."
Tell her I... Tell her I said hi.
Mate, where... Where are you?
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
I had to head out of town for a while.
Well, why don't I talk
to the boys, we'll work out...
Yeah, he's anxious. He's unsettled.
At this point, we feel that
we could lose him... at any time.
We need to get John out here
and prepare to make the final push.
The interstate job
was in preparation for a larger shipment.
Mark, here,
has put you forward for this, Henry.
And this is just the start, mate.
This is nothing.
This is just a fuckin' run.
It's a remote airfield,
hour-and-a-half out of town.
John's concerned about security
and we need you to case the site.
When the delivery is made,
you'll take 10% of the profit.
To be clear, Henry,
that's over $100,000 each.
I've been, uh,
doing the security down here
for nearly five years
and, uh, it never gets old.
We're open to the public
on Sundays, by the way.
Oh, right, yeah.
I might bring my boys out.
Yeah, you should. They'd enjoy it.
You like the look of that, eh?
You want to sit in the front seat?
I was 54 when I started.
I learned with my son.
I had a fear of heights,
but, uh, when you get in here,
it feels really safe.
- Yeah.
- It feels very safe.
It does feel safe.
How much are these worth?
Well, there's, uh, no ceiling
in the price of planes
but, uh, that, um... that plane back there,
that's, uh, $60,000.
We've disproved his alibi.
She was on the machines at the local RSL.
He couldn't have been
with her at the time.
Where was he then?
Not... not there.
Have you seen the records from the NT?
I'm reading them.
Follow me, please.
Take a seat. There's fine.
I'm Detective Sergeant Cross.
I'm the controller for
the Covert and Specialist Operations crew.
I'm here to inform you
that at the close of the coronial inquest
there'll be a UC sitting
next to your person of interest
on his return to WA. This is Paul Emery.
- Hey.
- Hi.
The intention will be
for Paul to make contact
with the POI on his return trip,
see where that takes us
over a two-week period.
I'm afraid, unless they decide
to take it further, that's...
That's it.
You're here to brief us
about his background.
- Right. But he did it.
- Mm.
And I know they've probably told
you he isn't worth the effort,
but he did it.
Well,
we've only just been allocated this.
Tell us what we can use
to get him to talk.
Is this Peter Morley?
No.
Is this Peter Morley,
otherwise known as Henry Peter Teague?
Who's this?
My name's Kate Rylett.
I'm a detective senior constable
in Queensland.
As the detectives would've informed you,
you've been summonsed to appear
at a coronial inquest in Queensland...
Henry Teague.
...into the suspected abduction
and murder of James Liston in 2002.
I'm going to give you my phone number.
I'll be your point of contact
from here on.
And what if I refuse to come?
If you don't want to come,
the Queensland coroner
will issue a warrant
for you to be taken into custody
and brought before the inquest.
After the inquest,
we'll provide you with transport,
as I understand that
you currently live in Western Australia.
We'll ensure you're returned
to your place of residence,
assuming you aren't required
to remain in Queensland
at the close of the process.
We've reviewed the brief
of evidence prepared by Detective Rylett.
Paul Emery?
And we can see reason
to invest WA Pol resources
in your person of interest.
You'll remain here as a controller,
work with us on this.
We're initiating an operation
that would mean introducing Mark here
as part of a criminal organization that
can relocate people, erase histories...
...offer him a way out.
It's dark.
I step out the front of my house.
And I get this feeling
of lightness come over me.
So I start to run.
And then I'm up in the air
and I'm flying over the back fences
and the houses that I grew up in.
Fixed-wing licence costs $10,000.
Two $5,000 payments.
Hey, figure how useful I'd be, Mark.
I... I could be landing on airstrips
all over the country, you know,
making deliveries.
Yeah?
All right. We'll head over
to the airfield after that.
We're going to go meet him out of town.
Henry.
Mark.
- All right?
- Yeah, good.
There's a car to be ditched.
Police have eyes on it.
Make sure it's not parked where it is.
I'll send you the details.
Henry, there's, um...
I don't know if you're aware of this,
but there's a subpoena
that's been issued for you.
Nah.
Yeah. Queensland Coroners Court.
Are you aware of that?
No, that's done. I went through that.
No. This is different.
Another inquest, is it?
Yeah, apparently they have
some new information.
- Can't let you hold on to that.
- Yep.
Thanks.
- Is that it?
- Yeah, that's it.
What was that about?
Uh... I was in the same area
when this person went missing.
Police harassed me for it at the time.
Nothing came of it, so...
How many times have I told you...
If I'd known there could've been
another subpoena, I would've told you.
What?
Yeah. I am.
Now?
All right.
Yeah, fuckin' all right. I'm doing it now.
What is it?
I've got to turn around.
Why?
The airfield is, uh, not on tonight.
John's in town.
We're gonna go, um...
We're gonna go see him.
It's probably about the airfield.
Could be about the inquest.
Huh?
It could be about the inquest.
I really don't fuckin' know.
Okay. Well done.
And I'll give you a call this afternoon.
- All right. Take care.
- Hey.
- Hey, hey.
- How you doin'?
- Good, good.
- Uh, Henry, John. John, Henry.
- Yeah.
- Good?
- You remember Henry?
- All good?
- Yep.
-All right
-Cool.
- Take a seat.
- Yep.
Yeah. Grab yourself a seat. There, there.
Park yourself up the end there, Henry.
So, I, uh, actually need to
talk to you about this inquest
that you've heard told of...
Heard tell of.
I just need to... to sort that out.
Yeah, uh...
Got a criminal history.
Stealing, uh, bit of violence.
Fuckin' hell.
Uh... Hey, uh, let me...
- Yeah, John, let me...
- Fuck's sake.
Yeah, I'll sort it out. Hold on.
I've got it.
I... I did time for the violence, you know?
I was upfront with Mark about that.
- Wasn't I, mate?
- Yeah, absolutely.
And I was questioned about
the other thing at the time.
There we are.
Nothing came of it.
Sorry about that.
Excuse us a minute.
Where's he gone?
I don't know.
I'm gonna go
see what's going on.
John.
You okay, mate?
Wait outside. Wait in the hall.
I'll call you later.
Hey, we're, um...
- I should... I should be here.
- Mark. Fuck off.
Yeah. Yep.
Mm.
Yeah, all right, then. Um...
I'll see what he says.
I'll give him a call then.
I'll be right back.
Fuck! Fuck!
What's going on?
He's fuckin' falling to pieces
in there. Fuck!
Fuck. Hey, hey.
- ...who tell me...
- Fuck.
- ...that you're the one who's responsible...
...so you have to tell me
what we need to take care of.
Nothin' to tell.
Okay.
What falls on you falls on all of us.
All right?
So I received information this morning
that says you're the one... who's done it.
And I... I don't care what you've done,
whether you done him
or killed him or what have you.
I mean, there's...
there's nothing you can tell me
that's gonna upset me.
What I care about is being lied to.
I'm not lying.
You've had every opportunity
to be upfront with us.
And if you're gonna...
be dishonest in front of me
and say you had nothin' to do with it,
- that's not what I've heard.
- Yeah.
And I'd have no choice but to cut you out
and you'd be back to nothing.
Yep.
Yeah.
And if they put you away for this,
there's nothin' I can do.
And there's a...
There's a stigma, there's a...
there's a... a stigma about
this kind of thing inside.
So, you know, I can create alibis,
clear the site,
remove evidence, relocate you.
I mean, you've seen that.
All right.
Sorry. Henry, what was that?
I killed him. I killed the boy.
Jesus Christ. Fuck yes!
Well, you know,
you're gonna have to take me through it
'cause we need to know
what we have to take care of.
Uh...
I saw him waiting at the underpass,
so I pulled the car over,
and started to chat to him for a while
and I talked him into the car.
Cops have taken the car, searched it,
came back with nothin'.
They haven't found the body, obviously.
And where did this happen?
Just, um...
What happened?
John said we've got to go and fuckin'
wait there in my fuckin' car.
What? What is it?
Nothin'. I don't know. Fuck. Uh...
Just put the work on hold
for a while or something, um,
while he sorts a few things out.
- You told him about the airfield?
- Yeah.
Look, I don't know how much
I can tell you, man, all right?
He was dead before anyone
knew he was missing.
Before the police were called.
Before his family even
started looking, he was dead.
Detectives will regroup in Queensland
to determine if arrest will be made.
The undercover operation will continue
with Detective Sergeant Cross
to return the suspect
to the scene of the of fence.
The site itself will need to be contained
in preparation for a search for evidence.
Henry,
I'm what's referred to as a cleaner.
The organization's brought me in
to ensure the police can find nothing
that could be brought against
you at this new inquest.
So talk me through it all
and I'll decide the right course for us.
I read all the press
and reports and that.
It wasn't a black car,
it wasn't two... two men.
I was on me own.
I didn't park at the overpass,
I parked behind it at my old church.
It happened in an old demountable.
Uh...
So here, it's, uh,
about an hour and a half
north of the city, out in the mountains.
- It was an old forestry site.
- Where is the demountable?
Uh, they took it away when...
when they closed the site.
There's nothin' in it, so...
Couldn't there be traces in there?
No.
All right.
Well, what happened after he, um...
after he died?
I took him out a bit further, you know,
covered him up with grass, branches,
that sort of thing.
Left him there, went back about a week
or two later and he was almost gone.
What do you mean?
There were just little pieces of him.
No. No, we have to find everything.
What about his clothes?
I threw them in the creek.
- How long ago was this?
- About eight years now.
Why did you take his clothes off?
I don't know, Mark.
I suppose you had to get rid of 'em.
What have you done then?
I went home.
How'd you do it?
- How do you mean?
- How'd you kill him?
- I put my arm around his neck.
- Right. Show us on Mark.
Mark, can you just pop yourself down
and we'll take a look at that.
All right.
All right. Yeah. It doesn't matter.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
- You need to take us there.
- Yeah.
- Need to clear everything.
- Can Mark come?
- Yeah.
- Ah.
It doesn't matter where we sit
as long as we're fuckin' together.
Like, you know, the same fuckin' row.
So the flight is sorted.
Uh, well, he'll call me in five
but I'm gonna go sort the car out.
Hey.
Henry.
Um, I'm gonna...
Mate, I'm... I'm... Come here.
Come here, mate. Fuck.
I'm just...
I'm so proud of you, brother.
Yeah.
This briefing
has been called to determine
whether an arrest
should be made of Peter Morley,
otherwise known as Henry Peter Teague,
in the abduction and murder
of James Liston,
eight years ago on the 12th of May, 2002.
As you're all aware,
this is the largest missing-persons case
in the history of our state
and is one of the largest
in the history of our country.
I'm going to the bathroom.
The investigation has
spanned over eight years
and is one of the largest joint operations
ever undertaken by interstate agencies.
Peter Morley was born to a normal,
middle-class military family.
There is no evidence to suggest as a child
Peter Morley was the subject of abuse.
This investigation
has completely disproved Morley's alibi...
He's just gone to the bathroom.
...and has
unearthed the full details
of his previous assault of a child
in the Northern Territory
for which he served two years in jail.
Lights, please.
This child was taken from
a family crisis center in the NT in 1996.
He was not known to the offender.
Attending doctors observed that the child
had lacerations and abrasions
to his legs, arms and torso.
His hair, face and body
were covered in dirt,
with blood present in the nose and mouth.
He had blackened eyes,
several closed fractures,
a collapsed lung,
severe bruises beneath his hairline,
and deep cuts to his scalp and genitalia.
The overall pattern indicated
widespread and repeated applications
of both blunt and sharp-force trauma.
Contusions to the throat
in association with
hemorrhaging in the eyes
was indicative of suffocation.
He was found barely alive
in the remnants of a burnt-out car
less than 100 meters
from where he was taken.
On returning to the site of the abduction,
Peter Morley offered to lead the search
for the person responsible.
Hello?
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
- Sorry.
- Nah.
Thought you'd fallen in.
I can't fuckin' breathe, man.
I can't fuckin' breathe.
- Yeah, you can.
- Nah.
Yeah, you can.
Ready?
I want to
raise a few issues here.
Regardless of his assault
on this other child,
in this case, the time lines are thin,
even with the break in his alibi.
We're talking about an hour
to abduct a person...
I have to be clear,
this is a practiced offender
- who's placed himself at the scene...
- You've been clear.
- You've had your time. Now sit down.
- I want to clarify something.
Let's have some contention in the process.
I want to clarify something.
The duration of the assault in the NT?
Fifteen minutes.
There's never been anyone
locked up in Queensland without a body.
New South Wales there has. Not here.
I, um... I mentioned the yard
where you talked about shredding the cars.
Is that somewhere that we should head to?
- Nah, mate.
- I just thought maybe...
No, Mark, no.
What were you wearing on the day?
I threw it all on the fire,
burnt it all, shoes as well.
- There's nothing left?
- Nothing left. Nothing.
- Where are the ashes?
- I threw them out on the lawn
and then I got the dirt
ripped up and taken away, so...
Fuckin' well done.
That's gold. Fuckin' gold.
I didn't mean to do it, though.
I didn't know it would happen.
It's like how the words
are coming out of me mouth now,
like how I'm saying it to you now,
like it's nothing.
- How far from here?
- Not far.
That's my old church there.
That's where I was married.
Don't know what I was fuckin'
thinkin' of at the time.
Yeah.
This is where I picked him up, here.
No, don't fuckin' pull over.
There's a camera there.
There's a camera there, mate.
Just keep going.
This isn't
about whether he did it.
It's about whether
or not it's prosecutable.
And you can talk about
an unsolicited confession all you like.
This undercover operation
induces a suspect to confess.
It's inducement without evidence.
This is where I threw his clothes.
There's nothing here.
That's good.
I strongly submit that we
continue the covert operation
while the area's being searched
because if you go for
an arrest without evidence
and you find nothing, he walks.
I refuse to put the victim's family
through that for nothing.
As you're aware,
the commissioner has tasked me
with making a decision as to whether
or not an arrest is to take place.
Without evidence, he walks.
And that will be
my decision to make.
Just pull in up there.
Is this it?
Yep.
So this is where
the demountable was?
- Yeah.
- So you killed him in there...
and you dragged him down where?
I don't remember that water being there.
It was here though.
Here.
You sure?
Yeah, there's nothing.
It's all right.
Hold it there!
Stay where you are, mate!
Just stay where you are!
Thank you all for your attendance.
I'll let you know at the outset that
we won't be able to answer any questions.
I can confirm that earlier today,
an arrest was made
in relation to the disappearance
of James Liston on May 12, 2002.
Police are currently securing a large area
in anticipation of an extensive search.
The search area itself
is located in the Queensland floodplain.
The issue that we are facing
is that flooding over the past eight years
may have removed any remaining evidence.
Henry Teague.
As informed earlier,
you're here under arrest with regard
to the abduction of James Liston
on the 12th May, 2002.
I haven't done this, you know.
Nothin' to do with me, mate.
As long as you didn't do it,
there'll be no evidence
and you've got nothing to worry about.
Now, you got a minute.
Anything you need?
Anyone got a smoke?
We'll be undertaking
a basic search of the forest covering.
We have around four acres to manage.
Additional Forensics are
searching the demountable
which was relocated when the site sold
and where it's alleged
that the victim was killed.
Don't disturb potential evidence.
If you come across anything,
pause and raise your hand.
- How we looking?
- Found nothing.
- Nothing at all?
- No.
The divers have finished with
the lake, but no, nothing.
Right.
No, hold on.
It's night.
I'm in my house.
My son is asleep in his room.
And I hear a voice.
It's coming from downstairs.
I walk toward it.
I can barely breathe.
It's not a person talking.
It's a tape recorder.
I press the button to turn it off.
But when I turn it off...
the voice keeps coming...
...keeps talking.