Subtitle created by - Aorion -
"The Shallows (2016)" ^ (Run time 01:18:55)
Woo hoo!
Woo hoooo!
Whoa!
Help me!
Helm me!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
THE SHALLOWS
Is that you at the beach?
Oh, no, no.
That's my-That's my mom.
Oh.
Yeah, she came to this beach
when she kind of...
she was pregnant with me.
I've never been but...
It's kind of our beach.
That's my little sister.
Are there more photos?
Um. You want to see more photos?
I can...
If you look only at the phone,
you're missing what is around you.
It's only for your eyes.
Real.
Authentic.
You're right.
Thank you.
Sorry, I'm American.
Not too many gringos here.
- Yeah, bummer.
- Thank god.
Anna:
I'm not going to make it to the beach,
my head is spinning :(
She's not coming.
Who?
Uh.
My friend, you know.
You know, the girl we
left back at the hotel?
You know, she smelled like
Don Julio and bad choices.
She always does this to me.
She just disappears.
She's like the Fantasmo, no?
You know-You know Fantasmo?
- Fantasma. Cuerno.
- Yes, Cuerno.
The whole reason I planned
to come on this trip, Cuerno,
was to find the secret beach.
And now she's stuck back at
Islas Rocas with an Irish flu.
Nursing a hangover.
Yes, hangover.
Major hangover.
Nancy:
My professional opinion is to take
2 Advil + Zzz = ☺
You do not like it when someone
change your plan, do you?
No, I don't.
It's just...
You know, it's not fair.
You know why though?
It's because I'm reliable.
You know reliable?
Bossy.
I am reliable.
- Yes, bossy.
That's me.
Very bossy.
Anna:
Have fun! We'll catch up later.
Did you find the  name
of the secret beach?
Hey, um.
What is this beach called?
You're not going to tell me, cool.
Cool frio.
You're tengo frio.
Not possible.
It's too hot here.
I mean you're cool.
You are being cool.
You know what?
It's okay.
American.
Is this the one?
Yes.
This is paradise.
It's perfect.
This is the island of
the pregnant woman, no?
The island.
- No.
- Yes.
The nose... the breasts...
and her stomach.
No.
Yes, it is for me.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
- No, no, no, please.
- No, please.
- Please. Please, I insist.
- No, no, no.
We were going the same way.
I live close by, so... don't worry.
- Oh. Are you sure?
- Yes.
Okay.
- Well, thank you.
- You're welcome.
I'm Nancy.
Carlos.
Charlie.
- Nice to meet you, Charlie.
- Nice to meet you.
I apologize for my Spanish.
I learned it in... high school.
You're in school?
No.
I mean I was in medical school.
But we didn't have Spanish there,
just cadavers.
I'll shut up... now.
Okay.
And dark in a few hours, so...
Oh, I never surf at night.
And how you...
getting out from here?
Uber.
Who is Uber?
Never mind.
Thank you, Carlos.
Thank you again
for taking me here.
- It means a lot to me.
- Okay.
What did you say the
name of it was again now?
I just forgot...
for some reason.
Careful.
Always.
Hey!
How are you?
Uh.
I can understand only a little.
I don't understand.
I'm sorry.
He say that it's hard to paddle
when there is a current.
Yeah, I wasn't expecting that.
I almost got caught on
the inside coming out.
You, American?
Yes. Yes, American.
Yeah.
California.
Uh.
Close, Texas.
You surf in Texas?
Yes, we have surf in Texas.
It's just not like this though.
Hey, this is a secret place,
how you find it?
Someone told me about it
a while ago.
What's it called?
If I tell you,
I would have to kill you.
Well, that would ruin my day.
Anything oddly out here
I should know about?
There are some rocks over there.
There's only 1 tide a day.
And when the tide gets low,
it becomes an island.
There's some nasty fire coral.
It stings like a jellyfish.
Okay, thank you.
Still have no idea
what you are saying.
He says that you should
come over here.
The wave breaks better.
Oh, I'm okay-I'm okay.
I'm cool here, thank you.
Careful, gringa.
Strong current here for
a little girl from Texas.
I think I'll be alright.
Yeah.
Yeah!
Calling Short Crop
- Short Crop?
- Hey.
- Guess where I am.
- Do you wanna?
Oh my god.
No way.
Mom's beach, right?
It's just as beautiful as
she said it was.
Ah, I wish you were here.
- I wish she was here.
- Does that mean you're alone?
Oh, I wasn't gonna come all
this way just to wuss out
because I lost my plus one.
That's how you wind up
on Nancy Grace, okay?
Excuse me.
I am supposed to be the boring,
overprotective sister.
You're supposed to be
the fun one.
Sis, the surf here is insane.
You would not believe the
perfect tube I just caught.
I can shoot tubes
just as good as you
if you would just
take me out!
I'll take you out as
soon as I get back.
I love you, sister mama.
- I love you too, Short Crop.
- Is that Nancy?
- It's Dad.
- Just tell him it's all fine, okay?
- Uh. No, it's...
- Love you, bye.
Hey, Nance, don't hang up.
Give me the phone.
Chloe.
- Hey!
- Hey, Papa.
Hey, sweet pea.
Where are you now?
Mexico.
I don't know what to say, Nance.
I'm at a loss.
- I don't-I don't, I can't understand.
- I don't expect you too.
- Well, help me out then.
- I don't know.
What do you-
What do you want me to say?
Say you are coming back.
Say you are not dropping out
of med school after all this time.
After all this work.
- You know, just don't quit.
- Okay, Dad, that's enough.
Can we just not do this
right now, please?
But, that's what you love.
You help people.
Well, not everyone can be helped, Dad.
You know that.
Don't do that.
- Don't make this about her.
- What else would it be about?
If you want to make this about her,
then you stink in it.
She was a fighter.
It's just too far,
too hard, Dad.
You know.
And for what?
It all ended the same.
Just come back, Nancy.
Please.
I got to go, okay?
I'll see you soon.
When?
- I don't know.
- Nance.
I love you, bye.
Anna:
Meeting up with the cute guy from last
night... Don't wait up for me.
Yeah, girl.
It's getting late, let's go in.
- I'm gonna catch one last one, thanks.
- Okay.
Nice meeting you guys.
Farewell.
(Buenas noches.)
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Help!
Hey!
Help me!
I'm here!
I'm right here!
Help!
Yes.
Yeah.
Here!
No!
Help!
Please help me!
COME BACKKKKK !!!
Oh god.
Where are you taking me?
Too far.
Okay.
You are not going to
feel a thing, ma'am.
Just put some Novocaine
injections to numb the area.
So, you're just going to
feel a little pressure, but...
You're not going to
feel the stitches, okay?
Okay?
Ahhhhh!
Tie up the suture.
That's right.
That's a nice union.
One more and then
we'll send you on your way.
Here we go.
Okay.
Okay, ma'am.
Nice clean wrap.
Get in line, buddy.
Just keep it elevated, ma'am.
Someone's coming.
Okay.
You're going to be fine.
5 HOURS
TO LOW TIDE
There we go.
I got to get some
blood flowing.
Now, let's loosen this
tourniquet for you.
God.
Come on.
There we go.
Okay.
Okay, you get 2 minutes
of blood flow.
LOW TIDE
Okay.
Compression bandage.
Eww.
You still out there?
Stay.
Good bird.
Aahhh!
Hello!
Hey !!!
Yeah.
Hello!
Turn around!
Come on!
Hey!
Help!
Help me!
Yeah.
Here, here.
Help!
Call for help!
My backpack.
My backpack!
It's over there.
Yes! Yes!
Over there!
Teléfono.
Please, go get it!
Yes!
Inside, the teléfono.
Telephone, please hurry!
Please.
Hurry!
No.
No, no, no.
No!
Stop, come back!
Come back, you can have it!
You can have it, come back!
Come back, please!
Please, help me!
No.
No, there's a shark!
Wait, it's okay.
Just don't go!
No, there's a shark!
Stop!
No!
Shark!
Shut up.
Stop!
Get out of the water!
Get out!
Stop!
Go back!
Shark!
Don't worry about it.
There're no sharks here.
Stop!
Get out of the water!
Get out!
Go back, get help!
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Come on!
Come on! Come on!
Swim!
Come on!
Come on! Come on!
Swim!
Come on!
Come on, I got you!
I got you.
Come on. Come on.
Come on!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Help!
Help me.
- Help me!
- Come on!
- Help!
- I got you.
- Help me!
- I got you, come on!
- Help!
- I got you. I got you.
I got you.
3 HOURS
TO HIGH TIDE
25 MINUTES
Come on.
You're okay.
I'm not bailing you, little buddy.
Let me see you.
I'm not very good
at wrought though.
But it just looks
like a dislocation.
Like a separated shoulder.
I think it's the same.
We'll see, uh.
I'm just going to
do this quick, okay?
It's gonna hurt
just for a second,
and then you're gonna be okay.
On three.
Ready?
One.
Two.
Three.
I think we did it.
Hey. Hey. Hey.
That's a terrible way
to say thank you.
Now you got a chance, huh?
Huh.
And here comes the tide.
Camera.
That's the third time.
I got you.
32 seconds from
the whale to the rock.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Woo hoo!
Woo hoooo!
Whoa!
Help!
- Come on, I got you!
- Help!
I got you! I got you!
I got you!
Come on.
Hold on.
Huh.
Someone got you.
30 or 40 yards.
1 minute swim.
I can make that.
I need a head start.
10 MINUTES
TO HIGH TIDE
This is Nancy Adams.
It's April 26th, 2016.
If you find this,
please send help right away.
I've been attacked by a shark.
He's killed 3 other people
since I got here.
He's still circling so, um...
He's got this,
big old whale over here.
But, that's the problem.
I swam right up on
his feeding ground.
I've been bitten
pretty deeply into my...
my gastroc and quad muscles.
I have a deep gash running
vertically down my medial thigh.
and it turns lateral
just above my knee.
And right here, there's one rend
across my-my posterior calf.
I'm losing a lot of blood.
Gangrene is setting in.
I feel like I'm losing
my strength.
I don't think
I have much time.
The island I'm on is going to be
taken by the tide in a few minutes.
I'm about 200 yards off the shore,
of this beach.
I never found out
what it was called.
So...
Um.
This is useless.
There's a buoy, which
I'm going to try to swim to.
About 30 or 40 yards away.
See here.
That's...
That's the plan.
Um...
If you find this,
can you just um...
Can you just delete
that first part and...
And send it to...
10231 Oliver Crescent Drive,
Galveston, Texas.
That's my home.
That's-That's where my...
That's where my dad
and sister live.
Hey, Pop.
Hey, Chloe.
Um.
I finally got that alone time.
Super overrated.
Um.
You know, I'm not-
I'm not totally alone.
I've got this little dude, Steven Seagull,
here keeping me company.
Show them your wing.
I fixed him for you, Chloe.
I just don't want you guys to worry
and I don't want you to feel...
You know bad or anything,
'cause...
I love you so much.
And I miss you
more than I ever...
I ever realized I could.
Dad, I got to get off
this rock soon.
Um.
But I want you to know
I'm going to fight.
I am.
Just like she taught us.
And you were right.
I love you.
I love you so much.
Time to go.
It's okay. It's okay.
You got it.
Good job.
You're gonna make it, buddy.
You're okay.
Okay.
Shit.
Oh, you're kidding me.
Huh!
You didn't like that,
because it stings like jellyfish.
This is my head start.
Come on.
Okay.
No, no, no.
Come back.
Come on.
This is Nancy Adams.
It's April 26th, 2016.
If you find this,
please send help right away.
I've been attacked by a shark.
He's killed 3 other people
since I got here.
I'm losing a lot of blood.
I feel that I'm
losing my strength.
I love you more, Short Crop.
I'll be home soon.
Magical beach.
No way.
Mom's beach, right?
Not everyone can be helped.
I don't want you to feel...
You know bad or anything.
I got to go, okay?
I'll see you soon.
Hey, sweet pea.
She was a fighter.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I'm going to fight.
Just like she taught us.
Uh-uh.
No!
Where are you?
Fuck you.
Oh shit!
No!
Ow!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Miguel!
- Here. Here's the place.
Here.
Papa! Papa!
Look at the water!
What?
Where, son?
There. There.
Look. There.
Go quickly.
Run!
Call for help!
Hurry!
Relax.
Breathe.
I'm okay.
Subtitle created by - Aorion -