Boss, I need
a bathroom break!
Please.
Dear Lord, help me!
Get the hell
out of here.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Well, that's what you get
for drinking on the job, Sloane.
Hey, Sloane, take it easy!
Sloane! Sloane!
Damn it! Sloane!
You can do it!
Sloane.
Uhh...
Dear God help us.
# Hush, little baby,
don't say a word #
# Mama's gonna buy you... #
He's so beautiful.
That's the ugliest thing
I ever saw.
Don't worry about it, Tommy.
You don't have to look pretty
to work down at the slaughterhouse.
What is that diseased freak
still doing out here?
We closed for good now.
Uh, I think
he likes it here, sir.
Ain't no reason for that
ugly beast to still be here.
Jess, we need to get that oversized
retard the hell out of here.
We, sir?
Just you.
Hello, Hewitt.
We're shutting down
the place today.
You know that
'cause I done told you.
Shutting down for good.
We ain't packing
no more meat.
Ain't killing
no more animals so...
you just leave the equipment.
You just get on home now, okay?
You gotta go, I said!
You gotta get the hell out
of here, you dumb animal!
What are you doing?
Shh! Keep your voice down.
This is how you
sneak up on 'em,
- how you catch 'em.
- Catch who?
Gooks in the swamp.
Eric, the only thing you're
gonna catch in this water is disease.
- Chrissie, come on.
- No, I'm not going in that water.
Consider it the last
wish of a soldier.
Oh, no.
No, you've been getting last wishes
this whole past week, G.I. Joe.
And you call
yourself a patriot.
- You know what I think is patriotic?
- What?
Me driving you across
state to go to Vietnam. Again.
You goin' all the way
to Vietnam, baby?
No, honey, base camp's
far enough for me, trust me.
Just try to relax, baby,
'cause today I'm
going to use my tongue
in ways the Lord
never intended.
- How's that sound?
- Okay.
# All right now #
# Baby,
it's all right now #
# Whoa... #
Mmm...
# Let me tell you now #
# I took her home
to my place #
# Watching every move
on her face... #
This may come as a shock
to you, but most men
are into this
kind of thing.
I'm sorry.
I'm just a little distracted, Bail.
I mean, I just
keep thinking,
how does a person
go back there?
You know,
how do you do that?
It doesn't make him any more
heroic than you, baby, okay?
Yeah, but he thinks I'm
going with him, Bail.
Eric thinks I'm going
to Vietnam with him.
Well, he's your brother,
he loves you.
You know, he'll
get over it, okay?
Just close your eyes.
Let me see your hand.
You're gonna love this.
Can I look?
Yeah.
Eric, you got that
from a Cracker Jack box!
Wha... I... I had to eat
17 batches to find the one I wanted.
How many?
- Two.
- Okay, girls or boys?
One of each.
And what are
their names?
- Bonnie and Clyde.
- No.
- Come on.
- Bobby and Janis.
And where are
us and the kids gonna live?
California.
Right by the water.
Don't leave me.
I ain't never gonna
leave you, beautiful.
I'll give you everything
you want, baby.
Starting with this.
This is what
you're gonna tell him...
you're going to walk
right up to Eric,
and you're gonna tell him
that you're going to Mexico
and you're not gonna join
him in this stupid war,
no matter what some
draft card says.
Okay?
Get your bony ass ready, soldier!
Moving out at 1700 hours.
What's 1700 hours?
You better be
getting some, Dean.
What the hell are you
still doing here?
Go home.
We're out of business.
You and your family are
the only ones stupid enough
to still be living
in this town.
Your kind belong
in this shithole.
Operator.
May I help you?
You're gonna have to speak
more clearly, ma'am.
I don't understand. You're gonna have
to speak more clearly.
I'm your friend, Hewitt.
Come on, y'all. Look alive now.
Take one last look
at that motel over there
'cause this here's your
lodging for the next two days.
What, are you gonna put
mints on our pillows too?
I'll tuck you in
special every night.
We're going
on a road trip!
# Hey well, I'm the friendly
stranger in the black sedan #
# Won't you hop inside
my car? #
# Got peaches, got candy,
I'm a loveable man #
# Take you
to the nearest star #
- # And I'll love you #
- # Love you #
- # I'll need you #
- # Need you #
# I want you,
got to have you, child #
# Great God in heaven
you know I love you... #
So what are you
gonna miss the most?
- Hmm?
- When you're gone,
what are you
gonna miss the most?
Fishing for
compliments here?
No, never.
- She is fishing.
- I am not.
Come on, tell me.
Besides you?
Nothing.
I mean, family
and all, sure,
but Dean's gonna be
right there with me.
- Right, Deano?
- Hoo-ha.
Oh, cool!
Don't you just love
a man on a motorcycle?
It's like Peter Fonda
in "Easy Rider."
- Hey guys, don't stare.
- Coming up fast.
Y'all, don't stare at them.
Baby, they're coming
a little too close.
Whoa whoa whoa.
Stop it!
Hey!
Fuck you!
Hey, we better get out of here.
Get down.
Hey! Get off, asshole.
Drive faster!
Man, what the hell's
your problem?
- You okay, baby?
- Yeah.
- You're all right?
- Yeah, I'm good.
- Thomas in there?
- No, he ain't here.
We got a... we got a situation
on our hands here.
I just came back
from the slaughterhouse.
That 'tarded nephew
of yours killed a man.
Now I'm gonna have
to apprehend him.
I thought you might
want to accompany me,
help finesse the situation,
as it were.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
You know what else
Jesse was saying?
Honestly, he tells me
that you can bring a horse
to "organism"
using your finger.
You believe that shit?
No, it's what he said.
Who's the fool that tested
that theory out, I'd like to know?
God damn, I wouldn't
mind doing it.
But I'm just saying,
a bunch of sore horses
running around
out in some farm...
Anyway, staying
around this town,
there's no more jobs,
no more money,
no more food.
It's downright suicidal.
And I'm the last bit
of law enforcement that's left.
Hell, I'm moving
to Michigan next week.
I often ask myself,
"What makes a man a killer?"
I don't mind saying:
You raised that retard right,
me and you, we ain't
taking this drive right now.
You can't have a creature
like that around normal folk,
- that's what I'm saying.
- He ain't retarded. He's misunderstood.
Oh, shit, there he is!
Jesus Christ.
You stay put.
I'll let you know
when I need you.
Put down the weapon, boy!
I seen what you did
back there, Hewitt.
This doesn't have to be difficult
unless'n you make it so.
Just put the weapon down.
Don't be stupid.
I think we've got
a problem, Sheriff.
Shit, I just killed the whole
fucking sheriff's department.
Damn, I wondered
what that felt like.
You really think you're something
in that outfit, don't you?
Here's your pants.
Supper's on the table.
Ladies love
a man in uniform.
That slaughterhouse meant more to this
town than them fools will ever know.
Just a matter of time now
before this town's overrun
by bikers and hippies.
Most families
have already fled.
Well, I say
let 'em go.
Let them flee to the hills
and the cities
that pollute our air,
and our water and our minds.
Us, we're staying
right here.
The ashes
of six generations of Hewitts
have been tilled
into the soil of this farm.
We will never abandon
the place of our birth.
We're on our own
now, people.
And alone
we will
rise above it all.
People may not remember
what we say here tonight,
but they sure as shit
gonna remember what we do.
Thanks to
the good sheriff here,
we ain't gonna
go hungry tonight.
Matter of fact,
we ain't never
gonna starve again.
Mm-mm-mm.
Charlie, say grace.
Mama, I told you
Charlie's dead.
It's Hoyt now,
Sheriff Hoyt.
Lord, thank You for all
this bounty that You've
provided for us here
this evening. Amen.
Tommy, you come on in here
and join us for supper.
Come on now, son.
Oh baby, look! Come on,
can we stop at that store?
It's just like the one
in California. Please?
Yeah yeah.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Come on, Bail,
you'll love this.
These places have tons of character.
Y'all have some beautiful
things in here, ma'am.
Okay...
It'll take you a little while
to get used to things in 'Nam.
The people,
the smells, but...
But what?
You'd be amazed at the things
you can get used to.
Um, is everything okay
with you and Dean?
Uh, what do you mean?
Bailey, come on. You guys have been
exchanging odd glances this whole trip.
Oh...
Excuse me, ma'am, can you tell me where
the bathroom is, please?
Through the back.
Pretty.
But pretty only goes skin-deep.
Ugly is to the bone.
Leave them be.
Come on, Bailey.
Look, we've been through
a lot together.
Whatever it is, you can tell me.
Me and Dean are
going to Mexico.
He's not gonna
go with Eric.
And uh, he's not
going to Vietnam.
Chrissie...
- what do you have to say?
- I say, go.
Get the hell away from this war, okay?
Just cling to what you got.
Then why are you
letting Eric go back?
- It's just in him.
- What's in him?
- The war.
- What do you mean?
Look, you do something long enough,
eventually you start to like it.
Hah!
- Bitch.
- Scared the titties right off her.
God damn it.
Broke my mirror.
You think the girls
are gonna be all right
driving back alone
after they drop us off?
Oh, I'm not worried
about them, Dean.
Are you sure you got
nothing to tell me?
Can we go?
You all right?
Yeah... let's just go.
You didn't even buy anything, baby.
Yeah, it was... it was nothing like
the one in California.
I guess we'll just have to go back
to that one then.
What are you
doing, man?
- What the hell are you doing?
- I'm not going, Eric.
What do you mean,
you're not going?
I'm not going, Eric!
You think I don't
hear you at night, man,
in your sleep, wailing from
what you've done over there?
Now, how could you
want that for me?
I'm glad Dad's
not here to see this.
What, his son
the coward?
Well, guess what, Eric,
I am not like you!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
All right?
I am not ready for this shit!
I have no problem
with the Vietcong over in
Vietnam or whatever...
What the hell do you think
I'm going back for, huh?
- I'm going back for you!
- Stop it!
You think you're the only one who's
ever been scared?
You think I wasn't scared?
You think I'm still not scared?
Shut up!
What does she want?
Pull over!
Oh God. Jesus Christ,
don't pull over!
Shit, she's got a gun, Eric.
Eric!
Shut up!
Stay calm.
- What are we gonna do?
- Eric, she's pulling...
Oh my God!
Look out!
God...
Chrissie.
Buddy, Dean, Deano...
I'm gonna get you help.
I'm gonna find Chrissie.
Chrissie!
Wow, man, I am impressed.
- Y'all are tougher than I thought.
- What do you want from us?
Oh... everything.
How about we get this robbery thing
out of the way, huh?
Fuck.
You play along, and I won't have to kill
this fucking cop or you. Get up!
I'm glad you're
here, officer.
Oh, I just bet you are.
Whoa!
Sir.
You sit down and
you stay right there.
You kids okay?
Why don't you step out
of the car, if you don't mind?
- He shot her! He shot her!
- She can't move, sir. She needs help.
Sir, I can't find
my girlfriend.
Get a grip
on yourself, son.
Sir, I can't find...
Now, that was
for your own good.
Okay, come on kids.
Let's get out of the car now.
Sir, she's... she's really badly hurt.
Right, well okay, kids.
I'm gonna ask you nicely
one more time.
Get out of the fuckin' car
or I'm gonna blow your fuckin' head off.
Come on, you can make it.
Ooh-ee!
You kids must have
been hauling ass.
Look at the fucking
mess you made.
Hey hey hey.
Come on now.
I'm just here
to help you.
Come on now.
- Go on. I ain't gonna hurt you.
- Sir, sir, please.
I'm not gonna
hurt you.
You fucking motherfucker!
See there? That didn't
even hurt, did it?
There ain't no fire
in this accident.
Which one of you assholes
burned his draft card?
Get on over here, boys.
- Come on, get over here.
- No.
God damn it,
get over here!
Which one of you boys'
name is Dean Hill?
Honey, you're name
ain't Dean, is it?
I am, sir...
I'm Dean.
Well, hey, dean.
Good to meet you.
You kids took one
big, nasty, giant shit
right in my backyard.
Now we do know that you're
a coward, right, Dean?
I'm gonna to give you
a chance to die a hero.
All right, get her in there,
God damn it.
I'm starting to think you
like wasting my time, blondie.
Hurry up!
- I saw Chrissie.
- You did?
She's okay.
Just don't say anything.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Where is she?
- Shut up.
Hey, Monty, come pick up
this damn wreck.
It's about a quarter mile
south of Hodd's place.
There's a motorcycle too.
Is having a dead biker chick ride
shotgun proper police procedure, sir?
Honey, if that
was your mama,
would you want me to stick her
in the trunk like a dead animal?
I just think
this is bullshit.
You got something to say
about this bullshit, do you, Dean?
No, sir.
You wouldn't lie to me,
would you, Dean?
Where is the gun?
You look through all this
shit on the road?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Is that how we agreed you'd
address me over official FCC airwaves?
No, "Sheriff."
Oh...
pretty little rascal,
ain't you?
Don't you have to read us our rights
or something, Sheriff?
Who in the hell put you assholes
in charge anyway?
You see, that badge is
the authority around here.
And I ask the questions.
And what brings
you kids here?
Sir, we were just
passing through,
on my way
to reenlist, sir.
A doughboy.
Hot damn.
I was in the army myself
almost a year.
Marines, sir.
Six of one,
half dozen of the other.
Heh, don't make
no damn difference.
You look kind
of young to me.
Where was you stationed?
Vietnam, sir.
Vietnam. Really?
You kill any commies?
Uh, a handful of gooks, sir.
Where are you taking us?
Where are you
taking us, sir?
How was it over there?
Well, it's a...
it's a different culture.
But you'd be amazed at the things you
get used to over there, sir.
You don't say.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
This the sheriff station?
No, it's Mama's house.
Oh! Don't even think
about it here.
What are we
gonna do?
I'm gonna kill
this motherfucker.
Hey!
You kids best not be making a mess
in my car or you'll clean it up.
- He knows, Eric.
- What?
He knows you're not me.
- No, he doesn't, Dean.
- Hey, Tommy!
- Stay the course.
- We're out here!
Come on, boy,
get over here!
- What is that?
- Get the lead out of your ass!
Come on, big guy!
What is that?
Go ahead, get her
on out of there.
Come on, private!
Oh my God.
I'm gonna get
us out of here, okay?
Dean! Stay with me!
I need you
to be a soldier.
People are gonna come
looking for 'em, I know it.
You have made
a big mistake!
Boy, are you dumb.
Nobody's gonna miss those
creatures, not one person.
Not now,
not when they gone.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Let's see.
Anything in here?
A bunch of shit.
Oh...
You little bastard,
I know you've got more in there.
Come on, Tommy, ain't no different
than the slaughterhouse.
Meat's meat, bones bones.
Get it done.
My daddy always told me
that if you want to be a good farmer
you gotta keep your livestock clean.
Clean goat
is a happy goat.
What the hell do you
want from us, man?
Are you happy yet?
Hey!
H... hey, help us.
Help us down, please.
I don't get involved
in his affairs. No.
Please, help me.
Please, please.
No! No!
Help me! No!
No!
- No!
- Bailey.
- I didn't know.
- Didn't know what?
I didn't know you were
going back there for me.
Let's figure out how
to get out of here, Dean.
By God, I'm gonna make
a soldier out of you yet!
No! Please, please!
Are you ashamed
of your country, Dean?
No, please! No!
What do you think,
soldier?
What would be the proper
punishment for treason?
Just please
let him go, sir. No!
I can't make out a word you're saying,
you know it, asshole?
You're killing him, sir!
Please!
No no no!
Please, sir!
Ain't nothing I hate worse
than a draft-dodging hippie protester.
I'm Dean!
It was my draft card!
And you'd just stand
here and let him die.
Sir, could you let
him breathe, please?
Please, can you
let him breathe?
- My apologies.
- Eric!
Oh shit!
Well, so now you want to play
soldier. Is that it?
Your brother
saved your life.
I'm gonna fucking
cut your head off.
Yeah, you just keep
sweet-talking me, dumpling.
Help me!
Back in 1952, Korean War,
yours truly was a P.O.W.
That's "prisoner of war"
for you,
and I know what in the hell
I'm talking about.
Used to be
Sergeant Major Hoyt.
Back in those days
there wasn't no rules.
No regulations like
there are today.
You got captured,
you had two choices:
You starve to death
or survive.
Now, you had to eat.
Rations were scarce.
So, well,
about once a week
some poor soul was chosen.
Chosen?
You fucking idiot!
I just told you we had to eat!
Ain't you listening
to me? Huh?
I'd say that's the ultimate sacrifice
for your country, wouldn't you?
Why are you doing this?
Got to get
you cleaned up.
We're gonna have company.
You don't want to look
dirty for company, do you?
Huh?
This is your lucky day!
Now what happens if you kids
drive all the way up to Austin
just to find out that you don't even
qualify to be in the army?
I'm concerned about
your physical fitness here!
Now, doesn't that
make you feel special?
Huh? Don't it?
Please.
That would be,
"Please, Sheriff."
- You got it?
- Please, Sheriff.
Hey, boy, there you go.
I knew you could do that.
That wasn't so hard,
was it?
How would you like to just
stand right up here today
and just walk
right on out of here, huh?
I'd like that, Sheriff.
Yeah, well, freedom ain't free.
You know that, right?
What you gonna
do is 20 push-ups.
20 push-ups stand
between you and freedom.
This shit is what heroes
are made of, you know?
Well, come on,
I'm waiting!
Let's get with
the program, sunshine!
Come on, you can do it!
Get those push-ups now!
No!
Shh, now don't cry.
Don't cry.
No.
No!
You shut your cocksucker,
you son of a bitch!
One!
Whoa, that was a really
fine push-up there. One...
Two...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
We've got ourselves a regular
American hero here, ain't we?
Three.
Come on, sweetheart.
# Hush, little baby #
# Don't say a word... #
Ow!
# Mama's gonna buy
you a mockingbird... #
Eight.
What's it gonna be?
You're gonna be
the motherfucker who eats?
Or are you gonna be
the poor sorry motherfucker
who gets ate?
# If that mockingbird
don't sing... #
# Mama's gonna buy you
a golden ring... #
Don't give up, Dean!
Show this motherfucker!
Show me that you
ain't as fucked up
as the rest of your
useless goddamn generation.
Eighteen!
# If that golden... #
- Come on!
- Nine...
# ... Is gonna buy you
a looking glass... #
Go!
That's only half of one.
That don't count, boy!
Don't give up, Dean!
- 20.
- Yeah!
Don't cry.
No!
- No.
- I never had me a little girl.
Got more guts than
I thought you had, boy.
I'm a man of my word.
You're free to go.
I'm gonna
fucking kill you!
My money says
he ain't going nowhere.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Stop!
Please, stop!
Please stop!
Look... my friends, they...
they have my friends, okay? They're in a
house over there through the woods. I...
Look, they have your friend.
They took your friend.
I saw you both
at the store.
He shot her.
The sheriff shot her.
Show me where.
Weather has been
so hot lately.
It's important to drink
your liquids, you know?
The body needs
to hydrate.
I got me some of that breakfast tea...
that's what they call it...
and I fixed me up
a batch of that
and I had it over a big fruit jar of ice
with plenty of sugar.
And I had that
breakfast tea for dinner.
Tastes like paradise.
Not a bit
of difference.
Iced tea.
Yeah, iced tea.
You know
what else is good?
- Iced coffee.
- Oh.
Delicious.
With them little cinnamon sprinkles.
Dean. Dean!
Dean, you did good.
But we gotta hide, okay?
Come on!
Do you have any idea where
the hell we're going?
Yes, it's...
it's here somewhere.
Sometimes...
I just can't stop eating
them little chocolates.
They're so good.
I put coconut in them.
Oh, sweet Jesus.
Hoyt! Hoyt!
Come here! Hoyt!
Eric!
- He's in here!
- Eric! Get me out of here!
- Shut your mouth!
- Oh, my!
He's here! He's here!
He's here!
Help! Help!
There's keys over
there on the counter.
Damn you!
A man's home is his fucking castle!
- What the fuck are you doing in here?
- Oh no!
Hey!
Find the truck. Go!
I'll get Dean! I'll get Dean!
Unlock the door!
Thomas, Thomas, get up here!
I need you!
Come on, Dean, come on.
Hey! Get back here,
you skinny bitch!
No!
Come on, we're gonna
get out of here.
Dean, go! Go!
Come on!
Shoot me, you asshole!
You're not a soldier!
You hold that gun like a fucking girl!
Get out of my way.
You're not a candy-ass,
are you, Sheriff?
Pull the fucking trigger!
I ain't finished
with you yet.
Well... let's just go see
if we caught anything.
Well well well...
it's a good thing
you didn't go to Vietnam.
Something like
this might've happened.
You don't like playing with me
anymore because I'm a pussy.
That's what you said.
Well, my nephew Tommy
ain't no pussy.
Maybe you want to play
with him for a little while.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
That's it.
Okay, so what
are we gonna do?
We? I'm gonna get
my girlfriend.
No no, look.
What about my friends?
- What?
- My friends.
Fuck your friends.
You're on your own.
You asshole!
Shit.
Dean, Dean. Oh fuck. Thank God.
What happened?
- Chrissie. Oh, thank God.
- Oh, Jesus Christ.
- No no no. Don't!
- I'm sorry.
Just stay still.
Okay, are you okay? You're okay.
They're psycho.
Come on, where's Eric
and Bailey? Come on.
In the house.
You need to go
get help, Chrissie.
Okay?
There's no help to go for.
I have to go in there. You're gonna stay
here. I'm gonna come get you, okay?
Okay.
Don't you think you're
gonna go anyplace, huh?
I love you.
No! Come on! You don't... you don't
have to do this, man, please.
No! No. No!
No!
You don't have
to do this.
You son of a bitch!
Fuck you!
Fucker.
Huh?
What the fuck...
Oh shit!
- Uh, he shot me! Uh!
- Shut up! Shut up!
Where's the girl?
I'm gonna blow your head off.
Tell me where the girl is.
I'm shot! Shit!
How many times I gotta tell you
not to play with guns?
Oh, Jesus, oh...
Now look what you've
done to yourself.
- I didn't do it.
- Stop your damn whining, Uncle Monty.
Mama, get some
towels in here.
Uncle Monty made a mess.
Sheriff.
Who in the hell are you?
- What do you want, boy?
- I want my girl.
Take me to her
or I'm gonna blow your head off.
Okay, all right.
- Where is she?
- Thomas!
Hey! Do not fuck around.
Where is the girl?
Come on.
Help me!
Thomas!
Thomas, where're you at?
Eric, are you okay?
What are you doing here?
You gotta get out of here.
- You're... you're gonna be okay.
- How bad is it? Tell me.
- No! No!
- It's all right. I can't feel it.
- I'm gonna get you... it's okay.
- Did he cut it off?
- It's okay.
- I can't feel it.
No! No!
I'm cold.
How... how many?
- Three.
- Boys or girls?
All boys.
What are their names?
Paul and Christopher...
and Eric.
Okay. Okay.
It's gonna be okay.
I promise.
I promise, okay?
Take it easy.
There she is.
Help me.
That's not her.
Shit, that ain't her.
You don't want
to see the other girl.
Just shoot him!
You dumb son of a bitch.
Get him, Tommy, come on!
Damn it! Come on, Tommy.
This is one
of those assholes
who used to fuck with you
in the schoolyard, Tommy.
Come on, Tommy, get over here!
Get that thing going!
Let's go, Tommy!
Come on!
Crank it up!
Let's go!
What it is, asshole!
Yeah!
You beautiful bastard, you!
You fucking asshole!
You son of a bitch!
Comin' in my fucking house...
Oh, God.
You have to
get out of here.
- No no no!
- Get out of here.
- No!
- Yes, Chrissie, please.
Hide!
What are you doing?
Don't. No.
What are you...
No!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Thomas! Tommy.
Thomas, quit playing with your
fucking dolls and get up here!
I'm glad you brought
your little buddy.
Hmm, I like
your new face.
Come on, Tommy,
get up here.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Please! Please!
Help!
Please, please, somebody help!
Now this will take your
fever down, all right?
See what you've done?
You killed that sheriff
and you started up a whole whirlwind.
Mama, please stop
your damn bellyaching.
Uncle Monty,
I love you.
You know that, and I always do
what's right by you, don't I?
And you trust me,
don't you?
Yeah, I trust you.
Just do something.
Take care of you.
Get in here, boy!
- Uh! Ow!
- Oh, I'm sorry.
Tommy!
- Now, this ain't gonna hurt...
- Huh?
...much.
What's that on your face?
Mama, you get over there
and hold Uncle Monty.
- Why?
- 'Cause he ain't gonna like this much,
that's why.
- No!
- What the fuck is this?
Surgery.
Come on, Tommy.
- No!
- Oh my God!
Oh, bullshit.
Look at that!
Now, Tommy,
that's goddamn sloppy.
That'll get infected.
Even him up. Come on.
- Huh?
- What?
- Sheriff, no, stop!
- No!
There you go.
Nice work, Tommy.
What did
you do that for?
Balance.
I'll get Tommy
to wrap this up.
Please, somebody help.
Okay. Shh.
You're gonna
be okay, okay?
Shh shh, I'm sorry.
It's okay. You're safe.
They know you're here.
I'll have Mama throw on
another plate for supper.
You... you can stay?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I think we need a little more
garlic in this one.
Mama, a little more
I'll go set the table.
Oh, shit!
It's okay, Mama.
Just wash it off. It'll be fine.
Don't step on the fingers.
What the hell are they
doing on the floor, anyway?
Good thing you keep
a clean house.
I wonder whose tongue this is.
That's that fuckin' biker.
# Hush little baby, don't say a word #
# Mama's gonna buy you #
# A mockingbird #
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
# If that mockingbird
don't sing #
# Mama's gonna buy you #
# A golden ring... #
# If that golden
ring turns brass #
# Mama's gonna buy
you a looking glass... #
Why are you doing this?
No talking until after
I've said grace, asshole.
Now...
let's give thanks
for the bounty that's been given us.
Bow your heads.
I was hungry
and He gave me meat.
I was thirsty
and He gave me drink.
I was a stranger
and He took me in.
This family has endured
through adversity and pain.
- We have endured.
- Dean.
We have prevailed.
We will never ever
go hungry again.
Amen.
I have
a question for you.
One that involves
the family tree, the...
lineage, if you will,
So I guess this
one's for the table.
You guys fuck
all your cousins
or just the ones
you find attractive?
You blasphemous bitch!
This is redemption, lady!
That's what this is!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh, you're all gonna pay
for your sins. That's right!
And especially you!
Mama... go take care
of Uncle Monty.
You know what, Mama?
I don't think this
one likes your cooking.
But who gives a shit?
She's gonna be sucking
her soup through a straw
for some time
to come now, ain't she?
Come on, Monty,
take a sip.
You gotta have something
to build up your strength.
Please do it.
Just do whatever you're gonna do,
you bunch of degenerates!
I will not have you
speak ill of this family.
Come on, now,
open your mouth.
No. No. No.
Set her free, child.
No! No!
No! No! No! No!
Take that one downstairs!
No, you stay away from me,
you fucking animal!
You get the fuck
away from me! No!
Get your hands off me!
You dirty animal!
No! Dean! Dean!
Can't you see?
Your friend ain't with us no more.
No! No! No!
Here we go.
Dean! Help! No!
No!
Hey!
Where in the hell
you going, bitch?
She's gonna tell them all
what we done.
There comes a time when
every boy becomes a man.
You motherfucker!
Now we'll see what kind of soldier
you are, Sheriff.
One!
That was beautiful
form, Sheriff!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Two! Halfway doesn't
count, dickhead!
Three! Is that all you got?
Is that all you fucking got?
Fucker! You killed
my girlfriend!
You fucking asshole!
Fuck you!
My money says
you're not going anywhere.
Fuck.
Chrissie!
From 1969 to 1973
the Hewitt family murdered
33 people across the state of Texas.
To this day their killing spree
is universally considered
one of the most notorious
and perversely sadistic crimes
in the annals
of American history:
The Texas Chainsaw Massacre.