Raymond!
Ray? Sweetie?
Ah, I play it loud.
Like, I can't hear him.
Pack your things,
you're going back to the hospital.
I'm calling Daddy and he is taking you back.
Mom said you have to hurry.
- Hey.
- Is that the thing for the bank?
Yeah. Yeah, that's a commission.
Butterflies? So not metal.
I know, I know, I agree.
But most people don't like metal.
Most people's taste is in their...
Have you not showered yet? We're late.
Guys, can we listen to something
just a little bit less heavy?
Metallica?
I'm not sure
that's what your mom had in mind.
Wow. It's gorgeous.
Lived in Texas my whole life.
It's always been hot but, well...
...even Satan's praying for it to rain.
As y'all can see, everything's true
to the turn of the century period.
Yeah, I... I love this wallpaper.
- Special, ain't it?
- Yeah.
And through here, north facin',
double hung windows.
Sunlight streamin' in.
I'm not one for flowery words,
but tranquil comes to mind.
Zo, this is twice the size of the room
that you have right now.
Have fun, you're not gonna see any of them
with all the posters that you have.
If there's even one teddy left...
...you have to buy me some more.
- Okay?
- Yeah. Of course.
Could make a mighty fine bedroom
for a teenager down the track.
When she's ready for some space of her own.
This is gonna be Daddy's studio.
Or a studio. Yes, indeed.
Okay. By law I have to fess up
to any death in the house.
And in this case there were two.
Um, sweetie...
...I had left my bag in the car
and it's got some documents I need.
- If you want me to leave, just ask.
- Okay.
And now you can't sell it
which is why the price is so low.
Next showings at eleven,
got 'em lined up all day.
Folks love a bargain.
After all, what are we talkin' about here?
A sweet little old lady who accidentally
fell down the stairs...
...and her dear old hubby
who couldn't stand to live without her.
Sad, indeed...
...but it's not like
Charlie Manson lived here.
Can you give us a minute, please?
Thank you.
- You don't find it creepy?
- What?
- The couple?
- Yeah.
No.
No, I actually think it's really romantic.
He loved her so much he couldn't
live another day without her.
- You just want this studio.
- What? No.
I'm not even thinkin' about this.
- Can you hear that?
- What? What?
- Wait.
- What do you mean, what?
That right there. Astrid...
Jesse...
- You can't hear that?
- No, I can't hear that. What is it?
Buy me.
You don't hear that?
'Cause it's screaming at me.
I can't ignore it.
Can I help you?
Zo's gonna have to change schools.
She'll be alright, she's a brave kid.
It's like two buses for me
to get to the salon.
Not if we get a second car.
You have to do more commissions. We just...
we cannot do this on my salary alone.
I mean, rent is one thing
but this is a serious mortgage.
I know, Astrid, why do you think I'm
painting fuckin' butterflies for a bank...
...even though it makes me want to puke?
Astrid, please, chill.
Alright. Here.
Please just... just take a hit. Okay?
Exhale.
Good.
Close your eyes.
Repeat after me...
...we just bought a house.
- "We just bought a house."
- Yeah!
And it's a beautiful fuckin' house.
- "And it is a beautiful fucking house."
- Yeah.
We're gonna be happy.
"We're going to be happy."
'Cause we never have to look
at that view ever again.
Come here.
County Sheriff's office, open up.
Can you open up a little so I can see?
Uh...
You know why I'm here?
I got a call about some loud music.
What's your name?
Ray.
You gonna help us both out
and keep quiet, Ray?
Yeah.
Let me hear you say it.
I'm gonna help us both out and keep quiet.
Good. I don't want to have to come back.
If I come back...
...I got no choice but to give you
citation or ticket...
...or worse, place you under arrest.
I'd much rather not.
It's never as bad as you think.
Seriously, you just tough out the first
30 minutes and then the rest is gravy.
I hate gravy.
Alright, go forth, brave soldier.
Don't let your schooling get in the way
of your education, alright?
Yeah. I love you, Dad.
Hey, Zo.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh, my God.
- Zooey.
- I haven't gotten you that good in ages.
Yeah, that was hysterical.
That was super funny.
Thank you.
How was your first day?
Sucked big time.
Hey, hey.
It'll get better, I promise.
Okay, it just takes time.
Yeah, anything new, it just takes time.
What happened to the butterflies?
Jess? Jess?
Jesse!
Where were you?
What?
I'll get it!
Hi.
There's someone here
and it's not the pizza man.
Hi.
I've got one just like that.
A flying V.
You got a red Flying V?
I want a Gibson Flying V
like Kirk Hammett from Metallica uses.
He is my favorite guitar hero. I asked
Mom and Dad to get one for my birthday...
...but you know, Gibsons are really
expensive so I'm getting a little cheaper...
Excuse me.
- Can I help you?
- Mmm.
I need to come home now.
This is Mommy and Daddy's house.
They're dead.
Oh, my God. I'm so sorry.
I'm really sorry about
what happened with your parents.
But you don't live here anymore.
Okay. It's time for you to leave.
They won't let me play it loud.
- I need to play it loud.
- You need to leave, now.
- Dad.
- Jess... Jesse.
You need to leave before I call the police.
Alright, that's it, I'm calling the police.
I'm callin' 'em right now.
You were mean.
You say, "treat everyone like
the way you want to be treated."
You didn't do that.
What?
Well, the poor guy, obviously
has something wrong with him...
...and his parents did just die in our house.
We've come to the place...
...where we joke about the idea of the devil.
With the horns, and the tail, and all that.
But that is Satan's lie...
...to distract us
from the reality of who He is.
He is no mask in a Halloween store.
He's not what you see in the movies.
He is an active, violent,
anti-God personal reality.
And as much as we refuse
to admit it, He lives through us.
He uses us to carry out
His unspeakable deeds.
For we are His pawns,
we are His demons on Earth...
...we satiate His hunger.
If you have the slightest bit
of greed, in your heart...
...He will turn it into an avalanche.
He will slither into your soul.
That's really great, Zooey, that's not
gonna win you any Academy Awards.
You're not supposed to go if you're sick
because everyone else gets sick too.
Well, it looks like we got
an outbreak on our hands.
Oh, my God. Dad.
I said I wanted a Flying V
and he's given me his.
And a Marshall, Dad,
he's given me his Marshall...
Dad.
I can keep 'em, right?
Please. Please.
No. I can't let you keep this guitar.
Hey. Hey.
I'm gettin' you a guitar and an amp
for your birthday. Come on.
Not a Flying V, and a Marshall.
I know that Leonard
already rejected my portfolio.
- But I just need...
- Leonard doesn't look at artists twice, Jesse.
Yes, I know, but please.
This is different.
I've never had a muse before.
I don't remember painting this.
It's like it's... it's like somethin'...
It flowed through me.
I'll see what I can do.
Rocky?
Here, boy.
Come on, Rocky.
Just gonna go get Rocky.
Rocky.
Here, boy.
What the fuck?
I'm so sorry.
Hey.
Zo.
Okay, you know what?
I deserve that. Okay, totally deserve that.
I'm really sorry, Zo.
It's only my second day.
I don't know anyone.
And you just left me here.
I was painting.
I thought that I was in there
for five minutes.
And I stepped outside and the sun
had gone down and I panicked.
I didn't think that
I was in there for so long.
I just... I completely got lost in it.
- Don't do it again.
- I won't.
- Swear.
- I swear.
On my grave.
I swear.
Can we please be friends again? Please?
Are you gonna let me keep the guitar and amp?
Hello, Austin, it's been a while,
but are you ready to get heavy?
I said, are you ready to get heavy?
Scissor kick off the Marshall stack.
Thank you, everyone.
Throughout the ages,
in all the various religions of man...
...there is one constant.
The personality of the being we call Satan.
In Samaria, He was Baal.
In Egypt, Set.
In Persia, Orin.
In China, He was chief
of the warlock, called Wu.
There is always the dark God.
The fallen God.
There's always Satan.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Did you tell her that she
could keep the guitar because...
...you know, I thought
that you said that you...
Oh, my God.
Is that...
I didn't mean to do this.
Okay, what's going on?
This... this is our daughter on fire.
- She can never see this.
- Okay, well, then destroy it.
I can't.
Why?
Because it isn't finished yet.
- No, it is, if you want it to be.
- No. No, it's not that simple, Astrid.
It's like these children are inside of me.
Begging, screaming to be let out.
And I don't know why.
Come on.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
He wanted it to be you.
I wouldn't let Him.
'Cause you're a special one.
No. No, no, no. You can't be loud.
He'll make me do that thing I don't wanna
do and I don't wanna do that to you.
Please, please, please. Please, be quiet.
If I take my hand away,
are you gonna be loud?
- No.
- Mm-mm.
Cross your heart?
- And hope to die?
- Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Help!
Don't! Don't!
No!
Get out!
Get out! Get out!
Were the doors locked?
Uh, yes, they were but, um...
- Jess went out to the studio...
- I'm so sorry.
It's not your fault.
It's his fault.
Now you mentioned that
he'd lived here before you all?
Mm-hmm.
- Still the same locks?
- Yeah.
Then there's every chance
that he has a key...
...which means you need to change them locks.
Okay.
And I think it's best if you folks move
into a motel. Even just for a few days.
Give us some time to run the prints
and take a real good look into this guy.
I'll be stationed outside all night
until you're up and out in the morning.
So don't you worry.
You're gonna be alright.
Try and get some sleep, okay.
It's gonna make you feel a lot better.
What if he comes back?
Well, that's why the police lady is outside.
What if he gets past her?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Astrid. I'm so sorry.
I thought that you were...
I'm okay. I'm okay.
I'm ready for school.
- No...
- Sweetie...
Sweetie, you don't have
to go to school today.
It's safer than here.
If he comes back, I'll smash him.
I'm gonna be late.
Bye.
Oh, fuck.
- Hey.
- Jesse.
- Yeah.
- It's Mara.
I showed Leonard your painting.
He approves.
- That's, uh, that's...
- He'd like to come by your studio.
- See what you're working on.
- Yeah, yeah. No, definitely.
- That's great, any time.
- Leonard's got an opening at three.
- Wait, today?
- Yes.
No, I can't.
I have to pick my daughter up at three.
I can push it back to two.
But that's all I can do.
Take it or leave it, Jesse.
Come on.
What this is, Jesse, is a show of faith.
But I'm willing to take that chance.
Because your latest work is...
...wonderfully disturbing.
Fuckin' painting nearly killed me.
Le sang de la terre.
- I'm sorry.
- The blood of the Earth.
The world's oldest unblended cognac.
That's what we've been sharing.
Beside the moment of course.
Now that you're being represented by Belial.
It's time for you to start
getting used to nice things.
Uh, Leonard...
...I'd love to sit here and drink
this whole bottle with you right now...
...really, I would,
but I gotta pick my daughter up.
I'm sure your daughter won't mind
if you're one or two minutes late.
I'm already pushing it.
What's a few minutes in the grander scheme?
Actually, it's everything.
I'm not gonna get into it
right now, just trust me.
I can't be late.
Well, as they say...
"nothing of true worth comes without some...
...sacrifice."
To sacrifice.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh, no.
Come on!
Come on.
Zooey!
He's right.
You are the sweetest candy of them all.
I have to do that thing I don't wanna do now.
Please. Please.
Let me go, please!
Please!
You...
...swore on my grave.
Look, um...
I know it doesn't seem
like it right now but...
...she's actually very lucky.
When he was twelve, he did
the same thing to a 9-year-old girl.
Hit her over the head with a rock
and then he tried to bury her.
Case went to juvenile court and he
ended up in state psychiatric for 20 years.
Does it say in there...
...why he did it?
"I have to feed Him children.
Because children are His candy."
He goes on to clarify who "He" is...
...none other than Satan himself.
Thanks for your patience.
How's she doin'?
Like I was tellin' Jesse here.
I think the best course of action
is to put you into witness protection.
And how long does witness protection last?
As long as it takes to find him.
Just the gas?
- Need a hand with that?
- Nope. I got it.
- You sure?
- Yep.
Okay.
Alright.
Thank you. Your key, officer.
- Thank you.
- Uh-huh.
- I really feel bad for that little girl.
- Yeah.
It's gonna be a long time
before she sleeps through the night.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Where is he? He was just here.
- Dad?
No! No.
Zo. I'll be right back.
Zooey! Zooey!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
He's right outside of our door!
- Run!
- Zooey, come on!
No. No. No.
No!
Mom! Daddy!
No! No! No! No!
No!
Jesse.
Jess...
No. Zooey, Zooey.
Please, don't hurt her.
Please, don't hurt her, please.
No, stop!
Zooey, don't.
- No! No!
- No, no. No!
No!
Mom!
No, no! No!
Please, please, please.
Please.
Jesse.
Jesse, you have to wake up, he's got her.
Jesse!
Where is she?
No! No!
No! No, no, no!
No, no, no!
Look, look, look! Look.
It's Him.
Hang on, Zooey!
No, no, no!
Daddy!
No, no.
Zo... Zooey. Zooey, you need to come to me.
- Just jump really fast.
- I can't!
Please trust me.
I'm gonna catch you, Zo.
Are you okay?
Zooey.
Where are you going?
I can feel them inside me...
...begging, screaming to be let out.
And I don't know why.