Don't be afraid.
Do you believe in sin?
There's nothing to believe.
"The battle against the Devil, which is the principal task
of Saint Michael the Archangel, is still being fought today,
because the Devil is still alive and active in the world."
Pope John Paul II
What follows is inspired by true events.
- You finished?
- Yep.
Then wash up and come eat.
I've washed up.
Well, then eat.
And when you're done,
I'll need a hand with the casket.
How'd she do it?
What?
Kill herself.
Michael, I've told you this many times.
We serve the dead,
but we don't talk about them.
It brings bad things.
We keep dead people in the house, Dad.
How much worse could it get?
- Are you kidding me?
- No, Eddie. I'm not kidding.
Wait, why?
So I can get out of here.
Why not tell him you wanna go to college?
I mean, you got the grades. You can do it.
- You think he'd pay for that?
- Shit, man. Seminary school?
Wait, wait, wait. Wait.
Seminary school, really?
Wait, is this your way of telling me
you're gay? I'm just joking. Okay? Joking.
Man, you don't get it. In my family, you're
either a mortician or a priest. That's it.
Well, then change your name.
It's too late. I took the entrance exam.
- You what?
- I passed.
I'm leaving Monday.
That's... That's crazy.
Dude, I've looked into it.
It's a four-year degree
before you even take your first vows.
If it doesn't work out, I can always leave.
Wow. Such faith.
You know what, Eddie?
You're such a dick.
Cool. Awesome. Whatever, dude.
I will never confess to you.
You know that, right?
These are on the house.
- Wow.
- Gonna get heat for giving away beers?
Not if they don't know.
How about for banging the customers?
Screw you, Eddie.
Drink up. I'm off in 10.
Lickety-split.
"Lickety-split"? Pbbb.
You better make the most of that
before they chop your wiener off.
Goodbye, wiener.
Don't worry.
The pain is gone.
God has taken it...
...away.
Michael. Come.
Don't be afraid.
Four years later.
This is always a special Mass for me...
... as I look upon our new deacons...
... as they prepare to go into the world
with Christ's message.
So in the next few months,
you will face your last assessments...
...and then be asked to take
your final vows to become priests.
So I leave you with these words to
consider, from the Gospel of Saint John:
You did not choose me...
...it was I who chose you...
...and I send you forth
to bear fruit that will last.
Michael.
Exam results.
You aced psychology.
- Art history too. Congratulations.
- Thank you.
So, what happened with theology?
It's like you blew it on purpose.
I've been distracted.
End of the year, that's all.
Drop by my office this week.
We'll discuss it.
Okay.
Yeah, jump. Take him out.
Dude, honestly?
Michael!
Michael, wait!
Call an ambulance!
Bless me, Father.
Father.
Bless me.
Please, Father.
I don't wanna die like this.
Uh, through the power vested in me:
Let the fire of the Holy Spirit descend,
that this being may be awakened...
...in the world beyond
the life of this earth...
...and infused with the power
of the Holy Spirit.
Lord Jesus Christ, I ask
that you receive this child...
What's your name?
Sandra.
I ask you to receive this child,
Sandra, into your loving arms...
...that she might pass in safety
from this crisis...
...as you have taught us
with infinite passion.
By this sign, you are anointed with the grace
of the atonement of our Lord Jesus Christ...
...and absolved of all past error
and freed to take your place...
...in the world he has prepared for us.
Amen.
Michael.
I still don't even understand
how it happened.
You shouldn't think about it.
It was an accident. Really.
It's hard not to think about.
I feel somewhat responsible.
You know the average age
of a nun these days?
Sixty-nine.
Three thousand parishes across the U.S.
Don't even have a priest anymore.
You give this speech
to everyone who tries to leave?
No, just those I believe in.
I quit smoking and
now I'm addicted to these.
You know, what I saw the other night,
it was really something.
I know experienced priests
who wouldn't have handled that.
I just repeated a few prayers
over a suffering girl.
And the words meant nothing to you?
Father, listen to me,
did you understand my letter?
Yes, I decided not to
pass it on to my superiors.
- Why not?
- I think you're making a mistake.
I think this is the part where I say, "It's
not you, it's me" and "Let's just be friends."
Here's the thing.
Tastes like shit.
If a seminarian doesn't complete his vows,
then under Article 15...
...the Church has the right to convert
the scholarship to a student loan.
That's over 100 grand of education
you'd owe us.
Why would you do that?
Oh, no, no, no.
I'm not saying I'm going to do it...
...just yet.
You were a mortician
before you joined us, am I right?
I imagine that means
you're not very squeamish.
What is this about?
Last year, the Vatican received over a half
a million reports of demonic possession.
- That's something of a record.
- I'm still not following.
An order has been passed down...
...to place an exorcist in every diocese
across the U.S. By this time next year.
As you might imagine, it's not
a highly sought-after position.
There's a new program at the Vatican...
...designed to reteach the clergy
the rite of exorcism.
I've been asked to keep an eye out
for potential candidates.
Wait a minute, you...
You want me to be an exorcist?
Why?
Why would you want me?
I don't know what I believe in.
That's right.
I remember in your letter...
...you explained how you used
the priesthood to run away from things.
The truth is, you could have run
in any direction, but you ran here.
Why?
Just take the course.
And then if you still wanna leave when
you get back, we can talk about it then.
Two months in Rome.
How bad could that be?
Keep the change. Thank you.
I'm guessing there's no cable.
By the time an exorcist is called
to assess a possible possession...
... the parish priest would have ensured...
... that all psychiatric explanations
had been exhausted.
He would have questioned
the possessed himself...
... and forwarded his assessment
on to his bishop.
With the bishop's permission...
... an exorcist is then summoned
to determine possession.
Often, early signs of a possession
are subtle.
Social withdrawal...
...apathy...
...a persistent tremor in a limb.
It can go unnoticed
until the victim is deep within...
...the demonic spirit's grasp.
This was taken at an exorcism in Turin.
The woman survived without food or water
for eight weeks...
...before the demon released her.
This man's jaw spontaneously dislocated
while being read the Lord's Prayer.
He made no physical contact
with any object...
...nor was he met with
any physical force.
Demons are the devil's foot soldiers...
...often operating in groups
much like a squadron...
...infesting their victims.
It is the job of an exorcist...
...to determine the number of
possessing demons and their names...
...something the demons protect
with great ferocity.
And when the exorcist has a name...
...he can then begin to
assert control over the entity...
...and cast it out.
Who have we here?
- Michael Kovak.
- I'm sorry?
Michael Kovak.
Oh, yes.
The American.
- Yeah. Sorry I'm late.
- Yes, I prefer punctuality to apologies.
Welcome. Sit down.
Die, priest, die!
The most identifiable sign
of a possession...
...is the negative reaction
to sacred objects.
Crucifixes, holy water.
The man that you have just heard...
...was reacting to a crucifix
placed on his head.
- Excuse me, Father.
- Yes?
What if he was suffering from
the delusion that he's possessed?
Wouldn't he react in the same way?
Admittedly, it's very easy to
confuse psychotic illness with possession.
It's up to the exorcist
to discern the difference.
So how do you do that?
Well, there are many ways.
For example, paranoid schizophrenics
are not aware that they're deluded.
Neither are the possessed while
they're being possessed, are they?
But people who are possessed
have periods of lucidity. That's my point.
So do schizophrenics.
One can't suddenly manifest
abilities simply because one is deluded.
The man on this tape is German.
How does he spontaneously
speak Russian?
How could a boy in a village in Africa
found 400 miles from his home...
...claim that he was abducted by aliens?
It's just as unlikely.
But we're willing to call him crazy
and your German man not...
...because he believes in aliens,
not God.
We're not here
to scrutinize religion with science.
The object of this course is to view
phenomena through the lens of faith.
So which do you believe in,
aliens or God?
The jury's out on both.
Interesting perspective for a priest.
I'm not a priest...
...yet.
So you're having a final fling
with atheism?
Well, I guess it's more like an ex-girlfriend
who keeps coming around.
Angelina.
We are going to the library..
Are you joining us?
Thank you, gentlemen. See you at Mass.
Michael. Walk with me a moment.
I understand you were taught
by Father Matthew.
That's right.
He's a dear friend.
We studied together at Loyola.
He's asked me to keep an eye on you.
He thinks you've got great potential.
That's a lot of pressure.
For both of us.
What do you think of the course so far?
To be honest, I don't know
what to make of it.
I suspected as much.
Tell me, Michael, do you believe in sin?
Yeah, I just don't necessarily believe
the devil makes us do it.
He that committeth sin is of the devil.
Then that'd be all of us, wouldn't it?
And if we're all of the devil,
how do we fight him?
Tomorrow, I recommend you take
your doubts for a walk around Rome.
You can pay a visit
to an old friend of mine.
Father Lucas?
He's Welsh. Jesuit.
His methods are a little less orthodox.
Studied under
Father Carmine De Filippis.
- I don't know what that means.
- It means he knows his stuff.
He'll be happy to provide you with
the kind of proof you seem to need.
Excuse me, I have a Mass to say.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Jesus.
- Father Lucas?
- Yes?
Hi. I'm Michael Kovak.
- Oh. You're the American.
- Yeah.
- You don't like cats?
- Not particularly.
Welcome to Rome.
It's infested with cats.
I've tried giving them names
but it's pointless.
A cat won't come no matter what
you call it. They do as they please.
Anyway, welcome.
Make sure they don't come in.
No. Hey, hey.
Father Xavier tells me you're troubled.
I don't think Father Xavier
explained the situation.
He explained it well enough.
I've arranged for you to meet someone.
Speak of the devil.
God bless you, Father,
thank you for seeing us.
There's no need to thank me.
Put it in the kitchen.
Sit down.
Have you fed them?
No, they don't need feeding.
Lucia. Gabriella. Dante. Federico.
Where's Hermione?
Come now.
No. I want to see Hermione.
After. Come.
If you wanna watch, you have
to help me. I'll need to absolve you first.
Help with what?
The exorcism. What do you think?
Or you can stay down here
with her aunt.
That could be fun.
It's up to you.
Whatever you do, don't address the girl
directly, no matter what she says.
And if I ask you to hold her down...
...it's best you grab her arms
from behind...
...and try keeping her
in a seated position.
The spirit is pretty devious.
Hasn't shown itself yet.
- The spirit?
- Yes. Spirit.
Demon. The devil.
If it hasn't shown itself,
how do you know she's possessed?
All right, give me something,
anything that's yours.
Put it in this.
What is it, a dollar bill?
Come on, do it. Quickly.
It's for your benefit.
What else?
Oh, yes. It's Michael, isn't it?
I absolve you of any sins you may
have committed now or in the past...
...in the name of the Father,
Son and Holy Spirit.
- Amen.
- All right, come on.
Oh, yes, one other thing. If it does manifest,
don't even look into the girl's eyes.
Whatever you do, do not address it.
Do not speak to it. It's the devil.
- Leave that to me. Do you understand?
- Cool.
- Do you understand?
- Yeah, I get it.
Well, just say so.
Bow your head, keep praying
and good luck.
How are you?
The same.
Have you eaten?
What about your baby?
You need to eat.
Okay.
Um...
What's happened since Tuesday?
It won't stop now.
Even when I sleep it talks.
Okay.
Now she's gonna guess what's in the bag.
Rosaria?
See the bag?
Tell me what's in it.
How could I know that?
Then I want you to guess.
I don't know.
Clear your mind and guess.
It's not a test. Just guess.
I don't want to.
I'm ordering you to guess! Guess!
Show her.
There you are.
Knowledge of the unknowable.
It's the quickest test for possession.
The devil is working in and through her
right now.
Okay.
Uh...
Did it tell you what was in the bag?
Is it talking now?
What's it saying?
Disgusting things.
It's important you tell me.
Has it told you its name yet?
Do you know its name?
Tell me its name.
Tell me now.
In!
I can't talk now,
I'm in the middle of something.
Shut up, shut up.
Shut up, priest.
You must not touch me.
You are disgusting.
Keep your dirty hands off me.
Shut up! You must not speak.
Don't touch me!
Go away, priest. Go away!
You stink, you are disgusting.
Rosaria.
Open your mouth.
How do you feel?
Okay.
Okay, that's it.
Really? That's it?
Well, what'd you expect?
Spinning heads, pea soup?
Spiritual liberation can take months,
sometimes years.
So she's still possessed?
Yeah.
I know you don't believe me, but...
Tell me...
...does a thief or a burglar turn on the
lights when he's robbing your house? No.
He prefers you to believe
that he's not there.
Like the devil. He prefers you
to believe that he doesn't exist.
It gets complicated when no proof of
the devil is somehow proof of the devil.
Yeah.
The interesting thing
about skeptics, atheists...
...is that we're always looking
for proof, certainty.
The question is, what on earth
would we do if we found it?
- "We"?
- Oh, yes.
There are times when I experience
a total loss of faith.
Days, months when I don't know
what the hell I believe in.
God or the devil,
Santa Claus or Tinker Bell.
But...
...you know, I'm just a man.
I'm a weak man. I have...
...no power.
Yet there's something that keeps
digging and scraping away inside me.
Feels like God's fingernail.
And finally I can take
no more of the pain...
...and I get shoved out
from the darkness...
...back into the light.
Something like that.
Anyway, enough philosophizing
for one day.
If you have any more questions,
you know where to find me.
I got my eye on you. What you doing?
You're in Rome and you go to McDonald's?
Oh, hey.
Come on. Let me buy you
an Italian coffee.
Where were you today?
Xavier kicked you out, didn't he?
Yeah, I've plea-bargained down
from being burned at the stake.
So you're just vacationing now
on the Church's dime?
Yeah, and yours.
Seriously, why are you taking the course?
Why are you?
Are they recruiting nuns for exorcists?
"Nuns"?
I'm sorry, I just naturally assumed...
Yeah, naturally.
Well, if you're not a nun,
why are you taking the course?
I'm a journalist. I'm covering
the course for an article.
I see. And I thought
you were just buying me a coffee.
There's a lot of interest in this.
A lot of debate.
Look...
...I know you saw Father Lucas today.
I've been trying to get an interview
with him, but he's been reluctant.
What is it you want?
- I'd love to know what you saw.
- You're asking me to spy?
No, I'm asking you to report
your own experiences.
Listen...
...I'm just interested in the truth.
Seems like you are too.
Just as there is a hierarchy
of angels, ranked in ascendant order...
...so, too, is the realm of evil ranked.
And just as each angel has a name...
...so, too, does every demon.
Beelzebub, Leviathan, Ba'al.
These are some of the names
we look for...
...when performing an exorcism.
Just bear with me for a moment.
Well, I think we should leave it there
and pick it up tomorrow. Thank you.
Michael, how's my old friend Lucas?
He's unorthodox.
No exorcism is orthodox.
He's treating a pregnant girl
that I believe needs psychiatric care.
You believe?
Father Lucas has been doing this
longer than anyone I know.
I'm telling you because I'm concerned.
It's not uncommon...
...to be overly concerned for the subject
in one's first exorcism.
You have to see that
it is the demon that's in pain.
Trust me. Father Lucas gets results.
At what cost?
Oh. What can I do for you?
Rosaria.
You remember this man?
He was sent by the Vatican.
I want you to answer his questions.
Hi.
It was terrible to see you
go through your suffering.
This is unimportant. Just nod.
Do you remember any of it?
He wants to know if you remember things
when the devil takes over your body.
She says it's like a dream or a nightmare.
This is yours, yes?
Do you know how it got in my pocket?
Did you put it in his pocket?
Tell the truth now.
It wasn't me.
Then who was it?
Rosaria, who was it?
The devil?
Why would she lie?
- She's 16.
- Yes.
And she's pregnant.
Who's the father of her child?
She won't say.
Ask her who gave her
the bracelet, please.
- Her father.
- And where is he now?
- He's gone away. He left the family.
- When?
Oh, I don't know.
A few months ago, I believe.
- What are you doing?
- I'm giving it back to her.
Remember the fat little bitch?
Killed herself.
She says to say hello.
Hell-o.
In the name of Jesus Christ,
name yourself.
By the authority of Jesus Christ,
I command you to declare yourself!
I command you to declare yourself now!
We are the fruit of her womb.
Speak the truth, in the name
of Jesus Christ.
We're strong in the Lord
and the power of his might!
In the name of Judas Cross.
Demon, name yourself.
Your name, demon! Your name!
Tremble before the Lord!
We're strong in the Lord
and the power of his might!
Now!
By the authority of Jesus Christ,
I command you to...
Hold her!
Help me. Help me.
Hail Mary, full of grace.
The Lord is with thee.
Blessed art thou amongst women...
Shit on your Holy Spirit!
He that dwelleth
in the secret place of the Most High...
...shall abide under the shadow
of the Almighty. He is my refuge...
...my fortress and my strength.
He shall deliver thee
from the snare of the fowler...
Rape me.
My fortress and my strength.
Lickety-split.
Thou shalt not be afraid for
the terror by night, nor for the arrow...
...nor for the destruction that wasteth.
A thousand shall fall...
...and 10,000 at thy right hand...
Father, please.
Don't let it hurt my baby.
They shall bear thee up in their hands,
lest thou dash thy foot against a stone.
Take it out!
Shit it out and eat it!
Our Father who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come, thy will be done
on earth as it is in heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread and forgive
us our trespasses, as we forgive those...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Help me.
You...
Hail Mary, full of grace.
The Lord is with thee.
Go to hell, priest!
Blessed is the fruit of thy womb, Jesus.
Holy Mary, mother of God,
pray for us sinners...
...now and at the hour of our death.
Amen.
- Hail Mary, full of grace.
- She's choking. Father.
Pray with me! Out!
And begone, you unclean spirits
of terror and darkness. Out!
Damned Legion, Satan, Lucifer, out!
Begone! We banish you,
we cast you out...
...in the name of the Virgin Mary, mother
of Christ, the son of the living God...
...in whom we live, and move,
and have our being.
Who lives in us and reigns in us
supreme.
We cast you out from
the nothingness and the darkness...
...from whence you came.
Out, demon! Out, Lucifer! Out, Satan!
Now! Begone! In the name
of the Holy Spirit.
Deliver this from the snare
of the fowler, from the pestilence...
...from the darkness.
Well, she's asleep.
She needs to rest.
So I'll send her home in a few days
so she can recover.
I thought you were required
to have a doctor present.
I am a doctor.
Has she seen a psychiatrist?
- Yeah.
- What happened?
Oh, she doesn't respond to treatment.
- Is she on antidepressants?
- No.
- No, she's pregnant.
- So she hasn't been medically treated?
Yeah. I'm looking after her.
Weren't you concerned for her health
up there?
Yeah, of course I was.
Well, how will her baby survive this?
See, it's very difficult to predict how
any of this stuff is gonna work out.
- Have you ever lost a patient?
- Yeah.
Yeah, a boy I once treated.
He was about 15 years of age...
...and he committed suicide...
...and I was depressed
for a few months...
...and I started to doubt everything
I believed in.
And I thought the devil had defeated me.
Don't you think she should
see a psychiatrist again?
You're still not convinced...
Oh, Christ! She was raped by her father.
She's internalizing her guilt.
"Internalizing"? Okay.
Still doesn't explain everything,
does it?
It doesn't explain
how she started to speak English.
Well, she's a teenager. She's listened
to a thousand songs on the radio.
What about these nails?
It could be that she swallowed them
to hurt the baby.
She clearly doesn't want it.
What about the voice inside her? That
wasn't a human voice, though, was it?
You be careful, Michael.
Why?
Choosing not to believe in the devil
won't protect you from him.
Michael.
Come.
Come closer.
You're not a coward. Don't be afraid.
It's just your mother.
Now...
...blow.
We want to do a good job, don't we?
The best we can.
Good. Now...
...pray.
Hail Mary, full of grace.
The Lord is with thee.
Blessed art thou among women
and blessed is the fruit of thy womb...
My love.
My flower.
Mother of God, pray for us sinners...
My beautiful.
Amen.
Can't get enough, huh?
Doing house calls today.
Take that, it's gonna rain.
Shut the gate after you.
Vincenzo.
What happens in your dream?
I'm being hurt.
By what?
A mule.
With red eyes.
It kicks me.
And bites me.
And do you try and run away?
Why not?
Because he says he's my father
and I must obey him.
Oh.
What else does he tell you?
He tells me...
...to kill myself.
Show him.
He woke up with these.
The mule from the dream?
Vincenzo?
The mule in the dream?
Mama?
Not Mama?
You hit him?
Are you lying?
Are you a liar?
Okay.
Come here.
Open your mouth.
Ahh.
Bring me his pillow.
Banish all the forces of evil
from this pillow.
Vanquish them. Destroy them!
Now!
Ah.
The devil!
We cast you out, every unclean spirit...
...every Satanic power...
...every onslaught of
the infernal adversary.
Be gone and stay far
from this creature of God...
...for it is he who commands you,
it is he...
He who would still the sea...
...the wind and the storm.
Flee, enemy of the faith,
you foe of the human race.
That's enough now, do you hear me?
No one is going to die.
Put the unholy tempter to flight.
And of the Holy Spirit. Amen.
I'm supposed to take care
of this place...
...but I feel so bad.
Never seem to have any time.
You ever wonder if the people
you help are just mistaken?
Yeah. Sometimes, I suppose.
But you still do what you do.
Why not? I haven't seen a prayer
hurt anyone yet.
So you're happy to have them continue
believing something that may not be true?
Yes, why not?
And what is it you believe?
I believe that people prefer to lie
to themselves than face the truth.
The truth, yeah. Certainty.
I will leave immediately.
I understand. Thank you.
Rosaria just tried to drown herself.
We gave her pethidine
and trazodone but she won't calm down.
Legally we can't give her anything else.
Look what I've done to her, priest!
And I'm not finished yet!
Leave it.
Let her see who is in command.
Demon. Deceiver.
Speak your name.
Never.
Why are you living in her?
Because her suffering is sweet.
What do you plan to do with her?
Eat the flies from her rotting flesh.
How did you enter her?
With her father's seed.
- So you remember being raped?
- Don't address it directly.
When the devil has nothing
better to do, he rapes his children.
I don't understand.
You know how to swear
in every language?
Therefore let us
go down and confound their tongue...
...that they may not understand
one another's speech.
You know the Bible well.
We know it very well.
Very clever.
Don't patronize me, doubter!
It is I who chose you.
- Why do you call me "doubter"?
- Because it's true.
A liar knows a liar.
Are you a liar, Rosaria?
What is it you want me to believe?
There's nothing to believe.
Then there is no devil
and you're not possessed?
You fear me, mortal!
How can I fear you if you don't exist?
You think you outsmarted him?
That's not the devil.
It's just a very, very sick girl.
She doesn't need a priest,
she needs a shrink.
He still has you fooled, hasn't he?
You forgot your bag of tricks.
He's a deceiver, Michael.
He's a deceiver.
Hold on. Hold on, Rosaria.
This is a tragedy. How could this happen?
Who worked here today?
I want to talk with everyone.
Tell me about the mother.
There was internal bleeding,
massive hemorrhaging.
We did everything in our power...
...but unfortunately
we couldn't save her or her baby.
What now?
Oh, nothing.
It's finished.
He took a life.
That's what he wants, ultimately.
He'll probably find someone else.
You should go home, get some rest.
You've had a hard night.
Yeah.
Are you okay?
I failed her.
You did what you thought was best.
Yeah.
I gotta go.
Take care of yourself.
You're a good man, Michael.
You have a good soul.
Defend it.
Guard it.
Cherish it.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
- Hey.
- Thanks for coming.
You picked a perfect day for it.
I appreciate you doing this.
- No names.
- No names. Promise.
There's no way she touched the baby
because she was restrained.
That's right.
What do you make of that?
It's confounding.
That's the story.
It's yours to interpret as you will.
You can call me
if you have any questions.
Thank you.
What changed your mind?
To do this?
I just needed to tell someone.
So let me get this straight.
You ran away from home
and chose a life of celibacy?
- How bad could home be?
- It sounds stupid when you say it like that.
It sounds stupid
because it doesn't add up.
Are you saying you never felt a calling?
My mother...
...she used to say
she felt the hand of God on me.
Did you feel it?
I wanted to.
- So how did you end up in all this?
- It's a long story.
We're not going anywhere,
so come on.
My parents committed my brother
to a mental institution when he was 19.
He was so tormented.
He said he heard voices
telling him to do things.
He used to tell me
it was the devil speaking to him.
Sometimes he would tell me
what the devil said.
And sometimes the things he said
would come true.
It frightened me.
He frightened me.
I know it sounds terrible, but it's just
easier when I don't think about him.
Hail Mary, full of grace.
The Lord is with thee.
Blessed art thou among women...
... and blessed is the fruit
of thy womb, Jesus.
Holy Mary...
... mother of God...
... pray for us sinners now
and at the hour of our death.
Amen.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I'm sorry to wake you, Michael.
I thought it best to tell you myself.
It's your father.
And he hasn't regained consciousness?
No. The stroke was massive.
He could stabilize
or he could stay like this.
I see.
I'm sorry. There isn't much more
I can tell you at this point.
I'm sorry, Michael.
I'll include him in my prayers.
We can help arrange your travel.
Thank you.
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
Airlines are warning
passengers to expect more delays...
... even when the dust from
the volcano in Iceland has settled.
Tonight, the ash plume has shut the
airports of 22 countries on the continent...
... with Italy and Switzerland among
the latest to close their airspace.
Thousands of passengers are stranded,
with some being told...
... it could be a week
before they get another flight.
- Once the ash clears...
- I need a room.
- ... a backlog of flights...
- No problem.
... will mean further disruption.
Valerie Rigg, Egetsa Coverage.
I'm calling to check
on my father's condition.
Istvan Kovak.
K-O-V-A-K.
I'll connect you.
- Michael.
- Yeah, yeah. It's Michael.
I'm scared.
It's okay. Dad, you're okay.
No. Something happened.
- It's okay, Dad.
- Where are you?
I wish you were here.
I'll be home soon.
Something happened with my flight.
Where am I?
You're in the hospital.
What is it, Dad?
Dad?
They're hurting me.
Who?
Dad?
- Mr. Kovak?
- Yeah.
- It's Dr. Vorachian.
- Yes.
Mr. Kovak, I'm afraid
I've got some very bad news.
Your father passed away this afternoon.
Uh, what?
Your father died this afternoon.
I'm very sorry, Mr. Kovak.
Well, that's impossible. I...
I was just speaking with him, just now.
Mr. Kovak, your father was
declared dead about six hours ago.
I was a witness.
I'm very sorry to have to tell you...
"Whoever lives by believing in me
will never die."
Lord have mercy, Christ have mercy...
...Lord have mercy.
Eternal rest grant unto her, O Lord,
and let perpetual light shine upon her.
May she rest in peace.
Doubter!
Michael.
A liar knows a liar.
Michael, they're hurting me.
Dad?
- I'm scared.
- Hey.
Wait! Dad!
- Where are you?
- Radre.
Radre.
Don't worry.
The pain is gone.
There's nothing to believe.
I don't know what's going on.
I'm hallucinating. I'm seeing things,
I'm hearing things.
I can't explain it.
I don't even know what I'm doing here.
Michael, what happened?
Look, I need your help.
I feel like I'm going insane.
Can you come meet me?
He's feeling
much better since the Father prayed for him.
Did Father send you?
The other day I saw her son
whisper something to her.
I need to know what it was.
Your son whispered
something to you the other day.
He's a baby.
He doesn't know what he's saying.
Please, it's very important
that you tell us.
Please.
He said...
...your father was going to die.
Who told him that?
He says you know.
He says you've seen it too.
Seen what?
The demon.
The mule.
- Where are you going?
- My father died last night.
What did you say?
I said, my father died...
...last night.
Oh, God.
That's awful. I'm so sorry.
How did that kid know?
I need to talk to Lucas.
Bless my dolly, Father?
Hm?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Father?
Father.
Let's get you inside.
- I don't want to lie down.
- Okay.
Then what were you doing out there?
Huh?
I said, what were you doing out there?
I'm not sure.
I found myself walking and I...
I think...
I think I did something awful.
It was terrible.
I can't pray any longer because
I'm no longer in a state of grace...
... and prayer is our only salvation.
It's your only salvation.
It knows you, it knows all your sins.
Secrets.
So you'll need help.
- With what?
- You'll have to lock me up.
Go find Father Xavier.
Because it is strong...
...this thing, this terror.
The terror is real, Michael.
It's real.
But you'll only defeat it
when you believe.
So go now, lock me up.
Go now. Lock me up!
I think Father Xavier has left for the day.
Please. It's very urgent.
He's going to Civitavecchia
for the weekend.
What's his cell number?
Hello, this is Father Xavier.
I am currently unavailable.
Leave a message after the tone.
This is Michael Kovak. There's
a serious problem with Father Lucas.
Contact me. I'm going to his house.
He belongs to me now.
Michael.
What was that?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What?
I don't know.
Lover of my soul
Let me to thy bosom fly
When the nearer...
Father?
I'm afraid he's out.
Come in, please.
Ah.
So shall we begin?
In time, Father.
I told you, he's not here.
Then who are you?
I'm just an old friend.
- "Friend"?
- Yeah.
I'm not sure I follow you.
Oh, you follow me, Michael.
You've always followed me.
Did you enjoy our gift,
the one we hung on your door?
You following me now...
...Michael?
Close the door, please.
We don't want to be disturbed, do we?
Your father says to say hello,
by the way.
Hell-o.
You don't know my father.
Oh, he says he enjoyed
his final little chat with you.
I'm guessing you didn't enjoy it
as much.
- You're a liar.
- Yes, that's what they all tell me.
Your father died at 4:20 P.M...
...in the same miserable hospital
in which your mother died...
...or passed away, as they say.
And his last conscious moments...
...were full of panic and full of terror.
Alone in that house of the dead
with no family to hold his hand...
...no loved ones to kiss him goodbye.
Because you deserted him, Michael...
...and this caused him great pain,
you know, in the end.
You hurt him most.
And all for God.
Are you reading my mind?
Yes. No.
Maybe. No. Yes. Rerhaps.
- Are you reading mine?
- What am I thinking now?
Oh, you're so tedious,
you little piece of mouse shit.
Do you think I'm afraid of you?
You couldn't even stand up to your father,
could you? Your daddy, your mommy.
- Mikey, Mikey, Mikey!
- Stand back!
- You don't command me.
- No, God does.
Oh, God does. Is that so? Wow, cool.
Awesome. Whatever, dude.
You and your puking truth!
You are nothing! You know nothing!
Doubter!
Cherish your doubts, Michael.
Jesus, lover of my soul.
This is lovely, isn't it?
Oh, I will never leave you. I will never.
So please, Mr. Preacher Man, please,
Mr. Priest, pray for God to help me.
Me, I'm just a poor little Welshman.
All dressed up for the carnival, Mommy.
God is not here, priest.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh, God, help me!
God help me!
Michael...
...what's happening to me?
- Oh, God help me.
- Father.
Tie me up. Tie me up.
Angelina!
Help me.
Now!
- Now what?
- I don't know.
- Maybe we should wait for Father Xavier.
- We can't keep him tied up till Monday.
If you don't wanna do this,
I'll understand.
No.
This is what I asked to see.
In the name of the Father, and of the Son...
... and of the Holy Spirit,
bless this, your servant.
Keep her safe from harm,
protect her from evil. Amen.
Amen.
Just repeat what I say.
Just repeat what he says, honey.
- Lord, have mercy.
- Have mercy.
- Unbeliever.
- Christ, have mercy.
- Have mercy.
- Doubter!
- Lord, have mercy.
Hell has no mercy!
I took the priest, I'll take you.
Let us pray.
"Save this man, Lucas Trevant,
your servant."
I'm no servant.
- Because he hopes in you, God.
- Hope is dead!
Let the enemy have no victory
over him. Lord, hear us.
Lord, hear us.
He can't hear you, he's not here.
God is dead!
Drive out, O Lord,
the power of the devil.
Hey, Angie, has he done it to you yet?
That's what he wants.
That's what you want too, right?
Be protected and safeguarded
in body and soul.
Hey, Mikey, I think she likes you.
Nice titties, yeah?
I invoke your holy name
and humbly request...
- ...that you snatch from this demon...
- Pokey hokey, pocus holy...
- ...this man who was created in...
- Created in sin.
- Who was created in your likeness.
- In your likeness of sin and filth.
In the name of your Lord,
Jesus Christ, your son.
- Climb up on my knees, sonny boy.
- Amen.
Amen.
By the mysteries of the incarnation...
...the suffering, the death and resurrection
and ascension of our Lord, Jesus Christ...
"...I command you.
By some sign, give me your name."
Your name, demon.
Tell me your name!
My love.
My flower.
My beautiful.
Hey, Daddy's calling from hell.
Michael.
What happened?
I can't do it.
It's more than just saying the words.
You've seen him.
What's not to believe in?
Me.
Don't you understand?
Then why are you here?
Something brought you here, Michael.
All the decisions you made.
You left your home, your father.
You came here.
It all led to this.
It's fate.
You're not alone.
What did you just say?
Michael.
Father.
Give up.
You don't have the strength.
You don't have the faith.
Just pray, Michael.
Well, hello, Angie.
And the Holy Spirit. Amen.
May I ask you a question?
When was the last time
you saw your brother?
Thy will be done on earth
as it is in heaven.
You little slut.
Don't listen.
Oh, don't listen. But isn't that
what you did, Angie?
Not listen to him? Your little brother.
Leaving him to rot away in that stinking
booby hatch, turning your back on him...
...when he was being strangled
by his own screams.
Do you remember that, Angie?
Do you remember?
You will never forget.
So we do what we do with him now.
He's living in the land of misery
and dread, thanks to big sister.
Oh, why the tears, sweetie pie?
I thought you wanted the truth.
Like laughing boy here.
He just lives for the truth.
Isn't that so, Mikey?
Just leave her alone.
You think I don't know all your festering
secrets? Your nickel-and-dime sins?
You were ashamed of your father,
he was ashamed of you.
You hated him, he hated you back.
It was a charming family.
How could God possibly love you
when your daddy didn't? Hm?
No. You were never
meant for God, Michael.
You were always meant for me, honey.
Enough!
Oopsie-daisy.
Close to home.
And that was no squeaky angel
your mother saw all those years ago.
No.
'Twas I.
You chose me long, long ago...
... when you were just an itsy-bitsy
little boy pooping in his pants.
Remember, Michael.
You remember, Michael?
Remember when you bent that cross?
If only you remember.
Remember, Michael. Remember.
Remember.
Oh, dear.
Our poor little savior all alone on his cross.
Yeah.
God chose you, Michael.
That's why you're here.
Just accept it.
- Yeah.
- Accept God.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Accept the devil.
- You can't win without him.
No.
All alone.
No!
Shall I pour the sick and rotting truth
of the dying world...
...into your precious, golden womb?
You remember his strangling screams...
...when you turned your back on him
and walked away?
You wanted the truth, little lady.
Well, here I am.
So how about you, kissy lips?
Do you feel that probing around
inside you, Michael?
Lucas, listen to me, please.
Lucas is not here.
He's never coming back.
You feel that digging and scraping around
inside you like God's dirty fingernail?
Do you believe in me now, Michael?
Do you believe in me now?
Yes.
Yes. I believe in you.
I believe in the devil.
I believe in you...
...so I believe in God.
I accept him in this moment.
I accept God.
I believe in God the Father,
the maker of heaven and earth...
...of all that is seen and unseen.
I believe.
I exorcise you, most unclean spirit.
Warp of vices, creator of agony.
In the name of Jesus Christ,
leave this man.
In the name of the Virgin Mary,
leave now.
I command you.
I, who believe.
In the name of our Lord, Jesus Christ...
...be uprooted and expelled
from this creature of God.
He who commands you is he
who ordered you to be thrown down...
...from the highest heaven
into the depths of hell.
Hear therefore and fear,
Satan, enemy of faith.
Fear him who was crucified as man
and who rose from death!
I will never leave you, Michael.
I will never leave you.
Speak your name.
In the name of Jesus Christ,
I command you, speak your name.
In the name of the Holy Spirit,
I command you. Give me your name!
It is God who commands you!
Your name!
Give me your name!
Ba'al!
I know you, Ba'al.
And I command you, retire therefore.
Depart from this place. Leave!
Surrender now.
In the name of the Father, and
of the Son and of the Holy Spirit...
...forever and ever.
It's good as new, huh?
Yeah.
Well, she wasn't a bad little bike.
You know, back in her golden days...
...she brought me out here
all those years ago.
Anyway...
So you're off. You're leaving.
Yeah, that's right.
Well, I hope you find your place
in the world one of these fine days.
- I hope so.
- Now, when you do...
...don't forget to say a few prayers
for an old sinner.
Throw a couple of Hail Marys this way
if that's not too much trouble.
That a deal?
- It's a deal.
- Good.
You know, the first day
you showed up...
...I thought you were so full of it, I was
tempted to kick you into the street.
But I didn't because I saw
quite a bit of myself in you.
Scary, isn't it?
- Yeah, it sure is.
- Yeah.
All right, that's it. Thanks for everything.
Safe journey. And one other thing.
Faith becomes you. Stay with it.
Keep fighting the good fight
with all thy might.
Cool.
Get out of here.
Goodbye, Father.
Bless me, Father, for I have sinned.
It has been six weeks
since my last confession.
And what are your sins?
Father Michael Kovak is one of 14 exorcists
practicing in the United States today. He now works
out of his parish near Chicago.
Father Lucas Trevant has performed over
two thousand exorcisms. He continues to practice
in a township outside of Florence.