(whooshing)
(light, enigmatic music)
(car rumbling)
(thudding)
What do you think?
You must be Richard.
I'm Luke.
This is my wife Jennifer,
sorry we kept you.
Three bedrooms,
one and a half baths
She's old,
but she's got good bones.
When was it built?
Come one inside and
take a look around.
You let me know if you find
any problems or whatnot.
Good bones, huh?
Comes with the furniture?
Yeah.
I guess, Richard got
the house on auction.
Hmm.
[Luke] He's been
meaning to fix it up a bit
but hasn't gotten
around to it yet, so.
He did like this.
He's giving us a
really nice deal.
Great.
Hey.
Give it a chance, huh?
I think this could be fun.
Playing house for a few months.
I'll go get rid of,
Mr. Personality.
A few months.
(click)
I haven't lived in a
house since I left.
And our apartment,
I think it'd fit in
within these two rooms.
It's a lot of house.
It's a lot to get used to.
It's only for now.
And I think this is gonna
be really good for us.
And once things
have settled down,
Chicago will still be there.
Promise?
Promise.
It's a nice house.
(gasping, rustling)
(knocking)
(click)
Hello.
[Luke] Meredith?
Mom.
Oh, well you just
look at this house.
It is so good to
have you back, Jenny.
You have no idea how
much I've missed you.
And you, Luke.
Handsome as ever.
Oh, welcome home, welcome.
Oh, and I've brought you a
little house warming gift
for the nursery.
And, some wraps from
over at Larry's Place.
I figured you must be starving.
We just ordered a pizza.
So.
Well, how was I
suppose to know that?
Could've called,
that would've worked.
Honey, it's okay, I'll
just put them in the fridge.
Meredith, thank you,
it was very thoughtful.
Well I figured you
must be starving.
No, really we are, here.
Come in.
Excuse me, dear.
Oh.
(chuckling)
I see you just
started to unpack.
We got here this afternoon.
I know, I know, just saying.
You have an awfully long
way to go, don't you?
Yes.
It's not so bad.
I was telling Jennifer
earlier, how exciting.
Yes, it's terribly,
terribly exciting.
Well.
Certainly is big enough.
I'm gonna go put
these in the kitchen.
Meredith, maybe you wanna
take a look around upstairs?
Sounds lovely.
Yes.
Jenny, coming?
Luke seems to be in high
spirits, doesn't he?
And you?
How are you?
You don't have to
tiptoe around me, Mom.
I'm fine.
Please don't lie, Jenny.
It doesn't suit you.
What do you want?
I want you to be happy.
I'm happy, things are great.
I'm glad to hear that.
After all the help
I've given you.
I don't need your help.
(laughing)
I beg to differ.
Where would you be
if I hadn't convinced
Richard about this house?
And help Luke get this job?
In Chicago.
Oh yes.
Raising a family on a
bartender salary alone.
Of course.
No.
I think this is going to
be best for both of you.
The three of you.
Besides, it's about time Luke
did something with his degree.
And you?
Can we not do this right now?
Still haven't talked about it.
There's nothing to talk about.
Your irrational
little episode.
Stop, Mom.
You know, I wasn't
exactly thrilled
when I found out I
was pregnant with you.
But I managed to keep
it together, didn't I?
You should leave.
I didn't act like
a spoiled child.
What you did was irresponsible.
Embarrassing, really.
Get out.
Of course.
It's none of my business.
I'm just so glad
everything's alright.
It's a lovely house.
Leaving already?
I should be going.
Let you two finish unpacking.
Goodnight, Luke.
Thanks for the wraps.
It was nice to see you.
Jenny.
Bye Mom.
Oh, I forgot to tell you.
I'm going to be throwing
a house warming party
for you here this weekend.
I've invited all of
my friends, of course
and some of yours.
What?
I'm going to make
a few appetizers
and dips and the like.
But you should probably put a
few things together yourself.
We can't have a party.
Oh and
make sure you've
finished unpacking, hmm?
I don't want anyone to get
a bad first impression.
(thud)
[Voiceover] She
made you curtains?
Yes.
[Voiceover] Oh
god, what a delight.
With elephants
and zebras on them.
[Voiceover] She made
you jungle curtains.
She made me jungle curtains.
[Voiceover] Oh
I just, I can't.
You have to put them up.
(laughing)
Absolutely not.
[Voiceover] Oh come
one, you're being no fun.
No, I already
explained to Luke.
Putting them up would
seem too permanent.
Next thing you know we're
painting the walls to match
and getting new carpet
and putting the
pool in the back.
We're not gonna
be here that long.
[Voiceover] Ready to
come back already, huh?
(sighing)
Oh yes.
[Voiceover] You're not
enjoying it even a little bit?
My life's in Chicago, Lauren.
(thump)
You're in Chicago.
There's nothing for me here.
[Voiceover] Yeah, I
know I want you back too.
Just stay positive,
it'll be over soon.
It's only gonna be
what you make of it.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
Honey, what are these?
Oh yeah, turns
out we have rats.
Hold on.
We have rats?
Yeah.
Down in the crawlspace,
I saw some droppings
this morning.
He says we have rats
in the crawlspace.
[Voiceover] Rats
in the crawlspace?
God, that's awful.
At least he didn't
find any dead bodies.
That would be a deal breaker.
Oh yeah, I forgot to mention.
Shut up.
I better go, sorry.
[Voiceover] No, I get it.
I've a problem
with my own anyway.
Brad's been drawing
on the walls lately
and he just ran by with
a handful of markers.
I'm afraid he's
feeling artistic again.
(laughing)
You think rats are bad?
Try dealing with a toddler.
Something to look forward to.
Come visit me?
[Voiceover] Done.
Miss you, love you.
[Voiceover] Brad,
I swear you put the.
(beep)
(clink)
(light, enigmatic music)
I'm gonna go to my Mom's.
Get those things for tonight.
She's out getting her hair done
so I figured now's
the best time.
You want me to go?
No, I want to
get out the house.
Cabin fever, huh?
I'm just starting
to feel a bit trapped.
In less than a week and she's
already running our lives.
Come on, it's not that bad.
She is throwing us a party.
She's throwing
herself a party.
I really don't think she's.
This isn't about us
Luke, it's about her.
It's always about her.
Jennifer.
Come here.
I'm sorry.
I'm overreacting.
Listen, if you go into to
it with a negative attitude
it's going to be bad.
It's just one night.
And I'll be there with
you the whole time.
I love you.
I love you too.
(smooch)
Want me to finish unpacking?
No leave them.
Let her know how inconvenient
this whole thing is.
(birds chirping)
(light, sensitive music)
(laughing, chattering)
That's good.
Okay.
And so, my mother sees
me on the floor that day
and my brother's not there
so she picks me up, she running.
Can you imagine having
something this nice?
And let me tell you
who's delighted is Luke.
Yikes.
(laughing)
Fair fight, huh?
Fair kind of conversation
to be part of.
That's good.
Jenny, oh my goodness, hi.
Hi.
How are you?
Look at you.
Oh.
[Burnett Woman]
You look amazing.
[Jennifer] Thank you.
[Burnett Woman] How
far along are you?
[Jennifer] About seven months.
[Burnett Woman] When did
you get home from Chicago?
Just a few days ago.
If you'll excuse
me, I'm so sorry,
I just have to take
care of a few things.
[Woman] It's great to see you.
You too.
She looks amazing.
[Woman] Yeah.
Excuse me.
Oh.
(laughing)
I'm sorry.
[Man] Sorry.
Um, I don't
believe we have met.
I'm Jenn.
You're Jennifer, right?
Yes.
I'm Walter, Walter Vance.
Very nice to meet you.
You're a friend
of my mother's?
An old friend, yes, yes.
I must say Jennifer, this is
quite the house you have here.
Hmm, it's
unique.
Oh very unique.
Yes.
Yes a very
interesting energy.
Thank you.
Is there anything
I could get you?
I'm so very glad to hear
your baby's doing better.
It was very close, wasn't it?
What was it, if
I may be so bold?
Was the baby sick?
Were you sick?
Who told you about that?
Walter?
(grunting)
Oh, there you are, Walter.
I've been looking
everywhere for you.
Hello Katherine.
And I was just getting
to know Jennifer here.
Oh Jennifer, what'd
you think of Walter, hmm?
He's my most eccentric friend.
[Walter] Now Katherine.
No, it's true.
Walter thinks himself
a bit of a psychic.
Or is it medium, dear?
Is that what you call yourself?
Neither, actually.
Pay no attention to her.
I pick up on things, that's all.
Energy.
But I'm a chiropractor
by profession,
just a chiropractor.
Just?
Don't be silly.
This man has a gift.
Now if you'll
excuse us, Jennifer,
I have some gossip I'm
just dying to tell him.
Very nice to
meet you Jennifer.
(chattering, laughing)
(dark, ominous music)
Let's give her
some room, okay?
I just don't want
it brought up, okay?
Anymore.
Thank you.
I know you'll understand.
[Luke] Isn't that
right Jennifer?
I'm sorry.
[Luke] I said
we're still deciding
but we're thinking maybe Tyler.
Oh, yes, that's right.
Tyler.
[Luke] You're
being awfully quiet.
Hmm.
It took a lot out of me.
[Luke] What did she say?
What didn't she say?
Oh, I'm terribly
sorry about this mess.
Terribly, terribly sorry.
She knows we haven't hung
up those damn curtains yet.
God.
You know we might as well.
Save us an earful, at least.
Luke.
They're not that
hideous, really.
No, I'm not putting them up.
Have you applied for
anything in Chicago?
[Luke] It's been a week.
So, no.
We're going to be here at
least until the baby's born.
That was the whole point
of this, you know that.
(sighing)
Look, I'll start looking soon
but while we're here,
you should at least try
to give it a chance.
I am trying.
We hosted the party.
You didn't talk to anybody.
You know, you could've made
an effort with these people.
Try to make some friends.
I like the friends I have.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
(rustling)
Whoa.
Sorry.
(clattering)
Someone's still here.
What?
In the bathroom,
there's someone there.
Go get rid of them.
(knocking)
(click)
(dark, ominous music)
(crickets chirping)
They leave?
Yeah.
(sighing)
I'm sorry.
It took a lot out of me too.
Come on.
Late?
[Luke] Yeah.
Forgot what it feels
like to be up this early.
Wish me luck.
Good luck.
I love you.
Love you.
(knocking)
(birds chirping)
(thumping)
(dark, ominous music)
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
(knocking)
Yes?
Is this a bad time?
No.
Can I help you?
I'm Marlene, I live next door.
Oh.
Right, I'm sorry.
I'm, Jennifer.
I thought I'd bring you these.
Welcome to the
neighborhood, all that.
Thank you.
It's very thoughtful.
You're from around here?
Chicago, actually.
My husband, Luke and I,
we're just here for a bit.
I, grew up around here though.
Oh.
Welcome home.
It's a blessing.
I'm sorry?
Oh.
Thank you.
Would you like to come inside?
Oh no, I, I have to be going.
I just wanted to say hello.
Thank you for the cookies.
Nice meeting you.
(scrunching)
(whirring, ticking)
(groaning)
(dark, menacing music)
But he's one of
those newer supervisors
anytime I asked him a question,
he just give me the name
of somebody else to
go talk to later on.
I don't know, I think
he was just hired
but he's really nice.
You look bored to death.
What?
No, Morgan sounds nice.
He sounds really
nice.
I'm sorry, I had a weird day.
No, no, it's boring stuff.
No, it's not really.
I'm sure Morgan is very
Nice.
(laughing)
So what's up?
Have you felt anything
off since moving here?
In the house, I mean?
[Luke] Off how?
Well, today
these boxes moved on their own.
I don't know.
I just felt like my
head wasn't on right.
What?
How long has
this been going on?
Just today.
It's probably nothing.
Never mind.
Jennifer, if you're starting
to feel strange again?
It's nothing.
Forget I said it.
Just don't like being
here alone, that's all.
(splashing)
(gasping)
(chattering, laughing)
No.
No, no no, no.
I don't care if you say no.
No, no, no, do you hear me?
No.
No, no, no, no.
(wind rustling)
(fizzing, pattering)
(creaking)
Luke?
Very funny.
(dark, ominous music)
What're you doing?
I'm almost done,
then it's all yours.
Not now.
Alright that's enough.
I'm sorry, I
I appreciate the
gesture, I really do.
But.
Talking to yourself?
Thanks for keeping
the water warm for me.
Thanks honey.
Luke.
[Luke] Do we have any
of that creamer left?
Luke?
[Luke] Just a second.
Luke.
Hmm?
Could we talk?
Yeah what's up?
There's um,
there's something.
(buzzing)
Hold that thought.
I'm sorry, what were you saying?
(knocking, gasping)
(chuckling)
I think you're gonna
wanna get that.
What?
Go on, get it.
What's going on?
Just open it.
Look who's in town.
(laughing)
Lauren.
Oh are you
surprised to see us?
What're you doing here?
I was gonna wait
till you were settled
but the train is cheap
and I had nothing to do.
God, I missed you,
I really miseed you.
I can't believe you're here.
Oh well, it was
Luke's idea really.
I'd love to take all the credit
but I guess your husband's just
a better person
than your bestie.
(screaming)
Oh god it is so good to see you.
You have no idea.
You know I've been
dying to see this place.
I love it, by the way.
So old, so bizarre.
Okay, so
real talk.
I know you're probably
tired of people asking, but
how are you feeling?
Can I tell you something?
And you have to promise to
keep an open mind about it.
Yeah sure.
What is it?
I think this house is haunted.
What?
I don't know for
sure, it's just
some weird things have been
happening recently, and
yeah, everything
feels so strange.
Luke said you've
been feeling weird.
He told you that?
Well yeah, yeah, but I
mean he didn't mention,
he didn't say that it was.
You think this house is haunted?
Tell me everything.
Things move.
Strange noises.
I thought someone was in the
shower with me this morning.
No way.
And did you tell Luke
about any of this?
I tried.
But the moment I
mentioned I felt something
he got upset.
And I mean I think
he thought it was
the whole baby thing.
You're sure it's not?
What?
[Lauren] I mean your
sure it's not stress or
hormones?
Hormones don't open doors
and move boxes, Lauren.
Look, I get why you might
why you and Luke might not.
Things got really confused
back in Chicago, right before.
You know, I.
I was feeling a lot of things
and I
I couldn't handle it.
But this is something different.
Lauren please, you
gotta believe me.
This is something else.
I believe you.
Thanks.
So
What're you gonna do?
I don't know.
I mean, what're
you supposed to do
when your house is haunted?
Pull out a ouija board?
Call a medium.
(chuckling)
There was this
guy at our party,
my Mom's chiropractor.
His friend said he was psychic.
Your Mom knows a
psychic chiropractor?
It's just.
(laughing)
(child cooing)
Oh.
Sounds like somebody's awake.
That one?
Ah hmm.
And this one.
(clattering)
[Lauren] Oh, uh oh.
Let's take this
one off over there.
I can't find anything
at this address.
There's an article from
the 70's about rezoning
but that's it.
No deaths, no murders, nothing.
[Lauren] So?
So it doesn't make sense.
I mean someone had to die here
for there to be ghost, right?
I don't think ghosts have
rules, Jennifer, I mean.
You're thinking too small,
what if
what if your house is
cursed or it's a poltergeist
or a demon?
Great.
I have an idea of
something that we can try.
But we'll have to wait till
tonight when Brad's in bed.
What is it?
Oh I'm not gonna
ruin the surprise.
I have to pee.
Great.
Can you watch him?
[Jennifer] Yeah.
[Lauren] Thanks.
[Brad] Hi.
Hi.
Hi Brad.
Brad, who're you talking to?
Hmm.
Hi.
Brad.
Do you see someone?
(clattering)
What do you see?
It's a ghost in here.
(growling)
(thudding, creaking)
You know, I was thinking.
Oh ho.
You're alright?
(gasping)
[Jennifer] A door
closed upstairs.
No way.
[Jennifer] I just heard it.
Oh then we have
to go check it out.
I'm not going up there.
[Lauren] Fine I'll go.
There's nothing up here.
Hi.
The ghost is attacking,
mu, mu, mu, mum, mum.
[Lauren] Shut the door.
[Jennifer] Why?
[Lauren] We have
to block any drafts.
This is what I used to
do when we were kids.
We shut the door, the windows.
Turn off the air.
And then you ask questions.
And if the flame moves
it's the spirit or the ghost
or whatever, responding.
Lauren, I don't know.
No, come on, here.
You've to put your hands on it.
Now what?
Ask something.
I don't know what to ask.
Fine then I'll ask.
Is there somebody down here
in the basement with us?
Jesus Christ Lauren, don't.
Shh.
Is there somebody or something
here with us now?
If there is something
in this house
please make yourself known.
Show us that you're here.
Give us a sign.
Lauren, look.
(laughing)
You jerk.
I'm sorry, it's just so.
(thumping)
What the hell was that?
Lauren, where you going?
Oh we gotta make contact.
[Jennifer] Wait a minute.
Lauren, stop.
Whatever you
are, show yourself.
[Jennifer] Come on,
let's just go outside.
Shit.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Something's coming.
Lauren.
Come on, come on, come on.
Lauren, no.
(screaming)
Whoa, what's going on?
Holy shit.
Oh my god you had us so scared.
Yeah I can see that.
What're you doing?
We are amateur ghost hunters
and we thought that
you were our ghost.
Ghost hunters?
Oh my god, you
had me so scared.
I need wine.
You were hunting ghosts?
We were.
You think the
house is haunted?
Yes.
Why didn't you tell me?
I tried.
I don't know.
Ah come here.
The house isn't haunted.
There's no such thing as ghosts.
Oh my god, my heart is
just beating out of my chest.
Seriously, you're
lucky I like you.
Wait, that's it?
I mean we're done now?
The footsteps were
Luke's so we're done?
Jennifer I've
been here all day
and nothing has happened.
The door shut by itself.
Listen, I get it.
New houses are scary.
Believe me every
time I move somewhere
I'm convinced it's
haunted and it never is.
There's always an
explanation for everything.
[Luke] Yeah.
[Lauren] Oh, um did we leave
the door open downstairs?
I'll get it.
(click)
(dark, ominous music)
(thudding)
Lauren, Luke.
(laughing, chattering)
[Luke] That is not true.
[Lauren] Well
obviously it's not true.
[Luke] It's not true.
At all.
[Lauren] Yeah, okay.
[Luke] Let me finish the joke.
Okay, so.
You never listen.
[Lauren] Well I'm listening.
No, no you never listen.
I am listening.
No.
Luke, I am listening.
[Jennifer] There's a hand
print in the crawlspace.
A what?
A hand print
in the crawlspace.
So?
So how did it get there?
Well, I
checked the traps a
couple of days ago
set a few new ones,
it's probably mine.
Jennifer stop
freaking yourself out,
just come, come sit
with us and talk, okay?
Luke was just telling
me a really funny joke.
Come on.
[Luke] Okay so
there're two hunters
they're amateur hunters
[Lauren] Two hunters?
[Luke] And the pro hunters,
they already shot a deer
and they're back at the place.
(swoosh)
[Jennifer] Luke?
What're you doing up?
[Luke] Someone is
laughing up there?
Laughing?
[Luke] They keep
saying your name.
[Jennifer] Luke, what are you?
(growling)
(gasping)
What'd you say?
[Jennifer] You heard that?
Luke I didn't say
anything, it wasn't me.
[Luke] Okay.
(creaking)
Brad.
What's wrong?
What're you doing up?
Brad?
I can't sleep.
Why not?
I'm scared.
There's someone in there.
There's someone in
here like a ghost.
Brad?
Brad what is it?
Is it what you
saw earlier today?
Brad look at me, what is it?
What did you see?
Come on.
Brad?
Brad look at me, what is it?
Brad what did you see?
What did you see?
Tell me, what did you see?
(clattering)
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
(screaming)
What's going on?
What going on?
What happened?
There's something out here.
Why is Brad out here?
I heard him out here, I came
out to see what was wrong.
He's bleeding.
[Luke] What?
Is he okay?
[Lauren] No, do you
have a first aid kit?
[Luke] In the bathroom.
Lauren?
(Brad crying)
Luke, I swear.
Stop.
It's three in the morning.
There was someone.
No, stop.
[Lauren] Come here,
it's okay, shh, come here.
(wind howling)
Are you sure you're
gonna be okay?
I mean I can stay another
day, if you guys want.
No, it's fine really,
thanks for coming.
Yeah, Luke, thanks.
[Luke] You're welcome.
Come here bud.
Say goodbye.
Bye.
[Luke] Bye.
Alright.
I know, we're
going, we're going.
Miss you, love you.
What's going on?
I told you.
The house is haunted?
Then how come I
haven't seen anything?
I live here too you know,
I haven't seen a thing.
But I have.
That should be enough.
Well what do
you suggest we do?
I wanna move.
Honey, we can't move.
Then I wanna call someone.
To have someone come in here
and figure out what's going on.
Jennifer there's
nothing going on.
There was a man at
the house warming party.
A friend of my mother's, he
said he picked up on things
and that our house has
an interesting energy.
Okay, so our house has
Fine.
Did he say get out of the house
or there's a ghost
in there with you?
I'm gonna call him.
No.
Jennifer you're not.
Please, I'm starting to
get a little worried here.
This is all starting to sound
like what happened in Chicago.
Luke.
I saw something.
You didn't see anything.
God you're stressed.
Your mind's playing
tricks on you that's all.
Look, it's like
what Lauren said,
"There's an explanation
for everything."
The next time something
happens, confront it.
Go see what it is.
Stay calm.
Go at it rationally.
And I think your
ghosts will go away.
And what if they don't?
They will.
Give it a few days.
I promise.
(knocking)
[Delivery Man] Mrs. Branagan?
Yes.
I need you to sign
here for me please.
Need help carrying this in?
No thank you, I'll be fine.
Well don't go hauling that
thing upstairs alone now.
Get your husband to take it up.
(dark, ominous music)
(thud)
(gasping)
(grunting)
(clattering)
(screaming)
[Jennifer] No, no.
Help.
(gurgling)
(screaming)
Jennifer, my dear how are you?
Thank you for coming, Walter.
Not at all.
I must say, I was
a bit surprised to
receive your call but
delighted though.
And you must be Luke.
[Jennifer] What're
you doing here?
I heard there was
a party here tonight.
Little birdie told me.
Am I late?
And Meredith,
lovely as always.
Well, I suppose we
should give this a go.
Let's head upstairs shall we?
(dark, melodious music)
Luke, Meredith, would you
excuse us for a few minutes?
I think it would be best
if I had a little talk
with Jennifer, alone.
[Luke] Wait, are you serious?
I think it would be best.
Let's go Luke.
He's harmless.
Let them have their fun.
We won't be long.
I'm afraid I owe you
a bit of an apology.
An apology?
Yes.
I should've been more clear
when agreeing to see you.
Your expectations may
not be met this evening.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I'm not a medium, Jennifer.
I'm not psychic.
I've never done anything
like this before,
reading.
Oh I have tried in the past to
contact the other
side, if you will but
well I never had
much luck with that.
You see, most people
expect someone like me
to come in and tell them
exactly what's going
on in their house.
Who's to blame?
A name?
A face?
What they can do to stop it?
But the very definition
of paranormal is
that, that can not be
explained or defined.
It is outside of our
knowledge, outside of our
understanding of the world.
It's the unknown.
Which I suppose is why
it's so terrifying, huh?
I'm fairly certain
there is something
going on in your house.
I felt it at the
night of the party.
And I feel it now, here
in this room with us.
But I'm afraid that's the
end of the line for me.
I don't know what it is.
And I don't think I can
answer your questions.
So that's it?
I mean you're not
even gonna try?
Jennifer, I'd, I.
So you're not a medium.
Fine, but
you said yourself you
pick up on things.
And you feel something
here, you just said that.
Yes, but.
Then try.
Please, just
ask it.
Ask it what it it is?
What it wants from me?
Please.
Do you know of anyone
who died in this house?
Any trauma of any kind?
No.
I looked online, I
couldn't find anything.
Nor I.
This is just a house Jennifer.
With seemingly no reason
why it should hold a ghost.
Don't you see?
I have tried.
Whatever's here
is much more
complicated than that.
(sighing)
Why are you here?
Excuse me?
If you can't help me at all
why did you even agree to come?
I've tried for so many
years to ignore this thing.
I guess I thought maybe
coming here tonight
would be different that,
finding I could help.
I was curious.
I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
So you're wasting my time.
Jennifer.
You come into my house.
You stare at my staircase
all mysterious and eerie.
You say something about my baby,
something you have
no way of knowing
and then you come
over here tonight
and tell what's
been terrorizing me,
is more complicated then
some run of the mill ghost.
And also there's nothing
I can do about it.
Jennifer.
No, get out.
If you can't help me,
you need to leave.
Jennifer, please.
I need to figure out
what's going on here,
do you understand?
I have a real problem,
I need real help.
Get out.
Jennifer.
(clattering)
(dark, mysterious music)
Walter?
I'll be off now.
Walter, wait,
what just happened?
Lovely seeing you
again, Jennifer.
No, please come back.
Walter.
No, stop.
Jennifer?
What's going on?
[Jennifer] Luke, stop
him, don't let him leave.
Walter?
You don't understand.
[Luke] Calm down, stop.
I'll call you.
(thump, grunting)
Are you trying to scare me?
Is that what this is?
You wanna go back
to Chicago so bad
you're trying to scare me out
of this house, aren't you?
What?
I can't believe this.
I should've never
agreed to this.
There was no reason
for Walter to come.
What about the closet door?
How are you going
to explain that?
It's an old house.
It's old wood, it was
humidity.
These things happen, Jennifer.
I mean seriously,
you need to take
a step back for a second
and listen to yourself.
Ghosts?
A medium, for Christ's sake.
It's all just a little.
What?
It's all just a little what?
Crazy?
I didn't say that.
You didn't have to.
Fine.
If that's what you
want me to say,
you're right.
You're acting crazy.
Walter saw something.
Luke, you weren't there,
you didn't see the
look on his face.
He said there's something
complicated going on here.
I saw enough.
Well, Luke listen to me.
Listen to me.
If you came to me and told me,
you thought the
house was haunted,
I'd believe you or at least,
listen to you.
But I'm not coming to
you with any of that.
Because I don't think
the house is haunted.
And honestly,
I don't think there's
anything to figure out,
except why it's so
hard for you to focus
on anything other than yourself?
What?
No more ghosts.
(splashing)
Hello?
(clattering)
(dark, ominous music)
(fizzing)
(thumping, thudding)
[Voiceover] Hi, you've
reached Walter Vance.
I'm not available at the moment
but please leave a message.
(beep)
(knocking)
Jennifer.
Hi, Marlene.
Can I come in?
Thank you.
Are these your daughters?
Uh hmm.
Lucy and Claire.
You're scared.
What?
You look scared.
Did you know the people
who lived in the
house before we did?
Hm hmm.
A family.
Nice people.
Do you know why they moved?
Just had somewhere
else to be I guess.
Happened pretty fast.
Do you know if they
experienced anything
strange in the house?
Strange?
Yeah, like
ghosts?
You think the
house is haunted?
I don't know.
Yes.
I think.
Have you ever?
Uh hmm.
'Cause I just
would feel better
if I knew someone else had
gone through it too, you know?
Luke doesn't believe me.
He thinks it's all in my head.
I feel like everything is
spinning out of control.
But I refuse to believe that it,
I mean there has
to be something.
Right?
Some sort of answer.
My daughters, they
they don't talk.
Since they were about four.
I had some guests over.
They made a game out of it.
I won't talk to mommy's
friends if you don't.
They haven't said
anything since.
It's called selective mutism.
There's nothing wrong
with them, they just
don't talk.
I took them to dozens of
doctors and therapists.
Nobody could tell me anything.
I went into debt,
I got obsessive,
I got mean.
I let my marriage fall apart.
And then about a year
ago I sat them down,
tried to explain things to them.
They'd never get a job,
never start a family, if they
didn't talk.
I told them if they could
just try a little harder,
help me out a little bit,
that they could get better.
They could talk again.
And then Lucy looked right at me
and she said, "We could
talk if we wanted to."
First thing she'd said
to me in 10 years.
"We could talk if we wanted to."
I used to think there was
a reason for all of it.
Now I'm not sure.
I think sometimes
things just happen.
There's no use ruining your
life looking for explanations.
My husband should
be getting home soon.
I'll walk you out.
I'm sorry for
barging in like that.
You're welcome any time.
Jennifer.
I hope you find what
you're looking for.
Luke?
[Luke] Up here.
Hey.
I know you don't wanna
talk about this but.
(clattering)
Did you hear that?
Luke, listen.
Oh.
(thud)
(banging)
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Luke.
Jennifer.
(screaming)
What is it?
What's going on?
Are you okay?
I just saw.
You were in the room with me.
What?
What's happening to me?
Oh boy.
Alright okay.
You're too wound up.
Just.
Luke.
It opens on its own.
(scraping)
Better?
Just rest.
I'll stay with you
till you fall asleep.
(thudding)
(dark, menacing music)
I get it.
(chattering)
Luke?
Oh jenny, you're up.
What's going on?
(chuckling)
Oh, we were just discussing
that you've been a
bit tired recently.
Weren't we?
Honey, why don't you sit down?
Will one of you
please tell me,
what's going on?
We're concerned.
Luke told me you gave him a
bit of a scare last night.
He did?
And he mentioned
that you were still
raving about ghosts?
It's just.
Well.
This has been going on for
quite some time, Jenny.
You've been acting strange
ever since you got back home.
And that stunt that
you pulled with Walter.
Stunt?
And hysterics last night.
Hysterics?
What are you talking about?
Well it all seems a bit
crazy, don't you think?
I'm not crazy.
Of course you're not, Jenny.
But you can understand why we
would both be alarmed, right?
There's something
going on in this house.
It scares me.
And it scares me even
more that the two.
Luke hasn't noticed
anything out of the ordinary.
That doesn't mean anything.
I don't understand.
We don't want you
hurting the baby again.
Now, I've made an
appointment for you
with a psychiatrist next week.
He's a very good friend of mine.
You'll see him three times a
week until the baby's born.
After that we'll reassess.
We just want what's
best for you.
(dark, threatening music)
(rustling)
What do you want from me?
(creaking)
(thudding)
(gasping)
(knocking)
Is your Mom home?
You Mom, Marlene is she home?
(groaning)
Please I need to
speak to someone.
You Mom, where is she?
Where is she?
Do you not understand
what I'm saying?
(dial tone)
[Voiceover] Hi, you've
reached Walter Vance.
I'm not available at the
moment but pleave a message.
(beep)
(groaning)
(screaming)
(light, melodious music)
Jenny?
What're you doing here?
Is everything okay?
Should I make some coffee?
I have decaf.
Coffee would be nice.
I know you and Luke just
want what's best for me.
I haven't.
I know Jenny.
I know.
This is nice.
It is, isn't it?
I have always cherished
our moments together.
Remember getting ready
for your pageants?
All that primping and preening.
Dolling you up.
(chuckling lightly)
Those are some of
my fondest memories.
You and me.
All that beauty and promise.
I have an idea.
(clicking)
You have always had
the most lovely hair.
I can't believe you're here.
Luke's in for quite
a shock tonight
when you get home
looking so beautiful.
I really am glad you're back.
I don't know what
happened with us.
But with the baby and the move
and everything,
I can't help but see
it as a second chance.
And who knows,
maybe the next one'll
be a little girl.
I have to use the restroom.
Okay.
I'll be here when you get back.
(thudding)
(squeaking)
(shattering)
[Jennifer] Luke just called.
I should get going.
We haven't finished your hair.
Oh I can just pin this back.
It sounded like
he had a hard day.
Jenny are you feeling okay?
Yes.
(thudding, gasping)
Jenny, why are you so jumpy?
Jenny what's happening?
I have to go.
Jenny?
(thump, shattering)
Jenny, what's wrong?
Jenny?
(car rumbling)
(knocking)
Walter?
Walter, please.
(screaming)
Ma'am?
Are you okay?
(dark, menacing music)
Get out of my head.
Get out.
Jennifer?
Jesus Christ.
Jennifer, Jennifer?
Luke.
Honey, what's going on?
What's going on?
It's the house.
We need to get
you to a doctor.
No, no, it isn't,
it's the house.
(growling)
Meredith?
Yeah, she's here, I don't know.
No, it's not good.
Get out.
Meredith I gotta go,
we'll meet you there.
Jennifer,
stay here.
(gasping)
(thunder rumbling, pattering)
I'm gonna get you
out of the house.
I just need to call the doctor.
It's the house.
It's in my head.
It wants you to think I'm crazy.
[Luke] Stay here.
I'm here.
Tell me what you want.
(scraping)
(screaming)
Luke.
(thudding)
(gasping)
Jenny?
Luke, she's awake.
(whimpering)
No, no, no, no, sweety.
Lie down, lie down, lie down.
You need to rest.
What happened?
You had an accident.
We didn't if the baby was.
Everything's stable now.
Honey, you just tripped.
It could've happened
to any of us.
No.
It wasn't an accident.
It pushed me.
It pushed me down the stairs.
You have to believe me, please.
It pushed me.
I'm gonna go outside.
I'm gonna let you two be
alone for just a minute.
(gasping)
I'm just so glad you're okay.
You could've hurt the baby.
Luke it pushed
me down the stairs.
We're gonna stay at
Meredith's for a while.
Luke?
Why are you doing this?
You think I did this?
I don't know what I think.
I fucked up.
I made a mistake, I
I should've gotten you real help
instead of bringing
you down here.
The house.
Please, stop.
Just make it through
this pregnancy.
For me, that's all I'm asking.
Make it through this
pregnancy, we could
we could figure
things out after that.
I know it's hard.
But I really think that
once you'll see the baby
you'll fall in love.
Everything will make sense.
You'll see.
Why don't you care?
Because this isn't
about you anymore.
It's about what's
best for this family,
what's best for us.
And if you really think you
can get me back to Chicago
with ghosts and mediums and
falling down the stairs,
let me just remind you that
you got me out of Chicago,
when you tried to give
yourself an abortion.
But I didn't do it.
But you would have.
If I hadn't walked
into that room,
you would have.
And really, there's not a lot
more in the way of scaring me
that you can do.
So just drop it.
Stop wasting your time and mine
and start making this work.
(dark, ominous music)
The crib?
It's nothing.
But she doesn't need.
Just in case.
Nothing to worry about.
We're moving back.
Just rest.
(wind rustling)
(scraping)
(splashing)
(whimpering, screaming)
(clinking)
(chomping)
Jenny?
You should eat your
food, it's getting cold.
Jenny, you're biting
your nails again.
Are you feeling?
She's just tired.
Drink your tea, sweety.
So, Luke, when're you
moving into your new office?
New office?
For the promotion.
Promotion?
Look.
What promotion?
I was waiting
for the right time.
We're leaving.
Maybe this isn't the
right time to discuss this.
Aren't we?
No.
I told them I'm
staying on, Jenny.
I like it here.
I have friends here.
And you know it's not the
perfect situation for me either
but I'm making it work.
I really think we could
have a good life here
if you just give it a chance.
You didn't think
this was something
you should've discussed with me?
We decided it would be best.
We?
Luke and I discussed what
would be best for the baby.
A stable environment.
Just for a couple of years.
Just until things settle down.
Then we can.
I'm feeling tired.
I'm gonna go lie down.
I'll come.
No.
I'll be fine on my own.
[Voiceover] Hello?
I'm coming to Chicago.
[Voiceover] What?
Jennifer, no.
You shouldn't be going anywhere,
I thought that you guys said.
I'm grabbing a few
things and driving up.
If you'll have me great
if not I'll find somewhere else.
I just called to let you know.
(birds chirping)
(thudding)
(creaking)
(screaming)
(buzzing)
(beep)
Luke?
[Voiceover] Where are you?
It trapped me in the bedroom.
[Voiceover] God
damn it, Jennifer.
There's something in the hall.
I have to get help.
[Voiceover]
Jennifer, calm down
you have to calm down, okay?
(groaning)
Jennifer?
I think I'm
having contractions.
[Voiceover] What?
(panting)
The baby's coming.
[Voiceover] Alright,
honey listen, I'm on my way.
The baby's going
to come, calm down.
You're going to hurt him
if you're not careful.
Jennifer you need
to get outside.
No.
[Voiceover] Jennifer, please.
Take a deep breath, okay?
I'm coming, you
need to get outside.
I can't.
(sighing)
[Voiceover] You can alright?
There's nothing in the hall.
Jennifer, there never
has been, alright?
You're sick, honey.
Alright I'm sorry.
Okay, I really am, I'm sorry.
But this is all in your head.
Aright, you have to
believe me Jennifer.
Please.
Jennifer?
Okay.
[Voiceover] Okay.
Alright, go to the door.
(panting, snifling)
I'm there.
[Voiceover]
Alright, good, good.
Alright, now close your eyes.
My eyes are closed.
[Voiceover] Alright,
great, that's great.
Alright, now open it.
Don't.
(whimpering)
[Voiceover] Jennifer, you can.
Alright honey, listen.
Listen to when I say this,
there's nothing
out there, alright?
I promise, there's
nothing there.
Say it.
There's nothing there.
[Voiceover] Okay.
Alright honey, open the door.
Alright, open your eyes.
On the count of three.
One.
Two.
Three.
(gasping)
Everything okay?
Yeah.
I'm fine.
[Voiceover]
Anything out there?
No.
It's empty.
[Voiceover] Alright just
just go downstairs and outside.
I'll be there soon.
Okay.
(dark, menacing music)
No.
(screaming)
(groaning, whimpering)
(banging)
(baby crying, buzzing)
There's nothing there
There's nothing there.
There's nothing.
There's nothing,
nothing there.
(screaming)
Stop.
(thudding)
(panting)
(breathing soundly)
(light, melodious music)
You wanna show him his room?
Sure.
(creaking)
(gasping)
Jennifer.
Pardon my mess.
I'm not accustomed to
having much company.
I'm sorry for how I acted.
For what I said.
Please.
We're both adults, no
need for pleasantries.
What can I do for you?
Luke and my mom are telling me
that the pregnancy
was too much for me.
At this point, I'm
willing to accept that.
But they're just a few things
that keep nagging at me.
You saw something.
Didn't you?
Right be fore you left.
No.
I saw your face.
I didn't see anything.
Something started to make
sense to me that's all.
What?
I don't believe
in God, Jennifer.
I don't believe in
life after death.
And if you pressed me,
I'd have to admit I
don't believe in ghosts either.
At least not the way they're
generally understood.
Stopped believing
all of that after
Charlie died.
'Cause I knew that if
there was an afterlife,
if there was any way possible,
he would contact me.
And he didn't.
He hasn't, not once
in over 20 years.
And how I tried.
But you said you pick up on.
Energies.
Yes.
But just that.
It's a lot less romantic
than ghosts, isn't it?
It's a lot less comforting too.
But that's all I was
ever able to pick up on.
I don't think there
is anything else.
Well if you don't think it
was a ghost then what was it?
You
have an energy, Jennifer.
I'm picking up on it right now.
You're afraid, frustrated.
I feel that.
And whether you're
aware of it or not,
it's bumping up
against my energy.
It's physically affecting
me, energy does that.
Well places, have
energies too, Jennifer.
Houses even.
And they're affected
in just the same way.
Let's say you go
into a place that
has a lot of energy
hanging around it.
Your house, say.
If you go into a place like that
and you're going
through something,
stress, anger, lot of
sorrow, regret, anything.
Well all that energy
you're pouring out
is going to bump up against the
energy that's already there.
It's gonna rough it up, you see.
Mess with it.
And then,
that energy that was
there is going to change.
It's going to react.
I'm not saying that's exactly
what's happening in your house.
But I am saying
that we often forget
that we're constantly
affecting everything around us.
People, environments,
old houses in Kansas.
You're saying,
you think this was all my fault.
You wanted my
opinion, there it is.
There's got to be
another explanation.
There's,
there's something else,
I won't except that.
Of course not.
You're too blinded by
your search to find
something or someone else
to blame, aren't you?
Well there are things much
bigger than us, Jennifer.
Things that aren't so
easily categorized or
or controlled.
You might have
better luck if you
stopped trying to
push everything
the way you want it to go
and started looking
at the source.
You don't know
anything about me.
Oh, but I do, my dear.
You moved into that
house and you hated it.
You hated this town,
you hated your mother.
You hated your husband
for bringing you here.
And most of all,
you hated that baby inside you
and what it did to
your perfect life.
From all I can see,
you've done nothing but hate.
Are you really
surprised that the house
started to hate back?
I shouldn't have come to you.
I should've known
you wouldn't help.
What're you even doing here?
Still in this town?
Now that everything is settled,
now that the baby is born,
I don't understand,
why don't you just leave?
[Jennifer] Believe
me that's all I want.
Then what's stopping you?
(creaking)
(thudding)
Hello?
Jennifer?
(buzzing)
Hey.
(frequency disturbance)
Luke.
(baby crying)
Luke?
(dark, menacing music)
(car rumbling)
(whimpering)
Grandma's gonna
miss you so much.
Are you sure this is
the right thing to do?
If you live closer I could
help you take care of Tyler.
Take care of you.
Plan was always to
go back to Chicago.
Your plan.
Well, I'm happy for you.
At least you're getting
what you wanted.
(engine revving)
(baby crying)
(enigmatic, melodious music)