Catch them.
Kill them.
What's wrong, Ronnie?
I love you, Jodie.
Suffolk County police.
May I help you?
Everybody's dead.
What do you mean,
"everybody's dead"?
A guy come running
into the bar and says...
... his mother and father are shot.
I've been to a lot of crime scenes,
never seen one like this.
Six members of the family
were found last night...
...in bed, shot...
...and killed.
Killed were car dealer Ronald Defeo,
his wife and four of their children.
The sole survivor of the family...
... 23-year-old
Ronald "Butch" Defeo Jr...
... is said to have discovered
the bodies.
The police state
that for his own safety...
... they're holding him
in protective custody.
Five of the victims were found
shot facedown on their beds.
The sixth was found in a closet.
No one seemed to stir in their sleep.
It's strange.
Suffolk County police have charged
23-year-old Ronald Defeo Jr.
The accused told police
he heard voices...
... coming from within the house,
telling him to murder his family.
Oh, God!
Damn it.
Hi, Michael.
Oh, hey, baby. You okay?
George, what are you doing
to my mom?
Nothing.
- Yet.
- You perv.
Come on up here, little man.
You can make it.
Oh, you're getting heavy.
Did you meet my dad?
No...
...never had the pleasure, pal.
Do I have to call you "Dad" now?
- Guess what.
- What?
- You can call me whatever you want.
- Anything?
- Yep.
- Cool.
- Anything.
Yeah.
- Stinky.
- Sure.
- Poopy-head.
- Yeah.
Crap-monkey-fart.
Okay, we gotta draw the line
somewhere, pal, that does it.
All right.
- This sucks.
- You're not kidding.
Billy.
Look, maybe we'll grab you
something on the way to school.
- What do you say, huh?
- I'm not hungry. I can walk to school.
No, you can't, and get
your feet off the chair.
I'll drop you a couple blocks away.
Nobody'd see.
- Mom, I'm 12 years old.
- Before you plan...
...your retirement party, we're gonna
drop you off at school.
We got a big day.
Why? Where are you guys going?
- Mom, can you help me?
- Oh, Michael.
Houses here are way out
of our price range, Kath.
Not according to this.
- Well, then it's gotta be true.
- Think positive, babe.
I'm positive that houses here
are out of our price range.
Look, when the business
is going good...
...we're gonna...
- There.
- What?
- That's it.
- Look.
- Honey.
Baby, look, 412 Ocean Avenue.
- It's beautiful.
- What?
Look at how friendly they are here,
honey.
They get like that when they think
they'll make a sale.
Let's just play it cool, Kath.
Kathy. Katherine.
Or not.
- Hi there.
- I'm Katherine Lutz.
Well, just call me Edith.
This is your husband?
- George.
- This is an amazing house.
You are going to love it.
Just follow me in here.
Careful on the steps there.
Holy shit.
Excuse me.
Let me show you
the rest of the house.
This... This is a mistake.
How's that?
No, I mean your ad in the paper.
This is...
It's gotta be a misprint.
I'm a contractor...
...and I know what a place
like this should cost.
And, you know, if this is...
Well, if this is true, then this is a...
The deal of a lifetime.
And what is wrong with that?
- Come on.
- I love it.
- There's a vibrant history here.
- Vibrant history, George.
In fact, the house was built
in 1692, at least the basement.
The rest of the house was added
from that foundation.
It's one of the oldest Dutch Colonials
in Long Island.
Wow, that's impressive.
This room would be perfect
for children, if you have any.
And the view's...
Well, have a look for yourselves.
There's a boathouse.
Oh, all you need now
is a boat, right?
Actually, George has a speedboat.
This place sounds
like it's made for you.
And this is your basement.
As you can see,
it's very spacious.
It can be a game room,
a playroom.
Well, let's... Let's have a look.
I'll just wait up here.
Yep, looks like a basement.
So, what do you guys think?
- I think you look foxy in that skirt.
- Will you stop it? Come on.
Yes, yes, okay?
It's a value. It's a value
for people with money.
Okay, look, if we do this, we're
gonna be eating dry wall for a year.
We deserve this, George.
You deserve this.
How many times you tell me
how hard you work for so little.
- Kathy...
- Maybe today is the day it all pays off.
- We'll make sacrifices.
- Huge sacrifices.
Yeah, I understand that.
Listen, honey...
...this is the life we want.
- We're happy?
- Yes, we're happy.
She's happy. I'm broke.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
So look, I gotta ask,
what's the catch?
There's always a catch.
There was a tragedy, a crime...
...a murder.
- I'm sorry, what?
In the house?
Several people, a family.
But, you know, we've moved on,
the whole town.
It is a distant memory now.
And the house is fine.
Really.
Doesn't it seem kind of strange
to buy this house, honey?
Well, houses don't kill people.
People kill people.
Just... Excuse us.
Do you think we can make it work?
You know what?
You want it,
then we're gonna make it work.
- Really?
- I'll work out of the basement...
...and you can, well...
...sell one of the kids.
- Hey.
A little one.
We're rich! We're rich!
We're rich in something,
but it ain't money.
Wait.
- You say your prayers?
- Yep, said them twice.
- What did you pray for?
- Lf I tell you, it won't come true.
Why don't you tell him the truth.
- What?
- Praying doesn't do any good.
William.
Nobody answered me when
I asked for Dad to be kept alive.
Don't say that.
Sometimes things happen in life
that can't be explained, Billy.
Billy, look at me.
I need you to give George
a chance, okay?
You're not being disloyal
to Dad by liking George.
He doesn't want to be anything
but your friend...
...and maybe one day
something more.
Nobody will ever
replace your dad, honey.
For you too?
For me too.
How's Billy?
He'll be fine.
- First call.
- Lutz residence, how may I help you?
- Can I talk to my daughter, please?
Yeah, sure, she's...
She's right here. Okay.
Your mother's gotta stop
gushing over me, seriously.
It's embarrassing now.
Hello?
- Hey, Ma.
- Hi.
No, we're all moved in.
- Yeah, Ma.
- Are you cold?
No, Ma.
Yeah.
- What is it, baby?
- Nothing.
- Are you okay, baby?
- No.
I don't feel well.
- Give me a kiss.
- I can do it, I can do it.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
No, you can't.
Come here, come here.
Honey, I'm gonna
make you some tea.
How many brothers and sisters
do you have?
- Chelsea?
- Hey, Mommy.
Hi, hon. Who are you talking to?
- The girl who lives in my closet.
- Oh, yeah?
- And what's her name?
- Jodie.
You know there are plenty of other
little girls to play with in town too?
I know, but Jodie says
they're all mean.
Is that Jodie?
No, that's someone else.
Who?
I'm not supposed to say who.
She says it's an A-hole.
You are not allowed
to say that word.
George, George.
- Look what I found.
- What is that? Where'd you find that?
Harry and I found it.
- Where?
- In the basement.
Not the basement.
My office.
You listen to me.
You don't go down there.
Understand?
Guys, would you help me
with the groceries?
Go on, go help your mom.
I'm sorry.
Go on.
- How are you feeling?
- Good, good.
I found a babysitter off a board
at the grocery store.
Billy will love that.
How about we call her
the young-adult-sitter?
Where's Chelsea?
Chelsea?
Chelsea!
Chelsea.
Hey, give me your hand.
Give me your hand, sweetie.
- Chelsea, go to George.
- Come on. Hey, give me your hand.
What were you thinking?
You could have fallen in the water.
Jodie wanted to see the boat.
Somebody should have been
watching you.
Billy, get up.
Billy, I gotta go pee.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Chelsea.
Goddamn it, Harry.
Seriously. You trying to kill me?
Come on, get away from there.
Hey, that's enough.
Hey!
George? Hon, what are you
doing down here?
It's the only place
that's warm in this damn house.
Somebody keeps opening
the windows.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What is that?
You tell me.
- Why don't you come back to bed.
- No, I can't sleep.
I'm sorry, baby.
Don't...
Don't talk to me like
I'm one of your kids, okay?
- What?
- That goddamn dog woke me up.
Billy's dog.
Found him in the boathouse.
- But you locked it.
- Yeah.
Hey, and guess
what I found in Billy's room.
You ready to talk
about those keys?
There's not a lot in this world can't
be solved with an apology, Billy.
I'm not apologizing
for something I didn't do...
...George.
Get to work, buddy.
"Get to work, buddy. "
"Katch 'em... "
George?
George, you down there?
What?
What's the matter?
Did you do that thing
with the magnets?
Nothing. Just seeing things,
I guess.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
You look hideous.
You're rather repulsive yourself,
Mr. Lutz.
- Where's the babysitter?
- Babysitter?
Told you guys,
I don't need a babysitter.
- I'm old enough.
- Baby, I know you can...
I'm not letting her watch us. She's
not coming in, I won't let her. I won't.
- She's not coming in.
- Billy, listen to me.
- I won't leave you alone.
- I can't believe you hired a babysitter.
- I told you I was old enough.
- Hi.
- I'm Lisa, the babysitter.
- Great.
Can I take your coat?
Okay.
Hi.
I'm Billy.
You sure you don't want
a babysitter?
Would you like me
to show you around?
No, it's okay.
I know it already.
I used to sit for the Defeos.
Kind of freaky being back here.
I'm Billy.
Yeah, I got you the first time.
Have a good night, Billy.
This is just what we needed,
don't you think?
Yeah. Definitely.
You feeling all right?
You know what?
I feel better.
I think I just needed
to get out of the house.
Come on, drink up.
Are you trying
to get me drunk, Mr. Lutz?
That's the appeal of marriage, hon.
Hopefully, I won't have to.
Be right out.
Hungry?
Kid, you read my mind.
The kids, they're...
They're going through
a tough time.
I guess they're just
adjusting to everything.
Yeah, well, we all are.
Do you feel different?
What do you mean?
About us.
About me.
Yeah.
Yeah, I do.
I feel like for the first time in my life,
I'm sure about something.
And that's you.
And I'm gonna spend the rest
of my life making you happy.
Oh, boy, you know how
to turn on that Lutz charm.
Some people say his tongue is fake.
I think it's all him.
Got this at a pinball arcade.
Cool.
So do you French?
Do I what?
Kissing, tongues.
No.
Did your family know the Defeos?
- The who?
- The family that lived here before you.
No, we just moved here.
Well, you know what
happened to them, don't you?
No.
I really shouldn't be telling you this.
Your parents are gonna be pissed.
It's okay.
Stop. That's not how you play.
- I can't hear you.
- Stop it. Let me try.
You're killing him.
So this wack job, Ronnie,
the guy that lived here.
People in this town say
he heard voices telling him to do it.
The guy was a nut. I mean, first
he thinks his dog's out to get him.
So he kills it.
A few days later, he thinks his family
is a bunch of demons.
So you know what he did?
Wasted them.
How did he do it?
Do what?
You are way too young to hear this.
So cover your ears.
And don't listen.
A rifle.
He went room to room,
splattering their heads as they slept.
He killed his brothers
in this very room.
Right here.
In these beds.
It's kind of gross
you guys still sleep in here.
Actually, it's fucking sick.
Yeah.
I'm totally freaking you out, kid.
I suck at babysitting.
This was the little brat's room.
Jodie's.
You know, they found her in there.
- Jodie says you're a bad babysitter.
- Yeah?
Well, Jodie's...
What's the word? Dead.
Is not.
That little shit got me fired.
Dare you to go in there.
You give me your Kiss poster
if I do it?
Okay.
You're going to make her mad.
Come on, guys.
Ha-ha, guys, this isn't funny.
Billy, Michael.
It's not opening. I can't open it.
- Unlock the fucking door.
- There's no lock.
This isn't funny. Let me the fuck out.
Billy, Michael.
Let me out. Let me out of here.
Let me out of here!
What's going on?
Let me out.
Hi, Lisa.
Look what Ronnie did.
Let me out!
Let me out of here!
Help me. Let me out!
I saw Jodie.
Who's Jodie?
The little girl.
She's dead.
She's supposed to be dead.
- It's one thing to pull a prank.
- We didn't pull a prank.
- It's another one to hurt someone.
- It was this house.
Shut up!
- George.
- I got this under control.
You don't have you under control.
What you guys did was wrong.
Stop it, Kathy.
Whatever you're doing...
...whatever you're saying
doesn't work.
From now on, I'm doing the
disciplining around here, end of story.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
This house is bad, Mommy.
Michael, honey.
There's no bad houses.
There's just bad people.
Why didn't you tell us
about the people who died here?
- Where did you hear that?
- The babysitter told me...
...that two little boys died
in our room.
Goddamn babysitter's an idiot.
Get to bed. We'll deal with this
in the morning.
No, I'm not sleeping in that room.
It's gross.
- Me neither.
- Wipe that stupid look off your face...
...and go to bed.
Run.
Why all the yelling, Mommy?
It's nothing. It's over now, baby.
I need you to tell me
what happened with Lisa, honey.
Lisa was being mean to Jodie.
So Jodie hurt her.
- Jodie.
- It's okay, Mommy.
Jodie won't hurt you.
She thinks you're a good mommy.
But the man who lives here...
...she says he's bad.
She wants him to go away.
He makes her do bad things.
Move it...
...from there to there.
Go.
And, Billy, don't come in
until you're finished.
What?
Is this discipline or torture?
Thought it was meat loaf.
When the body suffers,
the spirit flowers.
It's what my dad taught me.
His dad's not around
to teach him that, now, is he?
Billy, why is George such a jerk?
He's not a jerk. He's a douche bag.
And a weirdo.
And a doofus and a dipstick.
Catch them.
Kill them.
Catch them. Kill them.
Catch them.
Kill them.
- No! No!
- Look at me.
- No!
- What's the matter?
- God!
- It's me.
Baby, it's all right.
Do you use narcotics, Mr. Lutz?
No. But after this week,
I'm gonna give it...
...some serious thought.
Suffer from headaches, nausea?
Actually, I feel great now.
Weird as that may sound.
Well, there's no sign
of a concussion.
No sign of any bruising at all.
I want you to give Dr. Stone a call.
Wait, wait, wait.
This is a psychiatrist.
- Do I look nuts to you?
- I'm not trying to offend you here.
I'm just trying to help you
figure out the problem.
I feel like it's my fault, George.
- Kath.
- I was the one who wanted this place.
- I put too much pressure on you.
- This is the life...
...that I want too, okay?
We got the old American dream here.
Okay? There's no way in hell...
...that I'm letting that get away now.
I love you, George.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Billy, can I get my teddy?
She's real hungry.
Okay, go. And hurry up.
Mom finds out I let you out
of my sight, she's gonna kill me.
Hi, Mommy.
Look at me, Mommy.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God!
- Chelsea.
- Chelsea, don't move. Just sit down.
Chelsea.
Hold the ladder.
Honey, stay there.
Chelsea.
- Chelsea.
- Goddamn it, Chelsea.
Which way?
Which way did they go?
Going left.
Chelsea.
What are you doing up here?
I have to go with Jodie, Mommy.
Baby...
...you come to Mommy.
No!
George.
- Hang on.
- Hurry.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
George!
George, please, God, I'm slipping.
Chelsea.
What would you...?
Why would you do that?
Sorry. I'm sorry.
You can't do that to Mommy.
- Jodie wanted to show me something.
- There is no Jodie, okay?
- Yes, there is.
- No, there isn't!
- You have to stop this!
- Jodie's real.
- Jodie's real. She's...
- She is not real!
Liar! Liar!
Liar!
I've seen her.
She was gonna show me Daddy.
I just wanted to see Daddy.
Jodie promised to take me to Daddy.
She says I can stay here
so we can play together...
...forever and ever.
Do you miss your daddy?
Yes.
- Do you miss your daddy a lot?
- Yes.
I know you miss your daddy, baby.
But no one can see him because...
...he's in heaven.
He's with the angels.
I just got so scared.
What's the matter with you people?
Wacko family.
Father Callaway?
Father.
Kathy Lutz.
Hello.
Do you have a moment?
It's my family.
We've changed. It's...
It's like we've grown apart.
I don't think I understand.
There's something...
There's something evil in my house.
I know it sounds...
...crazy, I know that.
I would think the same.
I just don't know where else to go.
There was a family...
...lived here some time ago.
They had a similar problem.
The Defeos.
You knew them?
I'm living in their house.
Now, hold it steady.
Because if you get shaky,
I get shaky.
Go!
What, are you crying?
Why are you crying?
That wasn't so bad.
Pick up another log.
Hurry up, pick up another log.
Hurry up.
Put your hands up there.
No.
Put...
We're friends.
We're having fun, right?
Put your hands up there.
Go!
Come here, little girl.
You're my favorite girl.
Catch them.
Kill them.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
George.
I think there's something
seriously wrong here.
Something's not right.
What's not right?
We need to get out of here.
To just go. Just pack up and go.
No, no, no.
You know, you can't run away
from your problems, Kath.
Please, let's go, George.
- Somewhere. Anywhere.
- Did you hear that?
Do you hear that squeak?
I gotta fix that squeak.
Because, you know, these houses,
they're big...
Big projects. Kath, and you
can't just walk away from it.
How did you get so fucking stupid?
What?
Everything we have is in this house.
Everything.
I'm not worried
about our goddamn money.
Oh, our money.
George, we're losing each other.
Don't you see that?
We stay here,
we'll have a house for the family...
...only there won't be a family.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
It's always so cold in here.
Would you let the stove alone
and pay attention to me?
I'm not going anywhere,
neither are you.
So shut up about that!
Just shut up!
Goddamn it.
You're the one who wanted
this godforsaken house.
Well, now you got it.
Mom! Mom!
Home sweet home.
What is it, sweetie?
We can't find Harry anywhere.
He's gone.
I'll help you look in a sec, sweetie.
You seen Harry, George?
No, I haven't, Billy.
Maybe he ran away.
Harry never runs away, George.
What's the matter with you, William?
Get out of here now.
- Now!
- Fine. Come on, Michael.
In the name of the Father,
the Son and the Holy Spirit.
- Hello?
- Is your mommy home?
Hold on a second.
Mommy, there's someone
at the door.
Who is it, honey?
Come in, Father.
This is gonna sound strange...
...but you know the doll with one eye
that your daughter is holding?
Well, that belonged to the little girl
who lived here before you.
Yes, it was left here.
No, Mrs. Lutz, it was not left here.
Father, what exactly
are you trying to tell me?
I knew the Defeos very well.
I presided over their funeral.
Jodie Defeo was buried
with that doll.
Oh, heavenly Father.
Almighty God...
...we ask you to bless...
...and sanctify this house.
To bless all who live here...
...and to bring them the abundance
of all thy fruits.
Get out.
Father!
Why are you leaving us?
What's the matter?
It's okay. I'm here.
Catch them.
Kill them.
Oh, goddamn it, Harry!
Catch them.
Kill them.
There was a crime. A murder.
You know, the town has moved on.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
And it is a distant memory now,
and the house is fine.
We don't open
for a few more minutes.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
"Voices told him to do it. "
"He just moved into the basement. "
"Twenty-eights days later
he killed them all. "
Oh, my God.
"Reverend Jeremiah Ketcham. "
"He started a mission for Indians. "
"He slaughtered them all. "
"Over 20 bodies were found
in the lake. "
Catch them.
Kill them.
Father.
Why did you run away
from my house?
Why did you abandon us?
Your house frightens me, Mrs. Lutz.
I just read about this man,
Ketcham...
...who tortured Indians on my land.
On my basement.
I read about how he slit his throat...
...so that his presence
would live forever.
Do you believe this could be true?
Ronnie Defeo came to me
weeks before the murders...
...and he spoke about hearing voices
and seeing things in the house.
I didn't believe him until yesterday.
Mrs. Lutz, get you and your family
out of that house...
...right now.
- Hello?
- George.
George, I've just been to see
Father Callaway.
Listen to me, you gotta get you
and the kids out of the house.
George?
Are you there? George?
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Billy! Michael! Where's George?
He's in the boathouse.
George, we have
to get out of here now.
George!
Are you fucking crazy, George?
Have you lost your mind?
You tried to kill me.
- Chelsea!
- Mommy! Mommy!
I'm down here, Mommy!
Chelsea, honey,
what are you doing down here?
I think she misses her daddy.
Don't you?
Give me back my daughter.
I wanna talk to you. Wait.
I wanna talk to you!
Kids, get down here, now!
Kids, get down here!
- Billy, help me push this!
- Mom, where are you going?
Billy!
- Hurry. Go.
- Billy!
Mom, why are you wet?
Mommy! Mommy!
Come on, Mom!
Hurry.
Billy, come on!
Run! Go, go, go!
You're stuck! You're stuck!
Stay here!
Great!
Let go of my mom, you bastard!
Let go right now! Let go.
- What the hell is your problem?
- Let's go.
These kids are out of control.
- Mom, it's stuck!
- It won't open!
Where's Chelsea? Chelsea!
- Hurry, hurry, Billy. Hurry.
- Come on. Let's go. Be quiet, be quiet.
Billy!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I want you to hold on tight.
Jump, baby.
- Come on, honey.
- Come on.
- Come on, Michael.
- No, Mommy.
- No.
- Hurry, baby.
Come on, Michael.
- Come on, hurry.
- Let's get out of here.
- Come here. Come here.
- No.
You leave him alone.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Kill them.
Don't hurt him!
Back the fuck up!
Kill them.
Hurry. Let's grab some rope.
Kathy, kill me!
You kill me, or I'll kill you!
Nobody's dying today.
Okay, let's get him in the boat.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Why are we taking him?
Let's just leave him here.
I can't explain it to you right now. We
have to get him away from the house.
Don't even look at it, Kathy.
Let's get out of here.
Ripped by:
SkyFury
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)