Subtitles translated by Ghost0ne
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
The Pact
>>
Translated by ear.
Hey, Its me, are you coming down?
I know it's hard to Annie, but
we both have to deal with it.
What is that supposed to mean?
Yes, I'm being responsible ...
Someone has to take care of everything ...
And we are her children, for God's sake.
Hold on ...
I'm not go back to that house.
Annie, we are both supposed to be here.
Stop telling me what
I have to do.
You of all people
What does that mean?
What do think it means?
When was the last time you used?
You know what, fuck you.
That more than 4 years ago ...
before I became pregnant.
Fuck you too. Now that you're 'clean'
You've forgotten what she used to do to us?
You've forgotten how sick she was?
You know what, im just so crazy right now.
I have my own problems, work,
and yet all of this.
You know what, if you want to forgive her,
no problem, but I will not.
Thats Enough.
This is our mother's funeral.
Are you coming or not?
Connecting ...
Hey, how are you?
I'm fine. Eve is sleeping?
I wanted to say hi.
Oh? Really? I just put her down
Im sorry im on a neighbours signal, I might loose you
Can you just go get her please? now.
All right. ok
Hold on.
Honey ...
Hi, can you see mommie?
Mama? Mama
- Damn ...
Can you see my mommy baby?
Baby, can you hear me?
Shit.
Sorry, Mommy saida bad word.
Can you see me now, baby?
No.
Can you see Mommy?
I can hear you, but you can not see you.
I just wanted to say
how much I miss you.
I love you.
I love you so much and I'll see
you in a couple of days.
Honey, can you see me?
Yes.
Can you see Mommy?
Mommy, who's that behind you?
Disconnected
San Pedro, Los Angeles
Nicole?
Hey Nicole?
Voicemail.
Hi, Annie. No one knows where
Nicole is. If you find out, let me know.
Annie, Liz here. Can you call me right away?
Annie, I'm really worried about Nicole
I do not know where she is
Call me and we can figure it out
Shit.
Call Liz.
Hi this is Liz, Leave a message,
I'll call you back.
Its Annie. I just got to moms house.
I do not know where is Nicole is.
You know what that means.
So dont freak out, she will show up,
She always does.
I'll call you, bye.
Interview with Liz: You there?
Where did you go?
Call Nicole.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Shit.
Nicole?
Mom ...
Annie.
Hi, Liz.
It's been a while.
Yes.
Hi, you must be Nicoles little girl.
Its nice to meet you.
You never met?
No, but I saw the thousand pictures
everytime i checked my email.
Aunt Liz, can I
look out the windows?
Yeah honey go ahead.
so... erm have you still not heard from her?
- No.
But Annie, it's been 3 days.
You know how she is.
Probably couldn't handle all this
She will show up.
yeah yeah.....
you wanna get outa here? go to my moms place?
I do not want to be there alone.
Yes, I would love that.
Out like a light, I think that
time change really threw her for a loop.
I found these in my room.
I cant beleive i can actually smoke in here.
Since the time when I smoked.
It tastes like i'm 15.
Lemme see that necklace.
A cross? You?
Believe it or not, mom gave it me
when i was a kid.
I love it.
Shit ...
I cant even smoke in here.
I have a feeling that
she is going to try and stop me.
Was it really that horrible for you guys
growing up with her?
You have no idea.
Some people shouldnt have kids.
You shouldnt say that
There is a deep love
between mother and child.
I think it's a beautiful thing.
Is this the same deep love that made
Nicole take off on her kid?
Annie! We dont know whats hapened to her.
Yes! We do.
We have seen this over and over again
This is what we do in my family.
When things get tough, we take off.
my dad did it wherever the hell he is,
and now Nicole is doing it.
Then, why have you come back?
For Nicole... because we are sisters.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Grossvenor Boulevard 5550
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Shit ...
Liz?
Hey, Who is she?
Thats Nicole Barlow's sister.
shes Crazy.
I cant talk right now.
I'll call you later. bye.
I'm Bill Creek.
I know you told your story to a bunch of people
but ...
would you mind going ove rit with me?
Why do you want to know what happened to me?
I know your sister.
Been in here a bunch of times.
I dont need another person telling me i'm crazy.
Nice Smoke.
You know what I do
When I get the urge?
They told me you work as a waitress.
What else do you do or would like to do?
I dont wanna make friends.
You remind me of my daughter.
She's a little bit younger than you.
You guys are a lot alike.
She is a real fucking bithc too.
so, Where is she?
Your daughter?
Shes up in Seattle...
with her mother.
It's a sad story.
Let's talk about
why your here.
at 4 am and
claiming what you claimed ...
We sent people to check
because you refused to go back ...
I'm not going back to that house.
Your cousin is missing.
We found traces of a struggle.
So Annie ...
Let me ask you this
What would any cop in the
world begin to suspect here?
Why are you talking to me exactly?
You came here looking for help.
Yes ...
Well I dont need your help.
So your just gonna take off?
You better not leave town.
I'm gonna stick around, but its not because of you.
But because I want to know
What happened to Nicole and Liz.
Okay, okay.
Another reason to stick around
She's upstairs.
Grossvenor Boulevard 5550
Grossvenor Boulevard, CA.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
HEY!
You have to wear a helmet.
Merry Christmas.
house plan
Are you finally ready to order?
or did you have any questions?
You ok to wait here?
Yeah, yeah I'm fine.
You lived 16 years in this house
and you have no memory of this room?
I can see into the living room.
There are everywhere.
Its me and Nicole's room.
My mom wanted to find this place
She guided me here
because theres something here
something that will help us ...
to find out what
happened to Nicole and Liz.
Annie, its gonna take a lot more than that
to figure out where they went
Dont you understand? I was led here.
I can take some pictures, thats about it.
Why dont you beleive me?
Giles.
We talked on the phone and
you said that Stevie was around.
Sit down.
You want to fuck with it?
ARE YOU HERE TO FUCK WITH HER?
No.
Come on.
Stevie?
Do you remember me?
I'm Annie Barlow ...
from high school.
oh yeah ... Annie Barlow.
I just got back from
San Pedro in. ..
I thought of you...
Can you really do that thing
that everyone said you could do?
Take me to your mothers room.
I'm not getting anything.
Erm... what do we do now?
Where do you think we should go?
Down there.
Dont touch her.
Oh she's here.
What's over there?
Thats where she used to take us,
When we were bad.
Someone is in there.
Damn lamp.
It takes all the light.
Be careful.
I'm sorry.
I am very sorry for what
What happened to you.
What are you talking about?
I Can you see there and
I see what happened to you.
Its horrible.
Horrible.
Whats on the other side?
Last flashlight.
Whats with all the flashlights?
Electricity, It draws them out..
Hold this.
There's a second presence...
God, your sister.
What about my sister?
God ...
Shit.
This is where they go ... down below ...
Where they go... where they go...
Down, down below ... down below.
She didnt want anyone to know!
Stay away from her.
Damn it.
Help me!
Judas.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Stevie ...
who was that woman in there?
Who was that woman?
She didnt want anyone to know.
Stevie, who's Judas?
Why were you saying Judas?
She didnt want anyone to know.
Stevie, that wasnt my mother
it wasnt my mother.
Who was that? What happened to Liz?
What happened to my sister?
What do you think your doing to her?
Let me go, I'll talk to her!
Open the door!
Stevie, what did you see?
Damn it.
Shit.
Judas ...
Search results in your area
Judas - the mass murderer from San Pedro
seven known victims
Period of activity: 1975 - 1989
Victims Association
Signature with 'Judas'
adult content.
You must be older than ...
18 years to
see this content.
Serial Killer
Site murders
known victims of Judas.
Jennifer Glick, 20 years
last known victim,
found 11/10/1989, images
The death of a loved teacher
sparked a search for the killer.
Our family history
From left: Judith Barlow ...
From left: Jennifer Glick,
Judith Barlou ...
Charles Barlow.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Ok ...
Charles Barlow, born in 1947 ...
The Hospital of Saint John.
And... Judith Barlow.
u Born in 1950,
the same hospital of St. John.
So, my mother had a brother.
Thats right.
I dont see anything on him after the 1980 census.
Everything says her that he worked as a long shoreman
Yes.
I want to talk to Stevie.
Giles. - Giles.
No, listen. Dont put Gile son the phone
just get her.
OK, hold on.
Hi, Annie.
Stevie, I need your help.
That woman in the house, she was killed a long time ago
She was someone my mom knew
What did you feel at that house?
The presence told me that
your mother has done something ...
Something that she didnt want anyone to
know about.
But this thinsg was trying to kill us
wasnt it?
No, it was trying to
show us something.
Once you understand what it wants you to know
you will be free of it.
Yes, but how am i supposed to understand?
What the hell am i supposed to do?
I just want to know what
happened to my sister.
Annie, I can give you a tool,
You can contact the other side,
but ...
you should only use it
if you're ready to go all the way with this thing.
This woman who your mother knew
do you have anything of hers?
Yeah.
You've got to go back into the house.
If I do, do you promise me
that it willleave me alone?
Trust me.
Ok, tell me what I do.
Are you Jennifer Glick?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Yes
Shit.
What do you want me to know?
Judas ...
Wait ...
Was he my mother's brother?
Yes
Oh god.
Did he murder you?
Yes
ok, ok... I'm sorry ...
I'm sorry.
What do you need me to know?
Below?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
You fucking crazy son of a bitch.
Do it already!
Sister... sister...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I'm gonna eat some of your icecream with you.
: Redone by Ghost0ne.
>>
Translated by ear.
Download Movie Subtitles Searcher from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player