(OLD COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING)
(HEAVY BREATHING)
(HEAVY BREATHING CONTINUES)
(INDISCERNIBLE WHISPERING)
WOMAN: I love you, Lisa. I love you, Lisa.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I love you so much.
Listen to me, Lisa.
Hey, Lisa.
I have something to tell you, Lisa.
Listen to me.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
(DEEP VOICE) I have Something
to tell you, Lisa.
Mama?
(GASPS) Oh, God!
What are you doing up, sweetie?
Did you have another bad dream?
I dreamed about a swing.
Is there one at the new house?
Well, if there isn't,
I bet your daddy might just
put one up for you.
Come on.
Let's go get some breakfast, okay?
- I'll meet you in there.
- Okay.
HEIDI: What does the new house look like?
LISA: It's way out in the country
and there's just lots of room for you to play.
HEIDI: Can we bring my bike?
LISA: Of course we can bring
your bike, sweetie.
HEIDI: Even though I don't know
how to ride it yet?
LISA: You are gonna have lots of places
to learn how to ride your bike.
Hey! Heidi!
- Daddy!
- You done good, Daddy.
- Why, thank you.
What about you, huh? What do you think?
Who lived there before?
Nobody, honey.
That's why the bank gave us
such a good deal, right?
Why, thank you, Mama.
Well, maybe you'd rather live in there?
- No.
- That can be arranged.
- No, thank you.
- You could have the whole place to yourself.
- Nope. No, nope!
- Teddy bear could have his own room.
Come on, let's go. I'll race you! Come on!
ANDY: Go, go, go! Race Mama!
(STATIC ON RADIO)
The hell, baby?
You can't find a clearer station than that?
We're out in the boondocks, babe.
We're lucky we get running water.
Thank you.
Well, we don't need water,
- that's what beer is for.
- Mm-hmm.
- My beer, by the way.
- Uh-uh.
(RUSTLING)
(RUSTLING CONTINUES)
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
(YELLS)
(LISA LAUGHING)
You! Git! God! Shoo!
Git!
(CONTINUES LAUGHING)
You think that's funny, do you?
(DOOR CREAKS)
(RATTLING)
(CAR HORN HONKING)
Aunt Joyce!
(COUNTRY SONG PLAYING ON RADIO)
Kid, you grow like a weed!
Hi!
Look at you, Miss Homeowner.
Well, that didn't take long.
No suitcase?
- I am not a freeloader, Andy.
- Today or historically?
Stop it, Andy.
Joyce is just here to wish us well.
Is that so?
It's a goddamn curse
being right all the time.
It truly is.
JOYCE: It didn't work outwith Ray.
Was he the married one or the drunk?
Bit of both, turns out.
LISA: What about you? Are you...
JOYCE: Eleven weeks sober.
ANDY: - Shit, call Guinness.
(INDISTINCT WHISPERING)
On second thought
that's probably a bad idea.
JOYCE: I've got alimony coming in.
I wanna be near family.
Well, find a place near here, just not here.
JOYCE: Who lives over there?
That's just some old wreck
someone left behind.
I'm gonna haul it away.
A girl lives down there.
Nobody lives around here, baby.
When did you see a girl?
Just now.
You know, I've lived in worse.
"Near here but not here," right?
You did say that, babe.
(INDISTINCT VOICES)
(VOICES STOP)
(LIGHT soss)
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
(SCREAMS)
Stop it.
Mama?
Why are you crying?
It's nothing, sweetie. Nothing.
Aunt Joyce is out front,
so go say good night
and I'll come tuck you in, okay?
Okay.
Mama's crying.
Do you know why she gets sad?
Your mama gets feelings sometimes.
Feelings she doesn't much care for.
What kind of feelings?
Tell you what. I want you to try something
for me. Can you do that?
Look out there.
At what?
Don't really focus
on anything specific. Just...
Take it all in.
Feel anything?
WOMAN: Help us...
I think so.
And sometimes...
I see things.
That's because you were
born with a veil, sweetie.
Just like your mama and me. And our mama.
What's a veil?
It means that when you were born,
you had a sheen over your face,
like a wedding veil.
And sometimes folks
born that way have a gift.
They can...
They can sense certain things
that other people can't.
Mama never said anything about it.
Your mama doesn't like this kind of
talk of gifts and feelings.
So let's just keep this conversation
between us, okay?
Now run to bed. Please.
Love you.
I love you, too.
(INDISTINCT WHISPERING)
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I know, Mama.
Listen to me, Lisa.
I have something to tell you.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Just be a good girl
and listen to your mother.
Listen to me!
Lisa.
It's 6:00 a.m.
How long you been in here this time?
You saw something again, didn't you?
Here.
If these pills ain't working, we sure
as hell shouldn't keep paying for them.
They're working.
Just gets a little tricky
when they wear off, that's all.
You should finish getting dressed.
You'll be late for work.
- All right, darling.
- Thank you.
Careful, Heidi.
- You need any help?
- I can do it.
Okay.
All right.
(GRUNTS)
(INDISTINCT WHISPERING)
(SHRIEKS)
Hey, neighbor.
Heidi's been gone an hour
and I don't know where she is.
- Well, she's probably just wandering.
- Heidi is not a wanderer.
That's 'cause she's never had anywhere
to wander to. Now she does.
You're just gonna have to get used to it.
Heidi!
Baby, where have you been?
I've been worried sick.
I'm not supposed to say.
Who said that?
Damn it, Heidi, who told you that?
Mr. Gordy.
Who's Mr. Gordy?
An old man I met.
He said there was a swing set in the woods,
just like in my dream.
Remember, Mama?
Okay.
Okay, come here.
Joyce, get Andy on the phone.
This is it.
Mr. Gordy told me there was a swing here.
Well, babe, I don't see a swing.
I'll be damned.
There may not be a swing here now,
but there used to be.
(GRUNTS)
- Jesus.
- Walk much?
Babe, did this Mr. Gordy
say anything else to you?
He said there's money buried in the garden.
Okay.
Okay, sweetie, I want you
to do something for me.
How much money?
If this Mr. Gordy
ever comes up to you again
I want you to scream as loud as you can.
You understand me?
Okay.
Let's go.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
(STATIC)
(RADIO PLAYS)
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
(DOOR CREAKS)
Andy?
(QUIET LAUGHTER)
HEIDI: I'm not supposed to talk to you.
They think you're a bad man.
You're not.
- Are you?
- Heidi?
Was that Mr. Gordy you were talking to?
LISA: Heidi, why didn't you tell us
that you had an imaginary friend?
HEIDI: Mr. Gordy's not imaginary.
He talks to me.
LISA: I was standing right there watching,
there's nobody outside.
- Mr. Gordy's real.
- Heidi, stop it.
I don't wanna hear any more talk about
this Mr. Gordy. Do you understand?
Seeing things that aren't there, it's just
not a road that you wanna go down.
Good night, okay?
(JOYCE AND ANDY LAUGHING)
What the hell, Joyce?
You've been here a week and Heidi's already
seeing invisible friends?
Turns out this Mr. Gordy...
He's up here.
And you, encouraging her, coming out here,
digging up my garden,
going on some wild goose...
MOTHER: Don't be afraid.
Let them in.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
(GASPS)
(COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO)
Good Lord, woman.
What'd you do, rob a shopping mall?
Courtesy of my new sugar daddy, Mr. Gordy.
Did you tell Heidi
where the money came from?
No. And neither will you.
I'm sure there's lots of stuff buried
in these parts.
That doesn't mean that there's a Mr. Gordy.
I beg to differ.
Did you look at the deed to your house?
The previous owner?
Yeah, the bank owned it.
Before that. Check it out.
Straight from the county assessor.
Look at the name at the bottom.
The Gordy family owned all this land
going back 200 years,
and this J.S. Gordy was the last one.
Then the bank got it in the '70s.
Ask me how they got it.
Okay, you're gonna get
one shot at this, all right?
If this doesn't go the way
I think it's gonna go,
I'll never bring it up again.
Deal.
Heidi? Come out here a second.
I am looking for a husband for you.
They're all old. You marry them.
- Good girl.
- Okay, pick a winner for me.
But look at them all carefully first.
Can you do that?
You see something, Heidi?
You know that man?
That's Mr. Gordy.
Okay.
Told you he was real.
I told you and you didn't believe me.
Damn it.
My daughter is not conversing
with the dead.
She picked Mr. Gordy's face
out of 50 pictures. Explain that.
That's just your influence coming out in her.
You know what, I don't want you talking
about any of this with Heidi anymore.
You hear me? She is my daughter.
She can talk about it with me.
Why would she? You don't listen.
You just tell her what's what,
just like you did with me.
You needed it. You know what, you still do.
I suppose I'd be better off
numbing myself with pills?
- Stop it.
- What, you don't think I know?
That was Mama's trick, too.
And that worked out beautifully for her.
Joyce, go home.
There's nothing wrong with Heidi.
You know what it is, Lisa.
It's starting for her.
LISA: Heidi?
Are you awake?
PASTOR WELLS: When I hear
of a family moving to town,
I visit to see if they've found a church yet.
Because I happen to preside over one.
Oh.
Folks around here had been wondering
when this rather special
piece of property would sell.
Yeah? What's special about it?
Aside from it being overgrown as all hell?
Andy Wyrick.
Pastor Jordan Wells.
The property is special because
back around the time of the Civil War,
it was the Station Master's land.
But I'm sure you knew that.
What, like a rail road?
No tracks on this land.
No, it wasn't that kind of rail road.
Do you mean, like,
the Underground Railroad?
The folks who helped escaped slaves
make it up north? Wow.
That's right. Those people
were known as station masters
and one of the most well-known
lived right here on your land.
He actually hid slaves on our property?
Yes, ma'am.
Hundreds of men, women and children
passed right through here
with nothing but the clothes on their back
and the light of the moon to guide them.
They didn't have flashlights?
No, sweetie.
They couldn't even use lanterns.
The moonlight was the only light
that they ever saw.
It was the light of freedom
in the Promised Land.
The Station Master
was an extraordinary man.
Entire generations of families
would not exist
if it was not for the Station Master
and this piece of land.
So,
don't be surprised if you get visitors
from time to time.
Living ones, I hope.
- As opposed to?
- Andy's just having a little fun.
- I do that.
- Well, if you do get any visitors,
I hope you'll be more welcoming than
the previous owner, J.S. Gordy, was.
He didn't exactly share his ancestor's
hospitable nature.
Between you and me
there was something seriously off
about that man.
Mr. Gordy's nice to me.
(AN DY STAMMERS)
- Look, Pastor...
- Sweetie.
We'd better get our day started.
(INDISTINCT VOICES)
(VOICES SINGING)
(SINGING STOPS)
(RATTLING)
(FOOTSTEPS SCAMPERING)
(WOMAN SOBBING)
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hello?
WOMAN: Help us.
Help us.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
(GASPS)
Mr. Gordy!
What is that?
Tell me what it is!
- Heidi?
- Mr. Gordy!
Heidi!
You know what?
I think there is an invisible man around here.
It's me.
Did you miss your daddy?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Right answer.
I've got a little surprise for you.
- What is it?
- Oh, you'll find out. Come on.
Look what I found in the back of
your daddy's truck.
ANDY: Heidi, meet Chief.
Oh, my God!
Daddy, I love him!
Am I the greatest father
in the world or what?
- You'll do.
- Thank you.
I love you.
(CREAKING)
(BARKING)
Remember to bring Chief's bowl
back in the house after he's done.
Where's Chief?
Oh, for God's sake. Chief!
Chief!
Damn dog.
(BARKING)
Come on.
It's gonna be all right.
AN DY: Chief!
(WHIMPERING)
Chief sounds hurt.
Hey, Heidi, why don't you just sit down
right here for a second?
Okay? And...
Don't move.
Be right back.
(DOG WHIMPERS)
- Chief!
Hey! Here, boy!
Chief!
(WHIMPERING)
Chief.
How'd you get in there, boy?
(CREAKING)
Daddy?
WOMAN: Heidi.
All right, watch out, boy.
(BARKING)
What the hell?
Daddy?
Heidi.
Help us.
ANDY: Heidi?
Heidi!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
VOICES: Help us.
(SCREAMS)
Damn it!
I thought I told you to sit tight.
What are you hollerin' about over here?
Come on.
Let's get you home.
Hey, babe.
- You figure out what this thing is yet?
- Yeah.
It's a trap.
See, you bait that chamber there.
Animals, they get in
and they can't get back out.
They get weak and starve.
Easy pickings.
Then you get them back out through here.
The back door.
There's gotta be a better way to hunt.
That's just cruel.
No, it's smart.
If you're a taxidermist.
Already found three more of 'em
in the woods.
I figure they made good money
for someone, back in...
Well, whenever the hell
they still used locks like these.
Well, smash them all up so Chief
doesn't get stuck in them again.
Or Heidi, for that matter.
MOTHER: I love you, Lisa.
Don't be afraid.
Let them in.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
(PANTING)
Hey.
- What's going on, hon?
- Nothing.
HEIDI: I have a bike.
Do you?
It's pretty.
It's purpley.
What do you mean?
Really? People are coming?
What kind of people?
Who are you talking to now?
Mr. Gordy.
Is that right?
Well, ask him where there's more money.
I can't. He's gone.
Next time then.
He said there's people coming.
Who?
(CREAKING)
I swear, Heidi, we should take you
and Mr. Gordy on the road.
Who's there?
Stay behind me.
I got an ax.
Hello?
What the hell is this place?
Do you see her, too?
Yeah.
Mama Kay? Whoa.
It's okay.
My name's Prentiss.
This is my grandmother, Mama Kay.
- Is this your property?
- That you're trespassing on, yes.
We were told we could come back here.
Yeah. Bullshit. By who?
Woman in the trailer.
Said she's your sister. Sold us this.
Sister-in-law.
What is that?
The shoofly.
Prentiss?
Now help me sit on down.
I wanna visit with the little one.
Come on, little one.
Be all right, young man.
All right, you gonna tell me
why you came all the way out here
just to buy some ratty old quilt?
A long time ago, when this quilt
was hung out here in these woods,
it meant it was safe to approach.
Safe for who?
Mama Kay's ancestors for one. Mine too.
Do you even know
where you're living at, Mr...
Andy.
Our pastor said we might get visitors.
Something about an Underground Railroad.
This was one of the stations.
Mama Kay's always
wanted to visit this place.
The guy saved a lot of lives, I reckon.
And he deserved better than
what happened to him.
You don't need eyes to see, little one.
But you already know that.
What do you mean?
You asked your father
if he saw me.
Now, that makes you some kind of special.
My mama says I'm not supposed to
talk about that.
But you have to be careful
with a gift like that.
Because sometimes
the devil looks a gentleman.
You're telling me
all that took place on my property?
Yes, sir.
Right here.
Guess your pastor left that part out.
Yeah.
(JOYCE LAUGHING)
Family meeting.
Whoa.
Not you, kiddo.
You stay outside for a minute, all right?
Okay, Daddy.
Sit down, Joyce.
HEIDI: That man told Daddy
what happened here, didn't he?
Why can't I know?
LISA: It's just not a story
for little girls, sweetie.
I'm a big girl. You always say that.
You remember Pastor Wells
talking about the Station Master?
Well, back when he owned all this land,
he was what's called a taxidermist.
He also did something that
he didn't tell anybody.
He would help hide people
who were in trouble.
People like Mama Kay's great-aunt, Nell,
and her fiancé, Levi.
You see, Nell and Levi had fallen in love
and had dreams of getting married
once they were safe
and free.
ANDY: How the hell did people
even find their way out here?
There were guides called conductors
who helped them.
And these quilts, they were a code
from the Station Master
telling them where he'd meet them.
- Look here, you see this tree?
- Yeah.
There it is, down there. The meeting place.
The Station Master would come get them
and take them to a hiding place
somewhere on this property
until it was safe to move on.
Well, some of the other land owners, they
found out what the Station Master
had been doing.
Well, they didn't like it very much.
So they did some
very unkind things to him.
They hurt him just for helping people?
They didn't see it that way, sweetie.
ANDY: What happened to Nell?
Did she make it up north?
Nell and Levi never arrived.
No one knows what happened to them.
HEIDI: I told you something bad
happened here.
No, it was a long time ago.
All that evil is over and done with now.
It's still here, Mama.
I can feel it. It's in the woods.
- It's coming for me.
- No, it's not.
Heidi...
It's all in your head.
- It's not real.
- But Mr. Gordy said...
There is no Mr. Gordy.
Heidi, listen to me. You have to fight this.
- You have to put it out of your head or...
- I'll be like you?
Dry off.
If you loved me, you'd believe me.
It's because I love you that I can't, baby.
I don't hear you getting out of that tub.
Heidi Wyrick, don't make me
come back in there.
Heidi, what is taking so long?
Heidi?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh, my God, Heidi! Oh, my God! Oh, God!
Okay, okay, okay!
Come on, baby! Cough it up!
(HEARTBEAT THUMPING)
LISA: Heidi!
(SCREAMS)
Lisa!
Heidi!
Andy.
What happened?
She was convulsing and unconscious.
And vomiting sawdust and insects?
- Andy.
- Are you on any medication, Mrs. Wyrick?
You didn't see what I saw. I saw her.
You weren't there.
Heidi.
- Do you remember any of this?
- Yeah, baby.
I didn't dry off like I was supposed to.
So Mama pulled me out of the tub real hard.
I'm sorry, that's not what happened.
I think they've been through
enough for tonight.
Come on.
Just tell me exactly what
we're supposed to do here.
If you want my advice,
I suggest you consult with a psychiatrist.
Or a priest.
Thanks.
- Andy...
- Let's let Heidi rest up a sec.
It's hard when people don't believe you.
Isn't it?
Really, Lisa?
We're possessed by the devil now?
Good Lord, people,
it's a blessing, not an exorcism.
Please.
Hi.
Lord, we pray this night
for the soul of an innocent child
and the banishment of evil from this land.
I want you to pray with me now.
Can you do that?
In the name of the Father
I ask for the cleansing of fear and sickness
from the mind and the soul of this child.
I ask that you fill Heidi with the warmth
of your love into her heart
and that you call upon your angels
to watch over her
and protect her from danger.
Mom and Dad, would you lean down
and lay her back for me, please?
In the name of the Son,
call upon your righteous hand
to rid this place of all evil
that may roam here.
(INDISTINCT WHISPERING)
WOMAN: Help us.
I ask that you bless this child
in the name of the Holy Ghost...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
The souls of the lost,
forsaken and forgotten,
and let your cleansing light
shine down upon this place
and upon this little girl now and forever.
Amen.
May God's love fill your heart, child,
and give you peace for all of your days.
Now that wasn't so bad, was it?
You did great.
(RADIO PLAYING STATIC)
(FOOTSTEPS)
(CREAKING)
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
(THUMPING)
Mama?
(PLAYS NOTE)
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Pastor sent you away.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
ANDY: Lisa!
(GASPS)
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
(SCREAMING)
- Andy.
- Heidi's gone.
- What?
(ANDY COCKING GUN)
Call the cops.
Heidi!
HEIDI: Daddy!
Daddy!
Heidi!
- Any sign of her yet?
- No.
Heidi!
- Daddy!
- Heidi!
- Help me!
- Where are you, baby?
Down in the hole!
What hole?
Down here!
Daddy!
Oh, my God.
Heidi.
I can't get out, Daddy. I can't get out.
Sit tight, Heidi. I gotta find
a way to get down there, baby.
No!
VOICES: Heidi.
Please!
Shit!
Please don't leave me
down here with them, Daddy!
With who, Heidi?
(CREAKING)
(GRUNTING)
ANDY: Heidi!
Mr. Gordy? Is that you?
- Daddy, help me!
- Coming!
Daddy!
Heidi!
MAN: Heidi.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Heidi.
Oh, my God.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
(GROWLING)
Heidi!
- Daddy, hurry!
- Heidi, heads up. Coming down.
Daddy, hurry!
Help!
Watch out.
Daddy!
I'm coming, baby!
Heidi!
Heidi?
- Daddy!
- Heidi!
Jesus.
How the hell did you get down here, baby?
What the hell?
This is where the Station Master hid them.
Unbelievable.
How the hell did you find this place, Heidi?
The girl showed me.
Is that the one that you said
was down here with you?
No.
I think something else
is down here, too, Daddy.
I don't want to be here anymore.
That makes two of us.
MALE NEWS REPORTER: Most Pine Mountain
residents know the story of the Station Master
who helped slaves escape to freedom
as part of the Underground Railroad.
But last night, a young local girl
uncovered a sad, unknown chapter
in the saga right in her own backyard.
What authorities believe
are the remains of five males...
FEMALE NEWS REPORTER:
...discovered in an underground chamber
beneath the ruins
of the Station Master's cabin.
Now, the Station Master,
also known as Jefferson Gordy
was the great-grandfather
of the late J.S. Gordy,
who died in 1978.
MALE REPORTER: For all the lives that were
saved by the Underground Railroad
there were also many folks
who didn't make it,
who just went missing.
And today's discovery is a tragic reminder
of how dangerous it really was.
In this particular case,
when the Station Master was murdered,
there was no one to let
the slaves out, who were waiting below...
Will you please turn it off?
...and they probably starved to death
down there.
Reporting live...
You think that's Mama Kay's family?
They said five males, so I doubt it.
Hey.
What are you doing up?
I don't want to live here anymore.
It's all right now, Heidi.
The things that we saw,
they've moved on.
Their spirits aren't trapped anymore
because of you.
Joyce, please. Spirits?
Don't you understand
what's happened here, Lisa?
Those people in the chamber
wanted to be found.
That's what this has all been about.
Now they're free,
and there's nothing to be afraid of anymore.
Mr. Gordy said it's not safe here.
You've seen Mr. Gordy tonight?
He said I shouldn't have
gone down in that hole.
He said I let something bad come out.
Okay, it is time for you to go back to bed.
Heidi Wyrick, you follow me right now.
We can't be here anymore, Mama.
I went in the hole and the bad man saw me.
He knows we're here now and he's coming.
What bad man, sweetie?
The Station Master.
- I let him out, Mama.
- Well, Mr. Gordy is wrong,
because you know very well
that the Station Master was a good man.
No, he wasn't.
Andy, will you please tell her
that there is nothing to be afraid of?
Mr. Gordy said there was money buried
in the garden, Lisa, and there was.
He said that
something terrible happened here. It did.
For something in Heidi's mind,
Mr. Gordy is sure as hell right a lot.
Are you telling me that suddenly
you believe all this?
I believe there was a cave
full of skeletons on our land, Lisa.
Is there a...
A "bad man" down there, too?
Hell if I know, but,
I say we pack up the truck
and we haul our asses outta here
before we find out.
Heidi.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
(LOUD ZAPPING)
LISA: Andy.
I mean, you can't be serious.
We don't have anywhere to go.
I mean, where are we...
Where are we gonna go?
Baby, I...
I'm sick.
- Heidi and I are sick...
- You're fine.
Heidi's fine.
Tell me something.
How the hell did Heidi get down
in that hole?
Even if she could lift that slab,
which she can't,
it's a 25-foot drop after that.
She didn't have a scratch on her.
Did you ever think that
maybe Joyce is right?
Crazy Joyce.
That this isn't some kind of disease,
but I don't know, it's...
A Sift?
You try seeing what I see
and you call it a gift.
I'm just saying maybe it is.
And I'm done letting you tell our daughter
that she's sick,
that she's got some mental disorder.
I love you, I do,
but...
I won't
let Heidi live like this.
You understand me?
- I won't do it.
- Andy, please.
Look, I have seen enough to know
that it ain't up here.
It's out there.
Maybe it's trying to tell us something.
Maybe you should try listening.
It's sure gonna be lonely here
without you guys.
You should leave, too. This is a bad place.
No, sweetie, it was a bad place.
Now it's not. Because of you.
- I'm gonna miss you, baby girl.
- Gonna miss you, too.
(INDISTINCT WHISPERING)
(DOG BARKING)
Hey, Chief. Come on, buddy.
Jump up.
Good boy.
Hey.
Chief!
Chief! Hey!
Where the hell's that damn dog going?
Daddy, we need to leave right now.
Without your mama?
Yeah, I'm not sure how she'd take that.
It's all right. Let me go find Chief.
Be right back. Stay here and lock the door.
Chief!
Chief! Here, boy!
(RADIO TURNS ON)
(PLAYING MUSIC)
VOICES ON RADIO: Heidi.
Lisa?
Hello?
Why are you here?
(GROWLING)
Heidi. Heidi!
Heidi!
(WHIMPERING FEARFULLY)
(RINGING)
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
(COUGHING)
(GAGGING)
(OLD TIME COUNTRY SONG PLAYING)
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
(MUSIC STOPS)
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Andy.
(SCREAMS)
Oh, my God.
(SHRIEKS)
Heidi!
Oh, God... No, no!
(SCREAMS)
Heidi!
- Heidi!
- Lisa!
Oh, Andy! Heidi's gone!
Check Joyce's. Check Joyce's!
Joyce!
Heidi!
Damn it!
Joyce!
Heidi!
(THUNDER CRACKING)
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Joyce!
Come on! Heidi!
Joyce, Heidi's missing!
(DISCONNECTED RECEIVER
SIGNAL BEEPING)
Joyce.
Joyce!
Let me in!
Oh, my God!
(GROWLING OVER TELEPHONE)
Joyce, Joyce, can you hear me, Joyce?
Joyce?
(COUGHING)
Joyce!
Joyce, please! Heidi's been taken.
Where is she?
Joyce!
With him.
"With him"?
Who's "him"?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Joyce, who's "him"?
(DOOR CREAKS)
No. Not tonight.
No.
Not tonight.
Lisa.
Don't.
Where's my little girl?
They know.
Who's "they," Joyce?
Tell me.
Who's "they"?
Go.
Okay.
Heidi?
Heidi!
ANDY: It's a trap.
The animals can get in,
but they can't get back out.
They get weak and starve. Easy pickings.
Then you get them back out through here.
The back door.
(DOOR CREAKS)
Oh, God!
Heidi?
Heidi, baby?
Are you in here?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
(SHRIEKING)
You remember Pastor Wells talking
about the Station Master?
Well, back when he owned all this land,
he was also what's called a taxidermist.
- Mama?
- Heidi!
Heidi, are you okay?
Are you okay? I'm here.
It's okay, just listen to me.
I'm gonna get you out of here. Okay?
- Mama?
- Okay.
Mama.
Okay.
Okay, hold on to me. Hold on.
VOICES: Help us.
Okay.
Help us!
Can you stand up?
Okay.
Okay. Careful.
Okay, put your head down.
Okay.
We're gonna climb, okay?
It's gonna be okay.
Okay, hold on right there.
Okay?
You can do it.
(GROWLING)
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
(SHRIEKS)
Heidi!
Andy!
(CREAKING)
Oh, my God.
MOTHER: Lisa.
Listen to me, Lisa.
Mama.
You have to let them in.
Help us.
Let them in.
You don't listen.
ANDY: Did you ever think that
maybe Joyce is right?
Maybe this isn't a disease,
but maybe it's a gift?
JOYCE: Those people in that chamber
wanted to be found.
That's what this has all been about.
Now they're free.
Because of you.
ANDY: If these pills ain't working,
we sure as hell shouldn't keep
paying for them.
They're working.
Just gets a little tricky
when they wear off, that's all.
Let them in.
(VOICES SINGING SLAVE SONG)
I'll be back for you.
LISA: You know very well that
the Station Master was a good man.
No, he wasn't.
MOTHER: I love you, Lisa.
PRENTISS: Nell and Levi never arrived.
No one knows what happened to them.
(PEOPLE HUMMING SLAVE SONG)
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
(SHRIEKS)
- Mama!
- Heidi!
Oh, my God, are you okay?
Are you okay?
Where's your daddy? Who pulled me out?
It's okay.
- It's okay.
ANDY: - Heidi!
Daddy!
Oh, thank God. Thank God!
- You all right? You all right?
- Yeah.
Mr. Gordy?
Goddamn it.
You know the tire's supposed to go
below the branch, right?
You know what? (SHUSHES)
I don't wanna hear it.
No, it's all right, Andy. Heidi's gonna love it.
Every girl wants her own
dirty rubber nest up a tree.
Nobody likes you!
This ain't over.
JOYCE: Do you think Mr. Gordy knew
what his granddaddy did?
Probably why he didn't want anybody
on his property.
He wanted the Station Master to be
remembered for the people that he saved,
not the ones he...
Kept.
JOYCE: I keep thinking
about Mama Kay's family.
LISA: Well, they are in a better place.
That much I do know.
(HEIDI GASPS)
(LAUGHING)