Are you hungry? Let's just wait for...
Why?
You think I'm stupid, don't you?
Where did you go again?
I didn't leave.
Liar! Don't lie to me! I was
calling here and no one answered!
I just bought...
Idiot! Stupid! Don't take me as a fool!
I know you have a lover in this
building! Admit it! You animal!
What?
Will you stop?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
You're too much! I thought it was
something else.
Why? Who else were you expecting?
- No one.
- No one? You were expecting someone, eh?
No one really. That's why I was surprised.
You've been here two weeks and
you're not done fixing it up yet?
Lack of money.
Then borrow from our bank.
My boss is easy to talk to.
Or agree to my moving in
and I'll share my salary.
Who will take care of
your younger siblings?
Let's not complicate things. I all ready
argued with my mom about this.
Isn't she proud? Her only child is so
independent, he bought his own unit.
She says it's wrong. My savings, even
the money dad left went to this.
Show her it's the right decision.
That's why. Now I'll just make do.
Daddy's coming back next week.
I'll tell him I'm staying here.
I wish it was that easy.
You know, let's plan this.
Okay. Let's just take our time.
Oh, well. Just tell me when you're free.
What's this? You'll have to change
this bed too, okay?
I wonder who last slept here?
.Why?
- It's ugly-
- It's beautiful!
- It's ugly.
And it's free.
You know, you...you, meddler.
Ouch! I think my vein split.
Stop it! Someone might complain
because we're always noisy.
So, now what? You're in unit nine?
Yep. Seventh floor unit nine.
You should have gotten a unit on the
seventh floor. So it's lucky 777.
I think what's lucky is 888.
Try looking, so we'll know.
I can't sleep, it's too noisy!
The noises don't stop.
I keep complaining to the admin.
I look like a fool.
There's no guard to talk to.
The caretaker's always drunk. Shit!
I'll complain about you to the admin.
Don't mess around.
I'm going to eat.
Hi!
Hello!
(Screams)
(Angry man yelling)
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
You look like you haven't slept yet.
Who did you dream about last night?
No, man. It's just really noisy
where I moved.
Who's there?
Help us.
Who's there and what do you need?
Help us, please.
I don't want trouble.
Have pity on us.
Maybe the child can stay here for a
while. I want her to be safe.
Your husband might get angry.
Please...
When he beats me, he also
beats her.
My husband's about to come home.
Maybe she can
stay here when there's
trouble in our place.
What if he looks for her?
The building's big,
there's many places to hide in.
I'll say she's playing.
Please.
It's really just for a short while.
Until what time?
I'll get her after
my husband falls asleep.
Please.
She's nice. Quiet.
Has she eaten?
Lara. Her name's Lara. I'm Anna.
Jude.
We've eaten. Thank you very, very
much, Jude.
Go, go.
What are you doing here?
I'm just looking for Lara.
Where's the child?
I know you have a lover
in this building!
Lara. ls your name Lara?
You're going to escape, aren't you?
Are you fooling me?
You're using the child
for your foolishness!
Stop it, Bert. I was just
looking for Lara.
Lara, this is just a game, okay?
Hide and seek.
You can come out from there.
They can't reach you here. Your dad
won't know you're here.
Are you lying to me? Are you fooling me?
(Woman screaming)
(Gun shot)
Lara, come out here. You want to eat?
Lara, where are you going? Lara, wait!
What's a little noise?
It's too noisy.
The fighting is too much.
Don't mind it. Sit down.
I'm not getting my money's worth
here, Dante.
Won't the building's
management intervene?
Don't meddle, and no one will
meddle with you.
Just drink.
That's why a lot of tenants leave.
It looks like I got a bad deal here, Dante.
A bad deal? You got
the unit very cheap.
It's better that there's
only a few tenants. More privacy.
There's privacy, but no security.
There's fewer of you,
less association dues.
We can't afford overnight security.
I'm here!
Go, go, go! Go up!
Just think you're not hearing anything.
Man, why do you always lack sleep?
Hey, Marvin!
Sorry. What?
I was asking why you
always lack sleep.
Yes, just getting used to the house.
I can't sleep in the apartment.
Is it noisy again?
Yes.
Aside from that...
And my dreams are weird.
Man, even I would be afraid. That place
is scary. Maybe it's haunted?
I don't know. Maybe not.
What if it is?
I don't believe in ghosts.
Man, who's that behind you?
Asshole, don't joke like that.
Man, this is okay.
What's with you? You scared me.
You surprised me.
Just wanted to kiss you.
Your door was open.
I locked it...or didn't I?
Obviously, you didn't.
Wait, what's your problem? Why are
you becoming forgetful?
Nothing, just lack of sleep. I was
fixing things up last night.
Anyway, get dressed. Let's go out.
- Where are we going?
- Just get dressed. Come on.
Let's go, get up!
Daddy's best friend is a lawyer.
We can demand that your payment for
your unit be refunded.
Just look for another place.
You're becoming a nag.
I all ready like my unit.
It's just noisy sometimes.
You're the one who's complaining.
I just said it's noisy
and you're insulting me.
What insult? Who's insulting you?
You're criticizing my unit!
Did I say anything like that?
Isn't that the same?
You know, Marvin, there should be a
voice recorder whenever we talk.
You assume a lot of things.
I'm just saying I like my unit.
Pinky!
Marvin, let's just talk when
your mind is clear.
Don't go out from there until I pick
you up, okay?
Don't be sad. This will also end.
Let's go! You be nice, okay?
Don't move around too much.
It's better if you don't just play when
you're there. Sleep too, okay?
Don't be afraid of Uncle Jude. He's nice.
Smile. There you go!
Maybe she can stay here again?
Yes.
Baby, go in.
Thank you very much.
Why don't you leave him?
My husband's a policeman
with many connections.
This will be the last time.
I'm sorry. But I'm getting nervous.
Can you bring her to
another unit next time?
I should be the one saying sorry to you.
Don't worry, next time I'll bring Lara
to the next unit.
Go, go!
How long since you finished
that doll house?
You want to live here? Don't go back
to your house anymore.
Let's play hide and seek!
I'll be the seeker.
(Gun shot)
Lara, where are you going? Wait!
Lara!
Don't go there! It's dangerous!
Bert. Bert, that's enough.
You're just drunk.
- Come here! Are you hungry?
- Me? Drunk? No!
- I'm not hungry.
- Let's just rest.
- You want this? You want this?
- No! No!
- You want this?
- No! No! Bert!
Let's sleep. Why don't you rest?
Come, rest! Or maybe you're hungry?
Stupid! You, too!
Bert! Don't mind her! Don't!
Bert! Bert!
- Mom!
It's Pinky!
- Hasn't she come down yet?
- I don't think she went to work.
Why don't you make up?
She doesn't answer my texts
and calls. Bye.
Up? Up?
Did Pinky call?
No, sir. I've been here
since lunch, no calls.
You're just here.
That's why you don't want
me to move in, huh?
What?
Your woman's waiting for you.
Don't be silly.
I'm silly?
You came here to fight with me?
There was a woman outside earlier,
waiting for you.
Long-haired.
Maybe it's the woman next door who's
always knocking.
Why would she knock?
There's a couple in the other unit who
is always fighting.
Sometimes the woman comes around,
knocking at the apartments.
Asking for help.
Are you pulling my leg?
That's the noise I've been
telling you about.
I ignore her even when
she keeps knocking.
Pinky, please.
Sorry, okay?
Sorry I was short-tempered.
That's all right, okay?
Don't interfere with them.
If she insists, call the caretaker.
Sorry.
Sorry too.
- I'll bring you home.
- No, I brought daddy's car.
- I'll walk you down.
- No, you didn't even close your door.
Okay, you take care.
You take more care, there's a
woman who's always knocking.
I don't want to be beaten up
by a policeman.
I'll go ahead. Bye.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
This elevator is probably
older than me.
They say older is safer.
The elevator's big,
there's lots of space.
What about the blood I saw on her head?
Ketchup. Maybe it's ketchup.
Ketchup? Why would the child put
ketchup on her head? Are you silly?
Come on, Pinky.
Don't mind it, okay?
Oh my, I don't know any more.
I know what I saw.
Why would I make up a story?
Don't mind it. That child is naughty.
She likes to play.
Hide and seek. She always appears
out of nowhere.
Okay.
Let's just talk again later.
- Yes, love you. - Okay, love you. Bye.
Has your husband left?
He already left. This will be the
last time. Help us escape.
I'm feeling brave now.
You're the only one I can trust.
I don't know anyone in Manila.
I have no one else to turn to.
Where will you go?
Maybe you know a place where we
can hide. Anywhere.
I can't take it anymore. He fired the
gun the last time.
I don't know what will happen next.
Have pity, please.
This will be the last time.
Okay, let's see tomorrow. Just knock
when it's safe.
As soon as he leaves.
Thank you, thank you.
I'll just knock, okay?
It's too much! My neighbor makes
noise every night.
The wife gets beaten up every night.
Did you see them, man?
Even if I don't see them,
I hear the shouts.
Cool!
Poor woman.
What do the neighbors say?
I don't know.
Some have already left.
Why don't you move?
Can't. I all ready bought the unit.
Why don't you sell it?
It's not that simple.
Why don't you report it?
To whom? I told you our
caretaker's a drunkard.
Report it to the police.
Can't. The husband's a policeman.
Shit, man. Don't meddle.
Mind your own business.
Pitiful mother and child.
- Why are we here?
- I'll just show you the condo unit.
Who said I was looking for a condo?
Just take a look. You might like it.
It's just an option.
I don't have money to get another.
I'll share. Marvin, this is for us.
It's new.
What do you think of the one I got?
You're the one who said it was
noisy and unsafe, right?
You can't make me move. Neither you
nor mommy can convince me. Let's go.
Okay.
That's a lot. Who's going
to eat that, man?
I'm sorry?
How many times have you visited Anna?
Sir?
I've had it. You're seeing my wife?
You plan to steal her from me?
You're brave, huh?
I don't want trouble, sir.
I don't want trouble, too.
But my wife is stupid!
She'll go with any man!
She goes to you, doesn't she?
Every night? When I'm not here!
Sir, that's not true, sir.
That's why I don't like the child.
My hunch is that she's not even mine.
Is Lara your child?
Sir, I'm just new here, sir.
That child doesn't look like me.
You look like her, hmm?
Hey! This isn't your floor!
I have eyes everywhere!
You can't escape!
I'll kill them both! And I'll
include you, asshole!
- What are you doing outside?
- Bert, I'm just looking for Lara.
- You're going to escape?
- It's not like that.
- Where's the kid?
- She went out.
Are you lying to me?
- You're using the child for your
foolishness, aren't you?
Stop it, Bert.
Are you lying to me? Are you
making a fool of me?
I was just looking for Lara.
You fool! You idiot! Don't make
me look stupid!
You have a lover in this building!
Admit it, you animal!
Jude! Jude! Jude!...
Open the door! Jude, have pity on us!
Open the door! Jude!
Jude! Jude!
They're making noises again.
She's knocking on my door!
Have pity on me and Lara!
Jude!
Jude! Jude! Please!
Jude, please!
Have pity on me and Lara!
Jude, open the door!
Jude! Jude!
Jude! Jude! Jude, please! Jude!...
Jude, open the door!
Come here!
Come here.
Jude, open the door! Jude...
- What is my unit number, Dante?
- Unit 6! 7th floor, unit 6! Why?
(Gun shot)
- She needs help!
- I said that's foolishness!
The problem with you is
you're hard to talk to.
What, crazy?
There's nothing there!
What do you mean, nothing?
There are no people here, Marvin.
There's no one here!
But I saw them, Dante! I really did!
Marvin, you're the only one who lives here
on the 7th floor.
It's been a long time
since anyone lived here.
The last tenant left last week.
It's been three years.
That's where Anna lived.
Her husband Bert was a policeman,
very possessive.
Their daughter was Lara.
The couple fought every night. The wife
was beaten up, so was the kid.
Bert thought Anna had a lover here.
He thought Lara wasn't his child.
Bert was drunk every night. And there
was a fight every night.
Things got worse.
One night, they chased each
other down the hall.
She asked help from Jude,
another tenant.
Jude, open the door!
He didn't help her.
Bert chased her until they reached
the elevator. He reached her.
She was dragged down the hallway.
She was hit many so times.
Her skull was bashed in.
(Lara crying)
The child was chased into the elevator.
Her skull was also crushed.
Mother and child were dead.
That's where he lived. Jude,
whom Anna asked help.
Exactly where your apartment is.
But the gunshot earlier.
You heard it too, right?
I can hear all the noises you hear
when I'm downstairs or here.
It repeats. Every night.
That' why I just drink.
The husband committed suicide.
He shot himself in the mouth.
That's what we heard earlier.
(Gun shot)
Where's the man she asked help from?
He left right after the investigation.
What will I do, Dante?
Don't meddle.
Give yourself courage.
He should have helped her.
He should have opened the door.
Then his skull would have
been crushed too!
What? You thought you could
make a fool of me?
Where are you going?
You thought I didn't know? Admit it!
It's just noise. It happened,
it's finished.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Don't meddle!
Jude! Jude! Open the door!...
-No one lives here, no one lives here.
They're not here anymore. - Jude!
Jude, please!
No one's here.
I'm the only one who lives here.
There's no one else here.
They're not here anymore,
they're not here anymore.
There's no one else here.
No one else lives here.
What's your problem, Marvin?
Are you sick?
No, Ma. I'm okay.
May I sleep here?
May I sleep here? This is still your
home, remember.
Why do you look so tired?
It's nothing. I haven't slept because
I've been fixing the apartment.
Cleaning. Painting.
You don't need paint here.
Ma, let's not start. Okay?
Paint is poisonous. Do you have a mask?
Is my room still okay, Ma?
Just like before. Like you never left it.
- I'll stay here for a few days.
- Even a few years is okay with me.
Ma, please.
I can hear you.
Sorry, Ma.
Marvin, I know you haven't eaten.
Thanks, Ma.
Okay. Just leave it outside when you're
finished, okay?
Okay, Ma.
Marvin?
Are you here?
Why aren't you answering your phone?
Are you okay?
Marvin!
What happened to you?
Did your dad find out
about our plans? Asshole!
Marvin, daddy doesn't have
anything to do with this.
Marvin, let's go! He might
think you did this to me.
What happened?
It's hard to explain. Let's just go.
Tell me!
It's impossible but it did happen.
Let's leave.
Are you okay?
Tell me, Pinky.
Please!
I went to your apartment.
It was open but you weren't there.
I thought you went to that other girl.
Pinky, really!
I went to their unit.
I went inside.
What are we going to do?
Let's not talk about it now.
I just want to forget for a while.
I feel like they're following us.
That's impossible.
Marvin, the impossible already happened.
Pinky, please don't imagine things.
Marvin, I'm not imagining this!
Just think they're not real.
That they're gone.
They're gone.
Marvin, Why?
Nothing. Let's go.
Let's go.
(Laughing at the movie)
I'll just go to the comfort room.
Babe, excuse me.
Wash your hands.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Someone's here.
Someone's here!
(Pinky screams...)
Let's not be beaten.
They're not going to leave us alone.
They're not going to let us go.
Don't be afraid.
What do they need from us?
We don't know them, right?
How come? What do they need from us?
I don't know!
What do they need?
I don't know.
This has to stop.
How?
Fear is what will kill us.
We can't be afraid.
How will we fight them? They're
already dead, right?
I won't let them control my life.
You're being affected. They hurt you,
Pinky!
You're taking me home?
We'll explain everything to your dad.
And then?
I have to finish this now.
Marvin, what are you talking about?
Let's talk to your dad, Pinky.
Please!
Leave now or I'll call the police!
Understand!
Don't show your face here, ever!
Don't even attempt
to be a kilometer near Pinky.
Dad, please.
Leave now!
Dad!
Marvin, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, Marvin.
Dad!
Pinky.
I love you.
Sorry, sir.
Ma'am.
I'm sorry for what happened.
- Marvin, no!
- You don't have to be part of this!
Marvin!
I'm going to finish this.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Jude! Help us! Jude!
Open the door, Jude!
Open the door. Help Us.
(Angry man's voice)
Are you making a fool of me?
You're using the kid for your
foolishness!
Are you cheating on me?
(Woman pleading for help)
Jude Help Us! Jude!
Jude, open the door! Have pity on us!
Jude Help us!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Didn't I tell you not to meddle? What?
Sir.
Have pity...
What? You still want to?
Your boyfriend's crying.
(Lara crying)
Get in! Get in!
Don't come in here!
I'm just going to hit her, bro.
Leave the child alone. Don't
come in here anymore.
I'm just going to hit her!
I haven't started!
Anna, do you know how to use that?
Go ahead. Fire it!
(Gun shot)
Dead!
It's over.
Marvin!
Marvin, are you okay?
Marvin, I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.