Subtitles by explosiveskull
- Nice watch.
- Thanks.
What's
the water resistance?
200 meters.
And it's
got a date display?
Yes, it does.
I might have
gone for a metal strap
- instead of a leather strap.
- Really?
Yes.
I think I'd prefer
a metal strap.
I've had this one for years.
It's as good as new.
- What's the water resistance?
- 100 meters.
- How long have you had it?
- Nine years.
A little bored of it, actually.
I've been thinking
of getting a new one
for quite a while now.
Okay,
this is what we'll do.
We'll go to the place
where I bought mine.
If I tell them you're
a colleague, a friend,
they'll definitely
give you a discount.
Both the owner and his father
have been patients of mine
so I know them quite well.
Think about it.
- Hi.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Did you eat?
I just
had some apple pie.
Do you mind if I go grab
something to eat before we go?
- I'm starving.
- Sure, no problem.
Are you sure you
don't want anything?
- Chicken wings or...
- No, thanks, I'm fine.
Do you have money,
I can give you some.
No, I've
got money, thanks.
I'll be right back.
- Did you get a haircut?
- Do you like it?
Looks great.
Aren't you going
to eat your fries?
I'm saving them till last.
Why?
I really like fries.
I always save them for last.
I do that too.
Sorry I was
late today, Steven.
It doesn't matter.
I was over
at a friend's house.
He got a new motorcycle,
I wanted to check it out.
He took me for a ride,
that's why I was late.
It's fine.
He even let me
ride it for a little bit.
I hope you
were wearing helmets.
Yeah,
of course we were.
We weren't going
very fast anyway.
I got you a present.
Thank you very much.
What is it?
It's very nice.
Can I give you a hug?
Thank you very much.
That's fantastic.
It's water
resistant up to 200 meters.
Does this come off?
I prefer a leather strap.
It comes off, yes.
You can put on any
strap you like.
But metal are more hard-wearing,
that's why I got
you the metal strap.
It's more expensive, too.
Dad?
If Kim goes to the
party, can I go with her?
I don't
know, darling.
Your mother and I will
discuss it and we'll see.
I'd say they can go.
Claire is a very nice girl.
She's the girl you met at
the mall with her parents,
who asked about
becoming a doctor.
She's the one who wants
to be a cardiologist.
Yes, I remember.
How was work today?
Fine.
How about you?
I've decided to make
some changes at the clinic.
I think I'm going to get it
painted and buy a new couch.
Look at you, all
hunched over like that.
How many times do
I have to tell you?
You'll strain your back.
Your hair is Practically
trailing in your food.
Bob, you promised
me you'd get a haircut
and you still haven't done it.
- I'll get a haircut.
- Tomorrow.
Not tomorrow, Dad.
After the party.
I like his hair long.
He has lovely hair.
- What about mine?
- You have lovely hair, too.
We all have lovely hair.
I bought that dress
that you liked.
I'll wear it for you tomorrow.
I can't show it to you
now, it needed alterations.
I'm picking it up tomorrow.
The black one?
It was the black one
you liked, wasn't it?
Yes.
The other one looked
great on you, too.
But I think the black
one was perfect.
I'm worried
it's a little too short.
I'd like it better if
it were below the knee.
You look amazing, however
long or short the dress is.
Tomorrow I'm gonna
bake a lemon cake
and nobody's gonna
eat any of it but you.
- Not even the kids?
- Not even the kids.
Poor kids.
Did I tell you
Bob announced the other day
that he wants to be
an ophthalmologist?
Yes, you did.
Bob would be a coal miner
if you were one too.
Could you turn on some
more light, please?
General anesthetic?
General anesthetic.
How's that?
Perfect.
Hi.
Look, I told you, best not
to come to the hospital
- without calling me first.
- I know, you're right.
I'm sorry.
I just wanted to
thank you again.
And to show you my new
strap I got for my watch.
I exchanged the metal
strap for a leather one.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to put you
in this awkward position.
Goodbye.
Martin.
Come here.
What kind of strap did you get?
- Brown leather.
- Show me.
- It's very nice.
- You think so?
Or are you just saying that?
I really like it.
Next time you want to come
here, please call me first.
You have my number.
It's for your own good.
I might be with a patient or
in surgery, or in a meeting.
There's no point in you waiting
around if I can't see you.
It's for your own good.
- Good morning.
- Good morning, Steven.
I have those test results.
Shall I leave them on your desk?
Please do, yeah, I'll take
a look at them in a minute.
- Great.
- We've got the same watch.
Let me introduce you.
This young man
is one of my
daughter's schoolmates.
I ran into Martin and his
parents at the mall last week.
He told me he's very
interested in medicine.
He wants to be cardiologist.
Ah.
I suggested he
stop by sometime.
So he can see what being
a doctor's really about.
Martin, this is Matthew,
great friend of mine.
And an excellent
anesthesiologist.
That's great.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
Let me know when you're ready.
I've got to go back in now.
We'll talk on the phone to
arrange our next meeting.
- Alright?
- Okay.
Goodbye.
I think your
breathing's really improved
over the last three months.
That's what the
choir director said, too.
Did you tell her to
move you closer to the front?
Yes, I did.
She said she'd see
what she can do.
Bob, did
you water the plants?
Mum said she
would water them.
Your mother
works very hard.
That's why we said
it would be nice
to help out all that we can.
And we agreed that Kim would
take care of walking the dog.
And you would take
care of the plants.
How about I walk the
dog and Kim can do the plants?
You're too young to be
wandering around at night
by yourself.
- Thanks for the brush.
- You're welcome.
We have to go.
Tell Bob
to water the plants
now that the sun has gone down.
I watered them already.
Come on, we're gonna be late.
Goodnight, darling.
A full 40 years have passed
since the German cardiologist
Andreas Gruentzig performed
the first coronary angioplasty,
on September 16th, 1977.
Today, that first patient
is still alive and well.
Doctor Gruentzig, however,
had an unfortunate accident
and met with an untimely end.
In short, he is one of those
rare cases where we can say,
the operation was a
success, but unfortunately
the doctor didn't make it.
In the four decades
that have passed
since that first
coronary angioplasty,
many things have changed.
A new wave of techniques
and scientific breakthroughs
have brought us
- minimally invasive...
- I'm going for a cigarette.
- I'll be in the bar.
- Okay.
Endovascular
aortic surgery,
and new treatments
for heart failure
that include stem cell therapy,
left ventricular remodeling,
and by all indications
the rapidly expanding use of
mechanical circulatory support.
The guy that
made it told me what was in it.
And now I can't remember now
but it is very refreshing.
- Would you like one?
- No, thank you.
Try it,
it's really delicious.
You can use this straw,
I haven't touched it.
He hasn't had a
drink in three years.
High GGTs, elevated
transaminases.
Oh, good
on you for not drinking.
Well I wouldn't say no to a
cocktail if you're offering.
Of course,
I'll get you one right away.
We should go soon.
- Yeah.
- It's early.
He's got surgery
in the morning.
He needs to get some sleep.
It's still early.
We've have got
surgery in the morning.
Fine, okay.
How are the kids?
They're doing very well.
Bob has started piano lessons.
The teacher says
he's very talented.
Now we have to get him one
so he can practice at home.
I just haven't gotten
around to it yet.
I'm renovating the clinic.
I'm on the phone all day.
Our daughter started
menstruating last week.
- Great.
- Yes.
She was a little scared
but she's okay now.
You haven't seen her in ages.
Not since last summer
at the school choir.
Recital.
You and Mary should come
over one night for dinner.
You really shouldn't
stay late, either.
Drink that cocktail you've
ordered, get yourself home.
You've gotta be at the
hospital in six hours.
- Time to go, darling.
- Yes.
- Goodnight.
- Goodnight, Matthew.
- It was a good night.
- I think so.
Do you
have many friends?
Not that many.
I don't think people can
have a lot of friends.
I mean, it's difficult.
The most important thing in life
is to have good friends,
not lots of friends.
That's what my dad used to say.
Your father was
absolutely right.
Yes, I know.
I have a very good friend who
plays basketball in school.
Sometimes we play it together.
I also consider my
mom to be a friend.
I know it might sound strange,
but ever since my father died,
we've been very
close, me and my mom.
We talk about things,
lots of things.
And she helps me as much as
she can with a lot of stuff.
I help her, too.
I'd like to ask you a favor.
Only if you want to, of course.
I don't want you to feel
pressured or obliged.
It just seemed to me like a
good idea, so I thought I'd ask.
I'd like you to come
by my house one day.
To meet my wife and children.
I think you'll get along great.
What do you think?
Good afternoon,
you must be Martin.
That's right.
- You must be Anna.
- That's right.
These
flowers are for you.
Your husband told me
you like orchids but
I couldn't find any fresh cut
ones so I brought you roses.
How do you like roses?
Thank you very much,
Martin, I love roses.
That's very kind of you.
Come on in.
Steven is waiting
for you in the yard.
- This is Bob.
- Very nice to meet you.
And this is Kim.
Very
nice to meet you.
I brought you some little gifts.
That's
very kind of you.
It's a key ring with a
musical note on it for Kim,
because I know she likes music.
And one with a
smiley face for Bob.
What do we say, Bob?
Thanks.
How lovely.
Well, we should probably eat.
Are you hungry, Martin?
I'm starving.
How long have you been
in the choir, Kim?
Two years, since I was 12.
Do you like singing?
I love it but I
haven't got a very good voice.
- How old are you?
- 16.
Have you got
hair under your arms yet?
Yes.
I just got my first period.
Do you mind if I
light a cigarette?
- You'd better not.
- It's alright.
Just go over by the window.
Can you
sing us something?
What, now?
Yes, anything you like.
No, not right now.
She's embarrassed.
No I'm not.
Just don't feel like it.
When did you start smoking?
About eight months ago.
I was over at a friend's place.
It was a party, actually.
And this girl offered
me a cigarette
and I said why not and lit up.
That was a mistake, I regret it.
But it's too late
now, I'm addicted.
Can you show me
the hair under your arms?
Sure.
You haven't got that much.
Have you seen how
hairy my dad is?
No.
He's got three
times more hair than you do.
You've got a great body.
Thanks.
Do you wanna go out for a walk?
It's a nice day.
I'd rather stay
here and listen to music.
Is that my MP3
player or yours?
Mine.
And don't you dare take
this one and lose it too.
What kind of music
do you listen to?
All kinds.
I'm into metal and punk.
What about you?
I think it's worth listening
to all kinds of music.
Depends on my mood
and what I'm doing.
I'll come for a walk
with you if you want.
We can take the dog with
us if you don't mind.
I'd prefer if it was
just the two of us.
I get nervous around dogs
in case they get into a
fight with another dog.
The idea of separating
dogs fighting scares me.
♪ We
♪ We don't have to
worry about nothing
♪ 'Cause we got the fire
♪ And we're burning
one hell of a somethin'
♪ They
♪ They're gonna see
us from outer space
♪ Outer space
♪ Light it up
♪ Like we're the source
of the human race
♪ Human race
♪ When the lights started out
♪ They don't know
what they heard
♪ Strike the match, play it loud
♪ Giving love to the world
♪ We'll be raising our hands
♪ Shining up to the sky
♪ 'Cause we got the
fire, fire, fire
♪ Yeah, we got the
♪ And we're gonna let it
burn, burn, burn, burn
♪ We're gonna let it
♪ We can light it up, up, up
♪ So they can put
it out, out, out
Is this homemade lemonade?
- Yes.
- It's amazing.
My mom makes lemonade, too.
She hasn't made it
in a while, though.
I'll ask her to make some.
I love lemonade.
I'd like
to meet your mother.
And we can have a
lemonade contest.
She'd like that.
The kids' rooms are
amazing, so big and bright.
You're welcome to spend
the night if you want.
We can easily fit a mattress
on the floor next to Bob's bed.
You two can hang
out in the morning
and I'll drop you home
tomorrow afternoon.
Thank you very much
but I'd rather not.
I gotta get home tonight.
I don't like leaving
my mom by herself.
Whatever you want.
Where did you two go?
Just for a walk.
I love
this neighborhood.
So quiet, clean, beautiful.
Where do you live, Martin?
We live in a
not-so-nice neighborhood
in a not-so-nice house.
Up north.
What a charming boy.
Isn't he?
Yes, very.
How did his father die?
Car
crash, driving home.
Smashed into a pole,
killed instantly.
How long have you known him?
Quite some time.
He was a patient
of mine, years ago.
- Did you go to the funeral?
- I did go, yes.
Why didn't
I go with you?
I think
I told you about it
but you were busy or something.
You should tell
him to come round again.
I will, he'll
be great company for Bob.
I thought next time I could
take both of them out somewhere,
for a bike ride.
You should get that,
it could be the hospital.
Hello?
Hello, how are you?
I'm fine, Martin.
Is something wrong?
No, I just
called to tell you
I had a wonderful time today.
I'm very pleased to hear that.
Yes, I thought
I should return the favor.
So I'd like to invite you
to dinner, at my house.
My mom will be
delighted to see you.
She hasn't seen you in two
years, not since the hospital.
She'll make meatloaf.
That's very kind of you.
- We'll do that someday.
- Tomorrow night.
I told her already.
I've asked her to make
meatloaf and lemonade.
I'll be home by 6:30.
Around 7:30?
Did you come
by the hospital today?
No.
I was in school and
then I went to the gym.
Weren't you down at
the hospital today?
I was, but
I was really busy.
I just wondered whether you
came by and couldn't find me.
I thought we could
all watch a movie together.
If you don't mind.
I'd like
to watch a movie.
I'm sorry, I have
to be getting home soon.
I can't be out too late.
I didn't tell my wife
I'd be late tonight
and she might get worried.
You could call her.
Anyway, if you feel tired,
you could stop the movie.
Could go home and we
could watch the rest
next time you come.
Please, it's my
favorite movie.
It was also my father's
favorite movie too.
Special today is
blueberry waffles.
Why are
you telling me this?
Because I
want you to believe in me.
You're not a god, you
can take my word for it.
This is 12 years of
Catholic school talking.
I could come back
if you're not ready.
How do
you know I'm not a god?
- Oh...
- I think I'll go to bed.
I'm sorry I can't watch the
rest of the movie with you.
Goodnight.
Goodnight, Martin.
Groundhog,
legend has it he can predict
the coming of an early spring.
So I guess the question we have
to ask ourselves today is...
Have you
been married long?
16 years.
You
have lovely hands.
Thank you.
Most doctors
have beautiful hands.
So white and soft and clean.
- Really?
- Yes.
I remember your hands from back
when I used to visit my
husband at the hospital.
In fact, I even told
him about your hands.
And he agreed.
"You're right", he said.
"He has beautiful hands."
Thank you very much.
Do you remember me
coming to the hospital?
Of course.
I was a little heavier
then and my hair was brown.
Yes.
I got tired of it.
I dyed it about a month ago.
Did you prefer me
with brown hair?
Like it was back then?
I think it's nicer now.
Yes, I agree.
Would you like some dessert?
I made a caramel tart.
- No, thank you.
- Maybe later then.
You did have a lot to eat.
Can I take a closer
look at your hands?
Don't worry, he's
definitely asleep.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
In any case, he wants
this as much as I do.
I have to go.
I'm sorry if I made you feel
awkward, I didn't mean to.
But I won't let you leave
until you've tried my tart.
Please, I'll get
you a piece now.
Please, sit down.
I'm sorry, I
really have to go.
Goodnight.
Good morning.
What
are you doing here?
Why aren't you in school?
My heart aches.
What do you mean?
I'm in pain.
My chest, it hurts.
My heart.
I'm worried.
There's no need for
you to be worried.
I'm worried because
it's hereditary.
You're too
young to be worried.
That's what you
said about my father.
He didn't smoke.
He ate a very healthy diet.
He went swimming
almost every day.
He should have come out of that
surgery alive, but he died.
I smoke.
I started smoking recently.
It hurts here.
I hardly slept at
all last night.
My mom was so worried,
I slept in her bed.
If I had hair on
my chest and belly,
how would you attach these?
We'd shave the hair off first.
How long does it take
for the hair to grow back?
I don't know.
About a month, I suppose.
Your son told me that
you've got lots of hair
under your arms.
Three times more than I do.
And that you've got
a very hairy back
and a very hairy belly.
I probably do have a
little more hair than you do
because I'm older than you.
But soon you'll
have more hair, too.
It's all down to hormones.
Can you show me, please?
Can you take off your
shirt and show me, please?
Please.
Okay, you do have
more hair than I do
but not three times more.
Me and my mom thought
it would be nice
if you came by for
dinner tonight.
We could watch the
rest of the movie.
Does eight sound good for you?
That's very kind of you but
I just can't make it tonight.
I need to be at home.
Can't you get
away for a couple of hours?
I can't.
No.
Some other time.
My mom's gonna be upset.
Can I tell you a secret?
But don't tell her I told you.
I think she, I
think she likes you.
I mean, she's attracted to you.
But she says that's not
true, but it is, I'm sure.
And, to be honest, I think
you're perfect for each other.
You'd make a great couple.
She's got a great body.
You've seen it for yourself.
She lost weight and she
has a really great figure.
Your mother is very beautiful,
but the idea that she and
I could ever be together
is ludicrous.
Let me remind you,
I'm a married man.
And I love my wife
very much and my kids,
and that we are
very happy together.
And for your information,
you're absolutely fine.
There's nothing wrong with you.
But you really
should stop smoking.
Do you promise?
So we're okay?
There is nothing wrong with me?
You couldn't be healthier.
You should really go now
because I'm late for my rounds.
Don't use
that knife, here.
Use this one, it's much sharper.
There you go, doctor.
Thank you, nurse.
Oh, and don't forget
to slice off the cheeks.
- They're delicious.
- I can do that.
Where are you?
I called you 100 times,
didn't you see my calls?
Yeah, I'm here.
What do you mean you can't?
I got you a slice of apple pie.
No, no, you have to.
I've been, I've been waiting
for over a half an hour.
Just come for a little while.
I can come closer
to where you are.
Are you at the hospital?
I can bring you the apple pie.
What's, what's so important?
Is it a, is it an operation?
Are you at the hospital?
I love the
sound of those cooking.
Where were you?
I was
inside, making a call.
The fish
is almost ready.
Pass me your plate.
I'll get them.
I need to wash my hands anyway.
Thank you, my dear.
Do you need a hand?
No, that's okay.
I forgot to tell you, I
saw that boy yesterday.
Your daughter's schoolmate.
Martin?
Yes, right, Martin.
Couldn't remember his name.
- Where did you see him?
- At the hospital.
He was hanging around your car.
It looked like he
was waiting for you.
I tried to say hello but
he pretended not to see me.
That's impossible.
Can't have been him.
I could be wrong but
it looked a lot like him.
Take my piece off
the grill, will you?
I don't like it overdone.
Hi, Dad.
Hello, darling.
Where have you been?
Choir practice.
- Have you eaten?
- Yes, I ate earlier.
You don't have
to take the dog for a walk.
I took her out already, I
got back a little while ago.
Okay.
Dad, do you know
who I saw today?
- Who, darling?
- Martin.
Martin who?
Martin, that boy who came
over here the other day.
The son of your ex-patient.
He brought me back
from choir practice
on his friend's motorcycle.
He's really funny.
I laughed so hard my ribs hurt.
Yes, he is very funny.
Kim, I don't want you
riding on motorcycles
without a helmet.
I was wearing a
helmet, he gave me his.
Why didn't
you ask him to come in?
I did but he was in a hurry.
He had to get home.
Where's Mom?
She's
taking a shower.
Is there something you need?
I'm going to bed.
Goodnight, darling.
Did you wake Bob?
I did.
He just likes lying in bed
before getting up, leave him be.
You want me to squeeze you
some more orange juice?
He'll be late.
Have you seen the time?
School bus will be
here any minute.
Robert, do you have any
idea what time it is?
Get up and get dressed.
I can't get up.
You have 10
minutes to get washed,
dressed and eat your breakfast.
I'm not going to
drive you to school
and neither is your mother.
I can't get up.
Bob, get
up and get dressed
and stop messing around.
Dad.
My legs.
They're numb.
I can't move them.
I can't stand up.
Do you know
where you are right now?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I'm at the hospital,
the neurology department.
You're
absolutely right.
Can you tell me what
day it is today?
Thursday.
Right again.
Now, I'm going to take this pin,
and I'm going to touch the soles
of your feet and your toes,
and I want you to tell me...
Can you feel this?
For this one,
you're gonna sit up
and look right at me, okay?
Good.
Now stick out your tongue.
What happened?
Everything's
absolutely fine.
Larry gave him a thorough
neurological exam, it's nothing.
You two go home and
we'll talk tonight.
I won't be late, my schedule
today is pretty light.
Okay?
Maybe he
should get an MRI.
There's no need
to bother with all that.
He just got scared, that's all.
He's absolutely fine; you're
absolutely fine, aren't you?
Yeah.
I think maybe there
was a test at school today
that we hadn't
prepared for very well.
Yes, he wanted to
spend the day at the hospital
with Larry and us.
Let's go.
- Dad.
- Yeah?
Aren't you going to
show us an operating theater?
Another
time, darling.
They need me to prep
for surgery right away.
I have to go, I'll
see you tonight.
Excuse me, can
we get some help here?
He needs some help.
MRI, MRA both fine.
Blood work came back good.
Cardiogram, chest
X-ray, all clear.
Has he been under any
psychological stress lately?
Exams at school maybe?
- Yes.
- He's not stressed.
He's fine.
He's a little anxious but
that's just the way he is.
In my opinion, he
should stay in tomorrow as well,
just so we can
keep an eye on him.
What about a PET scan?
I don't think there's
any need for that.
What do you think, Larry?
And tomorrow he'll be well
enough to walk all the way home.
Yes, I don't think it's
necessary at this point.
Let's see how things go tomorrow
and we'll take it from there.
There's nothing to worry
about, in my opinion.
You go home, we'll speak tomorrow,
and I'll be here all day.
And, Anna, great seeing you,
even under these circumstances.
You, too, Larry.
- Goodnight.
- Bye, Larry.
And thanks for everything.
Do you want me
to let them know
you won't be operating tomorrow?
I said no.
Stop going on about it.
That won't
be necessary, Matthew.
I'll come by in the morning,
I won't go into the clinic.
I'll bring in those
doughnuts he loves so much.
Yes, I'm
sure he'll be thrilled.
- Where were you?
- At Claire's.
Is Dad asleep?
Yes.
How's Bob?
Bob is absolutely fine.
They're just keeping
him in as a precaution.
How are you feeling?
I'm fine, how do you mean?
I mean are you tired?
I'm absolutely fine.
I'm a little tired, that's all.
Okay.
See you in the morning.
Oh, and while Bob
is in the hospital,
you'll be responsible for
watering the plants, okay?
Did he go to the bathroom?
Did he get up?
He hadn't when I
passed by about an hour ago.
He didn't want to.
He didn't want to
pee or he hadn't gotten up?
- He didn't want to pee.
- Could he get up?
He was asleep.
I didn't want to
drag him out of bed.
Good morning, Doctor.
How are you, Mrs Murphy?
I came by to see Bob.
Kim told me what happened.
Hi, Martin.
How nice of you.
Did your friend Martin
come to see you?
I'll leave you alone now
so you can spend some
time with him, too.
I gotta go anyway.
I'll come by and see him
again some other time.
I offered to help him
go to the bathroom
but he didn't want me to.
He wet the bed.
I brought some lemonade
my mom made yesterday.
You should try some, let
me know what you think.
Thank you very much.
Darling, do you know
what's in this box?
What?
Cinnamon
doughnuts, that's what.
Come to the
cafeteria upstairs.
Come whenever you can.
I don't think
I'll have time today,
as you might imagine.
We'll talk some other time.
No, today,
to the cafeteria.
Just for 10 minutes, don't
stand me up like the last time.
I brought you a present.
You've given me so many presents
and I've not given you anything.
I thought that was rude of me.
Close your eyes.
Close your eyes, please.
It's a Swiss Army knife.
I shouldn't have told you that.
I just ruined the
surprise, I'm sorry.
Thank you very much, Martin.
That was dumb.
Martin, I have
to get back downstairs.
Okay.
I won't keep you much
longer, even though
you have been devoting less
and less time to me lately.
I wanted to say one more thing,
I'm really sorry about Bob.
- It's nothing serious.
- No, it is.
That critical moment we both
knew would come some day?
Here it is.
That time is now.
- You know what I mean.
- No, I don't.
Listen, Martin, I don't
have time for this.
Okay, I'm gonna
explain this very quickly
so that I don't hold you up.
Yes, it's exactly
what you think.
Just like you killed
a member of my family,
now you've gotta kill
a member of your family
to balance things
out, understand?
I can't tell you who
to kill, of course.
That's for you to decide,
but if you don't do it,
they will all get sick and die.
Bob will die, Kim will
die, your wife will die.
They will all get sick and die.
One, paralysis of the limbs.
Two, refusal of food to
the point of starvation.
Three, bleeding from
the eyes, four, death.
One, two, three, four.
Don't worry, you won't get sick.
You just gotta stay
calm, that's all.
There, I said it, as
quickly as I could.
I hope I haven't
kept you too long.
One more thing.
I'll be very quick.
You only have a few days
to decide who to kill.
Once stage three kicks in...
You remember what
stage three is?
It's bleeding from the
eyes, that's stage three.
Once the bleeding happens,
it's only a matter of
hours before they die.
Okay, there, I have
nothing more to say.
Unless you've,
unless you've any questions?
Has he eaten?
No, he's not hungry.
What do you
mean he's not hungry?
He's not hungry.
Come on,
darling, eat a doughnut.
- I don't want it, Dad.
- You do.
But you're afraid
your mother and I
will tell you off
for eating doughnuts.
Come on, eat it.
You have my permission.
You have our permission.
It's okay for him to eat a
doughnut, isn't it, Anna?
Yes, of course.
You heard
your mother, eat it.
Bob?
He doesn't want it.
- No, he'll eat it later.
- That's right.
That's right, eat it.
Now chew it, swallow.
Leave him alone!
He said he doesn't want it now.
He's going to
eat them right now.
He's completely run down.
That's why he keeps falling
over and crawling around
on all fours.
He's going to eat
them, all of them.
Five minutes flat, I want
to see that whole box empty.
That means, on the bus
there are winners and losers.
But it's funny because
it sounds like,
on the bus there are
20 hearts and 20 asses.
That is funny.
Are you on your period?
No.
If you're hungry, we can
order something later.
My parents won't
be back till late
and they've left me some money.
I'm not hungry.
You're the prettiest
girl I've ever met.
I have to go, I'm sorry.
Why?
Stay a little longer.
We can listen to some music.
I can't,
it's late, I'm sorry.
Are you mad at me
because of my dad?
Don't be stupid,
I'm not mad at you at all.
I thought I made myself clear.
I don't feel angry at
him, I feel sorry for him.
I have to go because it's late.
It's as simple as that.
Don't be a drag, I
thought you understood.
I'm sorry, Martin.
I love you so much.
He stopped eating today.
He refuses to eat.
Some of the tests
need to be done again.
Take a deep breath.
Hold it for a few seconds.
They
haven't detected anything.
Okay, good, breathe.
It's been less than a
day since his last tests.
I don't think the results are
gonna show anything different.
To be honest, I think
what we have here
is a clear case of some
psychosomatic disorder.
I'm inclined
to agree with Anna.
Well
what do you mean?
Shouldn't we rule out
all possible causes
before we resort
to the easy option
of a psychosomatic disorder?
We already have
ruled out everything else.
I think with
psychological support
and psychiatric
treatment, if necessary,
he will be just fine.
He'll walk again
and he'll eat again.
Of course he will.
Anna,
if Bob was near-sighted,
or had a cataract
or glaucoma then your opinion
really would be valuable.
But, thankfully, Bob's
eyesight is perfect.
And I can honestly say that
if he ever needed glasses
you'd be the first
person I'd consult.
But right now the boy can't eat
and he's paralyzed in
both legs, so, I'm sorry,
I'm not remotely interested
in your medical opinion.
Doors opening.
Doors closing,
please stand clear.
Come on, Bob,
let's go for a walk.
Up you get, there you go.
Ready?
There we go.
Bob?
Why don't we play a game?
What game?
I'll
tell you a secret,
something I've never
told you before.
Then you'll tell me one.
And whoever tells the
best secret wins, okay?
When I was your age I'd only
just started masturbating.
And I'd only just
started ejaculating.
Only a little, barely a drop.
I was worried that I had
some kind of a problem
because at school I'd
heard all sorts of stories.
Then one day, when my father
had had a lot to drink
and my brothers were out and
he was sleeping in the bedroom,
I crept inside, put
my hand on his penis
and started stroking
it until he ejaculated.
The sheets were
covered in sperm.
I got scared and ran out.
I've never told
anyone that before.
Now it's your turn
to tell me a secret.
I don't know.
I don't have one.
That's impossible.
You have to have one.
No.
I don't.
Bob, if all this is just
an act, you should know
that if you tell me
now, I won't punish you.
And neither will your mother.
We won't be angry
with you either.
It's not an act.
But if it is an act
and you don't stop
this stupid joke right now,
your punishment won't just
be no TV for two months.
I will take my electric razor
and I will shave your head
and make you eat your hair.
I mean it, I will literally
make you eat your hair.
I'm not kidding.
It's not an act.
I brought you a clean shirt.
Thank you.
Anything to tell me?
Hungry?
Want me to bring you
something to eat?
No, thank you.
Maybe you were right.
Maybe it's all psychological.
Everything will be
alright, you'll see.
Trust me.
We're in this together,
it's all gonna be fine.
Let's get you something
to eat, get some fresh air
and go up and see
the little one.
♪ Christmas is here,
bringing good cheer
♪ To young and old,
meek and the bold
♪ Ding, dong, ding,
dong, that is their song
♪ With joyful ring, all caroling
♪ One seems to hear
words of good cheer
♪ From everywhere,
filling the air
♪ Oh, how they pound,
raising their sound
♪ O'er hill and dale,
telling their tale
♪ Gaily they ring,
while people sing
♪ Songs of good cheer,
Christmas is here
♪ Sing merry, merry,
merry Christmas
♪ Merry, merry,
merry, merry Christmas
♪ On, on they send,
on without end
♪ Their joyful
tone to every home
♪ Hark, how the bells,
sweet silver bells
♪ All seem to say,
throw cares away
♪ Christmas is here,
bringing good cheer
♪ To young and old,
meek and the bold
♪ Ding, dong, ding,
dong, that is their song
♪ With joyful ring, all caroling
♪ One seems to hear
words of good cheer
♪ From everywhere,
filling the air
♪ Oh, how they pound,
raising their sound
♪ O'er hill and dale,
telling their tale
♪ Gaily they ring,
while people sing
♪ Songs of good cheer
♪ Christmas...
Dad, I don't want any fruit.
Just one bite.
For me.
I can't.
Okay.
Open the door!
I know you're in there!
Open the door or I
will smash it down!
Martin!
Open the door or I
will smash it down
and I will fuck you and your
mother just the way you wanted!
If anything happens
to my kids or my wife,
you'll die in prison!
Do you know that?
You'll die in prison!
How old was
his father when he died?
46.
Had you been
drinking that day?
He had an arrhythmia,
a stroke, and that was it.
I asked whether you'd been
drinking, not how he died.
How long has this been going on?
How long have you
been seeing this boy?
About six months.
- Where were you meeting?
- What does it matter?
Where were
you meeting him?
At a diner and then we'd
drive down to the river.
He's got issues, serious
psychological issues.
He always did.
I knew he acted weird sometimes
but now he's lost it completely,
he's become dangerous.
We have to take precautions.
Go to the police and take
some precautionary measures.
We're not going to the police.
We're not telling
anyone about this.
What's the point?
Had you been drinking when
you operated on his father?
Only a little.
That had nothing to
do with the outcome.
A surgeon never kills a patient.
An anesthesiologist
can kill a patient
but a surgeon never can.
For example, Matthew
has made mistakes
that have led to the death of
a patient, but I never have.
Bob seemed a little
better today.
He was in a better mood
and he was less pale.
Why didn't you tell
me you were seeing him?
At first I didn't
see him that often.
It was only recently that we
began meeting more regularly.
And I was going to
tell you at some point.
I felt sorry for him.
I gave him some money.
His mom's out of work.
Mom, when
are we going home?
Tomorrow,
or the day after,
when all of the tests are
done and the doctors say so.
But you're doctors, too.
Tell them we can go home.
We'll
tell them, darling.
Mom, did Martin come
by while I was sleeping?
No.
Can you turn me
on my side, please?
Is Dad here?
No, he'll be here soon.
Want me to get
some juice for you?
No.
Don't go anywhere.
Stay here.
Good morning.
How are you?
Aren't you coming by?
Okay.
Just my mom.
My father will be here soon.
You're here?
I can't, are you
coming up to see me?
You really
think that's possible?
Well let's see.
Okay, okay.
Yes, I stood up.
Can you see me?
Yes, thank you.
Yeah, I'm standing
at the window.
Can you see me?
I can't see you.
I'm waving at you.
Mom?
I want to stand up like Kim.
How come she can
get up and I can't?
You'll be able
to soon, my darling.
Kim's older than you,
that's why she can do it.
Soon you'll be strong
enough to stand up too.
Alright, I'm
going back to bed.
Mm hmm, me too.
Bye.
Mom, I'm going
over to the window.
Oh!
No.
Who were you talking to?
Martin.
He sends his regards.
I don't want you
talking to him ever again.
Why?
Because I said so.
Did you hear what I said?
Fuck you.
- What did you say?
- I didn't say anything.
Yes, you did, what
did you say, Kim?
Mom, let go, you're hurting
me, I didn't say anything.
I'm not like your father.
If this is the way you want it,
I'm confiscating your phone,
right here, right now.
That'll teach you to
be rude to your mother.
Give me my phone back.
You can forget it.
Don't be scared, Mom.
Don't get hysterical.
It's not that tragic.
Sometimes your body
hurts from not moving
and you can't sleep.
That's all.
The important thing
is to make sure
that everything you
need is within reach.
That's all.
You'll see.
You won't be able
to move either.
But you'll get used to it.
I really saw it happen.
It was
just a coincidence.
How can it be a coincidence?
How come neither of them
have been able to get up
and walk until now?
Darling, listen to yourself.
I saw it.
Okay, it just means
things are getting better.
That's all it means, that
Kim is getting better.
Now please go home and
rest awhile, please.
They're not better;
they're worse.
This afternoon
there'll be an emergency meeting
with the Medical Board.
Larry and I took the initiative
and invited two
outstanding specialists
from the Presbyterian
University Hospital of Columbia.
And they already flew
in from New York.
I'm meeting them this afternoon
to brief them about the case.
One of them's actually
a personal friend
of the director, Dr. Farrington,
you must have heard of him.
He's the best there is when it
comes to paralytic disorders.
Good afternoon.
Oh, thank you very much.
I'd like to talk to you.
I'm not gonna take
up much of your time.
Of course.
Um, I've only got 10 minutes
'cause I've gotta get to class.
So, what's up?
My husband told me
about you and your father.
Oh, he did?
Did he also tell
you about my mom?
- No.
- Oh.
Sorry.
Maybe I'm not the one you
should, um, hear it from but, um
ever since your husband
killed my father,
he's been flirting with my mom.
Constantly, flirting.
To be honest, she's got
feelings for him, too.
She thinks he's very nice hands.
Truth is, he has
beautiful hands.
All doctors have clean,
nice, beautiful hands.
So I told her, I said,
I've no problem with it
if you wanna go ahead.
I mean, he seems like a
nice guy, very nice guy.
And I don't wanna
get in the way of
her trying to get her
life back on track.
I'll be gone, I'll be gone in
a few years, I'll get a job.
If my husband made a mistake,
if out of negligence or,
I don't know what,
he caused this tragic
thing to happen,
I don't understand why I
should have to pay the price.
Why my children should
have to pay the price.
You know, not long after
my dad died, someone told me
that I eat spaghetti the
exact same way he did.
They said what an
extraordinary impression
this fact had made on them.
Look at the boy, look
how he eats spaghetti.
Exactly the same
way his father did.
He sticks his fork in.
He twirls it around, around,
around, around, around.
Then he sticks it in his mouth.
At that time, I thought
I was the only one
who ate spaghetti that way.
Me and my dad.
Later, of course, I found out
that everyone eats spaghetti
the exact same way.
Exact same way, exact same way.
This made me very upset.
Very upset.
Maybe even, um, more upset
than when they told
me he was dead.
My dad.
I don't know if what is
happening is fair, but
it's the only thing
I can think of
that's close to justice.
Time's getting on, and if I'm
late for class I'm done for.
Have a good day.
So I don't see any
reason for the children
to stay in the hospital.
You mean
you think you've done
everything you can?
Yes, Steven, I believe
we've done everything we can.
I'm sorry, but if I was
running this hospital,
I'd feel like a complete
failure, a loser.
I wouldn't be able
to sleep at night.
Goodnight, Anna.
Goodnight, Ed.
I suggest we sign the
release forms tomorrow
and they can go home.
Were you the anesthesiologist
for Jonathan Lang?
Thank you.
- Do you want...
- No, thank you.
Who's Jonathan Lang?
Male, 46 years old.
Patient of Steven's, died
on the operating table.
Anna, there
have been so many patients
over the years, so
many operations.
I don't remember him,
unfortunately, I'm sorry.
Can you find me his
file in the records
and show it to me, please?
I wanna see his medical
history and the cause of death.
I don't think that's
possible, I'm sorry, Anna.
I can't just share
files from the hospital.
Why do you need it?
Please.
Look, I can't
give you the file
but I can tell you a couple
of things about the case.
I remember him now,
I put him under.
But
what do I get in return?
What you didn't get
that day we came for lunch
at your house.
When?
Now.
Had Steven been drinking?
Yes.
Can it be
considered his mistake?
Yes.
It wasn't mine, that's for sure.
You know an anesthesiologist
is never to blame
for the bad outcome
of an operation.
The surgeon is
always responsible.
He'd had two drinks that morning
before we went in to prepare.
Luckily, no one else realized,
I was the only one that knew.
But, back then, that
wasn't exactly unusual.
You know that.
Thank you.
This meat is delicious.
You were right, after all.
The children are
much better off here.
I was even thinking
we might take them
to the beach house
for a few days.
A little fresh air and
a change of scenery
might do us all good.
Do you know what
I've been craving?
Mashed potato.
Why don't you make
some tomorrow?
You have beautiful hands.
I never noticed before.
Everyone's been
telling me lately
what beautiful hands you have
and now I can see for myself.
Nice and clean.
But so what if
they're beautiful?
They're lifeless.
Sometimes, Steven, you're
just an incompetent man
who goes on and on,
saying stupid things
like, "Let's do a scan.
"Let's do an ultrasound,
let's wear brown socks.
"Let's make mashed potatoes,
let's go to the beach house."
Excuse me?
Our two children are dying
in the other room, but, yes,
I can make you mashed
potatoes tomorrow.
Please don't talk
to me that way.
If you don't like
it, why don't you go
and live with Martin's mother?
I bet she'll talk to you better.
You wanted
the kids to come home,
and they came home.
What else do you want me to do?
Something to put an
end to all of this,
that's what I want;
can you do that?
You do realize, Steven,
we're in this situation
because of you?
So what do you suggest?
Tell me.
No, wait, I know, I've got it.
There is a way we can
put a stop to all this.
All we need to do is find the
tooth of a baby crocodile,
the blood of a pigeon and
the pubes of a virgin.
And then we just have to
burn them all before sunset.
Let me see, do we have any
spare teeth lying around?
Teeth, pubes?
Nope, nothin' here.
There's nothing in here either.
Let me see, nothing here.
Pubes, teeth?
Nothing in this box either.
Where are they?
I'm sure they were here
earlier, I put them here myself.
Who's been moving things around?
It's unbelievable.
I don't suppose you've
got any pubes I can have,
by any chance?
Oh, I forgot, you
don't have any left.
We don't have any of
the things we need.
There's no need for us to argue.
Everything's so
difficult already.
There's no point
making it worse.
If he was telling the truth,
wouldn't you be sick too?
Wouldn't you be
paralyzed already?
How do you explain that?
Yes, you're right.
Let's wait a little longer
until we're all dead
and then see what
you can do about it.
There's really nothing
to worry about.
You need to go to
the hospital tomorrow
and pick up more feeding
formula for the children.
We're almost out.
Okay.
Good morning.
Did
you get any sleep?
What time is it?
Ten past eight.
Get up and come with
me for a moment.
You remember Martin, don't you?
He came by for a play-date.
I told him the kids were
feeling a little unwell
and he'll have to stay
here until they get better.
Anna, go upstairs and make
him some of that lemonade
he likes so much, would you?
I'll stay here and
keep him company.
Please.
Let me go.
My mother's gonna
be worried sick.
Do you think your mother's
proud of you, Martin?
Do you think she's happy that
her beloved son is a murderer?
Murderer?
There's really no need
for such a dramatic,
sensational, old-fashioned word.
But if you insist,
the murderer, both
in my father's case
and our current
situation, is not me.
- Stop talking.
- Don't you understand
that you're wasting time?
And you don't have
much time left.
I said stop talking.
Steven, it's gonna be
better once it's done.
Start over, clean slate.
Don't you get it?
Sometimes I think you're
naive but you can't be naive.
You're a man of science,
you can't be an idiot.
But, if I'd only just met you,
I would seriously question
your depth of judgment.
I just want, want to show
you an example, ,
that's all.
Just one little example
to show you what I mean.
Should I apologize?
No.
Should I, should I
stroke your wound?
Actually, that would
probably hurt even more,
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
touching an open wound.
No, there's only one way
to make you and me
both feel better.
Do you understand?
It's metaphorical.
My example.
It's a metaphor.
I mean, it's,
it's symbolic.
Shut the door, Anna.
Now, Martin, you'll know
what it's like to die.
What it's like when
your head cracks open
and your brains blow out.
Don't shoot him.
And then?
Shut up!
Shoot me, then what?
- Answer.
- I'll bury you in the yard!
And you'll rot, that's what.
You won't be
able to explain it.
You won't understand how
it could have happened.
You'll say, "But I
only killed one person.
"How come four people are dead?
"I only shot one."
So if you're gonna dig
a hole in the yard,
better make it a big one.
Steven.
He didn't kill him.
How do you know?
I just do.
Anyway, he made
the right choice.
Otherwise it would have been
like killing four people
with a single shot.
Wouldn't that be tragic?
I'm going to live with Martin.
I want you to know that
I'm really sorry, Bob.
I really love you.
We all do.
Dad does, too.
But he's in a really
difficult position
and he doesn't have
much of a choice.
It's not because he
doesn't love you.
They bought me a piano.
Mom told me it'd
be here next month.
They didn't tell you so
you wouldn't be scared.
Bob, something terrible
happened yesterday.
I lost the MP player
that Martin gave me.
I don't know what's
wrong with me.
I've lost two MP players
in the last 10 days.
So I'd like to ask you a favor.
Can I have your MP
player when you're dead?
Please, please.
Please.
Dad.
Look.
I cut my hair just
as you wanted me to.
Good boy.
Well done.
I'm sorry I
didn't listen to you
and get a haircut right away.
I don't know what I was
thinking all this time.
I would get so hot and have
to comb it all the time.
It was a total hassle.
I should have listened to
you and cut it off sooner.
I'm gonna water the plants now.
No, darling,
I watered them this morning.
Tomorrow.
Dad,
I've been thinking about it
and I decided I wanna
become a cardiologist.
Not an ophthalmologist.
I lied to mom because I
didn't want her to get upset.
I think I prefer what you do.
It's far more interesting
and challenging.
The boy's very good
at math and physics.
Kim, on the other hand, apart
from her natural aptitude
for music, is very good
at literature and history,
areas in which Bob lags behind.
She wrote a brilliant essay
on the tragedy of Iphigenia
which she read out in class.
She received an A plus.
What about their
behavior in class?
They're both a little
restless, I'd say.
Equally so.
I mean, I've had the
occasional complaint
from their teachers about
some minor misdemeanors
but they've never been
rude to any of the staff.
In any case, if they
had ever acted out,
we would have told you about it.
Do you especially like one
of them more than the other?
If you had to
choose between them,
which would say is the best?
That's a difficult question.
I'm not sure I can
give you an answer.
I don't know.
I don't know what to tell you.
Thank you for
bringing them down.
I really wanted to see them.
I really wanted to see you.
Hi, Bob.
Hi, Kim.
Bob,
aren't you gonna come over
and let me give you a hug?
Bob?
No?
I understand; it doesn't matter.
You're a man.
The man of the house, now
your father isn't home.
You can go back to bed.
Don't trouble
yourselves for my sake.
You can take them away.
Anna, if you're gonna do
something, you'd better be fast.
The boy is about to die.
I believe the most logical
thing, no matter how harsh
this may sound, is
to kill a child.
Because we can
have another child.
I still can and you can.
And if you can't, we can try
IVF, but I'm sure we can.
I'm sorry for
what I did tonight.
I don't know what
I was thinking.
I was only thinking about
myself and no one else.
That was wrong of me.
I was frightened.
I shouldn't have been.
Let me be the one who
atones for your sins, Dad.
Kill me right here
in front of your eyes
so that you can be
sure that I die,
in case some fate spares
me at the last moment.
Kill me right here
in front of you
and leave me with the ultimate
joy of saving my own mother
and beloved brother
from certain death.
Mom, tell him.
Dad, please.
I would do anything for you.
I would even die for you and
here's my chance to prove it.
They're all asleep.
We can go now and
no one will notice.
All you have to do is
help me walk again.
My legs hurt after all
this time and I feel weak.
But it's okay.
It doesn't matter.
I knew at some point
this would all be over
and you would come.
I thought we could take
your friend's motorcycle
and run away together.
But you have to
make me well first.
I'll untie you if you promise
you can make me better
and we'll run away together.
Okay?
It's not working.
You have to try harder.
Kim's not in her bed.
I'm telling you, you
have to try harder.
Are you deaf?
Martin.
Try harder!
- Where is she?
- She's gone.
Where is she, what
did you do to her?
I love you so much,
don't forget that.
You gave me life
and you, only you,
have the right to
take my life away.
That makes perfect sense.
You are my lords, my masters
and I am just someone
who lives to obey your wishes.
I love you so much.
Remember that when
I'm lying in my grave,
unable to tell you
that I love you.
I love you more than
anything in the world,
you and my brother.
Where have you been?
I went
to the hospital.
Got the feeding formula.
Have you checked on him?
Did you give him the sedatives?
I let him go.
- What are you talking about?
- He's not downstairs.
I let him go.
Why would you do that?
Why did you let him go?
Answer me!
Are you a complete idiot?
It's not gonna make
any difference, Steven.
It's not gonna solve
anything, we both know that.
Mom?
Do you remember that day
when I was rude to
you at the hospital?
Yes.
Did you tell Dad about it?
Of course I
told him about it, Kim.
I didn't mean it, Mom.
Maybe it was just a side-effect
of the drugs or something.
Kim, can
you please be quiet?
Do your legs hurt,
do they feel numb?
Does your back hurt,
has it started yet?
Dad!
Quick, Bob's dying!
Bob's dying!
Dad.
Who's your best friend?
I don't know, Bob.
I have three.
Two boys and a girl in my class.
That's great, Bob.
It's good to have
a lot of friends.
Bob's eyes are bleeding.
Come to the living room.
- Now?
- Yes.
Now.
Steven, where
are the children?
They're already there.
I think I'm gonna wear that
black dress that you like.
Wear whatever you want.
Just hurry.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Subtitles by explosiveskull