What do you boys
think about going
turkey hunting this year?
-Think you ought to go...
-Mr. Willie, my momma
wanted me to ask you
would you come
down to our house?
There's some
kind of wild man
down there in the woods
by the creek.
Now, boy,
I want you to go
back down there
and tell your momma
there ain't a thing
in the world
to be afraid of.
I'll come down there
tomorrow and check it out.
Go ahead.
Yes, sir.
Thank you, sir.
You know that's
the third time
that ol' lady's
sent that kid
up here to tell me
there's a big ol'
hairy monster
down in my field.
I guess I'll have to
get down there tomorrow
and see about it.
I was seven-years-old when I first heard him scream.
It scared me then,
and it scares me now.
This is Fouke, Arkansas.
I grew up here.
The population was about
350 when I was a boy.
It still is.
Fouke is way down
in the southwest corner
where Arkansas joins
Texas and Louisiana.
If you've ever driven from
Shreveport to Texarkana,
you'll pass
right through Fouke.
Even if you don't
remember seeing it.
Aside from homes,
Fouke has several stores,
a couple of gas stations,
a post office and school,
garage and motel,
and two cafes for
the menfolk to stop by
for coffee and conversation
on the fish they've caught,
or the duck, quail, squirrel,
or deer they've hunted.
Fishing and hunting
take up a lot of
almost everybody's time.
Maybe Smokey Crabtree,
who lives way back down
on the edge of the Bottoms
will tell about
a mink or beaver
he or his son Travis caught.
Smokey raises beef cattle
and traps part time
and works as
a pipeline welder
when the good jobs
come along.
Travis walks and paddles
for miles every morning,
running his trap lines
before school starts.
Most of the people
who live around Fouke
are farmers or ranchers.
This country
is rich and fertile
with plenty of
grass and water.
Our land is veined with
a great network of
branches, creeks,
river and lakes.
Fouke is a right pleasant
place to live...
Until the sun goes down.
That day in the store,
Willie Smith
didn't believe me
when I told him
about a wild, hairy
creature in the woods.
He believes me now.
And he ran on East,
jumped over the fence.
It just seemed like
he just, sort of,
pushed it down
with his left hand,
just stepped over.
It was wounded and was
holding that right chest.
It had that right hand
on his chest
all the time that
it was in sight.
Maybe if it hadn't been
hurt pretty badly,
why, it might have
ran on all four legs,
I don't know.
But it wasn't.
It was running on
two legs at all times.
That was about
all I saw of this thing.
Something came through
here last night
and killed my two
prized shoats.
Found one of them
lying right here
deep gashes,
cuts and his tongue
was hanging out.
Looked like something
had strangled him.
I keep them off down here
by the creek in this pen.
And whatever it was,
got in the pen,
lifted both them 200-pound
hogs over the fence.
I couldn't find
no place where they'd
been dragged under.
I couldn't find no tracks,
so I figured
whatever it was,
came and left
travelling up and down
that creek.
Not knowing what
had killed them hogs,
I just threw them away.
I carried them way off
out there in the bushes
so the smell wouldn't
get back up to the house.
Next day,
I got up and
looked out there
and thought it
kind of funny
not seeing any buzzards
circling or anything.
So, came down here
and both hogs were gone.
That thing,
whatever it was,
must've come back,
and the grass wasn't
even disturbed,
where the hogs was.
What kind of thing
can pick up
200-pound hogs
and walk off with them.
I doubt if you
could find a lonelier,
spookier place
in this country
than down around Boggy Creek.
It twists and winds its way
across the Fouke countryside,
widening and narrowing,
sheltering within
its thickly wooded banks
a multitude of creatures
that run, fly, swim,
creep and crawl.
Eventually, Boggy
empties into Days Creek
and flows onward
into the Sulphur River.
Heavy rainfall half the year
causes our creeks
and rivers to flood
and spread over
wide sections
of densely thicketed
and forested bottomland.
In the Sulphur River Bottoms,
the water spreads out
for miles across
the bottomland.
A lot of which is
so densely thicketed
that only a few hunters
and trappers have the skill
to make their way
deep into this wild,
swampy country.
A lot of people believe
the creature prowls
back in here
most of the time.
But every now and then,
drawn to civilization
like a moth to flame,
he creeps out about dusk.
These nighttime visits
have set off waves of terror
around Fouke
for over 15 years.
What in the world
is this creature?
"Where did he come from,
and what does he eat?"
are questions I've heard
discussed a thousand times
around winter fires
and on hot summer evenings.
When the creature,
whom the newspapers
quickly named
"The Fouke Monster,"
was first seen,
he didn't seem to make
any special effort
to hide from people.
At least, Fred Crabtree,
a farmer who hunted a lot,
had that opinion.
He just didn't look like
anything I'd ever seen.
I thought at first,
it might be some
kind of a wild man.
I couldn't tell
under all that hair
just what it was.
I changed the shells
in my shotgun
from my squirrel shot
to my buck shot.
- More for my protection
than anything else.
If I'd have had my rifle,
I believe I could have
knocked him down easy.
But I doubt if I would have.
'Cause I kept thinking
there's just a chance
he might be a man.
And if I had shot that thing,
and it turned out to be a man,
I'd have had to live with that for the rest of my life.
Although he was
never sure,
Fred got the impression
the creature had been
washing his feet
in the icy water.
A few months later,
James Crabtree
was squirrel hunting.
Only a short distance
from the spot
where Fred Crabtree
had seen it.
I've spent
a lot of my life
in these woods,
and there was something
strange about that evening
that I couldn't put
my finger on it.
It was just a feeling I had.
There didn't seem
to be as many birds
and little small animals
out as usual.
In fact, they seemed
mighty scarce.
It stepped right out
in plain sight.
Right out there
in front of me.
And he was...
It was some kind of thing
that I've never
come across before.
Well, he stared at me
for a little while
and just slipped
out of sight.
I never saw him again.
Neither Fred Crabtree,
nor his uncle James
told anyone about
their experience for years.
They figured nobody
would believe them.
He always travels
the creeks.
That was one of
the first things
we figured out.
This little branch
feeds into Boggy Creek.
The Searcy family
lives here.
Mary Beth Searcy
is a teenage student.
Right now,
her older married sister
and her baby are visiting.
Her father's working
in another town,
and her younger brother
is spending the night
with a friend.
So, this evening,
just the two girls,
their mother and the baby
will be alone in this house.
They have no phone
and the nearest neighbor
is a mile or so
across the woods.
Mary Beth?
Mary Beth, would you
please hang something
over the window?
There's a draft on the baby.
Yeah. Okay.
Just a minute.
Come here, kitty.
Come here.
Come, kitty.
Mary Beth,
would you please
hurry up!
This draft's gonna
give the baby a cold.
Okay! Okay!
Mary Beth, what's the
matter with you?
What happened?
Tell me. Answer me...
It was a long
night of terror.
In a few minutes,
Mary Beth was revived,
and the three women,
shaking in fear,
freezing at every sound
in the darkness,
waited out the long
hours of blackness.
The baby slept peacefully
through it all.
Next morning,
they would discover
their dead kitten
completely unmarked.
Apparently, she had simply
been scared to death.
The beauty of the Bottoms
under soft moonlight
is transformed into
dark and menacing danger.
And the shadows of the night
trigger your imagination
into being places,
where possibly,
the creature is lurking.
Because you know
he's out there somewhere.
If, like this
13-year-old boy,
you've grown up as
a woodsman and hunter,
you never miss
an opportunity to
get yourself a deer.
Yes, there's
no doubt about it,
the dogs are
hot on the trail
chasing the deer
in this direction.
Later, they found
two-inch saplings
broken down by the creature
in his pain and fury.
They saw crushed underbrush
and blood stains,
which in the excitement,
no one thought to
gather a sample of.
But they did not
find the creature.
The terrifying stories
of face to face encounters
with the creature
triggered the Fouke
community into action.
A big hunt was organized
with some of
the best hunting dogs
in Arkansas
and Texas involved.
They even brought in
some famous dogs
from Tennessee.
I got to go along.
And I still vividly recall
how I was trembling
with excitement.
We'd heard that earlier,
some other dogs
had refused to
trail the creature,
cowering in fear
and running back
at the first whiff of his
sour pig-pen smell.
But we were confident
our dogs would
get the job done.
Hey, Earl, where did
that ol' boy go that
brought them dogs in here.
While several groups
hunted on foot,
others scouted designated
areas on horseback.
While we made our way
along the dirt road
he had been crossing,
the men on horseback
swept across the woodlands
along the creek areas.
About this time,
our dogs struck his trail
where he'd crossed the road.
- Go get him.
- Spot, go get him!
They found his trail.
Go get him! Atta boy!
Trail him now. Get him.
You've never seen
a more embarrassed
and angry group
of dog owners.
Neither one of these
famous hunting dogs
would trail the
creature's scent.
They whined,
tucked their tails,
and came running back
obviously scared.
I was sure disappointed.
Despite the failure
of the dogs to trail
the creature,
several groups of
hunters kept going
far into the night.
Later, we got word
that one hunting party
had got the creature
to scream angrily back
at a wounded rabbit call,
but moved deeper
into the forest
when they tried
to get closer.
Not too many of
the hunters were
interested in plunging
into thick woods
in pitch darkness
knowing he was out there.
Often I've tried to imagine
how the creature must feel.
Since his very appearance
and the sounds he makes
frightened us,
our immediate reaction
was to try to kill him.
I suppose if
a strange-looking creature
from another world
showed up,
he'd get the same reception.
Actually, at first,
the creature didn't
try to harm anybody,
but now, after being
hunted and hurt,
he suddenly disappeared.
So, far as we know,
he wasn't seen again
for eight years.
Where did he go?
Well, we believe
he simply headed back
deeper and deeper
into the Bottoms,
beyond the reach of men.
Only the alligator and wolf,
crane and possum,
and a thousand other
wild creatures
heard his occasional,
lonely cries
ringing out over
his watery domain.
♪ This is where
the story plays
♪ A world on which
we seldom gaze
♪ A page from the book
of yesterdays
♪ Birds and beast
and wind and water
♪ Here beneath
the bright blue sky
♪ No man's smoke
blinds the eagle's eye
♪ And things that crawl
or swim or fly
♪ Feed and breed
and live and die ♪
The seasons passed,
summers into falls,
winters into springs.
And somewhere in
the remote wilderness
of the Bottoms,
the creature spent his days.
♪ Here the Sulphur River flows
♪ Rising when
the storm cloud blows
♪ And this is where
the creature goes
♪ Safe within
the world he knows
♪ Perhaps he dimly wonders
♪ "Why there is no other
such as I
♪ "To touch
to love before I die ♪
♪ "To listen
to my lonely cry?" ♪
Now, none of us
Fouke boys would admit it,
but for a long time,
knowing the creature
might be around
had put a damper
on our pack trips
back into the wilderness.
But as time passed,
and stories and conversation
about the Fouke monster
died down,
teenage boys again
began to go off
on long camping trips
in the Bottoms.
Travis Crabtree
is the kind of fearless,
outdoor kid that
would have gone anyway,
even knowing the creature
was around.
There's nothing
Travis likes better
than to spend
the weekend camping
on one of
the hilltop islands
created by high water
deep in the Bottom land.
♪ Hey, Travis Crabtree
♪ Wait a minute for me
♪ Let's go back in the Bottoms
♪ Back where the fish
are biting
♪ Where all
the world's inviting
♪ And nobody sees
the flowers bloom but me
♪ Hey, Travis Crabtree
♪ Do you see what I see
♪ On the gentle
winds of morning
♪ A million birds are singing
♪ Like the bells
of heaven ringing
♪ And nobody sees
the flowers bloom but me
♪ Drop me on a patch of land
♪ Never stepped upon by man
♪ Where the crystal water
flows deep
♪ But the falcon flies high
across the yellow-eyed sky
♪ Lord, ain't it great
to be free
♪ Hey, Travis Crabtree
♪ It's the right life for me
♪ Rollin' alone in the Bottoms
♪ While the birds
and bees are crying
♪ Because the sun is dying
♪ And nobody sees
the flowers bloom but me
the flowers bloom but me ♪
When he's down
in the Bottoms,
Travis always stops off
for a visit and
a cup of coffee
with Herb Jones.
Herb Jones is a man
who likes a lot of privacy.
He's been living alone
in these Bottoms
for the past 20 years.
Hey, Herb!
Well, Travis.
Travis always enjoys
these visits with Herb,
and never fails
to bring him tobacco
and other supplies.
Herb can spin yarns
for hours
about his experiences
with the wild creatures
of the Bottomland.
Herb tells Travis
to be on the look out
for a big ol' wild boar
with double curled tusks
he spotted a day
or two earlier.
Herb limps because
he once accidentally shot
part of his foot away
in a boating accident.
Although he was all alone,
he made it out of
the Bottoms to a doctor.
I've been living down here
by myself for a long time.
About 14-miles by boat
from my place
to the nearest road,
then it's a pretty good
walk to town.
Them Crabtree boys,
especially that Travis,
always drop by
to see me
when they come
hunting and fishing.
They always brung me
tobacco and sugar
and stuff like that.
Even a bottle of wine
every once in a while.
Did you notice
my bottle tree
on the way in?
I use them bottles
as hooks on my trout lines.
I catch some mighty
big catfish and buffalo
on them lines.
And an old crane
flies over every day.
Looks at my place.
I don't know
what he's looking for.
Once you get to know
these Bottoms,
you never lack
for something to do.
People always ask me
why I stay down here.
I tell them I stay 'cause
I like it better here
than I would anywhere else.
Looks like they could
figure that out
for themselves.
And another thing,
people always ask me
have I seen
the Fouke monster.
Let me tell you something,
there ain't no such thing.
I've been living here
in these Bottoms
for better than 20 years.
I ain't never seen
nor heard no monster.
What was that?
I don't know,
but let's get out of here.
The creature was back.
Once again,
the lure of civilization
had brought him
out of the wilderness.
Soon, newspaper
headlines would herald,
"The Return of
the Fouke Monster."
And people would
get together around
Fouke to relate
the latest rumors
on the creature.
Every dead animal
found in the forest
was blamed upon him.
This dog and others found dead,
might well be his victims.
Excitement in the community
reached a new peak
when a farmer
named O.H. Kennedy
discovered these strange
three-toed footsteps
in Willie Smith's bean field.
Radio, newspaper
and television coverage
resulted in
nation-wide publicity.
...must not be over
four inches wide.
Mr. Kennedy,
you say you found
these tracks late Sunday.
Now, was that
late yesterday afternoon?
Yes, sir.
Just about sundown.
My wife and I went out
for a ride,
she's been feeling
poorly lately.
And we decided to stop by
the bean field
to see if the ground
was too wet to plow.
We called Willie Smith
right away.
Mr. Kennedy,
do you think
this creature could
be a sasquatch?
A... A sasquatch?
I don't believe I know
what that is, sir.
Well, the sasquatch was
the Indians' word
for a legendary giant tribe
of very shy people.
They live mostly in the woods
up in the Pacific Northwest.
Well,
I didn't see anybody.
All I've seen, sir,
is these tracks.
Well, now,
doesn't the sasquatch
have a normal five toes?
This thing here
has only three toes.
Yes, and the adult
sasquatch footprint
is bigger, too.
It's 18 inches long
on the average.
Could these be
gorilla tracks?
No, I don't think
it's a gorilla.
A gorilla has five toes,
and very seldom moves upright
on two legs for very long.
This thing, it had to
drop down on all fours
to travel this far.
What about
an orangutan?
This is the same thing
people around here
reported seeing
over the past few years.
He's reddish-brown,
that's the same color
as an orangutan.
Well, I don't think
this could be orangutan.
The number of the toes
are wrong.
Now, excuse me,
Mr. Kennedy,
you spend a lot of time
working in this field, right?
Did you ever see
tracks like this
when you were here before?
No, sir.
Can't say that I have.
There's a lot of fresh animal
tracks around this field
all the time.
Deer, wolf, bobcat,
and all kinds of
other tracks.
But I've never seen
anything like these before.
Well, Mr. Kennedy,
did you ever hear anything
out of the ordinary
down here?
Well,
I've heard some pretty peculiar things down here,
but I've never seen anything
unusual like this before.
I wonder
what moves the creature
to pick a particular patch
of woods
and return to it
again and again.
These woods next
to the bean field
must be one of his
favorite haunts.
More than what
I heard, I guess it was
what I didn't hear that
made it kinda spooky.
Even when that tractor
is running
and you can't hear nothing,
you get a funny feeling that
something's wrong.
Then, I think, wasn't sure,
but I think I'd hear
a low growl, a hoot,
a grunt or something
from back at the trees.
And you know that
someone out there
is watching you.
I tell you, there's some
kind of animal
hanging around this field,
all right.
And he's no animal
from this part
of the country.
He always
travels Boggy Creek.
That's Bessie
Smith's children
playing at the edge of
the woods over there,
where Kennedy
heard the creature.
Grandpa! Grandpa!
Be quiet. You're gonna
wake up your grandpa.
I saw him,
I saw that monster.
You're getting filthy
down there...
Grandpa! Grandpa!
We saw the monster.
Be quiet! You're gonna
wake up your grandpa.
If you don't be quiet,
you'll get a switch.
Well, Mom, will you come down
and see it if I show you?
Show me what?
-Show you...
-The Fouke monster.
You know there isn't
anything there.
Yes, there is!
Come on, hurry. He might go.
He's over there.
Let's go back home!
Come on!
Where now? Where did you see it?
It was right over there.
Right over there.
See, there isn't anything
over there.
- Well, there was.
- He was.
He was.
That's where
we saw him last.
Run! Go! Run!
Go! Run!
Run!
That's Charlie Walraven
coming down the road.
This road runs along
the north side of the woods.
It was long about dark.
I was heading into
town that evening.
When I seen this thing coming
out across the road
in front of my car.
I just couldn't even
believe what I was watching.
You know, I reckon
there's a lot of folks
that don't believe anything
until they see it
for themselves.
Of course,
if they're like me,
they'd be wishing
they hadn't seen
what they did.
You know, that thing's gonna
up and kill somebody
one of these days,
sure as the world.
On a bright, moonlight night like this one,
you'd figure he'd
stay out of sight.
But nothing seems
to worry him
when the urge to prowl
comes over him.
It could've been
a fatal mistake
if the man who lives here
had been home tonight.
He has a high-powered
rifle handy,
and knows how to use it.
His daughter, Nancy,
has invited
two girlfriends over
for a bunking party.
No, our team's
much better than Arkansas High.
-You know that.
-Arkansas High had a win.
I know,
but they're defensive.
Yeah,
look at their offense.
Nancy, I like the way
they cut your hair.
I think it's cute.
Well,
Frank liked it long.
He's been sulking
all week.
Now, don't pay
any attention to him,
he doesn't know
anything about it.
Did y'all hear something?
That's the wind.
I can't see anything.
Do you?
No, I don't see anything.
Then it must've
been the wind.
I hope.
Let's all have a Coke.
Do you all want one?
-Yeah, get me one.
-Yeah.
Nancy, there's somebody
moving around
outside this trailer.
Do you... Do you think
it could be some of the guys?
If it is, I'll kill 'em.
I can't believe it's them.
They went to that game
in Texarkana.
Listen.
I hear something breathing.
I can hear it, too.
Get the gun! Get the gun!
Where are the shells?
Go away!
Shh. Shh. Hey, shh. Shh.
I don't hear it anymore.
I don't either.
Be still, I'm gonna look out.
No.
Next morning
when her parents returned,
they would find the girls
still half hysterical
with shock.
Before the creature
finally wandered off,
he smashed flower pots
and overturned
everything in sight.
These radical changes
in his usually
cautious behavior
may be caused
by lonely frustration,
for he apparently is
the only one of his kind.
Normally, he never comes out
of the woods before dusk,
and then moves
very cautiously,
staying within quick return
to the shelter of the trees.
But tonight,
he's on the rampage.
It wasn't the first time
the creature had
prowled in the vicinity
of Howard Walraven's
mobile home,
which is located only
a couple of hundred yards
from where Boggy Creek
flows across Highway 71.
We heard him
lots of nights.
Sometimes, it sounded like
he was right outside
of the window,
it was so loud.
And I had my two good dogs
tied up right there
behind the house.
And they'd always get excited
and scared, you know,
whenever he'd come around,
we heard him,
but, heck, I never figured
he'd attack them.
It just looked to me
like he grabbed my dog
and ripped the hide
right off his back.
Now let me tell you something.
He killed the finest dog
that I ever had.
But I'm gonna get him
one of these days
and that's gonna be
all she wrote.
Sometimes,
the creature sticks
to one patch of woods
for a long time.
Then, impulsively
works his way
far up the creeks
before being heard from again.
The creeks...
He always travels
the creeks.
When he next showed up,
it was several miles upstream.
In the spring, this house was rented to two young couples
who moved in together
to save money.
They were Charles Turner,
his wife, Anne,
and Don Ford,
who was Anne Turner's brother.
And Don's wife, Sue.
Each couple had a small child.
Don and Charles had just
been hired
by a big cattle ranch
in the Fouke area.
Since both men
would be required
to work late at night,
the girls would be
company to each other.
Thank you. Thank you.
The two families
moved in on Monday.
Thursday night,
the first of a series
of hair-raising
incidents occurred.
Shh!
What's the matter?
Shh.
-Did you hear that?
-Yeah.
That chair... Put that chair
under the door.
Who do you suppose
that was?
I don't know.
Let's take the kids
and go to the landlord's.
I had a pretty good look around
and I couldn't find a thing.
Are you sure you don't
want to go back to my place
till the men get here?
No, no. That's okay
if you checked and you're sure
there's nothing here,
then we'll be okay, I think.
I couldn't find a thing.
But I'll come back
in a little while
and check on you.
Okay, listen, mister,
we sure do thank you
and we appreciate it
-so much...
-Well, you're welcome.
I'll wait here till
you get in the house.
Okay. Buh-bye.
Bye.
The next day, Friday,
the Fords and Turners
had visitors.
Don Ford's younger brother,
Bobby Ford,
and a cousin,
12-year-old Corky Hill,
arrived for the weekend.
They'd heard about the great fishing around Fouke
and were anxious
to wet a hook.
Y'all be back before dark.
Yeah, yeah.
We're gonna bring back
some supper.
Bobby.
Who told you the fishing
was good here?
They're here.
Just have patience.
Bobby, come here. Come here!
What do you want?
Just come here. Come here!
Boy, look at the size of
that guy's footprint!
That ain't no footprint.
That's funny.
What's so funny
about that?
He's only got three toes!
Well, it's getting
kinda late,
and the fish
aren't biting anyway,
so I think we oughta go.
Sure is spooky
down here.
I still say, that's the biggest
foot that I've ever seen.
No.
Shh. I think I hear something.
Go get Annie and Sue.
Get up, get up.
Bobby heard something.
My gosh.
It's back.
Shh. I heard something.
Shh!
Is that him back?
It's gotta be.
Corky, go get the kids.
I seen him!
He's coming around the porch!
Bobby, put that chair
under the door.
I think I heard a car.
It's Don and Charles.
Hey, Don. Hey, Don.
Listen, listen. I swear...
You wouldn't
believe what happened.
I've never seen
nothing like this.
-All right. Hold it. Hold it.
-You wouldn't believe it.
You wouldn't
believe what happened.
I just can't
- I just can't...
- I'm sorry, I ain't...
Calm down.
Everybody's talking at once.
That's right.
I saw it.
All right, just calm down.
He's been around
this house.
We can't all talk
at one time.
I told you there was
something funny
about that footprint I found.
I just told you there was.
Charles, this is the second timein two nights
that someone has been
around this house.
I think you oughta get
some protection, man.
Think we oughta
go to the landlord's
to get the gun?
That'd be a great idea.
Why don't you go down
and get the gun
- I'll stay here
with them...
Be careful.
...and everything will be
a little quieter.
Okay, I'm going
to go with you.
We're have a gun here
so y'all don't be scared.
Go on in the house.
No way. No.
I'm just glad Charles
and Don are home.
Yeah, me too.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Listen, Corky,
you gotta get some sleep
and so do you.
I'm gonna go on the bed.
Okay.
What happened?
I saw him!
I swear, I ain't ever seen
nothing like it in my life.
He just came through there.
I saw him.
He was long and hairy.
-It was like a bear
or something.
-Hold it, hold it, hold it.
Hold it. Don, go get the light
and we'll go see
what this thing is.
All right, once more.
If he's out here,
let's get him now.
I'll look back here,
just a minute.
Keep your eyes open.
Say, I ain't scared,
this ain't no thing.
What's that right there?
That right over there?
Is that him right there?
Yeah, that's him.
You better say something
out there.
-You better say something.
-Hey, man.
-Gonna shoot.
-Shoot him.
He's not saying anything.
Shoot him.
Shoot him!
See, right there.
-Get him?
-I don't know.
-Hey, I think you got him.
-I don't see a thing.
Shine your light over here.
I don't see anything.
Nothing out there either.
I think that you got him.
Hey, let's go get the sheriff.
Hey, let us through,
will you?
All right, leave the gun
here with me.
Did you shoot him?
We don't know. We don't even
know if we hit it.
He's going after the sheriff.
I'm gonna stay here.
-I'm gonna go with him,
all right?
-Go inside.
Hurry back.
There's something here
outside of the house.
What did it look like?
Well, best I can tell,
the thing was tall
and had a lot of hair.
Red eyes.
-Find anything, Constable?
-Not yet.
This piece been like this
the whole time?
No, sir, it hasn't.
Have you looked in
under there?
No, sir, we haven't
looked down there.
This is a panther track
and her little cub
with it under this house.
You mean a panther's
been living under the house?
That's what it is.
It's a panther track.
That wasn't any panther
we shot at, Constable.
That's what that track is.
You keep this shotgun
and this light, these shells,
and if you need me,
you come ask.
Okay, sir, we sure will.
I'm gonna drive
up the highway
to see if I can see anything.
We'd sure appreciate it.-Yeah.
And I'll pick the gun up
tomorrow sometime.
I sure do thank you
for coming by.
-You're welcome.
-Thank you, sir.
You're welcome. If you need me,
give me a call.
Okay, we sure will.
-We're damn glad you came.
-Yeah.
- Good night.
What kind of place is this?
I mean, we have a panther
living under the house,
somebody trying to break in?
Well, we've got the flashlights,we've got the guns.
Now let's all go to bed
-and get some rest.
-I'm with you.
Let's go to bed.
Come on, Annie.
Let's go. Come on, Annie.
I gotta stay here with
the thing coming in
through the window?
Don't worry about it.
We got the guns.
I don't wanna stay here
no more with that thing...
I gotta go to the bathroom.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What's the matter?
Back there.
Tried to come through
the window.
What's the matter?
My God!
Right there. Right there.
Tried to come in through
the window.
Get your gun, Charles.
Let's go.
There he is!
Hold this, Bobby.
Bobby, take the light.
You got him.
That's it! He fell.
I think you got him, man.
I think I saw him fall
over there.
Let's go see.
Be careful.
Be careful!
Don't get too far.
Come back!
Somebody come back here!
Bobby, will you go back
and take care of the girls?
Charlie...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Help! Bobby!
When Bobby
could not be aroused
from the state of shock
he was in,
everyone piled into the car
and raced to Constable
Walraven's house for help.
Walraven took one look
at Bobby,
arranged a police escort
and sent them on
to the hospital in Texarkana.
Nurse, what do you think's wrongwith him? He hasn't said a thingin the car on the way here.
Let's check him up.
Doesn't move.
Hasn't said a word.
Breathing's kinda funny.
You think he'll be all right?
Let's check.
We'll let you know.
Blood pressure's 60 over 40.
I think we better start
an IV.
He's in a state of shock.
Bobby recovered swiftly,
and the Fords and Turners
moved away.
They don't plan on coming back.
What the creature was after
inside the Ford house
is perhaps
the biggest mystery of all.
I was thinking about it today
when I decided to drive out
to our old home place,
now run down
and abandoned.
Standing out in this field,
it all comes rushing back.
And an icy tingle
starts down my spine
when I recall that
terrible, lonesome cry.
It was so long ago that
it seems incredible that the creature is still out there
somewhere right this minute,
maybe even watching me.
Of course, you may not
believe that,
or any of this story.
You may think
the whole thing is a hoax.
And that's your privilege.
But if you're ever driving down
in our country
along about sundown,
keep an eye
on the dark woods
as you cross
the Sulphur River Bottoms,
and you may
catch a glimpse
of a huge, hairy creature
watching you from the shadows.
Yes, he's still here.
And you know,
I'd almost like to hear
that terrible cry again
just to be reminded
that there is still a bit of
wilderness left.
and there are still mysteries
that remain unsolved,
and strange, unexplained noises
in the night.
♪ This is where the story plays
♪ The world on which
we seldom gaze
♪ A page from the book
of yesterdays
♪ Birds and beast
and wind and water
♪ Here beneath
the bright blue sky
♪ No man's smoke
blinds the eagle's eye
♪ And things that crawl
or swim or fly
♪ Feed and breed
and live and die
♪ Here the Sulphur River flows
♪ Rising when
the storm cloud blows
♪ And this is where
the creature goes
♪ Safe but in a world
he knows
♪ Perhaps he dimly wonders
♪ "Why is there is no other
such as I
♪ "To touch
to love before I die
♪ "To listen
to my lonely cry?" ♪
Where he searches,
where he goes,
this, of course, nobody knows.
But once you've heard
his lonely cry,
you can guess the reason why.
Whether he's a beast or man,
what drives him wandering
across the land?
His love for others
of his clan,
and loneliness,
he cannot stand.
♪ Perhaps he dimly wonders
"Why
♪ "is there is no other
such as I
♪ "To touch
to love before I die
♪ "To listen
to my lonely cry?" ♪