Jesus!
Are you still there?
No, I'm back.
I'm not sure I got the spelling.
It is a "Y" Okay, great.
Yes, thank you. Bye.
Honey, you there?
Pick up, pick up.
You're not there. Okay.
Look, it's a little after 6:00.
I'll catch a ride
and see you out there. Bye.
- Jack.
- Yeah?
The Balkans peace council is "comprised"
or "composed" of ten members?
Twelve members.
Oh, right. Thanks.
Composed.
What?
A three-block area
has been evacuated.
You might wanna avoid that route
coming home from work.
- What do you think, Cy?
- This'll make them sweat. It's good.
- I'll lead with it.
- Great. I'll see you Monday.
What?
- I gotta go.
- Come on, John.
It'll look bad, my star reporter
not showing up at the Christmas party.
I can't.
Mary's waiting for me.
It's a big house, isn't it?
It's a steal at this price.
That's if you want it.
But we're gonna have to
make an offer today.
The owner's highly motivated.
Think it over.
I'll make some calls.
Take a look around.
Okay.
Thank you, Brian.
Thank you very much.
It's okay.
We're just gonna look.
My God.
Here you are.
We were just making sure
there was adequate closet space.
Good. Good.
Well, this house is yours
if you want it...
but you have to
decide right now.
We'll take it.
Really? Oh, my God!
You know what I kept thinking
when we were looking at that house?
That we should get
a mattress for that closet.
I kept thinking that
it felt like a dream come true.
Come here.
- How fast can you drive this thing?
- Really fast.
Let's see.
Okay.
- We bought a really, really...
- Excuse me. We bought a house.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
We bought a big house.
Mary.
Mary, are you all right?
Mary, talk to me.
Are you okay?
Can you hear me?
Jesus Christ!
Hold on, darling.
911, there's been an accident.
Yes.
Nothing.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
You okay?
Yeah.
All right.
It's all right.
It's just me.
You didn't see it, did you?
See what?
What did you see?
I didn't see anything.
There's something wrong with me.
It's called a glioblastoma.
It's a temporal lobe tumor.
According to the doctor,
it's extremely rare.
One in...
600,000 gets this thing.
Did they say it was
a result of the accident?
No, it turns out...
that it's been there a while.
There's nothing else they can do?
They did the surgery, and they
couldn't get it all out, so they'll...
keep her on the chemo...
as long as her strength holds out.
That's working.
I think she's looking better now.
Good.
That's good.
Two weeks ago...
we were house hunting.
One day you're just
driving along in your car...
and the universe...
just points at you and says...
"Ah, there you are,
a happy couple.
I've been looking for you.
I've been looking for you".
I'm sorry.
For what?
For all of this.
I feel like
I ruined everything.
You didn't ruin anything.
Not a damn thing.
I want you to be happy.
You didn't see it, did you?
Yes.
Yeah?
She knew.
What?
She was drawing angels.
It was the meanness
of the campaigns...
the almost complete lack
of candor and honesty...
that turned the voters off..
I think that these parties
are demonizing each other.
They're projecting our own
personal fears and anxieties...
onto the national stage.
People don't like it. People are
very, very unsatisfied at the moment.
It makes them complacent because they
don't see any possibility of change.
2004... Is there a dark horse candidate
out there for the Democrats?
Well, I'm hearing a lot
about Russ McCallum.
- Governor of Virginia.
- Yeah, he might do what Carter...
Hey, I told her to watch.
Who?
Peter's friend Gwen.
She'll be there tonight.
Oh, God. Look, I don't think I'm gonna
be able to make that one tonight.
Come on, you can't keep
blowing this thing off.
I'm not. I've got an interview
with the governor.
I gotta be in Richmond
at 8:00 in the morning.
I almost forgot.
McCallum's office called.
They bumped the meeting
till tomorrow night.
Eddie, look, I...
Look...
she's not Mary.
Not by a mile.
But you know what?
No one ever will be.
Hey, Ed.
I'm sorry about today.
I'm sure Gwen is very nice.
Maybe some other time.
It's about 1:00 in the morning.
I'm a little wired,
so I'm driving down to Richmond tonight.
I'll talk to you tomorrow.
Bye.
Al I right, come on.
Hi. I'm sorry. I know it's really late,
but my car broke down just up the road.
I wondered if I could
use the phone.
Hello.
It's him.
I been waitin' for you.
You son of a bitch.
What are you doin'?
Get the door! Get the door!
Just stay right there.
Mister, I don't know who you...
Shut up!
Shut up.
Honey, Connie's here.
Well, hey, Gordon.
How you doin'?
Okay, why don't you just...
put down the gun and tell me
what's going on here.
Yeah.
He's come around three nights in a row.
This son of a bitch is stalking us.
- I'm John Klein. My car broke down...
- Let's let Gordon finish, Mr. Klein.
Two nights ago...
at 2:30 in the a.m.,
there's a bang on the door.
I open it up,
and here's this guy.
He says he wants to use the phone.
But there's something
creepy about him...
so I tell him to get lost.
Last night at 2:30 on the dot,
guess who's back.
You're sure it was Mr. Klein here?
I am absolutely positive
it's Mr. Klein.
- Crazy. This is...
- I am not crazy.
- I didn't say that you...
- So then what happened?
I warned him off my property.
I used the word "trespass",
and he still came back.
You're lucky I'm a Christian, because I
had the right to shoot you on my porch.
He'd have to been
inside the house, Gordon.
What?
Fine.
So tonight I figured the dumb fuck might
come back, and sure enough, there he is.
It wasn't me.
I don't know what's happening here.
Something's very wrong here.
I don't know these people.
I have never been here before.
I'm from DC. Look.
It's a wallet, okay? Wallet?
I'm from DC.
My name is John Klein.
Washington Post.
Yes.
Can I get out of this shower now?
You can wait for me outside,
Mr. Klein.
We'll run a check on him.
Anyone else comes by, forget the gun.
Just call me.
Just find out what he wants.
So, you didn't actually see the guy
before tonight?
No.
But I heard the knocking.
Three nights in a row.
I'll talk to you tomorrow.
I'm gonna give you a ride into town,
unless you wanna sleep in your car.
I can call for a tow
in the morning.
You're a long way from DC.
What are you doing here?
Driving through.
We're not on the way
to anyplace, Mr. Klein.
I recognize you.
DC Review.
- You watch that?
- We're not all bumpkins.
So I'm not under arrest?
You didn't steal anything.
You didn't hurt anybody.
No breaking and entering.
You've had trouble
with him before?
Gordy and Denise? No.
They're good people.
Things have just been
a little strange around here lately.
You still haven't told me what you're
doing here in the middle of the night.
I don't know.
Where am I?
Think you could show me
where we are on the map here?
We're right on the state line.
With Ohio.
- What time did you leave DC?
- 1:00 in the morning.
If I was doing 80 the whole way, it
would've taken me six hours to get here.
- There's gotta be a logical explanation.
- I don't know.
By the way, don't worry about your pal
the governor. I'll take care of it.
Yeah. Okay.
Thanks, Eddie.
- So?
- It's running fine, Mr. Klein.
- Can't find a thing wrong with her.
- Really?
Strange.
- All right, what do I owe you?
- Nothin'.
I said I can't find
anything wrong with her.
Mr. Smallwood.
Mr. Smallwood...
I just wanted to apologize for that
misunderstanding we had last night.
Are you sure it was me that came by
the last couple of nights?
Listen, mister.
Connie called me.
She told me that you check out,
and that's good enough for me.
I'm perfectly willing
to let it go.
But I don't drink anymore...
and I don't lie.
And as far as I know,
I'm not crazy.
So if you're accusing me...
Look, here's the thing.
I don't know how
I ended up here last night.
I didn't even know
I was in West Virginia.
Some how, between 1:00 and 2:30...
I traveled 400 miles and ended up
on that road by your house...
and I've got no memory of it.
And you call me crazy?
I was afraid I'd see you here.
Okay.
You didn't show up.
Too bad. I really wanted
to know what I look like.
Sergeant, I'm curious.
Last night you said...
things had been strange...
around here lately.
- What kind of things?
- You really don't want to know.
Now I really need to know.
Just your odd reports.
People seeing things they can't explain,
so they all come to me.
'Cause you're the cop.
Because they know me.
You know, if there are
other people in this town...
who are feeling as...
confused as I am right now...
I'd sure like to hear it.
The past few months,
people have been coming up to me...
and reporting that they've
been seeing strange things.
I don't mean the town speed freak.
I mean good, honest, church going people.
I've known these folks
my entire life...
and they seem down right embarrassed
to be bringing it up.
Bringing what up?
It's hard to explain.
Weird lights,
strange phone calls, you.
Seeing a UFO is one thing.
What do you do when someone tells you
they saw this in their backyard?
What is it?
My wife died two years ago.
She saw something.
Drew pictures.
Who showed you this?
It was right here.
There was only a foot or so
between its head and that branch.
That makes it about...
eight feet tall.
Yeah.
I was getting ready for bed and just
happened to glance out the window.
At first all I could see...
were these two red eyes.
I kept looking at it.
I couldn't stop.
I've never had that feeling before,
like I couldn't move.
And then I guess it just...
took off..
That may not make much sense,
but it's...
the only way I can
put it into words.
You didn't see it, did you?
It started about two months ago.
Every time I answered the phone
I'd hear it.
The first one was just
a loud beeping noise.
Now they're mostly
these creaking, howling sounds.
They all like this?
Well, once it was a man
talking really fast.
- What'd he say?
- I couldn't make it out.
- Some foreign language.
- Have you had the line checked?
I even had our number changed.
But before I got a chance
to give it out to anyone...
the calls started again.
It's not a question of believing them.
Like I said, they're honest people.
- How long you lived here?
- My whole life.
- I grew up right over that hill.
- On a farm?
Shucks, no.
A real live house.
Indoor plumbing and everything.
Sorry.
We even had shoes for church
and schoolin' and stuff.
All right, all right.
Where the hell are you?
I'm still here.
- West Virginia?
- Yeah.
Something's come up.
You're kidding. Something of
national interest in West Virginia?
No, scientific.
I'll tell you about it later.
Cy's beginning to look rabid.
Keep him at bay, okay?
Are you okay?
You sound a little stressed.
No, I'm fine.
I'll talk to you later.
We were parked up here...
and sort a making out
in the back seat.
And what happened next...
is sort of hard to explain.
Next day...
I woke up and...
both my...
my eyes were swelled up.
What did the doctors say?
He couldn't explain it.
See this one here?
It ain't never healed.
We're getting engaged.
That's good.
- I gotta talk to you.
- Okay.
Last night I woke up...
with the worst headache
I've ever had in my life.
I went into the bathroom
to get some aspirin...
and I happened
to look in the mirror...
and...
I swear to God...
I see something...
I can't describe.
But it sure as hell...
is not my reflection.
And then...
I hear...
this weird...
howl...
coming out of the sink.
And there's a voice.
It's a voice...
and it's saying...
"Do not be afraid.
Ninety-nine will die.
Denver Nine".
I even wrote it down.
He just keeps saying the same thing
over and over for an hour...
and then it stops.
And when I wake up this morning
I look at this piece of paper...
where I wrote down the words...
and this thing is on it.
I did not draw that.
- Gordon?
- What?
Gordon, you...
your ear's bleeding.
What?
This CAT scan is clean, Gordon.
No sign of any physical problem.
Are you sure?
Because this man's wife had a tumor.
What you had, Gordon,
was a first-class migraine.
- I can write you a prescription.
- That'd be good.
- Thank you, Doctor.
- There were other symptoms, Doc.
He had hallucinations,
heard voices.
Aren't they both associated
with glioblastoma?
I see nothing here to suggest...
something as exotic
as glioblastoma, Mr. Klein...
but if you'd like I can refer
Mr. Smallwood to another neurologist...
for a second opinion.
- He's wrong.
- No, that'd be fine.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Wait. Wait.
He's not wrong.
Nothing's wrong.
He's not wrong
'cause there's nothing wrong.
There's nothing wrong.
You go to a doctor with a bleeding ear
and he tells you you got a headache...
Yes, well, you're not sick,
so that is good news.
I wish I was sick. Then I would
know why this is happening.
You shouldn't say things like that.
What should I say, Denise?
I'm hallucinating.
I'm hearing voices.
Was your wife hearing voices
before she had her tumor?
No.
13 News is headed to the scene,
and we'll have a live report in minutes.
Again our top story, Domain Air
flight 9 out of Denver has crashed.
An airline representative is expected
to make a statement shortly.
There is no confirmation...
but all 99 passengers and crew members
are believed dead.
Wow, man.
Could I speak to
Alexander Leek, please?
- This is Leek.
- Mr. Leek, this is John Klein.
I'm working on
a pretty strange story.
I was hoping you might be able
to help me out.
I'm particularly interested in your
theories on precognition and prophecies.
Anything you want to know
is in the book.
Yeah, but the chapter that you have
on the entities you call...
Were you contacted...
or are you pretending to have
a professional interest?
Yeah... No.
I'm a reporter
for The Washington Post.
Well, I'm sorry, Mr. Klein.
I don't work in those areas anymore.
I don't understand.
To hear a voice is one thing...
but this isn't just a message,
it's a prediction.
It came true.
These things Gordon's having,
are they dreams or hallucinations?
The way he describes them,
they sound like dreams.
I don't know.
He believes they're real.
I had a dream like that.
Yeah?
It was nighttime...
and I was
in the middle of the ocean.
I was trying to swim,
but I was too cold.
I kept looking...
I kept looking for something...
to hang on to.
And there were presents...
floating all around me.
They were wrapped up.
They were tied with bows.
I tried to grab on to them,
but they kept popping away.
And then I started to sink...
like a stone.
There was nothing I could do.
I was falling.
But it felt good.
I was letting go.
I was letting myself go...
and...
all I could see...
was black...
and all I could feel
was the darkness above me...
and the lights...
coming from below.
I knew I was dying.
And then I heard this voice,
like somebody whispering in my ear.
"Wake up, number 37".
And then I woke up.
What do you think that means?
Number 37?
I have absolutely no idea.
I met him.
The guy who told me
about the plane crash.
You met him?
Yeah.
I met him.
Last night, coming home
from work about midnight.
I'm driving past the cement plant...
out by the chemical factory.
Right.
Something happened.
Bright...
flash.
Lightning.
Something...
encircles me.
Everything's kind of hot.
I feel like I can't catch...
catch my breath.
He looked human.
But there was just something...
wrong about him.
That's when I heard the voice.
The same voice
that I heard two nights ago.
He said...
"Do not be afraid.
My name...
is Indrid Cold".
And he said to me...
"In a place this size.
Equator.
Three hundred.
Three hundred will die.
Wait for me.
I will return.
I will see you in time".
And that was it.
It's a little...
Have a look.
She knew.
I didn't see anything.
You want to hear
the chief's latest phone call?
Yes?
- Thank God you're there.
- Gordon?
I know I sounded crazy the other day,
but things are getting weird out here.
Slow down, Gordon.
- He's here.
- Who's here?
Indrid Cold.
He's standing right next to me.
Get over to Gordon's right away.
He says Indrid Cold is there.
Gordon, let me talk to him.
Sure. Hang on.
Hello, John Klein.
Who is this?
My name is Indrid Cold.
Unless, of course,
you're Gordon Smallwood.
Your father was born
in Racine, Wisconsin.
He lived in a green house
on Monroe Street.
You don't remember
how your mother looked.
Okay, you got my attention.
- Where's my watch?
- In your shoe.
Under the bed.
Very good, John.
Thank you.
What's in my hand?
Chap Stick.
You're reading my mind,
aren't you?
Did you read my mind?
I have no need to, do I?
What's the third line of page 51?
"A broken smile
beneath her whispered wings".
Still more proof, John Klein?
What do you look like?
It depends on who's looking.
I want to meet you.
You already have, John.
I have seen you afraid.
You're afraid right now,
aren't you?
Can I ask you something?
Why ask me
what you already know, John?
What happened to my wife?
You were there.
Mary Klein cannot be found
by looking.
You will see her in time.
What's up, Connie?
Everything okay?
Did you just call John?
I've been asleep since 9:00.
Unless, of course,
you're Gordon Smallwood.
See? It's sticking up here
around 1,950 cycles per second.
But it never gets any lower
than maybe 1,930 or so.
But yours is way down here
in the normal vocal range...
anywhere between 1,000
and 1,200 cycles per second.
Okay, so this guy's vocal range
is much higher than mine.
What makes you think it's a man?
Still more proof, John Klein?
What is it?
Near as I can tell, it's...
an electrical impulse.
But whatever it is, it's not
coming from human vocal cords.
Why ask me
what you already know, John?
What happened to my wife?
You were there.
Mary Klein cannot be found
by looking.
You will see her in time.
This isn't like you. We used to rip on
this stuff. when it came over the wire.
Yeah, I know.
- It's different when it happens to you.
- Do me a favor.
Talk to Cyrus today.
Tell him you got the flu. Any excuse.
I'll back you up.
I just wanna make sure
you still got a job...
when you're done doing
whatever it is you're doing down there.
Okay, I'll call you from Chicago.
What time is your flight?
8:00 a.m.
Am I crazy?
No.
I am crazy.
Alexander Leek.
- Who the hell are you?
-John Klein. I called you last week.
Do you know what that is?
Stay away.
I need to know what this is.
Tell me.
Where are they seeing it?
Point Pleasant, West Virginia.
You can help me.
Follow me.
The nocturnal butterfly.
In ancient cultures, the moth
represents a form of the psyche...
or the soul immortally trapped...
in the hellish death realms.
Mothman.
That's what the Ukranians called him.
Rough translation, of course.
There were 100 sightings in Chernobyl
the year the nuclear plant went down.
Galveston, 1969,
just before the hurricane.
They saw it.
But seeing isn't always believing.
Look, there's never been
a single shred of evidence...
to show that these things
exist materially.
So you're telling me
these things do not exist?
Oh, they exist. All kinds of things
exist around us that we never see.
Electricity, microwaves,
infrared waves.
You know, these things
have been around forever.
They show up in cave paintings.
They're a normal condition
of the planet.
They're just not part of our consensus
of what constitutes...
physical reality.
What are they part of, then?
You're asking for an explanation...
for something...
that can't be explained
rationally.
You know the buildup of energy
before something happens?
The way your hair stands up
before lightning strikes?
"Before something happens".
Do you mean they cause disasters?
Why would they need to?
All right, then...
are they trying to warn me?
Their motivations...
aren't human.
All right,
then what do they want?
I have no idea.
What you really want
is to know...
why you?
Yes.
You noticed them,
and they noticed that you noticed them.
Most people aren't sensitive enough
to see them...
without some kind of...
trauma.
What happened to you, Mr. Klein?
Last week my friend
got a strange phone call...
from an entity...
a spirit, whatever.
It seemed to know everything.
Like God?
- It made predictions that came true?
- Yes.
His name was Indrid Cold.
It's perception, John.
They appear differently to everyone.
A voice, a light, a man, a monster.
If your friend thinks it's God he spoke
to, he's off by more than a few degrees.
Then how do you explain
that it knows everything?
Look at that.
If there was a car crash 10 blocks away,
that window washer could likely see it.
That doesn't mean he's God...
or even smarter than we are.
But from where he's sitting...
he can see
a little further down the road.
I think we can assume that...
these entities
are more advanced than us.
Why don't they just come right out
and tell us what's on their minds?
You're more advanced
than a cockroach.
Have you ever tried explaining yourself
to one of them?
How many people have seen it?
Ten. Twenty, maybe.
Listen to me. Something terrible
is going to happen in Point Pleasant.
Don't go back.
Stay away.
I can't talk about this anymore.
There is a reason...
that I ended up in Point Pleasant.
Something brought me there.
Whatever brought you there...
brought you there to die.
You're just in time. They're just
about to light this Christmas tree.
They have been
for the last two hours.
Isn't that Denise?
Is she okay?
She left Gordon.
He got fired from the chemical plant.
Just stopped coming to work one day.
Shit.
- Where is he?
- Who knows?
Be back in a second.
Connie.
What's wrong?
Fifteen more people
reported seeing that thing today.
Fifteen.
Three of them were cops.
I hate this, John.
I absolutely goddamn hate this.
How was Chicago?
What did he say?
He wouldn't see me.
Shit.
You all right?
It's cold.
Get in the car, warm up.
I can't.
I'm waiting for him.
Everybody in this town is looking at me
like I'm insane. You know why?
Denise and all the others,
they don't know, John.
I do.
I don't think you're crazy.
Okay?
You talked to him too, John.
You know...
I've been lying awake at night.
I feel...
like I'm sleeping...
but I'm awake.
That's when I hear him.
And lately, when I hear him...
all at once...
I understand.
Everything.
John, do you remember
the last time you were happy?
It's real.
These things are real.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I want you to be happy.
Yeah?
What?
This is your wake-up call,
Mr. Klein.
I didn't ask for a wake-up call.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
What happened to you, Mr. Klein?
I can't believe I got through.
Gordon, where are you, man?
Speak up.
Listen, John, he was right.
Mr. Cold was right
about everything.
Right? Right about what?
I can't hear you.
He was right about understanding.
It's real, John.
I want you to know.
- It's real.
- What is... What are you talking about?
You've got nothing to worry about.
I'll see you in time.
Gordon?
Can they tell how long
he was out there?
Looks like he's been dead
about eight hours.
He died of exposure.
What made you come out here?
- He called me.
- When?
I didn't like
the way he sounded.
When did he call you, John?
About an hour ago.
I can't stand this.
It didn't seem right
to bring this up at the funeral...
but as far as I know there's never been
any accidents at the chemical plant.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
I got your message the other day.
I meant to call you back, but I forgot.
Don't you remember
leaving me that message?
Chief, this is John Klein.
I didn't call him.
No, it's not me.
I analyzed both tapes
with the voice print.
I don't care.
It may be my voice. It's not me.
- It is not me.
- Listen to me.
I would swear in a court of law
that that's your voice.
Yeah, great. Thanks.
Shit!
Regular coffee to go, please.
Seventy-five cents.
Have a great day.
Do you know that woman?
- What woman?
- She just left. You didn't see her?
- No.
- That's strange.
She had long red hair, green eyes, real
pretty, and she was asking about you.
- Did you see which way she went?
- No.
- What did she say?
- She asked a lot of strange questions.
What are you doing here?
And she asked if you were happy.
- What did you say?
- I asked her for some ID.
- Did she give you any?
- No.
She just said "Tell John I'm sorry for
ruining everything", and then she left.
What's wrong?
Was it her?
That's your wife?
It was her.
- I'm not sure.
- What?
I mean, the hair is different.
- Oh, come on!
- What?
- This is the woman you saw.
- No, it isn't, John.
Now, I agree
there is a similarity...
Bullshit!
John, it's all right.
I'm not all right.
This is the woman you saw.
She was here. This woman.
Don't you do this to me.
I'm sorry, John.
I feel like
I've ruined everything.
I'm so sorry.
I need to know
what happened to you.
Please.
Come in.
I was a physics professor
at Cornell.
Tenured.
You can look me up.
One day
I started hearing voices.
The voices became messages.
Before long, I was fully convinced
that I was receiving...
predictions of disaster
from outside intelligences.
But you were, weren't you?
John, I had tapes
of their voices.
I knew a building was going to blow up,
and I tried to prevent it...
but no one listened.
What happened?
People died.
Many people died.
I was investigated,
almost arrested.
My wife divorced me.
My kids...
stopped speaking to me.
Do you know what four years in
a psychiatric hospital can do to you?
Everything...
gone.
Oh, you'll never understand
their messages.
You'll misinterpret them.
I did.
It almost destroyed me.
In the end,
it all came down to just...
one simple question.
Which was more important...
having proof...
or being alive?
Trust me.
I turned away years ago...
and I've never looked back.
Didn't you need to know?
We're not allowed to know.
It's me, Cyrus.
John, is that you?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's me.
Whatever you are doing,
you drop it.
Governor McCallum
is going to Charleston.
Then he's touring that chemical plant
in Point Pleasant today.
Now, I want you to go down there...
and meet him at the airport.
You listening?
Yeah, McCal I um...
at the chemical plant. Got it.
I need to know that
you're gonna be there.
John, are you there?
Ohio.
Great tragedy
on the River Ohio.
I can't call in sick just because
you have a bad feeling about today.
Just think about this.
Gordon saw weird lights in the sky.
They show up
over the chemical plant.
Josh gets a call from me,
but it's not really me.
I'm talking about something bad
happening at the chemical plant.
Then I get this message
from this Indrid Cold...
who's talking about
a great tragedy on the Ohio River.
Guess what's on the Ohio River.
The chemical plant.
Today Governor McCallum
is gonna be there.
I was on my way to interview him.
That's how I ended...
That's how I ended up here.
My God.
That's why I'm here.
He was right.
Who was right?
You saw Leek.
- He was part of the warning.
- What?
He was part of the warning.
Stop, stop, stop.
I didn't want to scare you.
He said...
He said the messages are real.
Something terrible
is gonna happen.
Connie, please.
We have to leave here now.
I will not live
my life like that.
I will not make decisions based
on messages from Indrid Cold.
He may be real to you.
He's not real to me.
Okay, I'm going to Charleston.
I'll be at the Marriott.
Get yourself reassigned.
I don't want you anywhere
near the plant today.
What if nothing happens?
What if there's no great tragedy?
What'll you do then?
- That's not the point.
- Well, I think it is the point.
- Gordon believed what he heard too.
- I am not Gordon!
I know what's gonna happen.
You have to leave now.
I have to report to work.
We can talk about this later.
- Governor?
- Good to see you, John.
I need to speak with you.
It's urgent.
- What's this about, John?
- It's the tour.
You can't do it. You can't go.
Listen to me.
Cancel it. Cancel the tour.
Cancel it. Make them
shut down the plant now.
The plant's gonna blow up
while you're there.
Where are the cops?
What are they doing?
- This is McCallum's chief aide.
- They don't know yet.
Have you received a bomb threat?
I didn't say anything about a bomb.
There's a source.
- I know this sounds...
- You're messing up here, John.
Get me Cyrus Bills at the Post.
Our top story takes us tonight
to Point Pleasant...
- where Virginia Governor McCallum...
- Turn it up!
toured the Edgewater
Petrochemical plant.
In what he's called
a successful review...
Governor McCallum has given
high marks to this petrochemical plant.
He is expected to call
for similar renovations...
at several Virginia plants.
WOWK-TV 13...
has an exclusive look inside
at what the governor saw.
Son of a bitch.
I congratulate my friends
at Edgewater Petrochemical...
on a job well done.
- Success here at Point Pleasant...
- Excuse me, Mr. Klein.
You have a message.
Come in.
- Back to Washington?
- Yeah.
- Do you have to go?
- I have to go.
- If this is about today...
- No, it's not.
I got a message.
I have to go home.
I have to be there noon
on Friday.
John, do you realize
what's happening to you?
I have to go.
Hey, it's me.
- Connie?
- Yeah.
I thought we could chat
for, say, 10 or 15 minutes.
- I'm sorry. Can I call you back?
- No,you can't.
- I booked you a flight.
- What?
It leaves Dulles
for Columbus, Ohio at 1:45.
I tried to get you on the one to
Charleston, but they're all booked up.
So if you leave now,
you'll just make it.
I can't.
It's Christmas Eve, John.
You shouldn't be alone.
I can't.
Yeah, you can.
You know...
when Mary got sick...
I couldn't help thinking...
this isn't real.
I can stop this.
I know I can.
No one can stop it, John.
Listen to me.
Planes are going to crash.
Earthquakes are going to happen.
People you know and love
are going to die...
and no matter what
that voice tells you...
there's nothing
you can do about it.
It's two years to the day.
He told me that she's going to call.
He said that Mary's going to call.
He's lying.
Whoever calls
may sound like her...
but it's not gonna be her.
I don't know what happens to us
after we die...
but I'll bet you
wherever Mary is now...
she's nowhere near Indrid Cold.
What if it is her?
She's dead, John.
The only important question now is
how do you want to remember her?
I miss her so much.
I know you do.
Of course you do.
But, John, listen...
you can miss her here
just as easily as there.
Even more easily because there,
you're all alone.
And that's just no way to be.
You do whatever you need to do...
and I'll understand.
But here,
we have dinner at 6:00...
and we open presents at 8:00.
And we hope we see you.
Okay?
Bye, John.
WJMP time is 5:51
on this chilly Christmas Eve.
Come on.
- You know what's going on down there?
- Some problem with the traffic lights.
Shit.
Great tragedy on the River Ohio.
My God...
Get off the bridge!
Everyone's gotta get off the bridge!
Get off! Everyone get out
of your cars and get off!
C.J., come on!
You've gotta get off.
Turn the damn thing down.
- What?
- You gotta get off the bridge now!
- Get out! Get out!
- Let's go!
Get off!
Get off the bridge!
Oh, God!
Go!
Get out of the car!
Get off the bridge!
Quick!
Let's get out!
Get out!
Come on. Get out.
All units, this is unit 64.
Get out!
Signal 33 on the Silver Bridge.
Rose, do you copy?
Signal 33 on the Silver Bridge...
Wake up. Wake up.
Here we go.
You are here.
I didn't know
if I was dreaming or...
I left DC right after you called.
You did call me, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, I called.
- How bad is it?
- It's bad.
But I supposed
it could've been a lot worse.
Are they done with the search?
Thirty-six.
Looks like about 36 people.
Jesus.
Thirty-six?
Wake up, number 37.
Wake up