Ah, there. Puccini should do the trick.
Let it carry you away.
There, now. Better?
Thank you. Oh, no. No, I
haven't always practiced here.
Mystory?
I believe there's a story
to be told on every corner.
I had a beautiful wife.
I had a beautiful home.
We had a perfect life together.
Brooke!
Underneath that clean, white surface,
there was the stench of decay.
Brooke!
Hello.
The IRS?
Yes. Yes, it's me.
Yeah, look, Mr. Goldblum. No.
No, Sir, I'm not trying to avoid you,
but I told you before all my returns
are handled by my business
manager. It's just a mistake.
It's their mistake.
You can't do this to me.
Yes. Yes, we can meet.
My office. No. No, no.
Not this afternoon. I'm
sorry. That is impossible.
Fine, fine. Whatever you say.
Yes, a checkup.
Yes, I could.
I'll see you then.
What is it, honey?
Look at this.
What?
There. You can't see that? The stain?
How could you let them send it back
looking like that? I can't wear that.
I'm sorry. I must have missed it.
Now, I have to wear this.
Well, what's wrong with it?
My diamond cufflinks. When I wear white
shirts, I wear my diamond cufflinks,
but I can't wear my diamond cufflinks because
they're still at the jeweler's having
the stones reset, unless of
course, you picked them up for me.
I didn't have a chance. I've been
working on a fundraiser all week long...
Things are going to hell around
here. This has got to stop, Brooke.
I wanted to wait until tonight but...
Happy anniversary.
Platinum. You are amazing.
What would I do without you?
I don't know.
They must have cost a fortune.
Oh, god.
I just...
Where are we going tonight?
That is my surprise. You
just be ready at seven.
Well, I need to know what to wear.
Your black dress.
Oh, that little black dress?
That little black
dress. Happy anniversary.
Honey, you know what?
You're not wearing anything.
Well, I was going to take
a shower after you left.
You were dressed like that
in front of the pool man?
I'm wearing a robe.
Yeah, but you got to be
careful. You know what I mean.
Alan, don't ruin it.
You've been smoking.
- I have not.
You're lying to me. I can
smell it on your breath.
Now, I have to brush my teeth
again. Just be ready by seven.
Fine.
Nothing. No matter how good
or how pure is free of decay,
once the decay gets started,
it can only lead to
rot, filth, corruption.
Hey. Hey, what is all that brown crap?
Make sure you clean that up, right?
Hey, your filter's shot, man. You need a
new one. I'll take care of it next week.
No. No, no. Not next week, I want
it done tomorrow. Do you hear me?
Oh, man. I'm busy tomorrow.
If you want to keep your job,
you'll have it done tomorrow.
Like I said, tomorrow, man.
The filth was everywhere.
The infection was spreading.
How deep did it go?
Right to the nerve.
Oh, yeah. Oh, baby.
Ah, yes.
Oh yeah.
Oh, that's good.
Get your filthy hands off her.
I am very disappointed in you.
Please, Mr. Feinstone.
- Doctor. Dr. Feinstone.
I am a dentist and this is my wife,
you filthy piece of shit.
Please, please.
Do you know what that means?
It means that she has got a
perfect bite. Come on, hon.
Show him how good your teeth are.
Show him your teeth, you lying
bitch, you cunt sucking whore.
No.
Show him.
- No.
No.
Is the dentist here or what?
If you could just have a seat.
Dr. Feinstone will see you
all just as soon as he can.
Jody has jamboree at 10:30.
There won't be a problem. We
don't want him to miss that.
Could you fill this out
for me, please? Thank you.
I'm sorry. I can't wait anymore.
He'll be with you just
as soon as possible.
I've been waiting over an hour.
Would you like to make
another appointment?
I had an appointment.
I'm sorry, Mr. Schaeffer. If you
could just relax and have a seat.
I know he'll be with you as
soon as possible. Mr. Schaeffer.
Any sign of him?
No.
Great. We're going to have
to rush the morning patients.
I know. I know. 8:30 already left.
This is all going to be
my fault somehow. Watch.
Good attitude, Jessica.
- Watch.
April. April Reign.
Where is he? I'm calling him.
Alan, what are you doing here?
Paula. I didn't want to call from
the house, but I'm thinking about
throwing Brooke a
surprise party next week.
I wanted to make sure
the time was good for you.
Yeah. What day?
Friday.
Friday is good.
You really should
schedule a time. A checkup.
God, I hate dentists.
Yeah, but we've got that filling
to redo. It's only getting worse.
Well, I guess I should.
The office will call then.
Matt.
Hey, what's up, baby?
What's up, baby?
Welcome to heaven.
It's kind of neat.
Well, Dr. Feinstone believes that
it helps to relax the patient.
I could certainly use some relaxing.
You're a beauty queen.
Just the state fair.
I'm sorry. The doctor is not in yet.
Okay, fine. Thank you.
Will you excuse me for a
minute? I'll be right back.
Dr. Feinstone?
You know I don't want
you anymore. You bore me.
Hey, like I said, tomorrow, man.
I'll throw her out into the streets
where she belongs with nothing.
Just fill this out for
me, please. Thank you.
Hi.
- I know I'm early.
You're not due until 11:30.
Couldn't wait, huh?
I know. No more braces. Thank god.
Tonight, I'm going to have
this really cool party.
I'd like you to schedule an appointment
for Mrs. Roberts for tomorrow afternoon.
Okay.
No, no. You've got your
seminar tomorrow afternoon.
Right. See if you can make
it first thing tomorrow.
Okay.
Oh, Mr. Schaeffer, your 8:30, had
to leave, but Jody Sanders is ready.
It's his first time.
Jody Sanders.
- Oh, that's us.
Jody, it's your turn. Isn't
this exciting, sweetheart?
I know you're just going to do great.
Hi, there. How you doing today, Jody?
Fine.
Is this your first trip to the
dentist? Are you a little scared?
No? Good. Give me five.
All right. Let's go.
Thank you.
I was lying down in my office.
I had a little migraine.
We're just glad to have you here.
Isn't this exciting?
Jessica, could you help me
with the patient, please?
I'm sorry. I didn't
know you had arrived.
I've been here for almost two hours.
We'll be in the rainforest room.
Jessica, where's the patient's tray?
It's all prepared.
I'll go get it for you,
O' king of the jungle.
Have you taken a look around, huh?
Yes.
We've turned dentistry
into interactive medicine.
What do you think about this
room here, Jody? Huh? Pretty cool?
You see, I think it's important
for the patient to enjoy a positive
dental experience conducive to continued
care. You ready to get started?
Today, I'm just going to
take a look at your teeth.
That's all I'm going to
do. Just a little look.
You can hold my hand, honey.
Okay. Now, I want you to open your
mouth nice and wide for Jessica.
You've built up quite
a practice, doctor.
A lot of money in
dentistry these days, huh?
I work hard.
Too hard to lose it all.
I'm sure that won't happen.
You're doing really good, honey.
If I kick her out,
she'll take everything.
What?
Every penny I ever made.
What did you do? He's bleeding.
He moved. He has to learn to sit still.
Mrs. Sanders, we're very sorry.
It's okay, Jody. We're going to go home.
This visit is over, Dr. Feinstone.
Mrs. Sanders...
- It's over.
Doctor, are you all right?
We can't take children anymore. That
child is spoiled. Spoiled rotten.
Mrs. Sanders, what...
It's okay, Jody. We're going to go home.
They're okay.
I remember my first time
at the dentist. I bit him.
Oh, we charge extra for that.
Under control. Keep it under control.
Alan?
Oh, my god. Alan.
Are you all right?
What's the matter? Here.
I'm fine. I'm fine. What do you want?
I just finished with Miss Reign,
but if you're not feeling well...
Is there a problem?
Oh, well. You don't have to see her.
There's nothing major indicated.
Why don't you rest for a while?
Hello.
Hello. Who is this?
It's me.
Alan?
Yes, your husband Alan.
I know who you are, silly.
Brooke, I was just sitting here
trying to remember our first practice.
Alan, you're not having
a moment, are you?
You know what you get
like. Take one pill.
I love you.
Is something the matter?
Alan, is everything okay?
I'm just running a
little late. That's all.
You'll have to meet me
at the office tonight.
Okay.
Tonight then?
Tonight.
Our anniversary.
All right. Bye bye.
Asshole.
Bitch.
April, the doctor is busy right now,
but he'll be able to see you next time.
Well, I think Steve, my
manager, wanted to talk to him.
He thinks my mouth needs a makeover.
It's the only part of me
he hasn't totally rebuilt.
Well, I'll make you another appointment.
Well, Karen. Who do we have here?
This is April Reign. I'm sorry,
doctor. I thought you were busy.
All the time. Decay is always
busy, so we're always busy.
How's the patient?
She looked fine, doctor. Nothing
that calls for immediate attention.
Good. We'll just take a little look.
Well, all she needed was a cleaning.
So I could be irresistible
with all the world at my feet.
There's a shadow here on number
31 right there on the X-ray.
Yes, doctor. There is some abrasion
on the lingual at the gum line.
Tell Jessica I'll need a filling tray.
Okay.
You have a cavity on one of your lower
right molars. It isn't too serious,
but we really should take a
look it before it gets any worse.
Will you have to drill?
They're your teeth. You wouldn't
want them to fall out, would you?
It's really not bothering me at all.
Well, we'll give you
a little anesthetic.
You won't feel anything at all.
I have this thing about needles.
Well, then, we'll give you a topical.
Needles really freak me out.
Have you ever had nitrous oxide?
Right through the snapper.
Jesus, here.
All right. Doggie bursts through fence.
Growl. Assailant shoots doggie.
Bullet goes right through here.
I think he shot the doggie.
Elementary, my dear Watson.
You don't think this is a robber,
do you? He's never used a gun before.
He's never had a dog attack him before.
To the lab. Check out the neighbors.
Cop stuff, huh?
Now, did you talk to
anybody else about it?
All right. Is that comfortable? Just
keep breathing nice deep breaths.
You have an interesting name.
Steve wanted to call me April Showers,
but I liked Reign, like a queen,
not just like Rain.
Just keep breathing normally. Everything
will be fine in a couple of seconds.
I'm fine. Why don't you take a break?
You don't want me to assist you?
Not necessary.
Are you sure?
Yes, doctor.
Open.
Right, right over there. There we go.
All right. Now, just keep breathing.
Are you a model? You look like a model.
Have you ever done any runway work?
It ain't easy. No sir. Those girls got
to be very confident to get up there
in front of those judges. They got
to have the walk. You want to try?
No.
We all got to have our secret dreams.
Go on. Stand up. Give it a shot.
No, I've never...
I don't know how. I've
never done anything like...
Come on. Take a few
steps to a new beginning.
Go on.
Hold your head up.
Like this?
That's it. More attitude. Throw
some attitude. Lots of attitude.
Do a little turn right
here. That's it. Beautiful.
Excuse me.
What the hell is going
on with April back there?
Dr. Feinstone is taking care of her.
- Yeah?
You okay, Sarah?
Oh, yeah. I was just stretching.
How are you feeling?
All right.
You don't hurt me, doctor,
and I won't hurt you.
Filth.
Whore.
All right. Just relax.
This won't hurt a bit.
That's what men always say.
They're the biggest liars.
Just keep breathing.
That's it. Deep, slow breaths.
I'd like to speak to the doctor,
please. He's got to know that April
and I have another appointment
and it's getting late.
I know and I'm sure
he'll be finished soon.
I hope so. You got a bathroom here?
Yeah, down the hall and to the left.
Excuse me.
May I help you?
I was wondering where the bathroom was?
It's right over there.
Do it to me, Alan.
Like a big, strong man.
Come on, baby.
Oh yeah, just like Matt.
Just like Matt?
Death is too good for you.
What?
- The nitrous must have run out.
I don't feel good.
You'll be fine in a couple
of minutes. Just relax.
I have to go now.
Please just stay there and sit
still for a couple of minutes.
Steve, Steve.
Please could you...
Please would you just sit back down?
Please. Please come back. Please.
This is not what I
advise. Would you just...
You come back inside?
What's the matter?
What's the problem?
Who are you?
I'm Steve Landers,
doctor. April is my client.
Steve.
- Yeah, baby?
Yes. Well, yes. She's had a
minor reaction to a small dose
of nitrous oxide. That's all.
- Wow.
No, no, no. It's nothing serious.
She'll be fine in a minute or two.
Okay. You're going to
be okay, baby? All right.
No.
Would you both like to just come inside
and sit down until she's ready to leave?
Some fresh air though might
bring her around a little faster.
Why don't you pick her up so she
doesn't fall? I'll be right there.
Okay. We're going to bring you outside
in the fresh air and you'll feel better.
We tried to make her feel
a little more comfortable
when she wasn't feeling so well.
This is the quickest way out.
We'll get you some fresh air,
baby. You'll be all right.
They're dropping like flies.
Candy, one of the tanks
of nitrous is dead.
I'm switching over to the other
one, but we need to order a backup.
More gas? Okay. You got it.
Mrs. Roberts will be
here first thing tomorrow.
She also asked if you'd
noticed anything this morning?
Noticed?
I don't know. Her dog was killed. She just
thought perhaps you'd seen something.
No? Okay.
Karen.
I'll be right back. We're almost
done. Then the doctor will see you.
I can't wait. It's all I've been thinking
about, just being able to smile.
What? I'm with a patient.
Look what I found in room
number one. Talk about heaven.
Did you show Alan?
Are you kidding? Did you see when
the patient left how she left?
He did something to her.
- Maybe they fell out of her purse.
Yeah, right and I can make
flames shoot out of my ass.
Well, give them to me and I'll ask him.
No. I don't want to cause any more
trouble. I'm already on his shit list.
I'll be with you in a moment.
Mr. Goldblum,
Dr. Feinstone is with a patient
and really can't be disturbed.
Look, lady. I'm telling
you he'll see me right away.
I don't think this is a good time to...
Doctor, this is Mister...
- Marvin Goldblum, IRS.
Ah, yes. Mr. Goldblum,
I was expecting you a little later.
As you can see, I'm a
little behind here right now.
You know, Dr. Feinstone, Alan...
You don't mind if I call you
Alan, right? You can call me Marv.
You got real tax problems. You
need to do a good job for me.
I got a little action back there.
All right. All right. Why don't
you just come in back here?
Thank you.
You fucking pervert.
I ought to kick the shit out of you.
What you did to April,
we're suing you, man.
Alan, what's happening?
This guy, this guy right here
is a fucking degenerate, a sicko.
We're going to sue your ass.
Is he all right?
Doctor, do you want
me to call the police?
No. I'm fine.
It's really not your day.
I'm fine.
- Are you okay?
I'm fine. The patient just overreacted.
You don't know what it's like.
The discipline, the long hours
and the lack of respect in a world
that goes on ignoring dental hygiene.
- Doctor.
What happened?
- You're okay.
I'm sorry, everybody. This
has never happened before.
Why don't you all just
please just go home?
This way. Come on. Easy.
Easy.
Is he crazy, Alan,
or something happened?
I told you. Nothing happened, Karen.
Come on. You know me better than that.
Look. Tell Candy to close up.
The rest of you take the day off.
Please, just go.
If it's what you want.
- Yes. Thank you.
Well, my mom isn't picking me up
until 1:30, so maybe I can wait
in case he can still see me.
I'm sorry, honey. You
heard what the doctor said.
I think it may have to wait another day.
Who do they think they are
with their vile infected lives?
Happy anniversary, Brooke.
Alan? Are you here?
Alan, we're going to be
late for the reservation.
Alan?
My dear.
I wanted you to be the first
to see my finest achievement.
Operatory number four.
La Scala, the home of the Italian opera,
the finest opera house in the world.
I wanted it to be a surprise
for you for our anniversary.
Impressive.
In a world where romance has
been replaced by technology,
in this room, the two are wed.
Please, sit.
Just how many pills did you take?
Do you hear how she hits
the high notes so perfectly
from the depths of her soul?
She sings of love.
All love.
We're going to lose our table.
Brooke, please. Humor me.
Well, Alan. I mean, this really
doesn't seem like a good time.
Brooke, it's our anniversary.
Pretty please?
Just enough.
We wouldn't want to lose you.
You thought you could fool me, huh?
Oh, no. I've been watching you. I've
been watching what you've become.
Filth, just like the rest of them.
You, Paula Roberts, Matt.
You wouldn't want me to cut
out your tongue, would you?
What would Matt think?
You wouldn't be much use to him then.
Tonight, you pay for all
that you've done to me.
Mercy?
You want me to show mercy?
Not tonight, my sweet.
I never use it, the pool.
I built it for you.
Maybe I should.
We could swim together.
That's the way we were meant to be,
together forever.
No one will come between us.
Dr. Feinstone. Gibbs, LAPD
and this is Detective Sunshine.
Is there something wrong, detective?
The world is full of
wrong, doc. May we come in?
I was just having breakfast.
The most important meal of the
day. I'm a fruit man myself.
We've got a couple of
questions we'd like to ask you.
There's been a series of
robberies in the neighborhood.
We were wondering if maybe you might
have heard something, seen something.
No, I've heard nothing, seen nothing.
Mrs. Feinstone?
- What do you mean?
Well, did she hear or see anything
out of the ordinary yesterday morning?
I don't think so but I could
ask her when she wakes up.
Well, she's a lucky lady. Soon
as the sun hits my eyes, I'm up.
Here's my card.
Give me a call.
Do either of you own a firearm?
No.
You're a dentist, right?
Yes.
That's a little like a
cop, a necessary evil.
What the...
Oh, god.
Brooke. Hey, Brooke.
God.
Shame on you.
No, man. Don't. Don't.
It's doctor,
Dr. Feinstone and Brooke is my
wife, you filthy piece of shit.
I am an instrument of
perfection and hygiene,
the enemy of decay and corruption,
a dentist, and I have
a lot of work to do.
Don't you guys ever
start on time around here?
It won't be long now. I promise.
Hello, Sarah.
Hi. I had to postpone the party.
Paula, would you like to come in?
Well, this certainly is a little
different. You can 86 the tunes, honey.
All right. We're just
going to numb up that molar.
Jessica, we're doing a
replacement on number 18.
I think Dennis shot the dog, Alan. He
knew I'd finally gotten attached to it.
What?
You didn't see anything
yesterday, did you?
No. Open wide.
God.
We're just going to let that
numb up for a second, all right?
It happened right after you left, you
know. Matt didn't see anything either.
Matt?
The new guy from the pool service.
That Matt, he's real good.
Jessica, give me the burr block.
How's he been working out for you?
Oh, we've been having a little problem
with our sludge filter lately, but
I think we've got
that all cleared up.
Doctor.
Doctor?
What?
Can I speak to you for a moment?
Just relax, Paula.
I'll be right back.
Doctor, what were you doing
using that doughnut burr?
You were destroying that woman's tooth.
Are you questioning me?
Don't you think I know
what my patient wants?
Doctor...
Don't ever do that
again. I run this office.
Yes, I know.
When I tell you to do
something, you do it.
Now, get back in there and
take care of the patient. Now.
Alan, I need to talk to you.
Do you think that this could wait?
I am in the middle of a procedure.
I don't think so. Candy just got a
call from a Mr. Goldblum from the IRS.
I think you should leave now.
When is he coming?
- Now, I guess.
Leeches. Bloodsucking leeches.
Where the hell is she?
She insisted on leaving.
You clearly haven't learned what it
takes to perform your duties here.
The patient comes first. You should
have made her more comfortable.
Wait a minute. Are you blaming me?
Not only am I blaming you, I am firing
you and don't expect a recommendation.
I have found your work here to
be thoroughly unprofessional.
Unprofessional? You're the one
who destroyed that woman's molar.
What about this? That woman yesterday,
the one they carried out of here,
what did you do to her?
Nothing.
Right. Like you had to
remove these to fill a cavity.
Everyone else here is
scared to death of you
but not me. I'm going to shut you down.
Jessica. Nothing happened.
Bullshit. I'm going to report
you to the Dental Association.
You filthy pig. You dirty, disgusting...
Oh, fuck you. You're the pig.
When are you going to see
a dentist about that tooth?
I'd rather live with the
pain. What have you got?
You were right, Sherlock.
This is not our robber.
A .380 caliber slug flattened
by the dog's cranium.
Surprise me, Sunshine. Surprise me.
There's about 300 registered gun owners
in a two-mile radius of the house.
Nearer, nearer.
Across the street, a Dr. Feinstone is
a fully subscribed, bona fide member
of the Encino Gun Club and a
registered owner of a .380 Walther PPK.
A regular James Bond.
James Bond regular.
No.
Sarah, you're up next.
Just go on back and let
him know you're next.
Okay.
Hi. Remember me?
I'm next.
She's been waiting an
awfully long time already.
Yeah, two years and one day.
Kid, you'll understand. See,
Dr. Feinstone can't kept me waiting.
It's in his own interest or
do we start the audit now?
Look, Mr. Goldblum, I...
It's all right, Sarah.
He won't be too long.
You understand.
I can't take this.
Kid, that's nice but
next time take the money.
I'll let myself in.
Hey, Doc, you got business.
Why don't you go in that
first room right there?
Yes, boss.
Real nice place here, Alan.
Hell, this place is like a palace.
Like your home.
You got all these beautiful
rooms here. Real special.
You're not going to
put them on, are you?
I was just in the gas closet.
You're not out?
What?
- Nerve gas.
I was hoping for a little
whiff of the goof today.
Please, have a seat.
What do you want from me, Mr. Goldblum?
Alan, I've seen your returns.
You're doing really well here,
but those deductions...
Whoo. I mean, really?
You didn't really think...
I mean, with penalty and
interest, it could cost you plenty.
What do you mean?
Alan, I'm your friend. I don't have to
go to my supervisor with this, you know?
Lot cheaper to pay me than Uncle Sam.
How much?
You can start with these.
We'll use laser bonding
to reattach them.
Good. Lasers, yeah. Make me look nice.
Hey, doc. Don't take
what I'm saying personal.
After all, we don't have
any secrets now, do we?
Got a great marriage.
I can tell by your returns.
You spend plenty on her.
Hot stuff.
Well, is she, Doc?
Really hot?
I'm sorry, Doc. I know I got
a dirty mind. It's this job.
You spend so much time in the sewer.
You can't help getting a little dirty,
but I guess as a tooth
man, you know all about it.
Mild sedation is called for. I'm going
to be administering some nitrous oxide.
Great. Go for it, doc. Seize the day.
I'll take care of your little problem.
Just breathe normally and relax.
Brooke. Such a waspy name.
Those shiksa broads really
know how to do the deed,
don't they, doc?
I love it.
Am I right or am I right?
What the hell?
You'd never be satisfied, would
you? Much worse than I thought, Marv.
The decay is out of control. It's
gone right through to your soul.
Come on, Marv. Open wide.
Hi,
I'm Matthew Zeigler. Estrada Dental
Supply Company. How you doing today?
What is today? Thursday?
Thursdays, I'm good.
Great. I'm your new area representative.
I was hoping to meet
with the doctor today.
You can meet me. I do all the ordering.
I'm the office manager, Candy Wittridge.
Hey, you hear it all the time. Every dentist
has a screamer or two for a patient.
Oh, god.
This may take a while.
Get your tongue out of the way.
Get it out of the way, god damn it.
Alan?
What? What is it?
Is there a problem?
No. No. Not anymore. Low pain
threshold. The patient is fine now.
Okay.
Thank you.
Have you seen Jessica?
She's not here. I had to let her go.
We're short-staffed as it is.
We'll just have to perform her duties
ourselves for the rest of the day.
That's all.
Maybe there shouldn't be a rest of
the day. Maybe we should close up
until things are under control.
Things are under control. Everything is
under control. This is a business, Karen.
My business. I cannot afford
to have a bad day. Please.
Go back to work.
I just don't get it.
Why would he want to shoot a dog?
He's a dentist. They're
capable of anything.
Did you know dentists have
the highest rate of suicide?
Let's go. Come on.
Call for backup. I'm going in.
- Okay.
Oh, Jesus.
Jessica?
Alan?
Help me.
Alan.
It's horrible, isn't it?
The discoloration,
the periodontal deterioration,
the smell.
We deal with this every day
and we clean it up, the filth they make.
They hate us for it.
Filthy whore.
She put his dirty, rotten in her mouth.
Don't fight it, Karen. The air
bubbles will go to your brain
and then it will be poof.
Dr. Feinstone.
Karen?
Doctor?
Dr. Feinstone.
Yes.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Sarah Andrews is still
here. I'm breaking for lunch.
Karen or Jessica can assist.
Shall I send Sarah back?
Yes.
Nothing goes on around here
without me knowing about it.
Candy, have you ever had the
slippery shrimp at Yang Chow's?
Not this week.
The doctor will see you
now. You can come on back.
Hey, can I take your order for a new
tropical flavored dental floss today?
Dr. Feinstone?
Doctor?
What we've got here is a seriously
derailed train. A man over the edge.
Black and whites will
meet us at his office.
Take a look.
I think they look great.
So sad. Now, it can only be ruined.
The rest of your life can only
spoil what we've made.
The idea that every second,
they're just rotting away.
Can you live with that?
I don't think you can.
Please somebody help me.
Sarah?
Sarah.
Sorry, Sarah.
Please. Let me explain.
Come on out now, Sarah.
Sarah. You can't hide.
Not from your dentist.
I know where you are.
Why didn't you answer
when I called you, Sarah?
So sorry, Sarah.
So young,
so innocent.
Still decay is just
knocking at your door.
Open wide, Sarah. Let me in.
Do you understand that's the way it is?
Do you?
I'm sorry.
Please. I won't eat candy. I'll
brush three times a day. Please.
Pretty please.
Pretty please, Dr. Feinstone.
Three times a day. Three times a day.
Three times a day.
No candy.
Three times.
Three times a day. No candy.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
It's okay. It's okay.
Just tell me where he
is. You're safe now.
He didn't say where he was going? Did he
say anything at all? A place, anything?
A good marriage. A great dentist.
Did he mention a name? Anybody?
A respected teacher.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
God, will you shut up? Don't you
get it? He's a fucking lunatic.
Did you say teacher?
I really think she need some anesthetic.
Pain is an abstract emotion.
It has to be managed, shaped,
disregarded as a distraction. Continue.
What have we got here?
A pulsating gum. A vile
and infected pulsating gum.
Just ready and waiting for lancing.
I want a second opinion.
My second opinion is extract.
Extract what?
All of them.
You heard me. Extract.
What is he talking about?
I want everybody to extract.
I said extract.
My god.
- Now!
Extract now. I said extract.
Why did you kill me, Alan?
Why?
You sick bastard.
Feinstone, drop the gun now.
Now.
Move it. Move it. Move it. Go. Go.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Damn.
Out of the way.
That way. That way.
Enough about me.
You sure want the anesthetic?
You won't feel the pain.
Okay, Feinstone. It's time
for your regular visit.
No. I won't. I won't go.
You can't make me.
I won't. I won't.
Okay, guys.
Please no.
Yes.