Lizzy my mom tells me there's
no such thing as monsters.
But she is wrong.
They are out there,
waiting for you...
watching.
They are in the dark...
Sometimes where you see them...
Sometimes where you don't.
I know that now.
Momma.
Stop. Stop shaking me.
Get up!
Stop.
Did I oversleep?
Yes. Get up.
I am getting up.
You said 8:00, it's 9:00!
Are you ready to go?
I packed for me, and I packed
for you.
Where's Roy? He said he was
gonna call me.
He's an ass.
Damn it, Elizabeth.
Get up.
Go load the car.
I should have had dad
pick me up.
Excuse me.
Get up.
I will.
I am.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm
sorry... I fell back asleep.
I'm sorry, okay!
You can't smoke in the car.
Fine.
Quit playing with that.
Give it! Give it!
You're too old for that.
You're too old for a lot
of things.
Turn on the car,
roll down the window.
I was gonna give you this
when we got there.
It was grandma's.
Yeah.
Why are you giving it to me?
Because you're not coming back.
I didn't say that.
Yeah, but you're not gonna...
If we stop in Darlington
tonight...
It's only 4 hours
until we get there.
Yeah. Just tell me
when you wanna stop.
You know what? Honestly, Lizzy,
I'm done, okay?
Just get in the goddamn car!
I don't want to!
I don't care! I'm not
gonna ask you again.
Look, I know this
is a big night for you.
I don't care!
Yes, you do!
It's my play!
Yes, and you are going to be
late. Get in the goddamn car!
Get your ass in there right now!
I don't want you to go.
What did you say?
I don't want you there!
Well, that is some tough fucking
shit, because I'm going.
This is a big night for you
and I know that.
Just drop me off.
Fuck you!
Don't talk to me like that.
Fuck you, fuck you.
Fuck you, fuck you, fuck you!
I hate you.
Fuck you.
Fuck you, fuck you, fuck you,
fuck you, fuck you!
Fuck you! Fuck you!
I hate you! I hate you.
It's my play.
You never come, you never care,
you never come to anything!
You know what? You know what?
Find your own goddamn ride!
Fuck you!
You sure you want to keep going?
I called dad and Jenna,
they said they'll stay up.
I wanna sleep there.
Are you tired?
No, I'll be fine.
I think it's gonna rain.
I hate thunder.
I know you do.
Hey... can I?
Crack your window.
What time is it?
I don't know.
Why don't you tell me?
It's 12...
:15.
And not a soul in sight.
Don't do that.
I'm just kidding.
It's not funny.
You need to lighten up.
I wish you listened more.
I wish you'd quit saying that.
Oh shit... damn it!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh, god!
Baby! Are you okay?
Look at me! Are you okay?
Are you okay?
Oh, honey, I'm so sorry.
Mommy.
Just tell me what hurts.
Ow!
Mom!
Ow, my wrist! Fuck! Oh, god.
Mom, you're bleeding.
Are you sure you're okay?
Mom, what do we do?
We gotta call 9-1-1.
Oh, shit.
Hello?
We've been in a accident.
My mom has... she hurt her head,
it's bleeding.
Where are we?
Tell them we passed the 40 like
30 minutes ago, going south.
We passed the 40 about
30 minutes ago.
Tell them that we...
At that fork...
Where there's construction...
Tell them where there's
construction...
We went on the old road.
We're on the old road.
I don't...
I don't know. Okay.
What did they say?
They're sending an ambulance
and a tow truck thing.
See if there's a band-aid
in my purse.
You want to get out?
What if it's still alive?
Baby, look at it.
It hasn't moved.
But still...
Ow!
Okay, try your side.
Hey... it's all right.
Come on, be brave.
Climb out.
Baby? You're gonna need
to call your dad.
He can come get you wherever
they're taking us.
What are you gonna do?
I gotta deal with this.
I'll have Roy come and get me
in the morning. Call him.
Hi, dad? Dad, we got
into an accident.
No, I'm okay.
Yeah, so is mom.
Um, no, dad... she wasn't.
Dad, she's fine.
No, it... it was raining and
there was something in the road.
It was scary. We hit a wolf.
Yeah, mom made me call.
Oh, god.
Oh, come on, come on, come on.
You can do it,
you can lick it, baby.
Just don't do it, just don't do
it, just go to fucking bed.
Just go to bed. Just go to bed.
Oh, fuck, fuck.
Is it dead?
I don't know.
It looks dead.
Yeah... it does.
Look at this.
Let's go back to the car.
Okay.
Some of those cuts on the wolf
weren't from the crash.
I think it was fighting
with something.
What?
I don't know, there are lots of
things that hide in the woods.
Can I see your arm?
Stay still.
Oh, thank god.
Maybe he knows...
Where they'll be taking us.
Momma...
Uh-huh.
Where'd the wolf go?
Ma'am? Ma'am, you all right?
Yeah, yeah, we're fine.
We're fine, it's just my wrist.
Sorry, sweetheart.
Station called, said the
ambulance is gonna be a bit.
Let me get your things,
put 'em in my truck.
I'll get your car ready.
Okay. Thank you.
I don't want to get out.
Baby, that thing probably just
crawled into the woods to die.
That's all.
My name's Jesse.
Hey.
I hope y'all aren't too
shaken up.
We hit a wolf, if you can
believe it.
Get out, I want to help him.
Well, nobody much takes this
road any more.
I'm not surprised that animals
don't think twice...
About crossing it.
Where'd it go?
Uh, I think it got up.
Well, shit... must've just
spooked it then.
All right, that's it.
Your ambulance will be
coming in a minute.
Okay.
There's a big wreck
on the highway...
It's slowing everything down.
It's okay, I think we'll
just stay in this car.
Can you hook it up
with us in there?
Yeah, yeah, y'all right, go on.
Aw, dang it.
You got a...
Axel broke in half.
You got oil pouring out like
it's trying to get away.
I'm gonna have to work on it
before we get going.
You want to pop it? Pop it?
Why would it run out
in the road?
Who knows?
It had to have seen us, right?
It's probably just running.
From what?
Dogs don't got teeth like this.
Their teeth are small.
We hit a wolf.
Damn it!
What time is it?
Late.
Late 30 or late 45?
Stay in there.
Baby, where'd you put my phone?
I want to call your dad.
I think it's in my bag.
He took it?
Holy... son of a bitch.
Go tell him we want our phone.
Go tell him.
Do I have to?
We have to call your dad, go on.
Go on, he's gonna be worried.
Okay, I'm going. I'm going.
Mister?
Jesse.
Mr. Jesse, we need our phone.
I'll be out in a minute. You can
go get it yourself.
Mister! I need the key!
Oh, goddamn it!
I'll be out in a sec!
Momma, come look!
Momma?
Oh, shit.
Mom!
I found it! I found the wolf!
Sorry we hit you.
Momma?
I hate you. I hate you.
I hate you.
Go away.
Should have got you a jacket.
Come here.
Did you hear me out there?
Uh, no, I guess not.
I called for you.
What happened?
I found it.
Found what?
The wolf.
Where'd you see it?
In the woods. Something ate it.
Should have left it alone.
I did!
Come on! Goddamn it!
We're gonna be gone soon,
and you know...
Birds will eat it in the
morning.
What would do that?
Baby, are you scared?
Hey! It's not gonna come
after people.
You promise?
I promise.
Where is the fucking ambulance?
Let's go, man! Come on!
What's his name?
Jesse.
Jesse. Hey, Jesse!
Come on, man, let's go!
Mister?
Hang on a sec.
Where is he?
He's down there.
Why won't he answer?
I don't hear him.
Hey!
Jesse?
Momma?
I'm going out there.
Let's just wait here... please!
You stop making this into
a thing. Honestly, stop.
Don't get weird on me. I'm just
gonna go out and find him.
Why?
Because I don't just sit.
Don't go.
Not one word out of you, not one
more word. You hear me, Lizzy?
Is he there?
Jesse!
Where is he?
You out there?
Oh, my god, oh, my god. Oh!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay. We're gonna be okay.
The ambulance will be here soon.
What if they never get here?
Stop, don't... don't think like
that. Don't think like that.
They're coming.
They're on their way.
I want my daddy.
Hey... hey! I'm right here.
I don't care.
Hey.
I told you... I told you not
to get out of the car...
And you never listen to me.
Nothing happened.
He could have killed you.
Nothing happened to me.
I'm okay, I'm right here.
I'm right here.
Momma?
What?
What do we do?
I don't know. I don't know.
Please don't! Please?
We can't just leave him
out there.
Please?
Agh! Oh, no!
Agh!
I don't know what to do.
I know what you think, okay!
I know what you think!
What is it? What?
I see it.
Turn around! Turn around!
Turn around!
Mom, where is it?
I don't know! I don't know! I
don't know!
Where is it? Where is it?
Don't look. Don't look,
don't look.
Mom.
Ssh... it's okay.
It's okay.
It's not.
You're an idiot!
You think you're so fucking
smart, don't you?
Well, maybe I feel a little less
with you being here.
I told you, over and over
and over again...
Don't touch my fucking beer!
It's my house!
It's my fucking beer!
It's my fucking house!
Dumb ass, it's not in there.
I told you it's not in there.
I know it's not in there! I know
where I put them!
Lizzy, where are you! Lizzy!
This is the last time! Lizzy!
Lizzy! Lizzy!
Where are you, you little shit!
Lizzy!
Momma!
Where are they?
I don't know.
Speak up!
Hey!
Get away from her.
She's got 'em, okay?
I fucking know that!
Well, get them!
Look at me.
Look at your mother!
Look at me!
Give me them.
I don't have them.
Give me them!
Shit.
Store closes in eight minutes.
Wait. Baby, wait!
Momma, i... I don't... i...
Mom! Mom?
Mom, please! Mom!
Ssh. Ssh.
Ssh.
What was that?
I don't know.
Was it a monster?
Monsters aren't real.
Ssh, I know.
You said...
I was wrong.
Ssh. Ssh.
I don't... I don't want to die.
The door to his truck is open.
I'm just gonna take a look.
No.
It doesn't know we're in here.
You don't know that.
Ssh. Ssh.
If we can get his keys,
we can get out of here.
He had them. He might have
dropped them.
Momma, I don't want you to.
I could just peek.
You can stay here.
Stay, stay here with doggy.
Mommy.
Be very quiet. Be very
quiet. It's okay.
What's out there?
I'm not sure.
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Ssh. Be still.
Be still. Be still, be still.
Stay quiet. Stay there.
Ssh.
It's come back.
It's okay.
It's okay. Ssh.
Momma!
Momma! Momma!
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Momma!
Hold on. Hold on, momma!
Help us! Please, help!
Please help us!
Okay, ma'am, stay where you are!
Please help us! Help!
There's somebody out there!
Ladies. Hey, hey, hey!
Get her away from it, please!
The monster, what the fuck?
Ma'am, relax.
Get us out of here!
We're just gonna hold
for a moment.
All right, now roll over,
please.
Fuck, you get us off
of this fucking road!
Get us off this fucking road!
Hey! Ma'am, hey, look at me.
Get off this fucking road!
Look at me, my name is John.
We're here to help you.
Get us away!
Dispatch, we need a medical
examiner out here...
And animal control as soon
as possible.
Squad cars can find the flares.
Please.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Mom.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
We're gonna go real soon.
We're gonna go real soon, okay?
All right, we're good to go.
Everything's gonna be okay.
You'll be okay.
Goddamn it, hold on.
You're okay.
Ah, damn it... Williams!
Let's get out of here.
Close the door. Close the door.
Mom, don't.
They can put it back in.
Close the door now.
What do we do?
Just stay close to me, okay?
Get back on the gurney.
Where is he?
I don't know. What happened
to you?
Just get us out of here.
I just need you to stay calm,
okay?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh, my god.
Go, mom, go, go, go!
Hold on to something!
Oh, my god.
We did it.
Ah, fuck you.
Oh, fuck you, you fucking devil!
We did it.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Ow.
No... no.
Mom.
Please wake up, wake up, wake
up. Please open your eyes.
Open your eyes, please.
Oh, no.
Wake up.
Oh, god, help. Help, help, help.
Mom, it's me, it's okay, it's
me, it's okay. It's okay.
It's okay... oh, please.
We have to get back.
Go, go, go, get back, get away.
Okay, are you okay? Oh, god.
Oh, god, are you okay?
My head hurts.
Show me, show me. Oh.
Is this my blood or your blood?
You're okay.
Okay.
Help us.
Help.
Damn it.
Oh, goddamn it.
God damn it.
You try to be quiet... okay?
Okay.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
No.
It's okay.
We need to make a fire.
Why?
Because we need to get you
to the road...
So you can get aw...
So you can get away.
Take it. Take it.
We can't go out there.
Look, they can't... they won't
know we're here.
They can't see you down here.
I've got a plan.
I'm gonna need you.
I'm gonna need you
to be brave, okay?
I need you to be brave.
I need you to be braver
than you've ever been.
Kathy I can distract it.
I can use the fire,
I can use it.
So I can go out there,
and it'll follow me...
So that you can go out there
and you can get away.
It'll get to you.
No, no...
It will be afraid.
Monsters don't like the light...
That's what night lights
are for, right?
Don't lie to me.
I'm not.
Yes, you are.
Yes, I am.
Listen to me.
I'm gonna die.
Real soon... whether I go
out there or not.
You can't die.
No, you can't die.
Why?
Because you... you are the
reason I'm here.
Kathy look at me.
When I call for you, I need you
to run as fast as you can.
Lizzy we could go together.
Don't look back. Don't look back
no matter what happens, okay?
With me, don't look back.
I'll get help. I'll get help and
they can come back, and they...
And then they can save you.
That's our plan.
That's our plan. Okay?
Lizzy! Lizzy, be ready!
Come back! Come back, I don't
want to go! I don't want to go.
You do what I say!
I won't leave you!
Baby, please? You do what I say!
Do what I say!
I'm here!
Are you scared?
Lizzy, be ready.
Lizzy, run!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Go away!
No, get away, get away!
Mom. Mom.
Lizzy.
Oh, mommy, mommy, please get up.
I want you to so bad, please.
Please, please, please.
Please get up. Please.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Mommy, get up, please, please,
please. Please.
Don't go. Don't go, don't go,
don't go, don't go, don't go.
Please, please, don't go, don't
go, don't go, don't go.
Please, please, please, please.
Please.
I have to go.
I love you.
I'm not afraid of you.
Come on. Come on, come on.
Come on!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hey, little girl.
Hi.
I'm not little.
I know.
Ssh, don't be mad.
But you said...
You don't hate me?
I don't hate you.
I don't hate you. Ssh.
You are gonna be so much better
than me... so much better.
You just wait and see,
it's gonna be amazing.
You are gonna get past me...
And you are gonna be able to do
whatever you want.
I just want you.
Lizzy my mom tells me...
There's no such thing as monsters.
But she is wrong.
They are out there,
waiting for you...
watching.
They are in the dark.
Sometimes where you see them...
Sometimes where you don't.
I know that now.
I'm not afraid anymore.