Subtitles by B[r]3
BrEaThE@PunkAss.com
Dentist.2.1998.DVDRip.XviD-B[r]3.avi
Ripped by B[r]3
Open wide, Brooke.
Wider.
Brooke: You know
I don't want you anymore.
( Laughing )
I, I didn't do that...
A stranger...
A stranger, Doctor?
I can remember those
awful things I did,
but for the life of me...
Doctor...
I don't know the man
who did them.
This stranger,
this evil Dr. Feinstone,
where is he now?
Gone, consumed by the...
rage that spawned him.
By that, you mean it's over,
you put your anger and
your wife's infidelity behind you?
No Dr., it is not over.
It will never be over.
Every second of every day...
asleep or awake, I see her face.
The faces of all of my victims.
You refer to them as
''your victims'',
even though you say you don't know
the stranger who hurt them.
He is me.
I am him.
Still he remains...
until love returns the soft...
whisper of his voice...
searching...
wanting...
that which he hath given...
with no reply.
And he is gone?
He is under control.
Shall we go?
Radio: Dr. Alan Feinstone,
the notorious psycho dentist,
broke out of the state mental facility
at Indio yesterday afternoon.
His hostage,
Psychiatrist Dr. Genevieve Cussler--
( Opera plays )
Man: So, you think
before the Doc went postal
he was socking money
away from you and the IRS?
And from you, his devoted
wife and help mate.
Excuse my bad manners,
but did he do that to you?
Cut your tongue out?
What a world, huh?
These are all his, huh?
Souvenirs from a trip
he took as a kid.
South Dakota.
Nebraska.
Missouri.
Jeeze, look at these
snow domes...
Oh, a set of
safety deposit box keys.
The answer's in
the postcards, huh?
All right.
They found the shrink's car
abandoned in Flagstaff.
Along with 7OO or so bucks
from her wallet.
Jeeze, he could be
just about anywhere.
- Bye, now.
- Thank you.
Mr. Wilkes?
Well, I'll be--
Larry Caine, come on in.
How long has it been,
five years?
It's good to see you.
Well, to what do we owe
this great pleasure?
Rush hour traffic.
Does that come with
an explanation?
Well, my car overheated
on the Alexandria bridge...
It was the morning rush hour,
that was it.
I couldn't face another
jawing mouth, another bicuspid,
I was weary of my life,
the city,
the moral decay that passes
as sophistication.
Felt like that myself some days.
So, I left my car
right there on the bridge...
I walked home, I called my lawyer...
and a long story short,
here I am.
Small town, honest people,
clean living.
But, I've got me a little
problem, ol' buddy...
( Intercom buzzes )
Yeah, Jeremy?
Bev, see if you can get
Harry and his drill over here.
Dr. Caine has lost the key
to his safety deposit box.
All righty.
It's a little irregular,
but here it is.
Thanks.
So, what are your plans, Larry?
Oh, to live in Paradise.
Great golf just outside of town.
I detest golf.
We'll change that.
Where are you staying?
The Paradise Motel.
The hell you are.
( Sinister chuckle )
Ahh, yes.
Jamie, have you rented the cottage?
No, not yet.
There's someone I want you
to meet. Come with me.
Larry?
Yeah, I'll be right with you.
Jamie Devers...
Dr. Lawrence Caine.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hi.
Yes, Jeremy tells me that
you're his favorite niece.
I'm his only niece.
Larry has just moved
here to Paradise,
lock, stock and barrel,
from that eastern den
of iniquity, Washington, D.C.
Actually I left the lock,
stock and barrel behind.
You've got the empty cottage.
I thought maybe you could
show it to Larry during lunch.
Uh, it's really small.
Well, it's just me.
This was my parents' house.
It's where I grew up.
And there's the cottage.
I'll take it.
No. No.
You having trouble sleeping, Doc?
I sure would if I were you.
Go away! Go away!
When it comes right down to it,
Caine is just a Feinstone.
And we all know what
a Feinstone is, don't we?
Do it, do it.
( Sighing with pleasure )
Yes, bleed.
( Knock at door )
Hello?
Larry?
( Distorted )
I came running over here.
I was worried.
( Normal voice ) I came running
over because I heard this loud noise.
I didn't know what to think.
I'm in unfamiliar
surroundings and...
I must have bumped into the dresser
on my way to the bathroom....
I can replace it.
Don't worry about it.
I can make another one.
- You made it?
- Yeah.
Here, let me do that.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
A little housework
always relaxes me.
Do you do windows?
As a matter of fact, I do.
Good, I think we're going
to get along just fine then.
- Good night.
In town, I think it's called
the ''Paradise Cafe''...
is it any good?
After graduate school in Seattle,
and a few lost years
contemplating the meaning of art,
in a world that was
consumed by commercialism...
I came to the realization that
actually creating my pottery
was more important
than thinking about it.
And so, here I am
back in Paradise,
bank teller by day,
artist by night.
Chicken fried steak
for the gentleman,
spinach salad for Jamie.
No wonder you stay so thin, darling.
Anything else?
Something wrong, sir?
No, no, I was just contemplating
a side of curly fries...
but I decided against it,
thank you.
Well, enjoy your dinner, folks.
Thanks.
So, you're fleeing reality
in search of a dream,
and I'm fleeing a dream
in search of reality.
What dream are you fleeing from?
My wife was a former
Miss Maryland,
thus we were the perfect couple
for the perfect dinner party.
You fled from that?
Did I mention the former
Miss Maryland
was attending parties
without me in the afternoons
thrown by younger male members
of the foreign diplomatic corp.
Yet, still he remains...
until love returns the soft
whisper of his voice.
Wanting, searching...
that which he has given
without return.
To Paradise.
May we, um... both find here
what we're looking for.
Larry, you okay?
Larry, what's wrong?
I lost a cap.
One of my caps has come loose.
We didn't put that in.
Yes, I know, I'd like the doctor
to re-cement it, please.
Fill this out.
( Phone rings )
( Sound of heart beating )
( Inner voice )
Don't do it.
Don't... don't do it.
Oh, God.
Oh, that's good.
Send in the next patient, please.
Please have a seat.
This won't hurt a bit.
Have you been drilled on before?
Would you like some gas?
Open wide, wider...
You have to stop moving.
If you move, I cannot proceed.
Why are you moving?
Why is everything moving?
Please, sit down. Don't move.
You've got to sit still.
( Phone ringing )
Woman answers:
Doctor's office.
Hello, Mrs. Anderson.
Appointment for when...
Hey!
What are you doing
with my patient?
Remove this cotton from your
mouth ma'am, so you don't choke.
What's going on here, what... ?
Relax a minute, dear, while I...
Bernice, look after Edna there.
Who the hell do you think you are?
That woman was in
respiratory distress.
Respiratory distress?
So, you're a doctor, that it?
Traveling the country saving poor
souls from respiratory distress?
I am a dentist.
Then you should know better
than to be poking around
in another dentist's business.
You going to wash your hands?
How about some gloves?
Bernice, would you bring
that box of gloves?
I'd appreciate it if you'd sterilize
your instruments one more time.
Anything else, doctor?
Perhaps the equipment
is too old for your liking,
or maybe you miss the music,
is that it?
You like a little elevator
music with your dentistry?
How about some Lysol
in the cabinets?
Sure you want me to put
in your cap?
You're the only game in town.
Yes, I am.
Open up.
This is a country practice, doctor.
Granted, it's plain and simple,
but the folks around here seem
to like it just fine.
So, I'd be obliged, city boy,
if you'd keep your opinions
to yourself
and your fingers out of
my patients' mouths.
( Continues honking )
Asshole.
Cretin.
Burns.
Burns!
( Country music playing )
You incompetent buffoon.
What are you doing here?
Look at this.
What did you use, library paste?
And you call yourself a dentist?
You stay away from me.
Bernice! Bernice!
Oh, Bernice is out to lunch.
In more ways than one.
Drill 'em,
fill 'em, bill 'em...
that's your philosophy, huh?
You know, you and your
ilk, Doctor Burns...
make dentists the boogeymen
of medicine.
Something to be feared...
to be avoided at all costs.
I've worked my entire career
to change all that.
You see, a trip to the dentist
should be pleasant,
something to look forward to.
That is, of course, if the dentist
in question is competent.
It's not the cap,
you're a fruitcake.
Funny you should mention that.
You're scaring me.
I'm trying to.
Now, repeat after me,
''I am an incompetent dentist...''
Say it.
I... am...
an incompetent dentist.
Now...
- I...
- am...
- a...
bogeyman.
I can deal with this.
( Opera music plays )
( Phone rings )
Your call is being answered by
a machine, please leave a message.
Love and kisses from
your favorite private eye.
I'm in Grand Junction, Colorado.
No luck so far,
next stop is North Platt, Nebraska.
Up with people.
Ciao, baby.
Too bad about Doc Burns, isn't it?
Yes. Yes it is.
And too bad for Paradise.
The answer is no, Jeremy.
Well, I didn't get where I am
by accepting no for an answer.
I have a responsibility. What kind of
town would this be without a dentist?
You won't even consider it?
No.
Just till we find somebody.
What part of ''no'' don't
you understand, Jeremy?
I did not give up a
lucrative practice in Washington
to start from scratch
somewhere else.
Sweet deal for somebody,
house, practice,
everything for a song.
Promise me you'll
at least think it over.
Afternoon, doctor.
Let me show you around.
A little spackle, fresh coat of paint,
maybe some new carpeting,
you've got yourself
one fine, little office here.
Come on in, city boy.
( Laughing )
Feinstone her, Dr. Caine.
Feinstone the bitch.
No, no, no...no.
Hey.
You're home early.
I wasn't feeling well.
What's wrong?
Um, a toothache. It's nothing.
I have an appointment Saturday
with Dr. Davis over in Otis.
That's 7O miles away.
May I look at it?
All right.
Want to open for me?
( Inner voices )
Feinstone her, Dr. Caine.
Feinstone the bitch.
Are you okay, Larry?
I'm fine, just open,
open wide, Jamie.
Sensitive?
It's nothing serious. You just have
a small cavity near the gum line.
And, um, I think it's
best if we fill it.
Is it going to hurt?
Shouldn't.
Want to open wide?
All right, turn your head a little
this way. There we go.
That's it.
That's it?
I didn't even feel it.
You're not supposed to.
Are you okay, Larry?
I...I'm going to
have to change this burr.
( Inner voice ) Feinstone her,
Dr. Caine. Feinstone her.
I am not crazy.
I am not going to hurt her.
Jamie:
Is there anything wrong?
No, no, I'm fine.
Just cleaning the instruments.
Be right with you.
Why is it so scary
to come to the dentist?
It doesn't have to be.
All right.
I'll have you fixed up in no time.
Ready?
I did it. I did it.
I'm a dentist.
I'm the best damn
dentist there ever was.
Are you excited?
Excited?
Yes, I uh...I think I am.
Well the people of
Paradise thank you, Larry.
Lawrence.
Hey, hey.
Picture time.
No, I just want Larry in front of
the sign. He's the man of the hour.
Boo.
You know, I could fix that.
Oh, I'm used to it.
Whenever you're ready.
Jamie, let me show
you the house.
I haven't really
changed the structure.
I mean the layout
is pretty much the same.
This is nice.
You've done wonders.
I believe a harmonious environment is
essential to the dental experience.
This one is just perfect.
Perfect?
Oh, not quite.
I'm reserving that for the operatory
that I'm creating upstairs.
Coming up, watch your back.
- I can't wait to see it.
- You'll be the first.
Ah, well.
My first patient.
-You look very nice.
- See ya.
Just a small country practice.
I think
I'm going to like it here.
I've got a feeling he's going
to be real good for this town.
( Phone rings )
Hello?
Hi, Jamie.
Are you still hard at work?
I'm about ready to quit for the night.
How's the filing coming?
At this rate I should be done
somewhere around the millennium.
- That bad?
- Worse.
- Anyway, I just called to say hi.
- Hi.
I'll talk to you tomorrow, huh?
- Okay.
- Bye-bye.
( Loud knocking at door )
- Dr. Caine?
- Yes.
Oh, am I glad to see you.
The cab jockey thought you
might be working late.
I thought I'd give it a shot.
My damn tooth is killing me.
Uh, come in.
You're a Hall of Famer, Doc.
A Hall of Famer.
You think when we're finished you
could give me a ride to the bus stop?
I've got to catch the 1O:4O to K.C.
A ride?
I'm a dentist, not a cab jockey.
You know, the motel guy said
the only dentist in town was dead.
I had to track you down.
You're kind of flying
under the radar, Doc.
( Laughing )
Kind of like Stealth Dentist.
Well sir, you found me.
I guess tonight
is my lucky night.
We'll see.
I'm from the left coast.
L.A., la la land.
Swimming pools,
movie stars, boob jobs.
I'm on my way to K.C. Thinking about
doing a little real estate speculating.
You know,
my rental car broke down.
And they started
to hassle me about it.
I told them to shove it, you know.
I'll just take the bus.
Have you ever been to L.A., Doc?
Have we ever met before?
God, I swear
you look familiar.
Go ahead and
open your mouth, sir.
You have a bus to catch.
I, I'm terrible with names,
but I never forget a face.
- Ah, ah.
- Hold still.
Doc, that hurts
like a bitch.
You're not going in there dry,
are you, Doc?
I mean, I'm not anti-narcotics.
I'll administer an anesthetic.
Good.
Hey you know, just last year,
I picked out a guy at Dodger Stadium,
two sections over. I knew this guy
from somewhere, I didn't know where.
And then it hit me.
St. Paul, 1983...
...footwear expo.
Florsheim booth.
I went over and checked it out.
It was him. Hee hee.
I never forget a face.
Have you every been to
Dodger Stadium, Doc?
No, that's not it. But don't tell me,
don't tell me. It's coming.
You're definitely
Southern California.
I detest baseball.
Oh, I'm never wrong, Doc.
Would you please sit still?
( Inner voice ) Ever been to L.A., Doc?
I swear you look familiar.
I never forget a face.
Oh I'm never wrong, Doc. Never.
You're definitely
Southern California.
You did that on purpose.
I know you.
Fishbein or Feinbein.
Feinburg... the crazy dentist.
Sir, sit back down.
I cannot leave that tooth untreated.
I took an oath.
Get out of
the doorway, nutball.
This crazy dentist of yours,
this Fein...stone,
Would he get
out of the doorway?
I'm sorry, man.
I've got to go.
Do you still want that ride?
No. I'm a walker.
You just couldn't have your
toothache someplace else, could you?
Insane, deranged, demented.
Psychotic, nuts,
nutso, nutcase.
Nutball, loco.
Loony, apeshit, wacko.
Oh, I didn't want to...
I didn't want to do it.
I tried not to. I tried not to do it.
Okay, okay.
I'm going to make this work.
I will make this work.
I am in control.
I am not crazy...
I am not crazy.
I am not insane.
I am not a monster.
Private eye:
Hello there. It's me.
Hey, how are you doing?
I'll bet you you'll never
guess where I'm off to next.
Paradise, Missouri.
Paradise, can you believe it?
See you later.
Back off, Bev.
I know, I just can't get
this image out of my head.
I keep imagining you in this canoe,
with this handsome, mysterious stranger.
Rushing down a raging river,
waterfalls...
boulders, white water...and he's
the only one with a life preserver on.
You're an alarmist.
No, I prefer to
see myself as a cynic.
And the cynic in me says...
- Hey.
Haven't seen you in a week.
Yeah, I got a job over in Otis.
I was staying with my cousin.
- I've got to go.
- Bye.
So I hear you rented your
cottage to the new dentist.
To Dr. Caine.
So what do you think of him?
He's nice.
Hey, I'm scheduled to do
some work in his office.
He's...he's not coming
between us, is he?
No.
Oh God, Robbie, you're not going to
propose again, are you?
Jamie Devers,
will you marry me?
No.
No? Why?
Because I...
like you too much.
No, not again.
- Enjoy your blueberry pie, sir.
- Ah, blueberry...
Got a minute, sweetheart?
I can give you a second.
Just figured you were the type that
would help out a fellow human being.
Give me a break.
I saw a guy in town today who
looked like an old army buddy.
Maybe you could
help me track him down.
I'm staying right at the edge of town,
in the Sleepeasy Motel.
Hey Bev. There's a little guy at
the end of the counter,
seems real interested in Doc Caine.
Asking all sorts of questions.
Thinks he knows him from the
service or something. From L.A.
What little guy?
You'd be surprised how
people neglect their teeth.
If they were only as
diligent as you, Margaret.
Some people never learn.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Jeremy needs you to sign these.
Hi Jamie. I'll be done with
Margaret in just a moment.
Hey, Margaret.
So I...I saw you earlier.
Where?
Oh, in town,
by the cafe, with some guy.
Robbie?
Robbie.
Is that his name?
Robbie... Well, you didn't
tell me about Robbie, did you?
There's nothing to tell.
( Muffled )
That's not what it looked like
from where I was sitting.
Is he a good kisser?
Did you see the part when he
was on bended knee proposing to me?
Proposing?
Yeah, it's a joke.
I mean, he does this every month.
He proposes every month,
it's a joke...
Spit, Margaret.
Robbie is one of my oldest
and dearest friends.
I mean I've known him
since I was in third grade.
Little kids, babies...
Friends. I mean, that's all it is.
That's all it ever will be.
- Friends?
- Friends.
Just friends?
( Hears laughing )
( Pneumatic nail gun )
Excuse me. Hello.
I'm with a patient,
could you please...?
Would you stop--
Hey. Hey, hey.
Hey.
I'm with a patient right now.
If you could just give me
15 minutes or so.
In case you haven't
put it together,
I'm the jerk who cut you
off the other day in town and...
anyway, I'm sorry.
No problem, man.
I'm Robbie Mauro,
I'm the drywall guy.
Aren't you living
in Jamie's cottage?
Yeah, yeah,
that's right.
- She's...spoken of you.
- Yeah?
About how you've been friends
since you were children.
I've been in love with
Jamie since the third grade.
Third grade, huh?
How about Jamie?
Oh, she's in love with me.
She just doesn't know it.
Oh yeah?
I'm terribly sorry...
I, I didn't know it was loaded.
( Typing - phones ringing )
Gotcha.
He doesn't exist.
What are you talking about?
Larry Caine.
He has no credit history.
I checked and re-checked.
The man is a blank.
He was somebody else
before he came to paradise.
Bev, this is nonsense.
No, there was a guy at the cafe. Said he
was sure he knew him from Los Angeles.
Not Washington.
Larry Caine is a valued customer of
our bank and an asset to our town.
I think you've been reading too
many murder mysteries, Bev.
Well, he could be one of those
Medicare fraud doctors,
who you see ducking behind
doors on 6O Minutes.
Thank you, Bev.
Dammit, Jeremy. He could be married,
with a wife and kids.
Thank you, Mrs. Swales.
( Phone ringing )
Bank of Paradise.
This is Jamie.
- Jamie. Hi.
- Hi.
Listen, I'm standing outside
the office on the grounds here,
and I've been thinking
about you all day.
And I was hoping you'd do me the
honor of joining me for dinner
at the most exclusive
restaurant in town.
No, not the Paradise Cafe.
Something much
better than that.
- Hi
- Hi.
- You look great.
- You too.
I love my dress.
But, how did you know my size?
Perfect only comes in one size.
- Where are we going?
- Shhh!
Oh Larry, I just love
what you've done out here.
Under the stars,
in the dark of night,
silence the woes,
and give love its flight.
Stay...
stay right here.
Don't move.
I should put these in water.
They'll keep.
No they won't.
I'll bring
you more tomorrow.
I want these.
( Phone ringing )
Don't answer that.
Answer what?
Robbie: Hey, Jamie,
I guess you're not in.
Look, my cousin Louis and his wife
are going to be in town Friday.
I figured wouldn't it be cool,
you and me have dinner with them?
You being my future wife
and all. It will be fun.
Oh, yeah.
This is Robbie.
Seriously, Jamie.
I'd like to see you more.
I can't seem to get that
Thanksgiving out of my head.
Let's go to my room, Larry.
Let me know. Bye.
( Beeps )
Your oldest, dearest, friend
is in love with you, Jamie.
No, he's not.
Mr. Drywall
is in love with you.
And how do you feel
about him, Jamie?
I told you
how I feel about him.
But you didn't tell me about that
very special Thanksgiving, though,
did you?
I had just...
Larry, I lost both of my parents
in less than 6 months. I just...
And...and what?
And I was invited over to a friend's
house for Thanksgiving dinner.
Robbie was there.
I was just lonely.
Larry, it meant nothing.
Oh no, it meant something.
Believe me. It meant something.
- You don't get it.
- Oh I get it. Believe me, I get it.
Would you stop cleaning
my kitchen.
I'm sorry. I...
Just can't get enough of those
blue collar types, can you?
Goes by the name of Caine.
ELEVEN ROSES TO SAY I'M SORRY...
And the twelfth one is with him.
In review of our membership...
He couldn't be Dr. Caine.
Hello.
Doctor's office.
Who is it?
It's Bev from the bank. She wants
an appointment for this afternoon.
- Is that all right?
- Yeah.
It'll be fine, Bev. 4:3O?
Any other calls?
Jamie?
No.
Desert Storm?
The Gulf War was over in 1991.
That would make this
magazine what, Bernice?
The answer is, ''out of date.''
This is an out of date magazine.
How many times did I tell you
to get rid of all of these?
Here, want me to help you?
I think I'd better go.
- Where are you going?
- Fact finding mission.
- Don't forget about tonight.
- Oh, I'll be there. With bells on.
Bernice?
Dr. Caine?
Hello?
Thanks for being on time, Bev.
Oh, jezze.
I, I wasn't snooping.
I just wanted to
look at my file.
Really. I've wanted to look at
my file since I was a kid.
Sanderson, Emil.
Your file is inside.
The first time I peeked in
my files I was in college.
Now, to more important things...
...this discolored tooth of yours.
Oh, it's been that way
since junior high.
It should have been
taken care of. Lean forward.
Let's have a look,
shall we?
Open wide for me.
Smile, a big smile.
As long as we're
bonding your incisor,
that's that discolored tooth,
we could do all your teeth,
make them a few shades lighter,
give you that Hollywood smile.
All of them? You think?
I'd just like them whiter
without anyone noticing
that I did anything.
If that's possible.
Anything is possible.
Open.
So...
You ever been to
Hollywood, Larry?
I went to
Washington D.C. once.
I bet you miss it.
Washington... home.
I mean, it's exciting.
It's our nation's capital.
Funny...
What's that, Bev?
There was this guy, passed through
town day before yesterday.
He said he was sure
he knew you from Los Angeles.
But that couldn't be.
You being from D.C. and all.
No. No it couldn't.
Could it, Bev?
He was grilling Shawna at the cafe.
A little guy, she said.
This little guy.
Does he have a name?
I don't know.
Well let's see
what you do know.
What are you doing? Hey.
Breathe, Bev.
Breathe.
Yeah.
Wake up, Bev.
It's time to go to school.
Five more minutes, daddy...
What?
Oh my God...
Oh, my God.
Larry, you can't do this.
What, bond your teeth?
Please let me go.
This is how we bond our teeth...
...in Hollywood, Bevie.
Bonding in bondage.
It's all the rage.
Please don't hurt me, Larry.
Oh sure. You come in here
under false pretenses.
Nose through my files, you sit there
asking all your wheedling questions.
And then you
beg me not to hurt you?
What world do you live in, Bevie?
Now the nerve's exposed,
and we can commence
with a little game.
A lie detector test,
if you will.
I'll ask a question,
and you answer it.
If you tell the truth,
I'll pat your head.
If you lie,
I shall do this...
( Screaming )
I think you get it.
Now the first question is:
What do you know about me?
I know what everybody
else knows.
Oh Bev, wrong answer.
Now.
The question was:
Exactly what
do you know about me?
I know that you're not
really Dr. Lawrence Caine.
That I'm not really
Dr. Lawrence Caine?
I know you were somebody
else six years ago.
Good. Good.
Now, next question:
Why all those clumsy
questions about Washington?
I didn't think
you lived in Washington.
You didn't think
I lived in Washington?
Good, good Bev.
Do you know who I was
before I was Dr. Lawrence Caine?
No.
No?
Wrong answer.
( Buzzer sounds )
( Sobbing )
Help me.
Somebody help me.
If you say a word,
if you utter a sound while I'm gone,
I will cut out your
vocal cords with this.
Do you understand?
- Robbie. What can I do for you?
- I got the last of the drywall here.
Well, I'm with a
patient right now.
Bev? Because I noticed
her car was out there.
Yes.
We're...bonding.
Help.
( Bev screaming )
The novocaine
must have worn off.
I'm going to have to ask you to
stay outside. It's very important...
Don't...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Bev!
Robbie!
Oh, Robbie!
No!
Bev, Bev, Bev...
Here we were, two pals
playing a friendly little game,
the minute I turn my back,
you cheat.
Get off me.
New game, Bevie.
Truth...
...or tooth.
What did you tell Jeremy
about Washington?
I didn't tell.
I didn't tell...
Your discolored tooth was a problem.
Not a problem any more.
I can see that you
floss regularly, Bev.
I like that.
Now, Jamie.
What did you tell Jamie?
( Mumbling )
Yeah?
Are you sure?
Oh, Bev. You liar.
Damn it, I broke it.
Darn. This is the part I hate.
I don't mind telling you, Bevie,
pulling teeth is like, well...
pulling teeth.
You're looking
much better already.
Give me back my drill.
Okay,
I've got a much better idea.
A much better idea.
Oh Bev,
you're going to love this.
We'll cut it out.
( Sinister laugh )
( Woman laughing )
( Dialing )
( Phone ringing )
Brooke...
The doctor isn't in right now.
Please leave a message.
It's me...
You can speak?
Both of us
overreacted last night.
And I'm sorry if
I said anything that hurt you,
that wasn't my intention.
It's too late for apologies.
Jamie:
I'm almost at your office.
Do you think
I wanted to do that to you?
Jamie:
I'm coming for the twelfth rose.
I worshiped you,
but then I saw you...
with him...
in your mouth.
I couldn't let you
keep your tongue,
not after that.
Jamie:
Larry? Oh, my God.
Stop it.
Stop.
That was weird.
Who is she?
It gets confusing
at times, Brooke.
I think
I should call the police.
Larry?
( Dialing )
( Busy signal )
Larry.
( Busy signal continues )
Through all the drama,
whether damned or not,
love gilds the scene,
and women drive the plot.
Come here.
No. Let go.
Damn cap
just won't stay in.
Jamie. Jamie!
Jamie.
( Door rattles )
Let me in.
Jamie,
are you in there?
I know you're in there.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Jamie?
Open the door,
just a crack.
You stay away from me.
- Jamie, open the door.
- No...
All right.
Have it your way.
( Skill saw buzzing )
Don't you see it, Jamie?
We're joined at the hip.
We're Rob and Laura...
We're peanut butter and jelly...
We're Marge and Homer...
We're green eggs and ham...
We're corned beef...
and cabbage.
No.
Open wide, Jamie.
( Opera music playing )
There we are.
There we are. There we are.
Do you have
any idea where you are?
On the cutting edge.
That's where.
On the threshold of a new
patient-friendly era of dentistry.
Behold...
...the dental environment...
of the future.
This is an empty room.
It is not just
an empty room.
It is a total
dental environment.
Bathroom accidents, the greatest
cause of injury in the home.
Wisdom teeth?
You're here for your wisdom teeth?
I had my wisdom teeth
out years ago.
Then we'll just have to do
a much better job this time.
Won't we?
Open wide.
You get away from me.
Jamie.
Brooke.
Oh, my Brooke.
( Ominous laugh )
Jamie.
I know you're behind there.
Come out.
Whoa, Matilda.
I'm not Matilda,
and I'm not Brooke.
Gonna let you in
on a little secret.
Killing is liberating.
You just might like it.
I can kill you with this.
But what if it's not...
plugged in?
What if it is?
Small town girl.
Nice, honest, small town little girl.
You're not going
to pull the trigger.
I'll tell you what:
I'll give you to three.
Then I'm going
to cut you a new smile,
and start
to have some real fun.
One.
Two.
Surprise.
They're new.
I just bought them.
Jamie?
( Softly )
I'm over here.
( Coughing )
Are you okay?
Where is he?
( Laughing hysterically )
That damned tooth.
Stop. No.