TIMECRIMES
Clara!
- Didn't you hear me calling you?
- You called me?
- Yeah. You didn't hear me?
- No.
- This was the one you wanted, right?
- Yeah.
- And the fertilizer?
- Up there.
Put it there.
- You'll assemble it out here?
- Sure.
Time flies here.
I'm going upstairs to lie down.
Telephone!
What?
What did you say?
Yes?
Hello?
Who is this?
This is a restricted terminal.
Record your message
or give your access code.
Right...
We got a call from this numer.
- What were you saying?
- Nothing. The phone rang.
Who was it?
They didn't say anything.
But I got some weird machine.
- Probably the workers.
- Today's Saturday.
Or a neighbor.
Is today Saturday?
I thought it was Friday.
When's the painter coming?
Nobody has our phone number.
Then what's the point
of having a phone?
Look at him.
Too weak even to argue.
- You haven't slept.
- Yes, I have.
"Yes, I have." "Yes, I have."
- Shit.
- What?
It's still recording.
This is all set.
You'll never get it
through the door.
Sure I will.
Otherwise we'll put it out here.
It's not worth worrying about.
- What do you feel like for dinner?
- I don't know. What have we got?
I don't know.
There's almost nothing left.
There must be a store
still open in town.
How about roast chicken?
I'm not taking the car again.
Come on, I'll clean up the kitchen.
I don't want to take the car.
Come on.
I'll go if the table fits
through the door.
Okay. If it doesn't, I'll go.
I promise.
Seriously.
No changing your mind later.
- I know you.
- Move, move, move!
- What?
- I can't see.
Sorry.
There's something up there.
In a bush.
Let me see.
- Look.
- Where?
There, by the bush.
There's a clearing on the left.
- I can't see anything.
- Here.
- Where?
- Give it here!
Here.
You win.
What?
The table doesn't fit
in the bedroom.
I'd rather lose the bet
than have you against me.
- Give me the keys.
- Okay.
Never bring this up again.
Not even once, okay?
Yeah.
What's wrong?
What do you mean?
The keys.
Here.
See you later.
I'll leave them by the door.
Okay.
Hello?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hello!
Hello?
Is anybody there?
Who is this?
- Listen...
- Who are you?
This is private property.
Where did you get that walkie-talkie?
I need help. A man is after me.
He's trying to kill me.
I jumped the fence and came in.
What did you say?
You jumped the fence?
What happened?
He stabbed me in the arm
and I ran here.
The door was closed, but...
- What was that?
- What?
It sounded like...
I just heard thunder.
You mean that?
Yeah. I think so.
Okay, listen. Stay calm.
I'm in another building.
I'll be right over. Stay there.
Okay, thanks.
Hello?
- Yes?
- Did you say something?
One question... Is the man after you
wearing a bandage?
Yeah, a pink one.
- I can see him.
- Where? Where is he?
Far from the house, don't worry.
There are surveillance cameras
everywhere.
I have the monitors in front of me.
He jumped the fence.
Is he coming this way?
Please, call the police.
I'll call them right now.
Hold on.
Stay where you are.
Hello?
- Hello?
- Well? How did it go?
I don't get it.
What's wrong?
I can't get an outside line.
You don't have a cell?
There's no coverage out here.
- What is he doing?
- Walking.
- In this direction?
- Yeah.
I broke a window. If he sees it,
he'll know I'm here. What should I do?
I don't know... Where are you?
In a laboratory.
I blocked the door.
No, come up here.
It's much safer.
Where?
I'm in a silo at the edge
of the property, up the hill.
And...?
There's a door down the hall
on the right.
Come up the hill. He's coming from
the other side of the house.
I don't think he'll see you.
If he goes inside, he'll find you.
He's getting closer.
Get outof there.
Get out of there!
- I'm coming out.
- Okay.
That was me. Come up the path.
Stay on it.
Hurry up. The sooner you get here,
the sooner I can turn off
the lights.
He shouldn't see them.
Where is he?
He's approaching the house.
What's he doing?
Keep quiet, I'll guide you.
He's checking the windows.
He's seen the broken one.
- Is he going in?
- Keep quiet.
He's going around the house.
He's seen the path.
Hold on.
Impossible. I've lost the signal
from one of the cameras.
I've lost another.
Shit I can't see anything!
I don't know where he is! Run!
Please, turn off the lights.
I see something on up there.
Is that you?
That's me, it's okay.
I hear the car.
It's him! He's coming up!
Can he get in?
No, it's okay.
- Can you lock that?
- No.
- Shit, let's go.
- There's nowhere else to go.
We're safe here.
What is all this?
You can hide in there.
What? What is that?
Look.
I can lower the hatch to hide you.
Does this door have a lock?
Is there another door?
Another way out?
Can we turn off these damn lights?
He'll never think to look in there.
What about you?
I have to lower the hatch from here.
I'll activate it and get in with you.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Okay.
Come on!
Who are you?
What?
- What did you do to me?
- I don't know what you mean.
You said you'd get in with me.
I said what?
You've been here before, right?
Was the tank full of white liquid?
We've seen each other before, right?
The liquid you're soaked in...
That tank
is still a prototype.
It's actually a...
- This was the one you wanted, right?
- Yeah.
- And the fertilizer?
- Up there.
Put it there.
You went back in time.
- Where are you going?
- Home, to call the police.
- No, wait.
- Stay away from me.
For God's sake,
you can't go home.
What?
You're already home.
Want another look?
- They're doing exactly what...
- Listen.
Today is September 16, 2006.
No, it can't be.
- What day did you think it was?
- I don't know.
But I got in the tank on the 16th,
and it was night already.
So you only traveled...
a little while.
What do you mean, a little while?
You're not listening.
You traveled in time.
Into the past.
That's why you can see yourself.
You traveled to a past where
you're still at home, in your garden.
So what do I do now?
How did you get in the machine?
How did I get in?
Look, I was at home, okay?
- And suddenly...
- Don't tell me.
It's better not to know details.
You found me at the silo
- and I asked you to get in the tank.
- Yeah, but you...
Okay. If that's how it was,
everything is solved.
Why?
- All you have to do is wait.
- Wait... for what?
There's nobody else here.
Come on.
What was your name again?
- Hector.
- Hector, right.
Who is the man in my home?
He's you.
- He's me?
- Technically
you're the same person.
He's like your reflection.
You're looking in the mirror.
Only this mirror
shows what you were doing
roughly about an hour ago.
But that man is in my home.
And he'll leave,
in the same way you did.
How can I put this?
Come on.
Excuse me.
You want one?
No.
Sit over there.
This is you. This arrow moves forward
from past to future, okay?
But at this point you enter the tank
and travel an hour and a half
into the past.
To here.
You become a sort of Hector 2.
The one at your house
- is Hector 1.
- Hector 1?
Hector 1, your reflection in the mirror,
remember? Look, you're here.
You're seeing yourself,
but there's only one arrow.
For how long?
Your reflection will last up to here.
This is what we'll do:
Hide here. I'll configure the tank
in the basement
and go up to the silo.
I'll have it ready
and I'll wait for nightfall.
Hector 1 will show up,
I'll get him into the machine
and send him to the past
So here's the deal.
What deal?
I'll bring everything back to normal
and you won't tell anyone
about any of this.
I shouldn't be here.
The center is normally closed weekends,
but I felt like staying.
I'm going up.
Yes?
Hello?
Who is this?
What the fuck...?
This is a restricted terminal.
Record your message
or give your access code.
Right.. We got a call
from this number.
- What were you saying?
- Nothing. The phone rang.
Who was it?
They didn't say anything.
But I got some weird machine.
- Probably the workers.
- What is this?
You called your house?
- Is today Saturday?
- I say lay low
and you call your house?
- You can't stop me.
- Then what's the point
of having a phone?
- Did you talk to yourself?
- No.
I called my house... that's it.
Did you talk to yourself?
My wife is at home with that...
Look at him.
Too weak to even argue.
- You haven't slept
- Yes, I have.
"Yes, I have." "Yes, I have."
Do you remember getting that call?
At your house?
Do you remember answering?
Yes.
Before I left,
I got a call from myself.
Then everything still fits, right?
I'm going up to the silo.
The tank needs to be filled.
I can't put a chain on you,
or lock you in the basement.
But if you alter events and stop
Hector 1 from getting in the tank,
it will be the end of your life
as you know it.
Shit. It's still recording.
And your wife will still prefer
being with him to being with you.
Can't I just go home and explain?
There are rooms upstairs.
I'll come and get you
when it's over.
I...
Fuck!
Who is that man
in my home?
He's you.
But that man
is in my home.
And he'll leave,
in the same way you did.
Technically you're the same person.
He's like your reflection.
Can't I just go home and explain?
It will be the end of your life
as you know it
What am I supposed to do now?
My God... What the fuck?
Hello?
Are you all right?
I'm okay.
What happened to your face?
I got hit. Nothing serious.
Don't move. I'll be right back.
I'll call an ambulance.
What are you doing?
I said to stay put.
No, I'm okay.
There.
Shit, no signal.
I'll find a phone.
Wait for me here.
No, don't go!
Please.
I'm a little dizzy.
You want some water?
Yes, thank you.
I'd be right back.
The sooner an ambulance comes,
the better.
Hold on, it'll come unraveled.
Here, let me.
I was just cutting my neighbor's hair.
That way it won't fall off.
I'll get help.
Wait for me here, okay?
Wait.
What's wrong?
I don't know how to explain this.
I need your help.
- Excuse me?
- Come on.
Have a seat and don't move
until an ambulance comes. Please.
What are you doing?
Let's go, that way.
Why?
- Please, that way.
- No.
I need your help with something.
Come on, follow me.
Let's go back to the road.
That way.
No, keep going forward.
I have to go.
That way.
Please.
Trust me.
Don't worry, it's okay.
I need you to do something for me.
- I'll explain later.
- Why not now?
It's not easy to explain.
No!
Shit!
Do as I say.
Turn your head to the right.
No, my right.
Now lower your head a bit.
A bit more.
Don't look at me.
Now bite your left thumb.
Slowly.
Like you're thinking of something.
Now pull up your shirt.
Take it off.
Now!
Slowly.
I'm sorry.
Whatever I ask you to do,
I won't hurt you.
You can put it back on.
We're done. You see?
Can I go now?
Hide there, by that rock.
Crouch there.
Take off your pants.
You can put them back on later.
Go on.
- What are you doing?
- I have to stand up, don't I?
Okay, hand them over.
Should I take off anything else?
No, it's okay. Give them to me.
Are you sure?
Yeah. Give me your pants.
What about my panties?
No, I didn't say that.
Hello?
No, fuck!
I need you to do something for me.
I'll explain later.
Why not now?
It's not easy to explain.
Hello!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
No, wait!
Hey!
Please open the door!
Listen to me a second!
I was in the garden...
This is my house, you know...
and suddenly I saw you with my...
I was far away...
For God's sake, don't call anybody!
Hey!
No, wait!
Wait!
Clara!
Bye!
- I'll have them by the door.
- Okay.
- It sounded like...
- I just heard thunder. You mean that?
Yeah. I think so.
Okay, listen. Stay calm.
I'm in another building.
I'll be right over. Stay there.
Okay, thanks.
Hello?
Yes?
- This is Hector 2.
- What?
The second one. Keep your voice down.
Hector might hear us.
Okay, okay.
He left the walkie-talkie
on the table in the basement.
All right
I'm the one wearing the bandage.
Get him up to the silo.
Make up something.
I'll show up in a car.
- Make up something?
- Hello?
- Yes?
- Did you say something?
One second.
Is the man after you
wearing a bandage?
Yeah, a pink one.
He'll never think
to look for you in there.
I have to lower the hatch from here.
I'll activate it and get in with you.
Come on!
The man with the bandage,
the pink mummy!
I admit it should have occurred
to me when...
Come on.
Where are you going?
To the house.
You need to be examined.
You're the first vertebrate
to ever travel in time.
That bull about surveillance cameras
could have used more preparation...
Surveillance cameras!
We could use some.
- What are you doing?
- I have to get back in!
What?
Something went wrong!
So you want to fix it now?
Forget it!
- Listen to me!
- We'll talk at the house!
- Come here!
- Forget it! No way!
What are you doing?
Come back or I'll tear it apart.
Go right ahead.
I'll wait for you at the house.
What are you doing,
trying to ruin me?
After all I...
What else has to happen before
you realize the implications?
I have to do it.
It's not going to happen.
The tank won't work.
Don't lie to me.
Your trip used up all the energy.
It's not easily renewable.
It'll have to be next week,
I don't know... Sorry.
There was something there.
There was, but it's not...
You took it out?
No.
Where is it?
I threw it away outside.
It's one of the batteries.
We can't do anything without it.
Come on.
This machine doesn't solve problems.
In fact, it creates them.
I just need a head start
on the other two.
I need a previous moment
to be able to...
Look, I had activated the machine
seconds before you appeared inside it.
It was turned off before that.
You can't materialize inside a machine
if it's off. It's impossible.
Seconds before?
How many seconds before?
Maybe 30 or 40. You'd have a 30
or 40-second head start. It's absurd.
If you travel into the past
and alter events
and stop Hector 1 from getting
in the tank, there will be 3 of you.
Which will likely cause a chain reaction
of events beyond your control.
I won't interfere.
Hector 2 will chase Hector 1
into the tank, like he did before.
My change won't affect his plan.
Then there will be 2 of you.
You and Hector 2.
Hector 2 comes up here,
I follow him and finish him off.
We'd be one again.
You have no idea what you're saying.
Hold on.
Why did you throw that thing away?
I can't let you use the machine again.
I'm sorry, I...
No, what I mean is...
You took out the battery
before I said anything, right?
Well, yeah.
Before I showed up.
Because I imagined...
One moment.
How did you know I'd want to use
the machine again?
You knew it all along.
Are you tricking me again?
You're tricking me again.
Tell me.
Please,
don't make matters worse.
You knew what would happen.
Why?
Because Hector 3 told me.
Hector 3?
Hector 3. The third one.
You're kidding me.
You weren't the first
to appear in the tank.
You were the second.
The first had appeared earlier.
He threatened me.
He made me act surprised
to see you.
He made me go along with it
He appeared earlier?
How much earlier?
Maybe 30 or 40 seconds.
But...
He left right after you.
I never found out what he wanted.
You've been deceiving me
this whole time.
After leaving the two of you,
I went up to the silo to prepare
for Hector 1's arrival
when suddenly I got a buzz
on the walkie.
It was Hector 1,
calling from the house.
No, much earlier. It was daytime.
It was Hector 3.
Hello?
- This is Hector 3.
- Who?
The last one. Listen to me.
I'm very sorry.
What happened?
I'm afraid everyone will know
what we did.
He seemed out of it, like something
horrible had happened.
He told me everything
that would happen.
That you'd show up here,
trying to go back to the past...
And he didn't say why, but he said
to stop you at all costs.
You'll be Hector 3 if you go through
with it. What I say won't stop you.
Happy?
Wait a minute.
You mean the 2nd trip I'm about to take
was already made?
Apparently you couldn't solve
your little problem.
You told me yourself it failed.
It makes no sense.
Wait.
You say Hector 3 called you
from his walkie.
Yeah.
You mean...
from this walkie.
Yeah.
Shine the light on it.
Over there!
I think this is yours.
All I ask is think it over.
Hector, what happened?
I have no choice.
Calm down and listen to me.
I'm from the future.
Your machine works.
- Where...?
- Listen to me.
- How...?
- Listen to me!
Or everyone will know
you turned it on
without authorization.
Right now there are 3 of me.
You're going to help me
get rid of the other two.
Hector 2 is about to come out
of the tank.
Help him get Hector 1
into the tank.
Hector 2? But...
He'll explain it to you.
- But...
- Stand there.
Calm him down.
I have to reach the house
before you.
Make sure he doesn't see me.
I have to get rid of him,
you got it? Calm him down.
Ask him who he is.
- But who's Hector 1?
- Go!
Shit! You're here!
Keep it down, he might hear you.
I need a remote for the gate.
- In the desk...
- Not for the white car. The others.
There aren't any others.
Then another car.
There's a truck.
The deal's still on, right?
When you get rid of them
you won't say anything, right?
- I told him...
- I know, but he won't listen.
He'll leave at some point.
What are you going to do?
Go after him.
Hello?
- This is Hector 3.
- Who?
The last one. Listen to me.
- I'm very sorry.
- What happened?
I'm afraid everyone will know
what we did.
Looks like you bet on the wrong horse.
I'm a failure.
Hector.
Hector?
Where are you?
Why did you have to turn on
the machine?
I don't know.
They won't turn it on
for another 6 months.
I won't be authorized to be there.
I guess...
You wanted to take a closer look
beforehand, right?
If you want to keep your job
and your life as you know it,
keep the guy with the bandage
out of the tank at all costs.
Why?
At least that way somebody
will be there to smack you.
What happened?
I think we're both running
from the same person.
He won't find us here.
- His face is bandaged.
- Yeah.
He's up there.
He won't come down here.
Have you got a telephone?
No. Sit here.
Wake up!
There's a house nearby.
Can you get up?
There it is.
Come on.
No, we shouldn't go in that house.
Careful.
Hello?
Wait here, I'll go check.
Hector!
What happened to you?
Nothing.
There's someone outside.
Across the garden.
He broke the fence.
A man with his face covered.
I ran down here to hide
and I heard someone on the stairs.
There's somebody in the house.
I called the police.
What's wrong?
My God.
Hello?
Who is that?
Come with me.
Hector...
Hide in there until I say.
Tell me what's happening!
No matter what you hear,
don't come out. Don't interfere.
Please!
Listen.
That guy is crazy.
He saw you from far away
and went nuts.
You have to hide from him.
You have to fool him.
Come on.
There's an attic upstairs.
When I say "now, " run upstairs
and lock the door behind you.
You're beautiful.
Now.
No, wait!
Hey! Please open the door!
Listen to me a second!
I was in the garden...
This is my house, you know...
And suddenly I saw you with my...
I was far away...
For God's sake, don't call anybody!
What happened?
Hector, what's going on?
Relax.
Hector...
It's okay.
We still have a while
before it starts raining.