www.SRTfiles.com
Subtitle by: inVINCEble / 3NO / Fixed by iLL
What is it now this early?
Its just a normal inspection, there's just a small problem at the site.
Go ahead, move along.
Wait, wait, your gonna quarantine my produce again dont you?
Just like the last time?
I promise, not this time, now move along.
Go
What a really bad day, rough morning, what more...
(PHONE RINGS)
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Come on
Ehhhh
Oh come on
What a really rough day for me
TRAIN TO BUSAN
-Im gonna hang the phone now, he's here.
It's okay if you and your mom would talk
-You hated her dont you?
Here
You thought i'd forgot your birthday don't you?
Go ahead, open it.
Come on, open it.
Why, don't you like it?
-I want to see mom.
Well, how would you like me to do that one?
-Busan
-Lets go meet mom at Busan.
mom, okay mom. -yes?
we're on our way now, see you
that song, why didn't you finished singing it?
how did you know? you weren't there.
Papa always know what you've been doing
Ahh.. That was close.
Whats going on?
Su-an, are you okay?
What's happening?
Now, we really need to keep going.
(CENTRAL STATION)
All departing passengers, kindly board the train now
as this train is now ready to depart for Busan.
Kyo-shi
Scarf
Excuse me, are you the one incharge? ive seen a suspiscious passenger
inside the lavatory, its been a while since then -really? lets see..
In a hurry?
We'll, you'll need to find another place because two people are
currently using it inside. You could go down there.
go
you sure you really wanna wait?
baby? how are you doing down there?
ahhh.. go ahead, take your time... take your time...
go there, go there...
she's gone, she's gone...
relax... relax...
Miss? Miss, are you okay?
Miss?
Hurry! Everyone Run!
Stand up!
(PANTING)
Conductor! We have a situation here!
(KNOCKS)
Run! Run!
-Oh my God!
-What in the Hell!?
Get away! Just go!
Get out of here! Head for the back!
Get up! Hurry!
Daddy!
Baby?
Sang-hwa! So damn loud!
Sorry, the thing is...
-Get off me!
You idiot! Go help her!
Hey!
What's with you?!
Have you gone mad?!
Baby?
Sung-Kyung!
You can run, right?
(Massive Violence, Increasing Casualties)
Get Away!
Close the door! The door!
Shut the door!
Quick!
Shut it!
Shut it now!
Just shut it!!!
I know her!
Where's the lock?
Buddy, how do I lock this?
Do you hear me?
Let it go
What?
I don't think they know how to open.
They attack because they see us.
What in the...
What are they?
Su-an, you okay?
Hey buddy,
What is it?
Don't you owe me an apology?
What do you mean?
Look at this chump
You shut the door in our faces, asshole!
You weren't the only ones in danger!
What a piece of work.
Come here.
I'll feed you to them.
Stop it!
Everyone's just scared.
-Attention please!
-Due to our current situation,
we wont be stopping in Cheonan,
-For your safety, please stay in your seats.
Hello, anyone there?
-Yes, go ahead
Do you even know what's going on back here?
Why aren't you stopping at Cheonan?
We're aware, sir
-This is the order from the control center.
-Please be seated.
That's nonesense! People are going rabid!
Stop in Cheonan, got it?!
Excuse me.
I'm really sorry but could she sit down?
She's pregnant.
-Okay
Sit, sit.
Thank you.
(Mother)
Mom
-Are you on your way?
Yes, we're en route.
Where are you? Why is it so loud?
-What's happening you say? Everyone's fighting.
-Are you and Su-an okay?
Why're you breathing like that, are you hurt?
-Seok-woo, my baby.
-Please take care of Su-an
Mom, you okay?
-My dear Su-an...
-I love her so much, but she only wants her mom...
-That bitch!
Mom?
-Dad!
-Is granny okay?
What the hell?
Sweetie, sit down.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
My fellow citizens
we're currently experiencing violent riots in all major cities,
resulting in many civilian and police injuries.
Riots led to shutting down of various districts,
and the rioters have forcibly attempted to destroy
or take government property,
For this reason, we're entering state of emergency,
in order to control current situations.
Thanks to our government's rapid response,
various outbreaks are being contained
Fellow citizens,
please refrain from reacting to baseless rumors,
and stay in the safety of your homes, (KEY WORD: ZOMBIES)
We must stay calm and trust the government,
in order to overcome such trying obstacle.
We believe that your safety is not in jeopardy
-Analyst Kim
Mommy's phone is off.
-Those in the front, hurry up!
Su-an, sit over here.
Don't worry, i'll give her a call.
Jong-gil, come sit down.
-You're older, you sit down
Im fine, take it.
-Baby, let's go over there.
Ma'am, take my seat.
-I'm okay, -No, please sit.
Child
Would you like one?
-Thank you!
What a great kid.
-We both got seats. -Keep walking.
Su-an, you didn't have to do that.
-Do what? -Being good.
At a time like this, only watch out for yourself.
Answer me.
Granny always had knee aches.
Sweetie...
May i have you attention please
our train will conclude service at Daejeon station
Military is deployed there, and will secure our train,
so once we arrive, please exit the train.
I repeat,
DAEJEON STATION is our last stop.
Which cities can be entered?
Yeosu, Uljin, Busan. What about Daejeon?
Excuse me, I need to use it.
What about Daejeon?
Why not?!
Sweetie, stay put.
Hey, kiddo.
-Yes?
Who is he? Your dad?
-Yes
Real dad? -Yes.
I wanna know.
What does he do?
-He's a fund manager.
Fund manager? -Yes
He's a bloodsucker.
He leaches off others.
-Don't say that in front of his child.
It's okay
That's what everyone thinks,
-Want some?
-It's what Sleepy eats.
-This is Sleepy. Say hello.
Baby's name is Sleepy?
-No, the fetus name.
-It's like a nickname,
-He's daddy too lazy to come up with a name yet.
Touch her belly.
-Right here.
-Go on.
-Felt it?
I made that.
-You idiot... -But it's true, No?
(Analyst Kim)
Mr. Suh, you called me at a bad time.
Wait, Wait!
Let me ask you something,
What?
I'm on KTX to Daejeon.
KTX? Right this minute?
Yes, I'm almost there,
Is it true military is deployed in Daejeon?
Yes, that's correct.
Is that so? It must be safe there.
Well...It's...
Min, It is safe, right?
Once you arrive, you'll be quarantined.
What?
I'm with my daughter.
Can you help me and my daughter?
But the thing is...
I'll get you a real scoop, do me a favor.
Don't go to the main square, come to the East one.
I'll let my men know.
Okay, thank you. Thanks so much.
All dead... All dead...
What's going on?
So quiet.
Is it Daejeon?
There's nobody.
Why isn't anyone here?
What's going on back there?
This is that violent incident i told you about.
-Your'e the conductor?  -Yes.
How many can fit in the engine car?
We must uncouple it and go to Busan.
-Uncouple? -Yes!
-We can't! -Why not?!
It can't be done here.
Then, where's the Military?
Right...
I only recieved a report about it...
-Where's my business card...
-I'm COO of Stallion Express,
-all routes into Daejeon are cut off.
-our busses are all rerouted
But what for?
The City's been quarantined!
They probably won't let us in.
But Busan is still open, let's go there!
-Wait, if that's true...
-We just take others.  -Take Who?!
-Let's check the station first.
Hey!
Dammit!
RESTRICTED AREA
Don't mind them
Come on sweetie.
Where are we going?
We're going this way.
-Just us? -Yes, Let's go.
What is it?
I'm going this way too.
Main square is that way, just follow other people.
I heard your phone call.
About pulling you two out.
I know others will be quarantined.
It's not true, Su-an.
I'll go tell the others.
- You don't have to. - Of course I do!
Forget them! We're all on our own!
You only care about yourself.
That's why mommy left.
Sweetie...
Here! Over here!
Please help!
Sweetie, stay right here.
Goddamit!
Hold on!
Go back up! Go! Go!
Mr. Min
- Mr. Suh! - I'm in Daejeon
Is everything okay there?
I can't contact my men!
- Mr. Suh! - I'm in Daejeon
Is everything okay there?
I can't contact my men!
What?
Is everything okay there?
I can't contact my men!
What?
Hello?
Help me...
Come on! Hurry!
Hurry up! Quick!
Take this!
Run! Come on!
Asshole! Come on!
Faster!
Hold them off!
- Over here! Run! - This way! Hurry!
Here!
This way!
Come on!
Hurry!
Why aren't we leaving yet?!
There are still more people!
Hurry up!
Come this way!
Hurry!
Faster! Here!
Granny!
Please get up!
No, stop!
My sister!
Hop on!
Me too!
Let me in!
Please!
How much longer? We have to leave!
No! my friends aren't here yet!
Those onboard must survive!
Ain't I right?
Conductor.
Please...depart.
Run! let's go!
Look, the train!
Run faster!
Snap out of it, idiot!
Watch out!
Control, 101 could not dock
at Daejeon due to outbreak.
Advise which station is
available to dock, over.
101, due to unstable comm,
it is difficult to advise.
Control, is 101 clear to reach Busan? Over.
101, we'll clear your route to Busan.
Control center, out.
Advise when you make contact with Busan.
101, out.
Attention everyone.
For those safety of those on board,
we won't be making any stops,
and head straight for Busan.
Conductor, can you hear me?
Go ahead.
Were you able to contact Busan?
No, the communication is erratic.
Full speed, no matter what!
Or we won't get in, understand?
Young-guk, where are you?
I thought you were dead!
I'm sorry!
No one else made it!
I'm sorry.
- Baby? - Mister!
Huh? Why are you answering? Where are you?
We're in the train washroom!
Washroom? which car?
Well... it's...
Car 13!
- Get your ass over here! - Baby
Was that my kid? Is she okay?
Washroom in car 13.
Gonna pass through?
Let's say you got through and rescue them,
how will you come back?
In car 15,
people are gathered there.
Car 9
Only 4 cars away.
I'll lead,
you in the middle,
and you in the back.
Block anyone attacking from the rear.
I heard you're a fund manager.
Then you're an expert,
at leaving useless people behind.
Wait till we exit the tunnel.
Let's go.
Come on!
Let's go!
Move.
Out of the way.
They stopped once we
entered the tunnel, right?
Probably because of darkness.
Yeah, I think so too.
There are even more here.
What do we do now?
There's no way around it.
Let's go.
NO SUBS FOR 2 Minutes
SUBS AVAILABLE NOW
Get that out of my face.
Yo, douche.
Felt good to see your kid thanks to me?
Are you grateful or what?
Why is your ringtone so tacky?
What's wrong with it?
How do i change it?
Am i funny? You little rat?
How tall are you?
181cm.
10km away, at 300km/h...
What?
2 minutes, upcoming tunnel
will give us 2 minutes.
- Can we do it? - We gotta.
If we miss this one,
there's another in 3km...
I bet you never get to
play with your daughter.
When she gets older,
she'll understand why you work so hard.
Dads get all the bad rap and no praise,
but it's all about sacrifice, right?
What's with the look? Did I sound cool?
People rescued. Heading over now.
My friend's coming here!
What did you say?
My friend from another car is coming over.
- Who's coming? - My friend!
He was in car 9, and he
rescued some people.
Rescued?
From there to here, passing
through those monsters?
Without any injuries?
You sure they're not infected?
Are you damn sure?!
What do you mean?
Look, look at them.
At a moment like this,
no one knows what happened
to their families.
We don't even know if your
damn friends are infected!
But allow them in here?!
I don't believe this.
Sir,
please say something.
They'll be here soon.
Sir!
Get over here.
One!
Two!
Run!
Jin-hee! Jin-hee!
Hurry the hell up!
Open up!
Hey! Open this door!
Jin-hee!
Open this door!
- Open up! - Jin-hee, Jin-hee
Open it now!
It wont budge!
It can't open it!
Smash it!
Stand back!
Hurry up!
Dammit...
You stupid idiots!
Come on!
In-gil!
Young-guk!
Stand back!
Stay away!
Stay back, baby. Please go!
Buddy, hey!
Take her and leave.
You have to go!
I said go, douche!
I'm getting tired, please go.
Take care of her, okay?
I'll hold them off, just go!
I'm sorry...
We have to go, let's go!
Yoon Su-yun!
Our baby's name!
Got it?
Why did you do it?!
You bastard!
We could've save them!
Why?!
He's infected!
He's one of them!
This guy's infected!
His eyes! Look at his eyes!
He'll become one of them!
Do you all want to die?!
We must throw them out!
Those of you who just arrived,
I don't think you can stay with us.
Please move to the vestibule.
Just go!
Get out!
Get out now!
Hurry up!
Move!
Go!
Leave us!
Get the hell out!
Out now!
Hurry!
It'll be safer for you to stay here.
No, I don't want to stay.
I'm coming with you.
But...
Get the hell out!
What are you waiting for!
Okay, let's go.
Get out! Rest of you!
Get out!
Get out of here!
Let's go.
Tie it faster!
More ties! Neckties!
Shut up! I'm working on it!
Yun In-gil
Great name.
Always helping others instead of yourself.
Why did you live like that?
What was the point?
So stupid...
Shut up! Be quiet!
Stay in your seat!
What a load of shit.
Finish up and do the other side too.
Thank you for everyting.
That woman...
Stop her!
Control, this is Busan-bound 101!
Requesting current
situation in Busan, over.
Control?!
Control!
It's your birthday...
Don't worry.
I'll take you to mom no matter what.
Aren't you scared?
Of course I am.
I'm scared too.
I was so scared.
I thought I'd never see you again.
I practiced that song just for you.
That's why I couldn't sing.
Because I didn't see you.
Will you stay with me?
Ex-wife
The person you're calling is not available
Analyst Kim
Yes, Kim.
Have you arrived in Busan?
Not yet, where are you? Is it okay there?
Busan succeeded in initial defense.
What? You sure?
NO SUBS For 1 minute
SUBS AVAILABLE NOW
Is this my fault?
It's...
It's not your fault.
Thank you...
Kim...
Attention please.
Due to a blockage on our track,
we have stopped at East Daegu Station.
We should either wait for the rescue team,
or we'll have to reach
Busan in another train.
As soon as I end this announcement,
I will find a working train and
put it on left most track.
What's going on?
I repeat, left most track.
If you're alive, please transfer safely.
Godspeed.
Will there be a rescue?
I heard that Busan is safe.
We have to move now.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Coast clear?
Yeah.
You go ahead.
We've got to find a way across.
What in the...
Over here!
No...
Oh no...
What now...
We have to move, come on!
Jin-hee, let's go!
Stand back!
Jin-hee!
This can't be...
I'm sorry...
Daddy! Wake up!
Daddy! Daddy!
What's going on?
Come on faster! Faster!
Dammit!
Help!
Sweetie, come here!
Su-an, Su-an!
Mister!
Sweetie!
Su-an, come here!
Mister...
Go! Hurry!
Come on!
Hurry!
Let's go!
Hurry! Hurry!
Daddy!
Here is the throttle, the brakes
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I see something
Approaching 2 subjects at our location.
Looks like a woman and a child.
Are you able to verify the subjects?
Its so dark on the other side
I can't clearly see them
Cant clearly see the subjects, unable to verify.
Kill them.
(CHILD SINGING)
2 survivors approaching
THE END