Afraid of flying?
You shouldn't be. It's really safe.
Except in that movie.
They had this, like, creature on the
wing of the plane.
Heard they based that on a true story.
Planes crash all the time.
They cover it up,
buy off the witnesses.
Where the hell are
the flight attendants?
It's all based on the aerodynamics
of hydrometeorology.
Hey. Ever heard
of the Mile High Club?
Come on.
He's sick.
I don't know if we should do this.
Oh, you think?
No. We should.
Get over here!
"You're going down."
I sure am, baby.
No. Rob!
Stop!
What the fuck's going on? Let's go!
Go, go!
Oh, God!
Mayday! Mayday!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Mayday!
Mayday! Mayday!
Cut!
Hey, guys!
When I say "cut," that means stop!
Thank you.
Sandra. You're not supposed
to fly the plane.
Jesus! Vanessa.
Thanks for getting the boom
in the shot again.
Poor Sandra.
He whines like a real director.
I'm sorry.
You know, who are we kidding?
She's no Jamie Lee Curtis, right?
But she'll get better.
Young man, that woman's acting would
be wretched in a porno film.
He's right. I've seen her in a couple
of them. She's really bad.
- I thought there was...
- Shut up, scrote.
Get me a cup of coffee.
Hi, Amy.
Let's try something new this time:
Why don't you get it right,
or I'll kill you?!
Let's try it again. Back to one.
Take 41.
Effects up.
Effects up. Effects up!!
- Roll sound.
- Soundspeed.
- Roll camera.
- Rolling.
Scene 16, take 41.
Fucking action.
As chairman of the film department...
I want to wish you all the best as
you return for the spring semester...
and remind you that yours is the
honor and the privilege to attend...
the greatest film school
that ever existed.
So let's try
and not burn the place down.
Mr. Solomon?
Did everyone have a nice,
toasty holiday?
I'd like to personally welcome
Melvin Zarcoff...
who joins us after a distinguished
Hollywood career.
Welcome.
Mr. Zarcoff...
is a veteran of over 50 films...
Ten bucks he croaks
before the end of the semester.
You don't have ten bucks.
You spent it on your shitty movie.
Come on. A little courtesy?
Yeah, shut the fuck up.
You're so mean.
Clive Lavey will be offering
a new super-8 course.
Action!
Which is required before
you go on to the video workshops.
He the one that did
Vampire Cheerleaders?
No, that was Nick LaVey.
Clive did the Splattertown sequels.
Not enough blood for me.
Some of you have yet
to submit your screenplays.
At the end of the semester,
you may submit your thesis films...
to be considered for the prestigious
Hitchcock Award...
which not only carries with it,
as you all know, a $15,000 stipend...
but, I'm proud to say, has become a
springboard to Hollywood success...
- for such alumni as...
- Cecily Spector.
Josh Bouvet.
Chip Voelker.
And Chip Voelker.
Young lady!
Come here! Come here. What are you
doing out here in the dark?
I was going to the library.
Alone? At this hour? In this weather?
Girl, get in this car. I'll drive you.
So cold.
No "Show me your badge,"
no "Can I see some ID?"
Can I see some ID?
I got no ID.
- Where you going?
- Over the bridge to the...
Library, right.
Good for you, baby.
My name's Reese.
What's your name, sugar?
I'm Amy.
Nice lion.
You ever hide a gun in there?
- What makes you say that?
- I'm a film student.
I had a class last semester
where we saw Pam Grier.
She had this film where she hides a gun
inside a lion like that.
Coffy.
That's one of my favorite films of hers.
I even have my gun
trimmed in gold like hers.
Look at that.
I've always been partial to Foxy Brown.
"That's my sister, baby.
And she's a whole lot of woman!"
You'll do action movies like Coffy?
I don't know. I have to make a thesis
film. I can't think of a good story.
I got a good story.
Yeah, it's about a campus serial killer
who murders eight students...
but nothing happens because the
prestigious university covers it up.
I heard this one.
It supposedly happened at Pendleton.
It was just an urban legend.
You didn't let me finish.
After the murders,
the chief of security...
who refused to go along with the
cover-up, is fired.
Spends the entire year looking
for work.
Finally lands an entry-level position
at another university.
Thanks for the ride.
- Oh, yeah, baby, any time.
- Have a good night.
Urban legend, my ass.
A lot of film historians don't seem
to be able to gauge...
the impact of mise en so? Ne
on cinema v? Rit? Storytelling.
On the other hand, it could be argued
mise en so? Ne or staging...
are two examples that are basically
mutually exclusive.
What is cinema v? Rit? If not...
the absence of staging?
- And so on.
- Come in.
- Godard's victims...
- Sorry. I'll come back later.
Draped in the trees in the French
countryside.
I just had an idea
for my thesis film so...
Come in. Sit down.
Hi, Dr. Fain.
So...
the movie is about a serial killer...
whose murders
are all based on urban legends.
That's pretty cool.
But not exactly what we've come to
expect from a Mayfield.
I know, but I think I'm ready
for a work of fiction.
I think you are too. You mind, Richard?
You can get the door...
on your way out.
What do you think?
Horror or suspense?
A little bit of both.
Just like Hitchcock.
Hitchcock's themes might
serve you well.
Paranoia, fear of imprisonment,
wrong man accused...
how the lines blur
between fantasy and reality.
So you think it's okay?
It's great.
Travis Stark.
Who would've thought
you'd be the next Spielberg?
- Yeah, right.
- Come on.
Enjoy it.
Next year you'll be in the real world.
Here's to unemployment.
Here's to you for saving my ass again.
Two more.
Do I get a private screening
when I get back?
We'll have to see.
I worked my ass off on your film.
- And every film you've done.
- I know, and I love you for it.
Thanks.
Here's to loving me for it.
Drink up.
Don't you have a plane to catch?
Wasted is the only way to fly.
I've got to go finish working on my
film. So have a safe trip.
See you when you get back.
That guy's a real spaz.
You know, I'm a director too.
Really?
Directors make a lot of money?
Pretty much.
Then you won't mind paying for these.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
911. Please state your emergency.
I just woke up in a tub of ice...
- Don't tell me. Your kidney's gone.
- Yes.
Honey, I got Princess Di on line four.
I got to go.
What?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
So check it out.
It's a tradition during finals week.
Everybody's up late studying...
and, at midnight, everyone
screams as a release of tension.
At the same time,
between midnight and 12:01...
a coed is brutally attacked.
Her screams go unnoticed, drowned out
by the screams of those around her.
True story, right?
Yeah, I heard it happened at Harvard.
No.
It's an urban legend.
Like that girl who eats a burrito
with the pregnant roach...
and the eggs hatch inside of her
nose?
Or like that girl who takes a bite
of a chicken sandwich...
and discovers that the mayonnaise
is really pus from a chicken tumor?
There's that guy who has crabs,
unzips his fly...
Okay!
You definitely have the idea.
But I have my thesis film.
There a role in it for me?
You can scream, can't you?
Mayday! Mayday! Mayday!
Mayday! Mayday!
You guys scared the shit out of me.
We're movie monsters.
- Want to be the Count?
- The Count sucks.
Get it?
Travis Stark, film genius.
- What are you doing?
- Looking for her.
She was looking through the window.
Trying to get her mack on.
Totally.
Sorry.
Let's play hopscotch.
Anyway...
- Is this your thesis film?
- Yeah, but it's not done.
I'm sure it's a mess right now.
I wouldn't call it a mess.
Right. I mean...
I just got my script approved
for my film, and thought...
maybe you'd want
to take a look at it.
Why don't you come by Tuesday night
and we'll talk about it?
Okay.
I'll call you about it.
On the phone.
I hear cell phones
give you brain cancer.
That's an urban legend.
Too bad.
This is what we're going to film.
Here's a twenty. Go wash my car.
Go ahead.
You know he's a P.A.,
not a slave, right?
Same difference. The guy's applied
to film school three times now.
Well, there's this girl...
who's afraid of the dark.
She puts her hand down,
and if her dog licks her hand...
she knows everything's okay.
Can I be the dog?
Because I'm a great licker.
That's what Dirk told me.
So anyway, when she wakes up
in the morning...
she walks into her bathroom and sees
her dog hanging from the shower rod.
- And a message.
Latex and cornflakes. We can do that.
Latex and cornflakes? One call to my
old man, and we can go digital.
Digital sucks. Latex rules.
That's not what your god
George Lucas says.
Yeah, well, fuck George Lucas.
- You're going to Hell, man.
- I know.
I need to talk to you, Mayfield.
In private.
Be right back.
- Where were you?
- This is a nice script, Mayfield.
Nice horror script.
It seems similar,
but I'm going for a paranoid...
That is bullshit. Mayfield,
you stole my fucking genre.
- Trust me, I'm not stealing anything.
- Trust you?
Yeah, I should trust you.
To steal a Hitchcock from me.
Nobody is going
to steal a Hitchcock from me.
Especially you, little girl.
Find yourself another D.P.
Are you all right, Travis?
I got graded on my film today.
C fucking minus.
How could that happen?
So much for the Hitchcock.
You don't need that.
You're better than that.
You're the most talented filmmaker
at this school.
Amy, I have no money.
I have no connections.
I feel really awful asking this now...
but I'm kind of desperate.
Toby dropped off my crew today.
You know another D.P. I could use?
Yeah. His name is Simon.
He shot my film.
I can give him a call if you want.
It's going to be okay.
I'll see you.
Hey, guys.
- Anyone seen Sandra?
- Naked, you mean?
Anyone not seen her naked?
I heard that!
- Watch out!
- Oh, my God!
She's...
Oh, my God.
Got you.
She's one hell of an actress, ain't she?
Movie magic.
Oh, my God.
Was I in the moment?
What were you doing?
Rehearsing.
I got an audition to play a coma patient
on ER.
- With help from Graham's daddy.
- It was nothing.
Thank you, baby.
Let's go watch her clean up.
You hear a noise while you're in the
bedroom. You come in here.
The camera follows you from the doorway.
Comes in.
You see the dog, you turn...
you see the message, then the killer.
You scream.
And that's it. Got it?
Picture's up.
Everybody shut up! Picture's up.
Okay, roll sound.
- I'll see you later.
- Graham, hello!
Can you hold on a minute?
Speed.
Pardon me?
Is this the set of Amy Mayfield?
Yeah, I'm Amy.
Listen, I need a reservation
for two for tonight. 8:45.
I'm Schorm Jabuscko.
Travis says you need
director of photography.
Travis. Yeah.
Thank you for coming. Unfortunately...
this camera is all we have...
Schorm.
You can call me Simon.
Don't worry.
I bring my own.
This is my baby...
baby.
You know,
you're a very beautiful woman.
Well, you're pretty cute too,
camera boy.
If you were a girl,
I would definitely fuck you.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Hey, baby.
- Hi, doll-face.
Can I give you a lift?
You already have.
Shit!
Jesus!
Idiot, Sandra. Idiot.
All right. Keys, keys. Where would I
be if I were keys? Keys, keys.
Goddamn it. Keys.
Hello. Where are you? Keys.
A mess.
Disgusting. Goddamn it.
Yes.
Cut.
- She sucks.
- Urban Legends, scene 3, take 28.
- Dog looks good.
- It does.
Action.
- You could turn it into a comedy.
- Scene 3
Take twenty-fucking-nine.
Okay, action.
Cut. Please cut.
What the...?
- This isn't us, is it?
- Wrong reel.
Oh, that's Sandra.
- What is she doing?
- That's Sandra's best angle.
That's definitely Sandra's ass.
Gratuitous ass shot.
Dude, that looks so real.
Right there. Get her.
They slash a major artery
and that's all the blood?
O.J. left more blood on the Bronco.
It was all right.
The dog was good.
Did you guys do this?
I didn't. Did you?
Simon?
No.
But I like it.
Where's the reel that was on this?
I don't know.
You swear you didn't do this?
Yeah, Dirk and I could do much better.
You don't think it was real?
No. Not enough blood.
Come on. This is classic Sandra.
- She probably staged it for her reel.
- Then, who shot it?
Guys. Travis Stark, he...
he's dead.
By now,
most of you have heard the news.
For those of you who haven't...
Travis Stark took his life
last night.
It's just hard to know what to say.
He blew his head off in the campus
tower. I mean, literally blew it off.
- Dental records wouldn't help.
- It's important for us...
to celebrate who he was...
and, what I believe,
he could've become.
He was a gifted filmmaker who raised the
bar for all of us.
But not only did he let himself down
he let us all down.
Everybody goes through a time when
they feel alone and helpless.
We need to go easy on ourselves...
and remember we're just doing
the best we can.
You know, in the movie
Day for Night...
Truffaut asked the question:
"Is film more important than life?"
He was a hell of a talent.
Are you okay?
No.
Have you seen Sandra?
Sandra's in a coma, Amy.
On ER in LA.
You should let me help you, too.
I know you're not hitting on me now.
With my dad's connections,
I can get your film done tomorrow.
I'd like to try it for myself.
That is hypocritical bullshit.
I know about you.
You're a Hollywood kid, like me.
What? I grew up in Chicago.
Not before 1992, you didn't.
You were 13 years old when you and
your mama moved from Beverly Hills.
After your daddy,
Taylor Mayfield died...
while shooting
the same nature crap that you do.
Don't look so surprised.
It's in your admissions file.
Being the daughter of an Oscar-winning
documentary filmmaker...
didn't hurt your chance of getting
into this school.
Why don't you cut
the girl-next-door crap?
You need to make it to save face...
just as bad as I do.
Maybe worse.
I'll see you on the set...
darling.
I heard he blew his head off
up in the campus tower.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hello? Who's there?
Travis?
They told me you killed yourself.
You knew him?
What?
My brother. You knew him?
I don't understand.
I'm Trevor Stark.
I'm his brother.
I didn't know that Travis had a brother.
When was the last time you saw him?
I saw him a couple of days ago.
Was he upset?
He was depressed because of
the grade he got on his thesis film.
He thought he'd lost his chance
at the Hitchcock Award.
I thought that's why you...
he...
killed himself.
Is that what everyone thinks?
Wait. Please.
If you're not Travis, why are you here?
Please.
My brother didn't kill himself.
Trust me. He wouldn't do that.
What are you saying?
You think he was murdered?
I know that's what happened.
- Have you said anything to the police?
- I can't.
Why not?
I just can't. Listen...
don't tell anybody you saw me here.
Please.
Something happened to my brother,
and I'm going to find out what.
Three, two, one, midnight.
And cut.
Thank you so much. Thank you.
All right, we're done.
You can go home. That's a wrap.
- Sorry it was so late.
- What's going on?
Nothing.
There's something wrong.
Nothing. Just...
Hang on. Hey, guys.
I need help with these wild tracks.
Great. They're gone.
I'll do it.
No, I just need a wild track of them
screaming. Get some sleep.
- You sure?
- Yeah, I got it.
I'll talk to you later.
I must smoke.
I need a bunch of loud screaming.
You're a very beautiful woman.
Is that a Beaulieu?
A Bolieux.
Can I see it?
No.
Have a good night.
Okay, and rolling.
Now, remember guys: Nice and loud.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Help.
Help!
Help! Help!
And cut.
Help me!
Hey, Foxy
Oh, Miss Foxy Brown
Go, girl!
Scared me to death.
Have you been watching
these monitors?
Yes.
Are you signing my paychecks now?
I thought I heard someone screaming
like they were being attacked.
Anybody else hear them?
I had my headphones on.
I was recording screaming.
Let me get this, you were recording
screaming, then you heard...
screaming.
Your movie's making you paranoid.
Can we play the last hour
of these monitors?
Last hour?
Honey, I have rounds to make.
You think I just watch movies?
- Can I just borrow the tapes?
- Borrow them?
I'll bring them back. I promise.
All right.
If you see anything strange...
and I mean really strange...
you bring these back
to me to look at.
And start wearing a bell or something!
Stan?
That's not funny.
I'm serious. Stop it.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Goddamn it! Girl, this is getting old!
Somebody's after me.
How'd you find me?
You see? I do watch those things.
One tape was in my bag when I threw it.
I ran out of the scoring stage, but...
I had another tape. I dropped it.
Did you see it?
I looked, but I didn't see no tape, just
your crazy white ass down in the sewer.
I saw Simon killed. I saw the attack.
Look, honey, without proof...
This is proof.
Vandals.
Any overworked policeman
with a caseload a mile long...
is going to look
at this as vandalism.
Baby, trust me.
It's the way it is.
Let me take you home...
get out of them wet clothes.
And maybe I can go home.
Hey, this is Travis. Leave it.
Hey, it's me, from the tower.
I don't know if you're staying there,
but I need to talk to you.
It's about Travis.
I think you're right.
After I got away, I realized the footage
of Sandra was real. It wasn't a prank.
You think your friend Sandra
was killed as well.
Yeah. And that would've
been the third.
Have you told anyone else?
I was going to tell the police.
You can't tell the police.
Why not?
That's the second time you've said that.
Look...
Travis and I both had a certain amount
of creativity.
I focused mine on lesser pursuits.
And as a result, my relationship with
the authorities isn't that great.
But thanks to Travis, I'm starting to
get my shit together.
He was always riding me about never
following through on anything.
So I owe it to him.
You know?
Yeah.
Reminds me of my dad.
He was a filmmaker...
documentaries.
After he died...
I thought that if I didn't make
documentaries too, that I'd forget him.
But he'd be proud of me to know I'm
doing something I'm passionate about.
That's why I decided
to make this fiction film.
Not because I had any chance
at the...
The what?
At the Hitchcock award.
The winner's guaranteed a shot
at directing in Hollywood.
You think
somebody would kill for that?
Maybe.
Wait a minute.
Where's your shoot tomorrow?
It's at the theme park outside town.
Because if you're right, whoever's doing
this is going to come after you again.
This is our chance
to draw out the killer.
Trevor, I can't.
I know you're scared.
I mean, so am I.
But don't we owe it
to Travis and your friends?
I won't let anything happen to you.
I will be there.
Trust me.
- I have a good story for you.
- Sandra's in a coma.
I heard he blew his head off.
Don't tell anybody you saw me here.
Latex and cornflakes.
- He was a talent.
- Don't act so surprised.
- So much for the Hitchcock.
- No one's going to steal it from me.
- Fantasy and reality.
- I'm good at that.
You need to make it to save face
just as bad as I do.
Tragic.
- Trust me.
- Paranoia.
I know about you.
- Fear of imprisonment.
- Not what we'd expect...
- Nice horror script.
- The wrong man accused.
- Especially you.
- My brother didn't kill himself.
Don't tell anybody you saw me.
- Trust you.
- Trust me.
Got you.
Quite the artist. What are you guys
working on? Another urban legend?
"The Tunnel of Terror."
A carnival comes to town.
Only, it's notlike other carnivals.
It has a Tunnel of Terror filled
with fake bloody corpses.
Everybody thinks
it's the scariest ride.
Then in the morning,
the carnival's gone...
and a bunch of children
are missing.
It turns out that the bodies
were real in the Tunnel of Terror.
This is the Tunnel of Terror?
It will be.
Hello, tenderfoot.
You must be as high as my tool
to ride the Merry Miners.
I told you.
Whoo, suki suki now.
Dead bodies, anyone?
Oh, my God.
- So this is our Tunnel of Terror.
- You'll be able to make it work?
- We need three hours.
- You only have one.
- Perfect.
- Just negotiate.
- Wonder Twin powers...
- Activate.
Split it. Coming through.
Good luck, boys.
Sorry, baby.
Dirk! How you doing down there?
Back to work, boys.
Power's up.
Take a look at these babies.
Hurry back up here.
These things are creepy.
Scared of miners? Weak sauce, man.
Shut up and come up here.
I can't believe Simon flaked.
I can.
What happened to
good old Simon anyway?
What's he doing here?
Carrying shit. He wanted to help.
So what?
It's my crew. That's "so what."
I don't want all these people here.
Take a look at these babies.
This little piggy went wee-wee-wee all
the way home.
Nice, man.
You bring up the strobes?
Let me do this one.
Did you call me a ho?
Don't you think you're over your head
on this little masterpiece?
You pull a power trip on me
in front of everybody?
You shouldn't do that. You know?
Not to me, you shouldn't.
I'm out of here. Pack up this shit.
This will take a long time.
You guys go eat before
we get stuck here all night.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
I'll stay here.
Just come back in an hour.
Okay. I'll bring you back something.
All right. Guys, lunch. One hour.
Just be careful.
Always.
The lights are in place.
How you doing?
Everything's fine.
Let her rip.
- I'm about to go take care of my baby.
- Use a rubber.
Dirk and Stan, you read me?
You okay in there?
Can you guys read me?
You coming in for a runthrough?
Yeah, I'm coming now.
Okay, you push the red...
No. No. Green.
Push the green button and pull the
pick ax. That should start the ride.
- Go for it.
- Copy that.
Howdy, tenderfoot, and welcome. Keep
your keister in the seat till the end.
Don't want to lose
any nuggets along the way.
So long, stranger.
She's coming in for a runthrough.
Hurry up, man.
Hurry on up!
We outdid ourselves this time.
She's going to love it!
Coming up.
Okay, guys, very funny.
Guys, okay. I'm really scared.
Just stop.
Guys, are you okay down there?
Nice set. Where's your crew?
There's the two of them.
They were both electrocuted.
Stupid kids.
And that's your final statement?
Anything else you could tell us,
other than the power going out?
Anything else, sugar?
We can take it from here, detective.
No, there's nothing else.
Okay. We'll be in touch.
Where were you?
Is this what you call following
through?
You didn't do anything.
You didn't protect me.
That's not true.
I saw what happened with Graham.
That's why I followed him.
When I came back, the police were
everywhere. What happened?
Exactly what you said would happen.
He came back.
And now Dirk and Stan are dead.
Oh, my God.
I trusted you.
Amy, I'm sorry.
At least we know it's not Graham.
Not exactly. I lost him.
I'm wrong about everything.
Why?
Dirk and Stan were sophomores.
They weren't up
for the Hitchcock Award.
So why kill them?
I don't know what to do.
I'm so scared.
It's okay.
I'm here now.
Listen.
You need to get some rest.
Then we'll go to the tower
and start at the beginning.
You need to go to sleep.
You're exhausted.
- I know, but...
- You're exhausted.
Maybe there's something we missed.
Something that will help us.
Just don't leave me again, okay?
I won't.
I promise you.
Vanessa.
I got your note.
Let me just tell you
how I felt when I read this.
What?
At first I was a little surprised,
but...
you know, not really.
But I...
Vanessa, I didn't write a letter.
What?
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Oh, God.
Who would do this?
Come on, come on!
Amy, what's going on?
What are we running from?
What is it?
What is it, Amy?
Oh, shit.
Who the fuck's there?!
What the fuck's down there?!
Who is down there?!
Oh, rats.
Come on!
What's going on? Is it a joke?
No, it's not a joke.
- Did you hear that?
- Yeah.
What the fuck?
I don't hear anything.
Somebody help me!
What the hell?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Amy. What's wrong?
It's Vanessa.
- What?
- In the tower!
Why weren't you there when I woke?
Amy, I found something.
You've got to believe me.
Let's get out of here.
So I got to thinking...
if the killer wasn't killing off
the competition for the Hitchcock...
only film students,
there had to be a connection.
But I couldn't find one.
So then I took you...
out of the loop.
My brother's thesis film project.
All the victims worked on it.
Got it.
That was just awful.
How could Travis make
such a shitty movie?
I think I saw something.
- It's a splice.
- So?
It's a hard splice.
See, there's splicing tape connecting
the last frame of the film...
to the first frame of the credits.
- That's not normal?
- No.
This is a final print.
It's a copy from a negative.
You shouldn't see splices.
Somebody changed the credits
on Travis' film?
Somebody changed the film
on Travis' credits.
To pass it off as their own?
There's one person
on this crew who's still alive.
Oh, my God.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Gone with the wind
Mayfield? What the f...?
Okay, okay.
What do you want?
Travis.
That should hold him.
What's the matter, Toby?
Looks like you've seen a ghost.
Professor Solomon.
Could you talk to them?
They have a gun...
Shut up!
Travis?
Professor.
But I thought...
Thank you for coming,
Professor Solomon.
Am I sorry.
Maybe you should sit down.
Pull up a chair, professor.
What's with the gun?
It's fake. It's a prop.
Oh, my God.
What's going on here?
Toby stole my film
and switched the credits on it.
Is that what this is all about?
Well don't flatter yourself.
Back up a step. Travis, why the
charade? I thought you were dead.
We'll get to that.
Toby's film was falling apart.
He knew mine was good,
because he did the sound on it.
No, I did not do the sound
on your film, you fake-suicide psycho.
You did it. You know that.
You gave me the credit
so I could graduate.
You never saw his film?
No, I never came near his film.
Professor, help me out here.
You realize what this means, don't you?
What?
I gave you an A in sound for nothing.
Film's a collaborative medium.
And who the fuck are you?
I put a gun in Travis Stark's mouth.
And I pulled the trigger.
Why?
To frame you.
As a matter of fact...
I need your prints on this gun
to prove you killed Toby and Travis.
And whoever this loser is.
Trevor, is it?
Cute.
Run, Amy!
Get up!
If you don't get out here,
I'll choke him!
Move.
Get out here
before you kill someone else.
Amy, don't come out.
True about twins? Did you feel it
when I blew your brother's brains out?
Guess it's going to hurt dying twice.
Let him go.
You got what you wanted.
You think this is what I wanted?
Fuck teaching!
What are you talking about?
When I was a student here...
the faculty was deadlocked
for the Hitchcock, between my film...
and a piece of shit by Chip Voelker.
So they asked a guest filmmaker
to cast the deciding vote.
Taylor Mayfield...
documentary hack.
With that one vote...
your father robbed me of a career
I should've had in Hollywood.
And I've been trapped here ever since.
But then...
Travis made a brilliant film.
And I saw my way out.
But I needed an alibi.
Then bingo.
You walk in my office
with that twisted little movie idea...
giving me the cover I needed.
You killed everyone
who worked on Travis' film...
to pass it off as your own.
Hey, babe, whatever.
While you end up
in some lesbo prison...
I'll be heading to L.A. with Travis'
film and a 3 picture deal.
That only works in movies, idiot.
Freeze!
Oh, thank God.
- They were trying to kill me.
- He's lying.
First things first!
I want the girl to drop the gun
and kick it away!
But he's lying!
I said drop it and kick it away!
Thank you.
Now, everyone out
of the creepy-ass graveyard!
That includes the undead!
Professor, drop the shovel.
She's the one you saw coming
out of the tower.
- Don't listen to him.
- Cross to me, professor.
You're safe now.
It's true, isn't it?
I saw you leaving the tower.
Listen.
But I never told anyone I saw her.
Motherfucker!
You fucking son of a bitch!
Watch out!
Okay, everybody, calm down!
What do you say, hon?
Give me your best shot.
You filmed Sandra's death.
It's called "cin? Ma v? Rit?".
Nice touch, don't you think?
It was out of focus.
But you know what they say.
Those who can't do teach.
What are you going to do?
Come on.
Do it.
Pass it to me.
Oh, my God.
Thank God.
That's my sister, baby.
She's a whole lot a woman.
We need help at the film department.
It has been a year of pain
and tremendous loss.
And our final award is also tinged
with sadness...
for its recipient is
no longer with us.
We are fortunate, however,
to have his brother here...
to accept on his behalf.
We're proud to give this year's
Alfred Hitchcock Award...
in memory of Travis Stark...
and The Gods of Men
Freeze!
You psycho motherfucker!
And cut.
- How many times we got to do this?
- Good. Print that.
We're going to do this one more time.
Back to one.
Let me give you a hand.
Listen. I am Amy Mayfield's agent.
We're not taking less
than a 3 picture deal.
- How am I doing?
- You're doing great.
You too.
Picture's up.
All right, let's try it. And rolling.
- Okay, let's get this.
- Soundspeed.
Urban Legends scene six, take two.
Mark it.
Don't you just love that movie?
I think we have a lot in common.