This is the police.
Help!
Help, please!
MADRID
JUNE 15TH, 1991
01:35 A.M.
It's okay.
Please, calm down
so I can understand you.
- What happened?
- Please, you have to come!
He's inside! He's inside!
Please, calm down.
Tell me what you're seeing.
Is there someone in your house?
Hello!
Detective!
That's the building there, 3C.
He's here.
Mom! Mom!
Detective!
We're going to send someone
right away. I need your address.
8 Gerardo Núñez Street.
Are you still there?
Hello?
Calling all units, we have a 402
at 8 Gerardo Núñez Street.
Any available cars please respond.
I repeat, 8 Gerardo Núñez Street.
EARLY MORNING, JUNE 15TH, 1991,
MADRID POLICE STATION 02-12
RECEIVED AN EMERGENCY PHONE CALL.
THIS STORY IS BASED
ON THE POLICE REPORT...
...FILED BY THE DETECTIVE
IN CHARGE OF THE CASE.
It's confirmed.
There are four kids,
two more are upstairs.
THREE DAYS EARLIER
THURSDAY, JUNE 12TH, 1991
Irene,
you get the bathroom first.
Lucia, let's go!
Get up.
Don't make any noise.
Come on, buddy, get up.
Let's go to school.
I want to go to school.
You want to go to school?
Great.
- You wet the bed again?!
- Yeah.
Come here.
Tell Irene
to clean you up in the bathroom.
Vero!
- What's wrong?
- Irene won't let me in.
- I'm taking a shower!
- Stop yelling!
He peed himself again.
Clean him up, you're older than him.
Fine.
I heard you.
I'm older, I came out first.
- Did you heat the milk?
- No.
Quite the older sister you are.
Lucia!
Pay attention, please!
The teacher said to bring
pictures to look at the eclipse.
- Pictures?
- Yeah.
Your turn. Not pictures.
Negatives, to shield our eyes.
Gross!
The towel smells like chicken.
You smell like wet chicken.
- Stop it! Vero!
- Lucia, leave Irene alone.
Take one of
the towels hanging outside.
Your shoes are untied.
You could have told me
about the pictures last night.
- Me, me, me.
- Fine, you do it.
- Everything OK?
- Yeah.
We had a birthday party
and closed at 2 AM last night.
I'm exhausted.
I came to get
a picture for a class project.
You rest.
I'm going to sleep some more.
I'll see you later.
I heard it was night.
It's all magic.
And a spirit
invited you to dream.
I know that lately,
I've barely stopped.
I feel like I'm rambling...
Dawn breaks so early,
and I'm so alone,
and I'm not sorry for yesterday.
If the stars light you,
today they're your guide.
You feel so strong, you think,
no one can touch you...
- What's up?
- I won't wet the bed tomorrow.
- What?
- I won't wet the bed tomorrow!
Good!
OK, go inside.
- How are you?
- Fine.
- You have fun?
- Yeah.
You know the earth
always revolves around its own axis.
It also revolves around the sun.
But the moon,
which is a satellite,
revolves around the earth.
When the moon goes
between the sun and the earth,
an astronomical phenomenon occurs,
and we call this a solar eclipse.
The moon's shadow
is cast on the earth's surface.
It's interesting,
because it's subjective.
It depends on
the subject looking at it.
What we see here today in Madrid...
...is not what they see
in Barcelona, or in Paris.
Next slide, please.
We can clearly see two different areas:
the shadow, or umbra area,
and the penumbra area.
The umbra has no light,
in total darkness.
Do YOU HAVE IT?
The penumbra is
the fragile shadow area.
Superstition has given
many explanations for eclipses.
Next slide, please.
Primitive cultures believed...
...that the sky
reflected what happened on earth.
So they believed
that during eclipses...
...darkness reigned over light.
In many cultures,
they thought that eclipses...
...were a good time for sacrifices.
Next slide, please.
Even human sacrifices.
In fact, they'll explain it
better in History class, but...
...the Maya
believed that human blood was...
Well, we're out of time.
We have to go see the eclipse,
but when we come back,
we'll talk about the different kinds.
Sara,
help me with the window, please.
If you don't have a picture,
take it from the box over there, OK?
OK.
And remember not to look at the sun,
only look through the negative.
- Wait a minute.
- No, let's go.
- Just a second.
- Girls, upstairs!
- Rosa, turn the projector off.
- OK.
Wait...
What's wrong?
We have to wait for Diana.
The one
who got held back?
Yeah, I told her what we were doing
and she wants to come.
Rosa, it was supposed
to be between the two of us.
Well, now it's
between us, and Diana.
She's really nice, anyway.
Besides...
Remember Manolo?
With the spiked hair?
The one who died
in a motorcycle wreck!
- He was her boyfriend.
- Why'd you have to tell her?
Sorry, it just slipped out.
But everybody knows
it works better with odd numbers.
Everyone's upstairs.
The coast is clear now.
Begoña,
what is this junk?
Not with these!
Girls!
Get in place,
it's about to start.
Come on,
over here.
Look,
the negatives and the...
Gross!
Stay together.
It's this way!
Hey, wait for me!
Here.
This is disgusting.
Have you guys done this before?
Yeah, in my village.
You said you have too, right?
Yeah, but with
paper cut-outs, you know?
Never with an official board.
THE GREAT ENCYCLOPEDIA OF THE OCCULT
They're dead, but that doesn't mean
they know everything, right?
What did you bring?
A picture.
What is that?
You need a personal item
of the person you want to contact.
A picture
isn't a personal item!
Of course it is!
It's personal if it belongs
to the person in the picture.
I didn't bring
any of Manolo's stuff.
Can you see it?
The moon is going between.
See the ring? See it?
Look, it's the solar ring.
I can't believe it!
Always look through...
Look at it with this, OK?
It's so beautiful!
It says to put
your index finger on the glass.
- Close your eyes.
- Why?
Because you
make contact faster.
Is anyone with us?
Is there
anyone here with us?
It wasn't me, I swear!
Who are you?
You want
to talk to one of us?
Are you...?
Are you Veronica's Dad?
Do you want
to talk to Veronica?
S...
P...
Y...
I spy.
- What do you spy?
- With my little eye...
- What are you, a dumbass?
- You're the dumbass!
I know you're moving it.
Vero,
did you move it?
Who are you?
It burns!
Vero, are you OK?
What's happening?
Vero!
No!
Please, Vero, let's go!
Please, Vero!
Find the flashlight!
Diana, the flashlight!
- Where is it?
- Over there!
- Rosa, I can't see!
- Fuck!
Here it is!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I've got it,
I've got it here.
I've got it.
Fuck!
The board is broken.
Where's Veronica?
Veronica?
Veronica!
- Diana, go get help now!
- We're gonna get in trouble.
Just go! Shut up!
Veronica.
Veronica!
What's wrong?
What are you saying?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Veronica.
Can you hear me?
What happened to me?
You fainted.
Follow my finger.
We tried to call your Mom,
but we couldn't get ahold of her.
She's working.
Have you ever
fainted like this before?
No.
Did you eat breakfast?
Yes.
Are you diabetic?
Veronica!
Would you listen to me?
Are you diabetic?
I don't know.
Blood sugar, any problems?
Family history with diabetes?
I don't think so.
Did you take any drugs?
- Pot, pills...?
- No, no.
- You sure?
- I'm sure.
Are you on your period?
- Veronica, how old are you?
- Fifteen.
And you haven't
had your period?
It's probably low blood pressure.
You might have an iron deficiency.
If you can,
I recommend eating red meat today.
Rest here for a few minutes.
Class is almost over.
- That's so cool!
- Girls!
We always have to wait for you!
What happened to your hand?
I cut it on
some glass during recess.
Will you let me see?
- Where's Rosa?
- They left already.
- They didn't wait for me?
- You missed the eclipse.
- The sun was totally dark.
- The sun was black.
It was really cool.
Why weren't you there?
I was in the nurse's office.
Hey, don't tell Mom about this.
- About what?
- About my cut, OK?
- Zip your lips...
...zip your lips...
...and throw away the key.
Come on, let's go.
- What's wrong, Irene?
- Sister Death is looking at you.
But she's blind,
she can't see anything.
She's blind.
- Wasn't she deaf?
- No, blind, not deaf.
BEST MOM IN THE WORLD
- Hi, Mom!
- Hey there!
Can I have
money to play Martians?
Fine,
you take it.
But just one round,
then you go home, OK?
Mom?
- Not in front of the kids, man!
- Mom!
Give me
the desserts for the 7!
Stop for a second, please.
Why do you cover up
such a beautiful face?
Mom!
I'll give you Tupperware
with macaroni for tonight.
Mom!
Get Antoñito
and go home to eat.
Come on!
I'm starving,
my stomach is rumbling.
- They're farts.
- You're the one farting.
Farts, farts, farts...
- Irene, heat up the food.
- Why me?
- I always have to do it!
- Antoñito, go wash your hands.
Because I'm the favorite.
What's that?
Nothing.
Go set the table.
Vero!
Didn't I tell you to set the table?
You keep an eye on it.
- This much?
- Yeah.
Then, in front of
the sun, there was...
- It was all black and dark.
- It was the moon!
You didn't understand
what the science teacher said.
Imagine a black ball
and then a yellow ball.
The black one covers the yellow one,
which is the sun.
-Irene, can you get some milk?
- You get it!
Rock, paper or scissors?
Rock, paper, scissors.
One, two, three. Now!
-I won!
- No, best two out of three.
Rock, paper, scissors.
One, two, three. Now!
Crap!
I beat you, I beat you, I beat you...
- You cheated.
- I cheated? You cheated!
I never complain when you win.
There's no milk
left in the fridge, over.
It's in the pantry, over.
Veronica?
Hello?
Irene, come here.
Veronica's all frozen up.
Veronica?
- Veronica!
- Good thing it says easy-open.
Veronica!
What happened?
You weren't moving.
And you puked.
Are you OK?
I'm fine.
Clean this up, please.
I'll get it.
Yeah, OK.
Yeah, I'll tell her.
Bye-bye.
Who was it?
Rosa.
Why didn't you give me the phone?
She said she couldn't come,
she has to run
some errands with her mom.
She didn't ask to talk to me?
No.
Hello?
Hi, it's Veronica.
Is Rosa there?
Hi, Vero.
No, she isn't here.
But she just called.
She just went out the door with Diana...
I thought
all three of you were meeting.
Vero.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm running late.
Tell her not to forget
that she has to be home by eight.
OK, I'll let her know.
Thanks, sweetheart.
See you soon.
Centella gives me time to enjoy,
Centella, Centella.
Centella gives me time to enjoy...
Girls, put your PJs on.
Seven! You're in the bathroom!
Doesn't count!
Vero told.
Let's start over.
Centella gives me time to enjoy...
Antoñito, that's enough!
You sound like a parrot!
If you don't know the jingle,
why are you singing it?
Yeah, yeah.
I see you...
Oh, time to myself...
Oh, time for life...
Centella gives me time to enjoy...
Centella...
Girls, behave.
Scrub hard, I'll be right back.
Girls, please.
What?
Oh, time to myself, time for life...
Centella gives me time to enjoy...
Vero.
Vero!
Antoñito!
- Vero!
- Antoñito!
Vero!
Antoñito!
Antoñito, what's wrong?
It burns!
What happened?
- What is that?
- It burns.
Did you touch the faucet?
I didn't do anything.
One, two, three, guess!
- A bird.
- No.
A flower.
No.
A dog.
Turn over.
One, two, three, guess!
- A balloon!
- Yes!
I'm sorry
I put the water on so hot.
It wasn't you.
What?
What did you say?
I won't wet the bed tomorrow.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Centella gives me time to enjoy,
Centella, Centella.
Centella gives me a shiny floor,
Oh, time to myself,
Time for life.
Centella gives me time to enjoy,
Centella, Centella.
Let's go...
...leave this room,
go to outer space...
...your eyes glaze over...
...all the same color.
Let's go,
leave this room...
...go to outer space,
your eyes glaze over...
...all the same color.
While nothing matters!
Nine...
Eight...
Seven...
Six...
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One!
Vero...
What are you doing here?
Veronica...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Dad?
FRIDAY, JUNE 13TH, 1991
08:29 A.M.
Antoñito, what's wrong?
It just leaked out.
It's 8:30?
- Come on, run!
- Why's it always Veronica's fault?
- No, no, don't close!
- Please, just a second!
- By the skin of your teeth.
- Thank you.
Thank you!
Becquer's "Legends" started...
...with an introduction
to transport the reader back in time.
A character would warn
the protagonist about a prohibition,
and then, this main character
would cross the allowed limit...
...and suffer
punishment for their infraction.
Alonso and Beatriz
die because of Beatriz's imprudence...
...when she forced Alonso
to go up of the Mount of Spirits...
...on All Saints Day.
In "The Kiss,"
Lope de Ayala attacks...
...his captain for profaning
the statue of Doña Elvira.
In short,
no one escapes the consequences...
...of passing the limit
that divides reality from fantasy.
Please open your copy of "Legends,"
we're going to read
"The Mount of Spirits" together.
So I'll start.
"On the night of the dead,
the pealing of the bells...
...woke me
at who knows what hour;
the monotonous
and eternal tolling...
...brought to mind this tradition..."
- Yes?
- May I go to the bathroom?
Of course.
"Once prodded,
the imagination is a horse run wild ..."
You know when you go inside a house,
and they've just made French toast?
It's easy to tell the smell.
That smell of cinnamon...
Fried bread...
Warm milk.
If you close your eyes,
it's like they're
on a dish in front of you.
You could almost take a bite.
I was
a Language and Lit teacher.
The French toast is a metaphor.
- What grade are you in?
- Ninth.
So you know
what a metaphor is, right?
And you also know
we aren't talking about desserts.
- Do you smoke?
- No.
Good.
They call you Sister Death.
I know.
- That doesn't bother you?
- No.
I like it.
Better than Sister Narcisa, right?
What's in your hand?
How do you know
I'm holding something?
You don't
always need eyes to see.
Can I see?
What you did here
is really dangerous.
I just wanted
to talk to my Dad.
It's not who you want to talk to.
It's who you talk to.
If it isn't my Dad,
then who is it?
- You have siblings, don't you?
- Three of them.
You'll have to protect them.
Protect them from what?
You all stop moving!
Stop moving!
Don't move!
But I'm alone.
No.
You aren't alone.
Someone answered your call.
And now walks with you.
Don't move.
In the name of
our Lord Jesus Christ,
leave this body
that does not belong to you.
In the name of
our Lord Jesus Christ,
leave this body
that does not belong to you.
Recess is over, girl.
Run, run, run.
Maybe you'll get away.
Rosa!
Hi!
Who's that?
Felipe, my cousin's classmate
from trade school.
- What did you want?
- You're mad at me.
Vero,
why would I be mad at you?
You didn't come over yesterday.
I had to go with my Mom,
didn't your sister tell you?
It's because of yesterday, isn't it?
The ouija board is stupid.
You say dumb stuff and move a glass.
You noticed something, too.
Rosa!
- You saw it, too, didn't you?
- Saw what, Vero?
- Since yesterday, I've been seeing...
- Rosa!
We have to go quick,
the store is going to close.
- Are you coming?
- Where?
We're throwing a party because
Rosa's parents are gone this weekend.
Why didn't you tell me?
Dude, she's telling you now.
Besides,
I doubt you can come, right?
You have to babysit
your brother and sisters.
Let's go.
Vero!
- Drop by if you can.
- Come on, we're late!
Lucia,
stop copying my homework!
THE GREAT ENCYCLOPEDIA OF THE OCCULT
This is boring!
It's always the same!
Antoñito, that's enough!
Go play in your room.
Lucia, stop copying your
sister's homework, you won't learn!
-I learn when I copy, too.
- You're such a piece of work.
You're going to do it, anyway.
Why do you care? You're so selfish!
You're always the same!
Then you do it one day
and I'll copy!
We could do rock, paper, scissors
but you do it better.
It's not that I do it better...
You have siblings, don't you?
You'll have to protect them.
VIKING SYMBOLS OF PROTECTION
Representing Madrid,
Lucia Gomez, 19 years old...
...she is a doctor,
lawyer, lifeguard and firefighter.
But there's a secret
nobody knows about Miss Madrid:
she's a robot!
And the robot has super duper
smart artificial intelligence.
Miss Madrid,
soon to be contender for Miss Spain.
What's that?
A thing we made in class.
How ugly!
Take that, Miss Madrid!
Will you win
the crown as Miss Spain?
Yes or no!
Soon in theaters near you.
Miss Madrid is 25 years old,
has 7 children...
Who is it?
Josefa.
- Where's your Mom?
- At the bar.
Uh-huh.
Wanna tell me what you all are up to?
What's wrong?
The lamps!
Are you dancing or what?
The lamps won't stop shaking!
- We're not doing anything.
- Really?
It looks like my
ceiling is going to crash on me.
Something else:
I've got a huge black stain,
right on top of your bedroom.
You have moisture problems?
- I don't know, I'll tell my Mom later.
- Yeah, right!
If you see her, that is, huh?
You'll sleep well tonight
with all that running around.
Fucking kids.
Shit!
Veronica.
What are you doing awake?
Lucia, it isn't funny.
I can see your room from here.
Help us.
You're the one who called.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Don't let it hurt us.
Irene!
Lucia!
Girls, wake up!
Vero! Vero!
What are you doing?
There was someone here
who wanted to hurt you.
There's no one in here!
We can't see it,
but it's here.
Look!
The amulets got burned.
Take your mattresses, let's go.
We're sleeping
together in the living room.
I'm getting Antoñito.
It's Benahavis.
Vero.
Go to sleep.
Why were you choking me?
I wasn't choking you.
I was protecting you.
From who?
From something bad
that came inside the house.
Who came inside the house?
Josefa?
No.
A being from the other side.
An evil being.
A ghost?
A spirit?
Don't be scared.
I'll protect you guys.
Because you're the oldest?
I'm glad you're my big sister.
I'm glad you're my little sister.
I'm not little. I'm in the middle,
because Irene came out after.
That's right.
Go to sleep.
I'll keep watch.
- Sorry, what's going on?
- It's a festival in Benahavis!
Veronica...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Vero, what's wrong?
What's going on?
It's back.
What's this?
- Mommy!
Can you tell me
what's going on here?
- A bad man wanted to kill Lucia.
- Lucia, are you OK?
Someone came in the house?
No, they didn't come inside.
They were already here.
- Vero!
- Nothing happened, Mom.
But was someone
in the house or not?
- No.
- Yes.
- I'm calling the police.
- A spirit.
- What?
- Yeah, a ghost.
I didn't see it, but Vero did.
- Were you watching scary movies again?
- Kind of.
Don't worry, Mom.
Vero protects us from the spirit.
Come on, let's pick
all this up and go to bed.
And you go to your room!
- But, Mom...
- No buts! Go to your room.
What happened?
- Tell me!
- Nothing.
Your sisters are little
and they've got a huge imagination.
Don't give them weird ideas
because then they can't sleep.
How do you know
if they can or can't sleep?
You're never home!
You don't know what goes on here.
So what goes on here?
- He wants to hurt us!
- Who?!
I don't know! I'm the one
who called him with the ouija board.
You played
the ouija board with your sisters?
- No, with Rosa!
- But...
Why are you playing
with such dark things?
I wanted to talk to Dad.
I know you don't care.
You stuffed his pictures in a box
so you don't have to look at him.
Don't say that!
- I just wanted to talk to him!
- That's enough!
You're reading too much of that stuff,
and it's having an effect on you.
It's the truth.
Vero...
I need you to grow up.
I need
to be able to count on you.
Because I'm on my own.
I'm the one on my own.
You're not making it easy.
I'm really tired.
We'll talk more tomorrow.
Nine, eight, seven,
six, five, four,
three, two, one!
- Vero!
- Vero, get up!
- Wake up!
- Come on!
- Get up!
Let's go!
Leave me alone, let me sleep!
- We're hungry!
- Come on!
We've got lots to do!
We're hungry!
- What are you doing?
- We're hungry!
Get out, leave me alone!
- Come on!
- Get up!
Let's play a game.
Give me your arm.
What are you talking about?
What are you doing?
Stop it!
Stop!
Don't!
Mom! Mom!
Help me, Mom!
Mom, help me!
Mom, Mom!
Mom, Mom...
Mom!
Leave me alone!
Mom, help me!
Mom...
Help me, Mom.
- I can't hear you.
- Mom!
I need you to grow up.
Mom...
Mom!
Mom...!
SATURDAY, JUNE 14TH, 1991
10:40 A.M.
- Did you make breakfast?
- Wait for the show to finish.
Always the same,
I'm sick of you guys!
Wait.
Why's this book here?
You don't know how to read!
Dad came to read it to me.
Come again?
- Dad came?
- He's coming back again tonight.
What else did he say?
That he's going
to take me to where he lives.
Antoñito, listen to me.
Listen.
If he comes back,
don't listen to him, OK?
Plug your ears.
How do you
plug your ears?
Great, like that.
And you call me, OK?
Yell my name really loud.
OK?
Kids, let's go!
- Hi, Mom!
- Hey there!
- What are you doing here?
- I need to go to Rosa's house.
- Right now?
- For homework. Can they stay here?
- Yeah. But come back soon!
- OK!
They're right.
You're a crazy old woman.
- Then why are you back?
- You can see the shadows, like me!
Maybe we're both crazy.
I've been trying
to stop seeing them for a long time.
I did this
to myself, you know?
Back then I didn't know
you don't need eyes to see.
I don't know how
to protect myself from them.
Amulets and crosses
don't work, they don't scare them!
Crosses?
God has got nothing to do with it.
Leave Him out of it.
How can I make them go away?
The same way they came in.
They have to go back
through the door you opened.
Bid them farewell.
Then you'll have to destroy it.
- Destroy the ouija board?
- No, the door!
You have to do right
what you did wrong.
What's wrong?
Sister, again?
I don't know how you can
get all the way down here.
What are you
doing here on a Saturday?
Sister was
helping me with a project.
She's in no condition
to help anyone.
This way, Sister.
The answer is in the books.
Look what great advice she gives.
You have to do right
what you did wrong.
Careful, Sister.
"You have to do right
what you did wrong."
"You should never
end a séance without..."
Without what?
"You have to do right
what you did wrong."
"You have to do right...“
"You have to do right
what you did wrong."
"You should never
end a séance without saying goodbye.
Whatever you don't say
goodbye to, stays with you.
If it doesn't work,
try again another time."
"Whatever you don't say
goodbye to, stays with you."
You have to do right
what you did wrong.
"You have to do right
what you did wrong."
The answer is in the books.
"You have to do right
what you did wrong."
"Whatever you don't say
goodbye to, stays with you."
You have to do right
what you did wrong.
"Whatever you don't say
goodbye to, stays with you."
"You have to do right
what you did wrong."
"You should never
end a séance without saying goodbye."
"You have to do right
what you did wrong."
Hi.
You made it.
Rosa,
I know what we have to do.
- Why'd you bring that?
- We have to do it again!
- What?
- We didn't say goodbye!
Whatever you don't say
goodbye to, stays with you.
- What?
- It says so right here.
- Cut the bullshit.
- We have to do it again!
- Put it away!
- Let's go to your room.
Where's Diana?
- Calm down!
- Where's Diana?
- Put it away!
- Diana!
- Let's go to your room. Diana!
- Veronica!
Diana!
Where's Diana,
have you seen her?
- Veronica!
- Diana!
Have you seen Diana?
What are you talking about?
Diana!
Have you seen Diana?
- No.
- Who is Diana?
Diana!
- Diana!
- No, what's your problem?
Diana!
- You haven't seen her?
- Veronica, please.
Diana!
Diana.
Diana, come here.
- What the fuck are you doing?
- Come on, we have to do it.
- Do what?
- The three of us together.
- Let me go, you're crazy!
- Come on, Diana!
- Leave me alone!
- Let go of me!
- Kicking you the hell out!
- Come on, Diana, Rosa!
Rosa! Rosa!
Rosa,
we have to do it again.
- You don't remember, do you?
- Remember what?
You whispered
something to me the other day.
What did I say?
Tell me, Rosa!
You said
you were going to die today.
- What?
- Vero, I'm sorry.
- What did you say?
- We were scared, we didn't...
What's that?
Did you bite yourself?
No, Rosa. I didn't.
Come on, let's go.
Rosa!
Mom!
Hey, you're in the way!
Can we go home now?
Wait.
Mom!
Where were you all day?
Take the kids,
they can't stay here forever!
Give me the leftovers for the kids.
Coming!
This is always dirty.
Because you always get it dirty.
Mom!
What?
Mom, close the bar.
Right now,
let's all go somewhere.
What are you talking about?
Mom, it doesn't
come when you're home.
Here we go again...
I'd love to close
and eat with you, but I can't.
- Ana!
- Coming.
Look...
Want to go
to the park tomorrow?
To spend the day, like before.
What do you think?
I'll make sandwiches to eat there.
You want to?
Ana, the leftovers!
You grab them.
Kids, let's go.
Finally!
- Let's go.
- Are we going home?
Let's go, sweetheart.
Veronica!
Goal!
Pedro Riesco scored.
After Ribera's mistake,
the first goal
in the game for the team...
You have to do right
what you did wrong.
- We're going to play a game.
- What game?
We're going to play a game
where you have to do what I say.
This game sucks.
Grab the candles
in the top drawer.
Antoñito,
draw this on the hallway walls.
- OK!
- Great.
I get to draw on the wall.
Mom's going to ground you
until you're at least 40.
Move the furniture.
We need to have space.
SATURDAY, JUNE 14TH, 1991
23:45
VIKING SYMBOLS OF PROTECTION
SYMBOLS OF INVOCATION
Not you.
Just the three of us.
Sit over there.
You guys close your eyes.
Is anyone here with us?
Is there
anyone here with us?
Who's here with us?
Are you here?
Yes.
We're here
to say goodbye to you.
You need to leave this place.
No.
We command you!
Repeat after me, girls.
This isn't your house!
Leave!
"To properly conclude the séance
and bid farewell,
participants should sing
a mantra or a soft song."
- We didn't do that, either.
- What's a mantra?
I don't know.
But it says
a soft song works, too.
Which one?
One all three of us know.
Centella.
Centella gives me time to enjoy...
Centella, Centella.
What is that?
Time to myself, time for life,
Centella gives me time to enjoy...
Centella, Centella.
Girls, keep going.
We can't stop.
Time for life...
Centella gives me time to enjoy...
Centella, Centella.
Time to myself, time for life,
Centella gives me time to enjoy...
Centella,
Centella, time to myself...
Come on,
don't stop!
Centella gives me time to enjoy...
Centella, Centella.
Gross, it stinks.
...time to enjoy, Centella, Centella.
Lucia, don't stop.
Centella gives me time to enjoy...
Centella, Centella.
Keep singing!
Don't stop singing!
Wait here.
Don't leave.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
He's here!
- This is the police.
- Help! Help, please!
Please, calm down
so I can understand you.
- What happened?
- Please, help us! He's inside!
He's inside!
There's someone in the house?
Calm down. We're going to send someone
right away. I need your address.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
8 Gerardo Núñez Street.
Antoñito, stay here!
What are you doing?
Antoñito!
No!
He's in the bathroom!
Antoñito!
Antoñito, Antoñito!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Antoñito!
Girls, stay there!
He's in the bathroom.
Antoñito!
Antoñito?
Are you OK, buddy?
Are you OK?
Let's go.
Girls! Girls!
Girls, where are you?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Irene, where's your sister?
Irene!
Lucia, let's go!
Let's
Run!
Come on, run!
Let's go!
Paco, the cops!
What's going on?
Girls, run!
Faster, come on!
Hurry!
Let's go!
Run, girls, run!
Open the door.
- Vero!
Where's Antoñito?
SUNDAY, JUNE 15TH, 1991
01:50 A.M.
Mom! Mom! Mom!
What happened? What happened?
Where's Antoñito,
where's Vero?
Where's Vero?
Antoñito!
Antoñito?
Antoñito.
Vero. Vero. Vero.
- Vero, Vero...
- Antoñito, come on.
- Vero, Vero, Vero...
- Antoñito, let's go.
- Antoñito, it's me.
No, no, no, no.
If he comes back,
don't listen to him, OK?
Plug your ears.
And you call me, OK?
Yell my name really loud.
Vero, Vero, Vero...
You have siblings, don't you?
You'll have to protect them.
Don't worry, Mom.
Vero protects us from the spirit.
You're reading too much of that stuff,
and it's having an effect on you.
Vero! Vero!
What are you doing?
We can't see it,
but it's here.
Why were you choking me?
I wasn't choking you.
I was protecting you.
- Did you touch the faucet?
- I didn't do anything.
Antoñito!
I'm sorry I put the water on so hot.
Did you move it?
Did you bite yourself?
It wasn't you.
Someone answered your call.
And now walks with you.
If it isn't my Dad,
then who is it?
It's me.
Vero, Vero...
Buddy, come here. It's OK.
Come with me. That's it.
- Where's Vero?
- Vero? She's fine.
Pellicer, send the medics up.
I repeat, send the medics up.
Vero! Vero!
Veronica.
Sweetie...
Detective.
Go ahead.
The girl just died.
SUNDAY, JUNE 15TH, 1991
02:00 A.M.
JUNE 15TH, 1,991,
DETECTIVE JOSÉ RAMÓN ROMERO...
...WENT TO THE HOME
ON CALLE GERARDO NUÑEZ NUMBER 8,
IN RESPONSE to
AN EMERGENCY CALL.
IN THEIR STATEMENT,
FAMILY MEMBERS DECLARED...
...THAT AFTER A SÉANCE
WITH THE OUIJA BOARD,
THE GIRL HAD SEVERAL
STRANGE SYMPTOMS...
...AND PARANORMAL EVENTS
TOOK PLACE AT THE HOME.
TWO OF THE INSPECTING AGENTS
SUDDENLY HAD TO LEAVE THE BUILDING,
DUE TO NAUSEA, DIZZINESS AND SHAKING.
THEY REMAINED 2 WEEKS OFF THE FORCE.
ONE MONTH AFTER THE EVENTS,
ROMERO REQUESTED A TRANSFER.
IN THE INSPECTOR'S REPORT,
ROMERO SPEAKS OF PHENOMENA...
...THAT IS "LITERALLY INEXPLICABLE,"
THE FIRST POLICE REPORT IN SPAIN...
...WHERE AN OFFICER CERTIFIES
HAVING WITNESSED PARANORMAL ACTIVITY.