(videotape rattles )
(videotape being loaded )
(VCR whirring )
( static buzzing )
( cameraman breathing heavily )
( soft conversation )
- ( heavy breathing continues )
- ( girl laughs)
- Hey! ( speaking Spanish )
- ( cameraman whispering ) Shh shh shh!
No. No no no.
Just be quiet.
- Cameraman: Oh shit!
- Aw, man, fucking...
Shit. Shit. Shit.
- Shit.
- Man: Hey! Hey!
- Get the fuck back here!
- ( car door opens )
- Hey, give me that fucking camera!
- ( car starts )
-( bangs )
- ( tires screech )
Cameraman: Yeah, so you're
watching that footage I sent?
Man:
Yeah, I fucking saw it. You--
Cameraman: So as you probably guessed,
your wife hired me to get that.
My problem is if I show it to her,
she stops paying me.
So I was thinking you might want
to make a counter-offer there.
Oh, and whatever number
you come up with,
you can put 300 bucks on top
for the dent you put in my car.
-( Indistinct shouting )
- Well, you scratched the paint anyway.
You know what? If I don't hear from you
by tomorrow, your wife gets that file.
- Goodbye.
- ( phone beeps )
- So what's the deal now?
- Ah, probably nothing.
Just this woman thinks
her son is missing.
He hasn't been to class in a week.
He won't answer her calls.
He's probably passed out
in a pile of beer cans.
In which case we're gonna
take the kid on a road trip
and rack up some expenses, 'cause we're
getting 1,000 bucks a day on this one.
Turn left up here.
- Woman: Your button cam's working?
- Yeah, it's working.
Woman:
This is it?
Yeah.
Woman: It doesn't look like
anyone's home.
She couldn't give you a key?
She doesn't have one.
She said the lock
on the back window's busted,
so maybe we can get in that way.
- Woman: And the cops haven't been here?
- No, the cops don't give a shit
about some college kid
who's missing for a couple of days.
( Distant barking )
Man: Here.
- ( Metal clanks )
-( unzips )
- ( distant bang )
- Woman: ls there someone in there?
- ( Crowbar clanks )
- Here. Come on, give me the cam.
There's nothing there. See?
Woman: It sure as fuck
sounded like there's something in there.
Man:
It's an old house.
Besides, if there is somebody in there,
I'm gonna want to talk to 'em.
(whispers )
Here.
( Low rumbling, creaking )
Ow.
- Man: You all right?
- Ow.
Just great. Ow.
Man:
You okay?
( Static buzzing )
Woman: Huh.
- Man: Um...
- What?
You know what? Stay in here, okay?
I'm gonna go check
the rest of this apartment and make sure
no one else is in here, okay?
- You got your gun?
- Yeah.
All right, good.
Just-- just, um, pull anything
relevant onto the drive.
Okay? And record everything.
That was part of the deal.
She likes me to do that.
Well, you took my camera.
Man:
Oh. Then...
All right, so I'll be right back.
Just, um--
just-- I don't know,
see what's on that computer, okay?
If it's encrypted, we can take it home.
If not, just pull what you can.
Got it.
( Water dripping )
( rustling )
- Man on recording: Show her tits!
- ( woman crying )
( door creaks )
( man on computer sighs )
I found a new one.
It's third or fourth generation
from the quality.
L-- I got it from some guy
down in Little Armenia
with a pawn shop.
He is definitely not the type
of guy you usually see
on here trading with us,
but I think he's somebody
who's worth checking in on again.
(thrumming )
(thuds)
( hissing )
Okay.
That's fucking weird.
Man on computer:
Most of his collection, I would say,
was snuff and CP, but he had
at least one that was the real thing.
I don't even think
he knew what it was.
' Anyway...
- ( clicks )
( floor creaks )
( static, electronic humming )
(video game beeping )
-( beeping )
- ( distorted voices )
A little bit of redness,
some irritation, but it looks okay.
- How's it working?
- Guy: It's good.
Um, yeah, I can see,
but what about my other eye?
- Follow.
- Okay.
(whirring )
You can't see anything
out of your biological eye?
- No.
- Okay.
How about now?
Yeah. I mean, it's a little better.
It's just kind of blurry and shadowy.
Yeah. All right.
Well, because your prosthesis is
attached directly to your visual cortex,
your real eye's essentially
battling with your camera eye
to give you input right now.
So when your brain gets used
to having that chip in there,
you should start to see more and more
out of your uninjured eye again.
Until then
you might see some glitches.
What do you mean by glitches?
Well, this is just being tested now.
Eye injuries like yours are quite rare.
So that's why we've installed
a recording chip
into the eye itself so we can
test the data that it's receiving.
Guy:
Right. Yeah, about that.
- Yes?
- Oh my God.
So if I want private time,
what do I do?
- How do I turn this off?
- Uh, well, you can't.
But that's just for this trial period.
I mean, you can't expect
the KPG Corporation
to just give you this implant
and not expect to test its data.
( Guy sighs )
Of course not.
So you guys are gonna sit around
and watch me take shits?
I'd say that's a fair compromise,
Mr. Middleton.
You can read a newspaper during,
or something.
- Mm-hmm.
- So make an appointment for next week.
We'll see how it's working.
Call me if you have any concerns.
All right.
Thank you.
( Man speaking on P.A. )
Middleton:
What the hell?
All right.
( Pop music playing
on car radio )
J' Fever, fever, fever... J'
- Middleton: All right, man.
- All right.
- Sure you gonna be okay, bud?
- Yeah, dude, I'm good. I'm good.
All right, give me a shout
if you need anything.
Guy:
See ya.
(keys jingle)
( lock clicks )
( sighs )
( exhales )
(video game music playing )
( teakettle whistling )
( game beeps )
( sighs )
(grunts)
( whistle fades )
( humming )
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What the fuck?
Where'd I put that controller?
_ Qh--
- ( loud crash )
( sighs )
All righty, then.
What the...?
Okay.
( Clicks )
What the fuck?
- Hello?
- ( static )
Hello?
Oh, come on.
What the fuck is this shit?
( Clicks )
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Oh shit.
-( Loud bang )
- Jesus!Fuck!
( Panting )
Oh shit.
Yeah. Yeah, I can tell
the difference
between a burst of light
and a fucking bloody person, okay?
I don't know, you tell me.
You're the doctor.
Look, I'm coming in there tomorrow
and you're gonna fix this fucking thing
and that's that, okay?
( Sighs )
Fine.
All right, thank you.
' ( Beeps )
- ( Sighs )
( sighs heavily )
Fuck.
( Low rumbling )
( scrape, clatters )
Hello?
Is somebody down there?
Seriously, don't fuck with me.
(whispers )
Oh, God damn it.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
- Hello?
- ( creaking )
- Shit!
- ( thuds)
( panting )
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Oh fuck.
- ( bangs )
Who the fuck?
- ( Rapid heartbeat)
- Shit.
( Rattles )
( deep breathing )
' ( bang on door)
' ( whimpers )
- Uh uh, hello?
- ( bangs)
Shit! Uh, okay!
I'm good.
- Thank you, you can go.
- ( bangs )
Oh shit!
Oh fuck!
- ( Hyperventilating )
- ( heartbeat slowing )
Oh my God.
- ( Birds chirping)
- ( moans)
(whispers )
Oh, God damn it.
( Gasps. deep sigh )
( exhales )
( distant sprinkler running )
( groans )
( sighs )
( doorbell chiming distortedly )
( mutters ) Oh shit.
( Groans )
Oh shit.
(grunts)
( whispers ) What the...?
Hey, are you in there?
Look, I can see you
through the peephole.
Middleton: Weren't you
at the doctor's office yesterday?
Yeah.
Okay, so what's the deal?
Are you following me?
I'm not following you. I--
look, just open the door.
Middleton: All right, listen,
I don't mean to be rude,
- but it's kind of weird, you know?
- Look, are you seeing weird stuff?
Like people who look dead?
You should really open the door.
( Sighs )
Thank you.
I'm Clarissa.
Middleton:
Yeah, come on in.
- Clarissa: Nice place, man.
- Thanks.
Clarissa:
Do you have any beer?
Middleton: I do. Yes.
What about painkillers?
Did the doctor give you any?
No, I'm not actually in any pain.
I'll just take a beer then.
Look, Clarissa,
I'm actually on my way out of here.
Dude, you're not gonna get anywhere
if you don't hear what I have to say.
Just give me a beer,
get one for yourself.
You're gonna need it.
( Middleton sighs ) Right.
( Electronic hum )
- ( hisses )
- ( cap clattering )
- Thanks.
- Sure.
I was born deaf.
When I was 16
my parents put me up
for a new cochlear implant.
It worked, obviously.
But I began to be able to pick up
certain frequencies in my environments.
What happened
to your eye anyway?
(sighs)
I was in a, um--
in a car accident.
So who's the little girl?
Middleton:
What little girl?
There's a little girl here.
I heard her crying when I came in.
But you know...
I don't hear her now.
Some people never
hear them or see them--
maybe once in their entire lives,
if they're open to it.
So...
when you can sense them,
they know.
They can tell.
That's why I wanted to find you...
to warn you.
Middleton:
Warn me about what?
Yeah.
The more you interact with them,
the more they can
touch you,
hurt you,
stuff.
Middleton: Well, tomorrow
I'm gonna get this fuckin' thing
taken out of my head
and that'll be that, right?
Don't be so sure.
Have you ever done
anything bad to anybody?
Look, if you get
the implant taken out,
they're still gonna be there.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
You're just not gonna
be able to see 'em.
I don't know,
maybe that's better.
Well, I guess-- oh shit!
Um, I don't want
to alarm you right now,
but there's a fucking creepy dude
standing right behind you.
I know. I can hear him.
- Do you know him or something?
- He was my uncle.
Oh, of course, right.
I mean--
well, I didn't mean to call him
creepy, but I mean--
- He wasn't a nice person.
- ( dance music playing )
Okay.
- Jesus.
- I know how to make him go away.
- Just focus on me.
- Okay.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Oh!
Holy shit.
( Chuckles )
No, don't look at him.
Look at me.
- ( Kissing )
- ( music continuing)
( music stops )
Oh.
Oh shit.
All right, you scientist assholes,
I want a copy of that footage.
Like, I want you to put it
on a disc or something,
but don't watch it.
Just get it to me, okay?
All right.
Oh fuck.
Oh, God damn it.
Clarissa?
Is that you?
H6)!-
(whispers )
Oh shit!
( Panting )
H6)!-
Oh God.
Oh shit.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
( Shrieking )
- Clarissa: Ow!
- What the fuck?
- ( Clarissa screaming )
-( roaring )
( gasping )
Clarissa, give me your hands!
( Shouts ) Fuck.
- ( Shouts )
- C'mere.
' L 9011 you.
' ( roaring )
- ( muffled screaming )
- Give me your hand.
( Gasps for air)
( gasping )
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
( distorted moan from pool )
' ( bangs )
' ( yelps )
( distorted moaning )
- ( electronic humming )
- Oh fuck!
( Roaring )
(whimpers )
( panting )
Oh oh oh oh.
All right.
You're coming out of here,
you fucker.
Eww...
oh, I can't look at this shit.
Oh God.
( panting )
Okay.
- ( Squelching )
- ( pained grunts )
(clinks)
- ( gasps )
- ( electronic whistles )
(moaning )
( deep growling )
( electronic beeping )
(yells )
( crashing )
Oh shit!
( Screaming )
( electronic noise )
( electronic hum )
( static buzzing )
( Clicks )
( tape ejects )
Larry?
Larry!
Larry:
Hey, keep your voice down. What?
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
I just watched something
really weird.
It couldn't have been reals.
Okay.
Is there anything on that computer?
I'm cloning his hard drive now.
It shouldn't take too long.
Here, look at this.
Tape is the final link for me.
Um, I know a lot of you
have posted that
it only affects you if you play it
in a correct sequence.
But I've been experimenting on--
( lowers volume )
- Is this the kid?
- Yeah, that's him.
I found some notebooks in his room,
kind of like journals.
Mostly just nonsense though.
I'm going through them right now.
Why don't you, like,
keep looking at these tapes?
The kid's a collector.
I don't know. Who knows?
Maybe there's something
relevant on them.
Oh.
Um... okay.
Man on computer:
We're all just electromagnetic energy.
If these analog tapes capture
the images of the supernatural,
they can affect our cerebral cortex.
They-- they--
- ( clicks )
- ( static continues )
( electronic hum )
- ( beeps )
- ( birds chirping)
( beeps )
(cellphone chiming )
Guy:
Hey, babe.
Amy:
Don't "Hey, babe" me, Mike Sullivan.
- We're supposed to be having breakfast.
- Mike: Yeah, but it's a beautiful day.
I just want to take the bike
out for a spin.
Amy:
I wanted you to take me for a spin.
You know, you ride that bike
more than you ride me.
Mike: Yeah, but you know the bike
is just a physical thing, babe.
(Amy chuckles )
Mm-hmm.
Now tell me you love me.
- I love you.
- ( woman chuckles )
Okay, good enough.
- Be safe, babe.
- All right, bye.
( Techno music playing in headphones )
( bike rattling )
Help! Help me! Please!
- Are you okay?
' MY boyfriend!
- You have to help my boyfriend!
- ( Mike mumbles)
- ( veins )
- I'm getting help.
No, please! Help Dan!
- Mike: Oh God!
- ( woman retching )
Mike: Hey.
Hey hey hey, stay with me.
- ( Retching )
- Mike: Shit!
Fuck! God.
( Faint growl )
- ( faint growling)
- Who's there?
The police are right behind me,
so you'd better run!
I got a big fucking stick!
(growling, moaning)
What the fuck?
Oh.
( panting )
Hey hey, come on, we've got to go!
- ( Roars )
- Whoa, aah!
- ( Screaming )
- ( chomping )
Ow, get off!
( Hisses, gr0al1iﬂ9 )
( distorted gibberish )
Die, you fucking bitch!
You fucking bitch!
(groaning )
(growling )
( panting )
(growling, grunting)
Oh God.
Okay okay Okay"-
( muttering )
( zombies growling )
(grunts)
Help. Help!
(coughing )
(grunting, coughing)
( retching )
( coughs, chokes )
(grunting )
(wheezing )
( breathing slows )
( exhales )
( silence )
Woman: Honey, are you sure
you know where you're going?
- This does not look like a trail.
- Man: Of course I know where I'm going.
- Just trust me.
- Woman: How can you tell?
- Man: Well, it used to be a trail.
- There's no trail here.
Man: This doesn't look
familiar to you at all?
Woman:
No, not whatsoever.
I mean it's pretty,
I'll give you that much.
Man:
Holy shit.
Woman:
Oh my God.
Is he...?
I think so.
It looks like
he's been bit by something.
Yeah.
Will you check his pulse,
just to be sure?
Nothing.
My God, I mean,
what could have done this?
Man:
I don't know.
An animal?
Oh, um, yes, hello.
We found someone.
He's, like, covered in blood
and there's no pulse.
We're on the bike trails and--
I mean, it looks like he's been
bit by something.
- It's a bite, right?
- That would be my guess.
Um, what state park is this?
I don't remember.
- This is Gold Stone State Park.
- Yeah, we're at Gold Stone State Park.
Um, but I'm not sure exactly
where we are here.
It's the--
the trail off of Highway One.
Yeah, on the trails
off of Highway One.
- Okay.
- They're sending somebody?
They're gonna send--
connect us with a park ranger.
Okay.
Holy shit.
- God.
- ( Mike wheezes )
- Wait a minute.
- Honey, what are you doing?
I think I heard a noise.
- What kind of noise?
- I don't know.
- It's like he said something.
- ( Mike moans)
Hey. Hey. Hey hey.
- ( Chomping )
- Hey! Hey hey! Let go!
- ( Growling )
- Get off me! Get off me, man!
- ( Crunching)
- ( screaming )
Woman: Get off of him!
Stop it! Stop it!
No!
- Get off, get off! Stop it!
-( blood squelches )
( shrieks )
Oh my God!
( Mike slavering )
(wheezing )
( panting )
( licks)
Mmm.
( Chomping )
( spits, gagging )
- ( grunting )
- ( man moaning )
( Mike panting )
(wheezing )
- ( chomping)
- ( groaning )
( gnawing wallet )
(gags)
( Spits )
Mmmm.
( Chomping )
(wheezing )
- ( chomping )
- ( Mike exclaims )
( chomping )
( man wheezing )
( moans )
( hissing, moaning )
( distant cheering, applause )
( moans )
(Mike grunting)
- ( cheers and applause )
- Yay!
Man:
Happy birthday!
Happy birthday, Bianca.
All right, honey.
( All screaming )
Man:
Go! Go!
- ( Hisses )
- Hey!
- ( Sizzles )
- ( veins )
(growling )
- ( Mike roars)
- ( yells)
Get in the car. Get in the car.
Let's go. Hurry hurry hurry.
Faster faster faster.
Hurry up- Hun')! UP-
Hurry hurry.
- Get in. Get in. Get in.
- ( loud growls )
( children screaming )
Come on, dude, do it.
( grunts )
Aah! No no no!
( screaming )
( chomping )
- ( growling )
- Oh shit!
- ( Engine cranks )
- ( growling )
- ( children screaming )
- ( tapping )
- ( engine cranking )
- ( low moaning )
( screaming fades )
( shotgun cocks )
( roars )
( growling, chomping )
( engine sputters )
( engine starts, revs )
(woman sobbing )
( teddy bear moans )
- ( moans )
- ( sobbing continues )
Amy on phone: Mike?
Mike? Mi-ike?
Hello?
Mike?
Mike, Mike, Mike.
Are you okay?
( Sighs )
You butt-dialed me, goofball.
Oh well, I love you, baby.
Can't wait for you
to get home. Bye.
(Mike whimpering)
( chomping )
( Mike gags, whimpering )
(gunshot)
( static, electronic hum )
( clatters )
Larry:
Hey, how's it going in here?
( Static buzzing )
Larry: Hey-
( static increases )
( both gasp)
sorfY-
I must've fallen asleep.
Oh my God.
Your nose is bleeding.
Don't tilt your head back.
It'll just go down your throat.
This one of your migraines?
Mmm. Mm-hmm.
Are your pills in your purse?
Yeah.
They're not in here. Could you have
left them at your apartment?
I don't-- maybe. I don't know. I--
All right, so what do you want me to do?
We passed a drugstore on the way here.
I could go back,
get you some aspirin or something.
Ayesha: Yeah.
I don't feel like moving.
All right, well,
I feel kind of weird leaving you--
Just go.
Okay. I'll be right back.
( Static buzzing )
( creaking )
( static increases, stops )
( electronic hum )
( man breaking up )
Malik, I'm getting audio, but no visual.
- Malik: You check the connection?
- Man: Wait wait.
Malik:
Okay, how about now?
Man:
That's, um--
okay, we're good.
- Malik: We're good?
- We're good.
Malik:
All right.
Let me see.
All right, perfect.
Now switch to Lena-cam.
Man:
All right.
Lena:
Do you see me, gents?
Crystal clear.
Adam, can you tell?
Adam:
No. From here, not a thing.
But if I zoom in...
- Man: The top button, Adam.
- Malik: Well?
Adam: Let's just say
you really have to be looking for it.
( Malik, in Indonesian )
Excuse me if I'm wrong but, paradise?
Yes, that's correct,
our paradise.
This, all you see before you,
is temporary.
There is a higher order,
another plane of existence.
My family and I, all of my disciples
we're getting closer and closer
to crossing over to the promised gates.
You mean in a spiritual sense,
metaphorically speaking--
No, not a metaphor!
It's as literal as it gets.
It's here in this world.
It has already begun.
We're on the precipice of...
We're on the verge of...
Do you have to be so close?
Just doing my job here.
Malik:
We'd love to discuss this further,
but in a more suitable location.
I was wondering
if we could come and visit
your family at the commune
and continue this interview...
No, I'm sorry.
I do not allow nonbelievers
to enter Paradise Gates.
Experience has taught us
that in your eyes we are seen
as nothing more
than a carnival freakshow.
- I understand, sir, but...
- Lena: Malik.
Excuse me, sir, but that's why
we want your approval.
We want to show
an unbiased view of your family.
No editorial slant,
just a platform for you
to show our viewers
the truth behind the ideology
at Paradise Gates.
What do you say?
(tone)
( electronic hum )
( children singing in Indonesian )
( clicking )
(man, in English)
Yo, Adam.
- Would you pass me the spy cam?
- Where?
In my bag.
In the front.
- Sure.
- Thanks, man.
( Camera beeps )
- Here, heads up.
- Whoa!
You're a fucking dick,
you know that?
Okay, guys'
( speaking Indonesian )
Madame, my name is Malik.
- This is my crew.
- Hi, I'm Lena. I'm the producer.
- Hello.
- It was quite a journey.
Yes, we found being
too close to the city
was a little dangerous for Father.
- It's safer for us out here.
- I see...
We can't let any harm come to Father.
He's our sole shepherd
on ourjourney to immortality.
- You've got a large compound here.
- Yes, out of necessity.
- Hi, what's your name?
- This is Lydia.
Hi, Lydia. Oh.
Thank you.
Did the other little girls help you?
I'm not a girl anymore.
Father took care of--
Enough, Lydia.
Tend to your sisters now.
Please follow me.
( In English )
Yeah, all right.
Adam:
Oh, wait. Wait wait wait wait.
Wait.
Hey, Lena, you want
to upsize that thing?
No, this is creepy, man.
I don't want to wear this.
Hey, Joni.
This belongs to you, man.
Malik:
Hey, Joni, Adam, come here.
Adam:
Coming coming coming.
( Rope smacking )
(woman speaks Indonesian )
How many children are in the commune?
Twenty in total.
How about Father?
Does he have any children?
- We are all Father's children here.
- ( man speaking Indonesian )
- Our Father...
- ( clicks )
( speaks English )
Joni, not too bright.
( Speaks Indonesian )
Sorry, madame.
Our almighty Father has a lot
of responsibilities for his family.
Adam.
Woman:
As you spend more time with him
- you'll grow to appreciate our ways.
- ( distant children singing )
Malik: How long have you
had this building?
For some time.
Ah, here are Father's
little chosen ones.
( Children continue singing )
Would it be okay for us to film them?
You can film only what Father allows.
(Joni, in English ) Hey,
we're not the only one filming, guys.
( In Indonesian )
Yes, those. Security purposes.
Please, this way.
Joni: Yeah.
Malik:
Okay, we'll be ready to start soon, sir.
I'd like to start by getting
your perspective,
then we'll move on
to your family and the commune.
Are you all right?
( Hisses )
- I am fine. I am ready.
- Okay.
( Malik whispers in English )
Dude, can you speed things up?
Don't forget his. Go.
(whispers )
Dude, there's blood on the mic.
( In Indonesian ) Sir, are you sure
you're okay to do this interview?
I've waited a long time for this day.
In that case,
we'll start straightaway.
- I'd like to ask...
- ( retches )
Father:
Wait. Are you okay?
I'm fine.
All right, so as I said...
-( Lena retches )
- ...I'd like to begin by asking you...
(whispers in English )
You okay?
( Lena, in Indonesian )
Excuse me, sir, the restroom?
Go downstairs, third door on the left.
- Thank you.
- ( Malik, in English ) Lena, you okay?
Just start without me.
- Are you sure?
- Lena: Yeah.
( Father, in Indonesian )
Come on, let's start.
( In English )
Yeah, um...
Hey, you know what? Sorry.
You want me to go check on Lena?
( Father, in Indonesian )
There's no need.
( In English )
Just to make sure she's fine.
( Father, in Indonesian ) Do not be
worried, Madame will take care of her.
It's okay, sir. Technical issues.
Exactly, sir.
He'll do field control
and leave us to talk.
Well, first I must start
with a somewhat challenging question.
A question that I am sure
is on most people's minds.
Regarding your lifestyle,
specifically the relationship
you have with the children here.
What's your point?
- ( Distorted music playing )
-( Lena sighs ) Okay.
Hey, kids, where's your teacher?
Wow, these are really great.
What's this a painting of?
( Madame clears throat )
Lena: I'm sorry,
I didn't mean to just barge in.
Beautiful, aren't they?
Lena:
Yes, they are.
But not as beautiful
as yours will be.
Lena:
Excuse me?
No, you will bear something
very special indeed.
You are very blessed.
- Wait, don't be scared.
- ( In English ) Hey, Lena.
You okay?
- ( In Indonesian ) Excuse me, madame.
- ( In English ) Lena, what's wrong?
Yo. Hey, Lena.
What happened?
( In Indonesian ) In order to follow
this path you have to remain pure.
I can help maintain that purity.
They bring their wives, their children
so that I may wash away
their impurities.
Wash away their impurities?
They're still children.
You may see it as unnatural,
but we see it as a progression.
I see it as underage children
involved in what many consider
illegal behavior, sir.
I have blessed them.
They will stand by me on the front line,
in the heavenly glow of the gates.
Oh, how long they have waited.
Men in robes may seek
heaven in the skies.
But not me.
I do not need to look upwards.
I simply look ahead.
For paradise is right in front of me
and I hold the key to unlock the gates.
Pull with all my might,
I will open the gates of paradise.
- This world of ours is temporary.
- Um... Malik?
- This is just the beginning.
- Sorry, the battery is almost out.
- ( In English ) Seriously?
- My bad.
- I thought I charged it yesterday.
- Man! Don't worry, I got this.
( Speaking Indonesian )
Sir, please excuse me a moment.
- Father: Where are you going?
- We need a spare battery.
I'll be right back.
( Joni exhales )
- ( thuds)
- ( sighs)
( in English )
Batteries, batteries.
( Unzips)
( indistinct conversation
on video feed )
It's been over a day, Adam.
(Adam speaks )
Listen, I need to know whether it's
going to be me or you telling Malik.
We owe it to him.
Adam:
Are you even sure it's mine?
- Malik and I haven't--
- Haven't what?
It's been a while.
Fuck! He's my fucking--
- he's my fucking best friend.
- And he's my fiancé.
Adam, I am pregnant
and you're the father.
Just cover your fucking camera.
( Lena crying )
Do you think I wanted this to happen?
Adam:
Hey hey, come on, come on.
Listen.
We can go see someone,
fix this,
no one's gonna know.
Lena:
What the fuck?
- Adam: What?
- Fuck you!
I don't need you.
I'll tell Malik myself.
And whether or not I keep this,
and whether or not he walks,
I still don't fucking need you!
What?
You heard me.
Fine.
Decision made.
Fuck me, fuck you, fuck him.
God damn it.
( Lena sobs )
( sobbing continues )
( clock bells chiming )
( in Indonesian ) In your opinion what
do you think about organized religion...
- It's time.
- ( static over P.A. )
Joni: What?
( P.A. echoing )
Brothers and sisters.
My children.
Lovers of my life.
Follow me,
for I have been the compass
of your souls.
Months...
- ( clatters )
- Even years...
Oh, it felt like an eternity.
But now we are approaching
the final steps.
Today, at this very moment,
- we will reach our salvation.
- ( Adam panting )
- ( door squeaks )
- This is it!
- ( Electricity crackles )
- The final key to Paradise is ours.
Father has been waiting for you,
we must go to him directly.
- My wives and my children.
- Take one cup each, my little ones.
- Don't waver from your path.
- Make sure to drink every drop.
Yesterday you were tainted and sullied.
Today you stand as angels of purity.
Don't be afraid, hold firm.
Guide yourself to the promised land.
Take into your hearts
what you're about to do...
Sir?
- Don't fucking interrupt me!
- ( clicks )
- ( Adam panting )
- ( monitor beeping slowly )
( squelching footsteps )
( camera clicks )
( in English )
Oh shit! Jesus!
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
- ( Screaming )
- Oh, fuck fuck fuck!
- Fuck it!
- ( Instruments crash )
( panicked breathing )
( metal banging )
( in Indonesian )
And for my sons and brothers!
Our path is filled
with unholy obstacles,
but as we step closer to him,
boulders shall become
mere pebbles.
I command you!
Vanquish them with me!
( In English )
What the fuck? Sir!
What the--
what the fuck? Sir?
- Wait wait wait, hold on, hold on.
- ( In Indonesian ) You didn't listen!
(in English ) Hold on, man.
Oh no. What? ( screams )
(grunting )
' ( 9a9ging )
- ( growling )
( Humming )
(humming continues)
( Father over P.A., in Indonesian )
It is our time now...
Stand up.
-( P.A. feedback)
- And give your bodies to him.
Lena: What?
- As we approach these final steps.
- Lena: No, you can't do this.
Know that we will soon
bask in his embrace.
( Approaching footsteps )
( Lena whimpers )
( in English ) Fuck.
( In Indonesian )
What the fuck is going on?
Rejoice, child,
the time has cometh.
(in English ) Hey!
- Stop! Stop!
- ( equipment clatters )
Adam:
Oh fuck. Fuck!
( Static )
(woman singing )
Father:
Virgins, angels,
all your desires--
He shall provide.
Until we meet again, my brothers.
Let us say goodbye
as we close this prayer.
Malik:
Lena?
- Lena?
- Amen.
- All: Amen.
- ( guns cock)
( shouts )
(Malik, in English)
No no no no!
- Hey!
-(gunshot)
Fuck, man!
(gun cocks)
( growls, grunts )
(thuds)
Amen.
( Panting )
( pained groan, coughs )
Holy shit!
(sobs)
- ( shouts)
- ( gun clicks)
(grunting )
( man in Indonesian )
Take his arms.
- ( Cocks gun )
- Bring him here.
(thuds)
( drags )
( Adam panting )
( Malik screams )
- ( gunshot)
- Adam: Oh fuck!
- ( Gun cocks)
- Malik: Help me!
- ( Gunshot )
- Adam: Shit!
- Malik: Help me.
- ( gun cocks, fires )
(gun cocks)
(Adam speaking Indonesian )
No, please don't!
Man:
Don't move, sir!
( In English )
Adam, run. Go find her!
( In Indonesian )
Please be patient, sir.
- Adam: No, please!
- I said be patient, sir!
(Malik, in English ) Go!
Adam:
I'm sorry, man.
( Man, in Indonesian )
It has been an honor to meet you, sir.
(gunshot)
- ( thuds)
- ( in English ) Whoa. What...
the fuck?
Oh shit.
( Lena screams )
- ( squealing )
- ( Father singing in Indonesian )
J' The day has come,
He will be here soon... J'
( Adam panting )
(in English ) Fuck!
(woman, in Indonesian ) Wait!
( Lena panting )
Father:
Our time has come!
Everything is ready.
J' The day has come,
awake is the promised one. J'
( Lena screaming )
( doors rumble )
( pipe clangs )
( Lena crying OUT)
( Lena screaming )
( power whirrs down )
( explosion )
( hissing, clicking )
(whispering voices )
( Father, in Indonesian )
You don't need that anymore, son.
It is... fulfilled.
(wheezing, gasping )
- ( voices stop )
- ( pipe clangs )
(Adam, in English ) Fu--
oh fuck! Shit.
- ( Panicked breathing )
-( pipe clangs)
- Lena!
- Adam!
- ( Screams )
- Fuck you, bitch!
(women muttering )
- ( pipe thudding)
- Adam: Bitch!
- ( Women wailing loudly )
-( pipe clatters )
(grunting )
( kicks)
Okay okay.
- Fuck.
- ( Lena crying hysterically )
Okay, Lena, calm down.
I'm here, I'm here.
Come on.
( Screaming )
Get it the fuck out of me!
Get it... out of me!
( Screams )
- ( Lena cries )
- Oh!
( Screaming )
Oh shit.
( Screaming continues )
( screaming stops )
(gurgling )
(growling )
What the--
( panting, snorting )
( roars )
( distant air raid siren )
- Joni!
- ( growls)
- Oh fuck! Joni--
- ( snarling )
Aw fuck, no!
( Kicks)
( panting )
( distorted singing in Indonesian )
- ( guitar twangs)
- Adam: Oh Jesus!
' ( Grabs)
'(grunting )
( hissing )
Get the fuck--
" Q0!
\ ( _
-( roars )
- Oh fuck!
Oh!
- ( Both moaning )
- ( bed squeaking )
What the fuck?
( Demon growls )
- ( siren continues )
- Fuck.
(gun clicking)
- ( all roaring, growling)
- Oh fuck!
- Shit!
- ( hissing )
Oh shit!
- ( Growling )
- No.
No. No no no!
( Panting, sobbing )
- ( demon's roar echoing )
- ( thudding footsteps )
( air raid siren blaring )
Fuck! ( yells )
Oh, fuck.
What the fuck?
- ( Engine starts )
- Come on!
God help me, come on!
Oh shit!
- ( Demon roaring )
- Oh fuck!
Fuck!Fuck!
- ( Demon roaring )
- Fuck!
- ( pounding footsteps )
- ( demon grunts)
- ( crashes )
( chokes )
(coughing )
- ( loud thudding )
- ( rattling )
( moans )
Fuck!
Oh fuck, oh fuck.
Come On, come On, come On,
come On, come On.
Fuck.Fuck.
( Demon growling )
Papa.
( Sobbing laughter)
( distorted scream )
( electronic hum )
( static buzzing )
Hey, baby, so I got you
both aspirin and ibuprofen
because I figured--
Oh no.
Help!
Somebody help me!
Why did you do this?
Oh oh.
( Garage door whirring )
Boy:
Come taste the flesh
of our slaughtered beast,
Earth creature.
Boy #2: Yeah, so we can eat
your body and collect your skin suit.
Boy: Aha! You fell
for our trap, Earth fool.
Boy #2: Now you will be
our delicious murder.
Quick, put him
in my digestive container
so I can feed off of his life juice.
- ( Water sprays )
- What the fuck?
Put that dog down, Rattlebox.
Woman: You keep feeding him
raw hot dogs, he's gonna get sick.
I don't want to be the one pulling
tapeworms out of our dog's behind.
- Oh, Tank.
- Boy #2: Ass worms.
- Are you guys filming this?
- Affirmative.
Good. Then we got it on tape
that you got your chores.
- What about Jenn?
- Woman: No.
She's got an exam to study for
and I want you two
to leave her alone.
You know in 20 minutes
Zack's gonna roll up in here, right?
Guys, look after Tank.
Okay?
Your mother loves you.
- Good job, Tank.
- ( licking )
Good buddy.
- ( Beeps )
- ( heavy metal music playing on radio )
( tires screech )
- Right on time.
- Where's Jenn?
- Boy: She's in her room studying.
- What? I can't hear you.
- Boy: She's in her fucking room.
- I can't fuckin' hear over this radio.
- ( Music stops )
- Boy #2: What the hell?
- You say she was in her room?
- Boy: Yeah.
Oh, perfect.
What the fuck, Gary?
( Beeps )
Boy:
What the hell took you guys so long?
We fuckin' lost our baseball game.
- Boy: 'Cause you guys suck.
- You suck.
So what's up for today?
All:
Oh yeah.
Boy:
We got some shit planned.
My sister and all her friends
are out back. Let's go.
- Let's make it rain!
- Boy #3: Your sister's friend hot?
- Boy: Yes.
-( beeps )
( laughter)
Jenn: Hey, who wants
some of Daddy's beer?
- ( Cheers, shouts )
- Your sister's gonna be so pissed.
Yeah, she's probably gonna
shit out her vag.
Gary:
Gross.
Hey, Randy, are you ready
to get your sister wet?
- ( Iaughter)
- Fuck off, dude. Don't film my dick.
Ready, aim,
- fire!
- Girl: Oh my God!
( Screaming, laughing )
- Jenn: Oh my God!
- Randy: Yeah!
Get drenched!
( laughs )
Assholes!
Seriously, get outta here!
- Go, you fucking twerps!
- Zack: Fuckers!
( Moans )
I'm gonna break your backs,
you little shits!
Randy:
Taste my hot love, lover boy.
Oh fuck!
Fuck!
Son of a bitches! Stop!
-( Iaughter)
- Zack: Get him!
- Fuck you! ( screams )
- Guy: Hilarious!
- See you tomorrow.
- Get the fuck back here!
Get me out
of this fucking cage!
See you later, biatch.
Gary: Whoa!
Come back here, you bitch!
( Door creaks softly )
(whispering )
Holy shit, your sister's hot.
Randy:
Fuck off. So is your mom.
Danny, what are you doing?
Are they actually doing it?
They are, I bet you.
Holy crap, they are doing it.
Let's ruin their fuckin' party.
- Randy: All right, hit it.
- ( loud techno music playing )
- ( whooping, yelling )
- Randy: Yeah!
- Yeah!
- ( screaming )
( shouting )
Get out, Randy!
Get out!
( Boys chanting ) Babies making babies!
Babies making babies!
Oh fuck!
Get out, Randy! Get out!
- Boys: Babies making babies!
- Jenn: Gary!
( Rumbling, static )
- Zack: That's it!
- Randy: Whoa.
- ( Pottery breaking )
- I'm gonna fucking rip your dicks off!
- Jenn: Turn off the light!
- ( shouting )
- Randy: Go go go!
- Zack: Get back here!
( Boys laughing )
- Oh my God, that was so lame.
- Randy: Turn off the light,
- turn off the light. Oh shit.
- ( door bangs)
Zack: I tasted your piss,
now I'm gonna taste your fucking blood!
- ( Eerie moans )
- Gary: Do you guys see that?
Randy:
What the fuck is that?
Gary: I don't know.
It kinda looks like a gravity--
- Zack: Give me that fucking camera!
- ( grunts )
Let him the fuck go,
you piece of shit!
Are you fucking kidding me, Randy?
You want to fight right now?
Oh stop it! Fuck off, Randy!
Why are you such an asshole?
- I didn't have a shirt on!
- Calm down, it's not even a big deal.
- Are you serious?
- You were supposed to be studying,
- not slam hogging.
- Oh, shut it, Gary.
And if I can't fucking erase this film,
I'm gonna fucking smash this camera.
Zack: You're bunch of fucking faggots.
You can suck my dick.
Gary:
I don't want to!
( Jenn whispering )
Put it down, Zack. Put it back.
Zack: This is it. I fucking
got you now, you piece of shit.
- ( Moaning on TV)
- Zack: What the fuck?
- Jenn: What is it? What's he doing?
- ( Zack laughing ) Oh fuck!
- He's fucking spankin' it.
- He's what?
- He's stretching his dick.
- Oh my God.
- Zack: He's jerking off.
- Oh God.
- Zack: This is it.
- That's disgusting.
No, this is it, Jenn. This is it.
This is how we get that fucker back.
Jenn:
Shh. Stay still, Tank.
Is this how they do it?
Yeah yeah,
I think-- I think it's good.
Just-- we got to get in there
before he lubes up that sleeping bag.
(laughs)
So disgusting.
Zack: Come on, it's good.
Let's just do this. Come on.
Jenn: Okay.
Help me get him down.
Jenn:
Go see Randy.
( Moaning on TV continues )
Tank, go, get out of here.
Oh fuck!
Tank, come back!
- ( Iaughter)
- Shh.
Well, if it isn't Randy Handy
the fucking hand job.
Caught you sticky-handed,
you little come-dick.
- "Come-dick"?
- Jenn, you'll ruin my life.
- Please give me the camera.
- Jenn: Yeah right.
I'm putting this all over the Internet.
- What's going on in here?
- Zack: Oh, nothing.
We just caught your friend
milking his dick in here.
You were coming
while we were sleeping?
- Fuck you and fuck you!
- ( blast of noise )
- Randy: Holy shit.
- Jenn: What the heck?
What's going on?
There's someone at your door.
- ( All gasp )
- Zack: What the...?
Where does your dad
keep his gun?
Gary:
In the closet.
Jenn:
Oh my God. Oh my God.
Randy:
Please tell me this is you guys.
- No, it's fucking not, Randy.
- Gary: It's okay. Shh.
Jenn: Yeah, there's people
in front of our house.
They just cut the power.
Highway 103-- 1967.
- Shh.
- Okay, hurry.
Zack:
Stop playing around!
Show your faces before I blow 'em off!
- ( Whooshes, thuds )
- Jenn: Zack!
- ( Boy whispers ) Shh!
- Zack!
Shit!
Give me that strobe light, Gary.
Zack!
Gary:
Oh God. Oh God.
- Danny: I think I want to go home.
- ( distant thuds )
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Did you guys hear that?
- Gary: Yeah, I did.
- Jenn, did you hear that?
- Jenn: Hear what?
( Static blasts )
- ( creatures roaring )
- Jenn: Gary!
( Tank yelps )
- ( squealing)
- ( Jenn screams ) Gary!
Gary:
Help! Hel--
let me out! Hey!
Hey hey!
- ( Water splashes )
- ( screams )
( deep groaning )
- Help! Help me!
- ( muffled screaming )
Jenn, help! Help!
- Jenn, help!
- ( muffled screaming )
- Help, Jenn, help!
- ( squeaking, gurgling)
Help.
- Help help!
' ( Splashes )
- ( kids yelling)
- ( tank whining)
- Jenn: Gary!
- ( loud creaking )
- Randy: Do you see him?
- Jenn: I can't see anything.
- ( Splashing )
- Jenn: Come here, Tank.
Hey, boy. Oh, good boy.
Randy, help me.
Randy:
I think I need to go to the hospital.
Jenn: Listen, you're fine.
Just don't look at it.
- Randy: Okay. Fuck.
- Come on, Tank.
You need to give me Tank.
Come on, dog!
- ( Echoing moans )
- Jenn: Gary!
- Holy shit, Gary!
- ( Tank whines)
Holy shit! Come on.
Come on, bud.
Randy, help me get him
on the dock.
Come on.
Help me.
Come on, Randy.
Help him out.
- You got him?
- Lift his legs.
- ( Randy grunts )
- Pull!
- Jenn: Shit.
- ( Tank whining)
- Jenn: Is he okay?
- I don't know. He's not breathing.
- Shit.
- Jenn: Shit.
Randy:
I don't think he's fucking breathing.
Come on, Gary, wake up.
What do I do?
- Randy: Uh, CPR! CPR!
- Come on. How?
- How? How fucking--
- Um... tilt his head back
- and pump his chest.
- ( explosion in distance )
- Jenn: Come on, bud. Come on, bud.
- Randy: Breathe in his mouth.
- Hurry up!
- ( creatures growling )
- Jenn: Come on, Gary!
- Randy: Oh shit!
- Hurry hurry hurry!
- Jenn: Come on! Come on, bud!
- Randy: Put your mouth on his mouth.
- Come on, Gary! ( blows)
( banging in distance )
- Jesus Christ! Come on, Gary!
- ( aliens roaring )
- ( banging )
- ( horn blaring )
Come on, Gary!
Get up!
Go 9Q!
( Aliens moaning )
Jenn: Run!
Go! Run! Go!
- ( Aliens moaning )
- ( Tank whimpers)
Randy: Come here, boy!
Tank, hurry!
Hurry! Tank!
- Jenn: Come on, Randy!
- Go go go go!
Right behind you.
Okay, Tank. Come here, Tank.
Come here.
Gar!!! are you okay?
Are you okay?
- Talk to me.
- ( Gary coughing)
- What are those things?
- ( Tank panting )
Jenn:
I don't know. I don't know.
- ( Branch snaps )
- Jenn: Shh shh.
( Loud groaning )
(whispers ) Fuck.
(Tank whines)
- ( barks )
- Jenn:Shh!
Oh shit! Get down.
Shit.
Get down. Get down.
Get down.
( Police sirens wailing )
Oh, thank fuck!
The cops are here.
-( Roaring )
- ( screaming )
Randy:
Go go! Shit!
( Sirens wailing )
Randy: We're over here!
We're over here!
( Loud bang )
- Jenn: Help!
- Randy: Where the fuck did they go?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Jenn: Help!
- Randy: What do we do?
Jenn: No!
- Please!
- Randy: What the fuck?
- ( Horn blaring )
- ( static buzzing )
( aliens moaning )
( Tank barking )
- ( Randy yelling )
- ( Tank snarls )
- ( alien roars )
- ( veins )
Gary:
Tank, Tank, Tank.
Buddy, are you okay?
Are you okay?
Everything's gonna be okay, buddy.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Jenn: Randy! Randy?
- ( Tank whimpering )
Randy, please!
- Gary, stay close to--
- ( horn blaring )
( aliens moaning )
( Jenn screaming )
Run! Run!
Run, Gary!
- Come on, Gary. Hurry! Run!
-( running footsteps )
Get in. Get in.
( Door slams )
( banging on door)
Are You okay, Gary?
Are you okay?
- Gary: I'm scared.
- I know.
- It's gonna be okay. ( screams )
-( banging, roaring )
Get up the ladder.
Here, I'll give you Tank.
Take him.
Gary:
Come on, Tank.
( Jenn screaming ) Gary!
Oh my God!
- Jenn!
- ( screaming )
- ( trapdoor slams )
- Jenn: Gary!
( Aliens growling, banging )
( Jenn screaming )
- ( Gary screams )
- ( aliens roaring )
(moaning )
(wood cracking )
(whooshing )
( screaming )
Help! Help!
Tank, don't let go of me!
( Screams )
( Tank yelps )
(whimpering )
(whimpering stops )
( electronic hum )
( static buzzing )
In other words,
I think I'm ready.
I know a lot of you
know my mother
and I just wanted to make sure
that you guys know
that she supports my decision.
Okay, now, it's time for me
to make a tape for myself.
Thanks for watching.
( Soft wheezing )
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Larry: Baby?
( Woman snarls )
( Larry grunting )
What are you doing?
- ( Shrieking )
- Larry: Stop it!
- ( Choking )
- ( bones snap )
( shrieking )
' ( panting )
' ( Static )
( skittering )
(gun cocks)
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
( skittering continues )
- ( shrieks, thuds )
- ( gunshot )
( Kyle raspily breathing )
( Larry gasps, whimpers )
(snaﬂs)
( Larry choking )
( loW growls )
( rock music playing )
(VCR whirring )
(children singing
in Indonesian )
- ( guitar playing music )
- ( singing continues)
( distorted music playing )
( music ends )
( videotape ejects )