VIRAL
Subrip: Pix
...cases were confirmed today,
according to state-run...
...quarantine alert and mobilized
a national epidemic prevention...
...showing signs of
the contagious illness
will receive special
treatment here.
...the Department
of Health has issued
a nationwide quarantine
and mobilized a national
epidemic prevention plan.
With concerns
that chinese authorities
may not be telling
the whole story,
American officials are
tightening screenings
at all points of entry
to the United States.
We'll hear about
the political pressure
around this issue later,
but first, Julia... begins
our coverage from Dallas.
...believed to be caused by
a small, wormlike parasite,
the public is calling
the condition "worm flu."
Symptoms include
increased appetite,
fever, bloody cough and,
in some cases, seizure.
While this is scary,
it's not like the common cold.
Worm flu can only be spread
through the transmission
of blood.
Nevertheless, U.S. officials
are on alert.
President Barack Obama issued
the following address
this morning.
We will continue to closely
monitor the situation.
We're also going to be working
on protocols, to do additional
passenger screening both at the
source and here in the United States.
All of these things
make me confident
that here in the United States,
at least, we...
the chances of an outbreak,
of an epidemic here
are extraordinarily low.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
You creepin'?
-No.
-Do you have food?
-I don't know. Maybe.
-Please?
Yoink!
-Help yourself.
-I cannot stop eating today.
I polished off a whole row of
Double Stuf this morning.
It's ridiculous.
-Hey.
-Hey, Evan.
"Hey, Evan."
-I didn't say it like that.
-Yeah, you did, though.
Seriously, you better step it
up before you lose your, like,
-new girl glow.
-Really? How?
Well, like, show
some boob, like...
-I don't have any boobs.
-You don't.
Maybe's, like, an ass guy.
It's not that big of a deal.
We're gonna be late, come on.
God.
God...
Now, you supposed to be
Little Miss Biology.
Don't tell me you afraid
of a dead frog.
Get him, girl.
God.
It looks like it's throwing up
-from its neck.
-Come on.
Em... do it.
I can't do this.
That is nasty.
You know what helps me
when I'm feeling squeamish?
Gum.
I'll leave it right
there for you.
Thanks.
Gum.
Lucifer?
You and the devil
on a first-name basis?
Unfortunately, yes.
Hey.
Em...
Thanks for getting me
in trouble again.
Calm down.
Em, wait up.
What?
You're the bestest sister
in the world.
If that's the hand that just
touched your vag,
I'm gonna kill you.
It was this one.
Dude!
All right, I'll see you.
-Bye, Emma.
-Hey.
-So you're Stacey's sister.
-Yep.
I'm Emma.
So... I am CJ.
-I've heard about you.
-That's tight.
What happened to your foot?
Yeah.
I broke it.
How'd you break it?
Shark attack.
It looked a little something
like this.
Come over later?
-Yeah, I'll try.
-All right.
Emmalicious, stay vivacious.
Thank you.
Peace out.
Real class act.
Just mixing with the locals.
You should try it sometime.
-Hey! What's his name?
-Evan, why?
-Evan!
-What are you doing?
Be a good neighbor.
Offer him a ride home.
-Don't!
-You want a ride?
-Taking the bus.
-Yeah, 's taking the bus.
It's, like, the last
stop. It's gonna take forever.
We insist. Don't we, Em?
Yeah.
Of course.
Why are you being such a bitch?
'Cause you don't have balls.
I have balls.
-Hey, Dad.
-You guys ready?
-Shotgun.
-Hey.
-No way.
Dad, we're giving Evan
a ride home.
-Hey, honey, you're on speakerphone.
-Hi, kids!
-Hi, Mom!
-Hey, Mom.
When are you coming back?
I have a meeting
in Kansas City tomorrow.
-Hopefully, the day after.
-I thought we were gonna
finish unpacking this week.
Please, Michael,
let's not get
into this right now.
All right. Fine.
I love you.
-Gotta go.
-Bye, Mom.
Bye.
You liking it? Here?
Shadow Canyon?
Yeah, I guess. It's different.
From Berkeley? Yeah, I'll bet.
You know, they say that moving
is supposed to be the third
most stressful life event,
after death and divorce, so...
Hey, Evan...!
-Seriously?
-Girls, stop it.
-She kicked my seat.
-Stop being a jerk.
Well, mind your own business
and maybe I won't have
-to kick you.
-You guys just cut it out, please.
Seriously,
why are you being a jerk?
She's being a jerk.
Just cut it out, all right?
You are!
Just leave me alone!
Stacey...
Hey, Mr. Toomey.
Hey, Stacey.
I'm Stacey; she's Emma.
Shoot.
It's gonna take me
a couple of minutes
to get all that down.
Well, it's easy to remember.
I'm the pretty one.
Mr. Drakeford,
thanks for the ride.
Any time, Ev. Take care, bud.
Bye, Emma.
Bye.
Hey, Evan?
Tell your dad I put
his pliers in the mailbox.
It's not my dad, but okay.
Alan?
I can't find my car keys.
Hey, there.
I better go
before she has a breakdown.
Have a good one.
-All right. Bye-bye.
-Bye.
Good luck.
Stacey...
what did I tell you
about texting at the table?
Do you see me typing?
I see you looking at your phone.
Okay, you want to play
"happy family"?
How are things with Mom going?
You're excused.
Thanks.
You okay?
No, my mom's been, like,
coughing in my face.
That sucks.
All right, you should have it.
Okay, lady in an elevator.
Watch.
This is some chinese shit.
My God. What's doing?
Just coughed blood on her.
Like, I feel like
that's super rude.
Is that real?
Hold on.
What are you doing?
Emma, did you really
just leave me
because I said I feel gross?
Hang on.
Emma!
-Don't be a jerk friend.
-I gotta go.
Emma!
Crap.
Where are you going?
I'll be back in a minute.
Why are you calling me
when I'm three feet away?
Your note said to call you.
-Okay.
-Could we make this quick?
I'm on a really
limited call plan.
Yeah. Sure.
Hello? Emma?
She hung up on me.
What have we got here?
Hey...
Bill, this is Emma.
She lives right here.
We just... we live right here.
It's nice to finally
meet you, Emma.
Likewise.
Now I can see why Evan's got
a little spring in his step.
Okay, Bill.
I'll be in in a minute.
Looks like
I'm getting the boot.
Hey, now don't go breaking
this little baby's heart, okay?
He is... Look at him,
he is sensitive.
-He is a...
-An asshole.
Yeah.
Kind of, yeah.
Good night.
Government officials
do not believe there is a threat
to the United States,
in spite of medical exp...
Good night, Dad.
Night, sweetie.
Can I ask you something?
Yeah.
Is everything okay
with you and Mom?
Things just seem
pretty weird lately.
I'm sorry.
I get laid off,
I go from teaching PhD
candidates to high school kids,
and, no offense, it's just...
I know it hasn't been easy
on you and your sister.
Right?
New school, new friends,
new house.
Things will be fine,
sweetie, okay?
Yeah, I guess.
Come here.
I love you, kiddo.
I love you too.
Good night, sweetie.
Good night.
That does hurt!
Okay, what is it
on a scale?
-What is it on a scale?
-It's just a six.
-Nasty.
-Disgusting.
I'm sorry, guys.
The botfly larva is
a multicellular parasite.
It's fairly easily
removed, as you saw.
And you just cover
that breathing hole
with a piece of tape.
Pokes its head up for some air.
Pull it out.
Ecuador, 1987.
Pulled that little guy
out of my elbow.
Now, I don't know if any of you
are following the news.
If you're not, you should be.
There's something going around
that's making people sick.
Most are now speculating that
it's parasitic, like this guy.
Can anyone tell me
what a parasite is?
Yes, Evan.
It's, an organism
that lives in another organism.
Or on another organism,
like head lice.
Remember when you had
head lice, Emma?
Did just stay that?
I'm sorry.
-No.
-Anyway, look at this.
Parasites, all right?
These guys cannot survive
on their own, okay?
They need a host.
Now, sometimes they live
peacefully inside their hosts,
but sometimes... this is
what fascinates me, guys...
Sometimes they take control,
going so far as to manipulate
their behavior.
Toxoplasma gondii.
This is a parasite that gets
inside of a rat's brain
and makes the rat completely
fearless around cats.
Why?
Because Toxo only reproduces
in a cat's intestines.
So the cat eats the rat,
and the cycle then begins again.
Is it like how zombies
are always biting people
to turn them into more zombies?
Know what? It's kind of.
I mean, the question being...
When does a host stop
being an animal
and simply become a vehicle
Gracie.
For the parasite?
-Are you okay?
-A vehicle, mind you,
with about as much control
as an airplane over a pilot.
This is always for the greater good.
-Are you okay?
It's always in
the name of reproduction,
of-of proliferation.
Now, this parasite that
we're dealing with overseas
is most likely single-cell.
Gracie!
Hey, have you seen a girl?
Gracie?
Gracie...
Gracie.
My God.
Help!
Help me!
What happened?
I don't know.
-What's her name?
-Gracie.
Gracie, hey.
Gracie?
Get help.
Go get the nurse.
You're okay.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Somebody help!
Help!
Over here, straight.
Open your mouth.
Look up. Up.
Great.
And, Emma, do you know
if Gracie has been exposed
to any livestock?
I don't think so.
Do you know
if she's come into contact
with anyone who's
traveled internationally?
Her mom got back from
San Francisco this weekend.
Okay, and did Gracie mention
anything about not feeling well?
Last night, she said
that her throat hurt.
This morning, when I saw her,
she looked pretty sick.
Did she describe
any other symptoms?
Yesterday, she said
she was really hungry,
but I didn't think there was
anything weird about that.
Okay.
Did any of her discharge
enter your nose or mouth?
No.
The health department
has just instructed us
to cancel classes for today.
Now, this is just
a precaution...
No. No, it was one of
the other girls in the class.
-Where is she?
-Hang on.
She's fine.
Honey, she's fine,
I'm telling you.
Mom, I'm fine.
See? She's fine.
What about you?
What's going on?
Nothing?
There's no cabs?
Stacey.
That's sick.
We need one of those.
They're checking all
the cars that are leaving town.
All right, guys, look,
Mom's stuck at the airport.
She can't get a taxi.
I'm gonna go pick her up.
I want the two of you to go
straight home, you got it?
How are we supposed
to get there?
-Hey.
-Hey, Gracie...
Gotcha, you're
talking to a machine.
Leave a message. Bye.
Hey, Gracie,
it-it's me, it's Emma.
Look, I'm really
worried about you, okay?
So please just give me
a call back when you get this.
Bye.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hi, Dad.
Girls, I can't
get back into town.
What?
They've closed
all the roads.
Well, where's Mom?
Is she with you?
No, she's not,
she's still at the airport
because they're not letting
people in the area, okay?
What's going on? Where are you?
I'm at the store
on route 26.
A bunch of us are waiting here.
Girls, listen to me,
this is important.
The whole county's
under quarantine.
What does that mean?
Means we're fucked.
Stacey.
It means that this thing
is serious enough
they don't want anybody
going in or out of town.
Now, I'm gonna head
back to the airport
and try and get your mom, okay?
We'll be back as soon as we can.
-Okay.
-Listen, promise me two things, okay?
Yeah. What?
No fighting
and no boys over.
Yeah.
Say it, promise.
Yes, promise.
Bye, Dad.
Okay, bye. I love you.
I can't order pizza.
The Web site's on crack.
Boy.
We could have
Great Grains cereal
mixed with meat-flavored
pasta sauce.
See, this is what happens
when Mom leaves us.
Mayonnaise could be useful.
Brownies?
For dinner?
Despite,
obviously, the extraordinary
pain and hardship,
of the families
and-and persons
who've been affected,
and despite the fact
that we have
to take this very seriously,
it is important
to remind ourselves
this is not an airborne disease.
This is one
that can be controlled
and contained very effectively,
if we use the right protocols.
What are you doing?
I was watching that.
It was boring and depressing.
Stacey, did you hear that?
Sta...?
Hello?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
-Stacey!
-What?
-Someone's standing at the front door.
-Who?
I don't know!
Come on.
I'm telling you,
I saw someone out there.
Don't just open the door...
Stacey!
See? Nobody there.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
My God!
I think you both just
shit your pants.
How did you even sneak
in here with crutches?
'Cause I'm a ninja
with the hide-a-key.
You know, there is a curfew.
I don't even know what
a curfew is.
-Stacey, Dad said that...
-Says a lot of things.
Hi.
Okay.
That her...?
You want to get some of this,
you got to beat me upstairs.
That's so sad that
you can't walk like a human.
This whole worm flu thing
is worse than the president
and CDC are willing to admit.
Since when does the flu make you
want to attack people?
That doesn't sound
like the flu to me.
And plus, you can't
just quarantine
half the state of California
and not declare martial law.
That's unconstitutional.
Hey, Obama,
you can quarantine my...
What is all this?
Hey, Bill, what's going on?
Stacey!
Boring.
Band-Aid. Boring.
What's this?
That's a flare.
Be careful.
Okay.
My God.
If you come
in contact with someone
"who exhibits symptoms,
please notify the CDC
"or your local authorities
via the Web site listed below,
or contact the CDC hotline."
Are we supposed to wear these?
I think so.
Why are you doing The Robot?
Did you just kill yourself?
I am so Asian right now.
That's not racist at all.
You're so serious.
Lighten up.
It is serious, Stacey.
Look at this stuff.
-Look at this?
-It's a flashlight.
Yeah, but it winds up.
Hey, Mom.
Is that your mom?
No, no, no, we're okay.
-Tell her I say hi.
-Yeah, it's just us.
-Where is she?
-Where are you?
She's still at the airport.
We're fine.
-O-M-G.
-What?
Beef taco filling
in a box in a bag.
What's your IQ?
...are saying,
"Don't worry, trust the CDC."
But, I mean,
patients are going missing.
This is crazy! I...
Infected people, under hospital
care, were are just gone...
This is delicious.
Good.
Try not to eat it all, okay?
It's all we've got.
This is very, very alarming...
Is that my phone?
You left it upstairs.
Why do you look so nice?
There's a party
-in Phase Two tonight.
-You do look nice.
-Thank you.
-We can't leave the house.
We're alone, Emma,
we can do whatever we want.
It's not cool, Stacey.
There's still a curfew.
What's not cool
is doing your homework
in dirty sweats when there's
no school tomorrow.
This is true.
-Cheers.
Well, have fun.
Thanks. You, too.
I will.
What?
My God, what a bitch.
Balls.
I'll see you around.
Hey!
Hi.
Are you wearing makeup?
Yeah, like,
a little bit, it's...
It was Stacey's, I...
Do I look like a hooker?
Yeah, but, like,
a really high-class hooker.
Okay.
Want to dance?
Cool.
You're a bad dancer!
Wha-what's in it?
Tequila.
And what else?
More tequila.
-Hey.
-Okay.
Where's CJ?
I don't know.
Asshole.
See ya!
I'm glad
one of us came prepared.
Shall we?
After you.
-I'm sorry, sorry!
-My God!
What a slut.
...different room?
-Anyone in here?
-Put your penis away.
-Okay.
Too bright.
Not pretty.
Better?
Yeah.
Cool.
Okeydokey.
What are we doing?
We're having a moment.
Why are you whispering?
I don't know. Why are you?
I like you.
What the hell is that?
-Stacey, wait!
-That ho bag!
-I thought that was you...
-Stay the hell away from me
or I take that sweatshirt
and shove it so far up your ass.
-Stacey, Stacey.
-You don't even...
What the hell was that?
-Hey, hey!
-What was what?
-What happened to your bra?
-They're not worth it.
-Delicious...
-Get off of me!
-All right.
-Piece of shit.
-Baby... B-Baby!
Stacey, wait, Stacey.
-I need a drink.
-Stacey, this is so lame.
I really don't think
you should care.
Emma?
My God!
Hey!
Yo, I'm talking to you!
Dude, hello.
Let her go!
I'm talking to you!
Answer me!
I know's a piece of shit,
but for two seconds,
I thought she was
actually my...
's infected!
Stacey!
Not in here. Come on.
-Get out of here! Come on!
-What's going on?
Stacey, what's wrong with him?
Okay.
My God.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Shit.
Is gone?
Stacey!
Stacey?
Did it get in your eyes?
Are you okay?
Okay.
Come on.
Hey, Stace, you okay?
Yeah.
I'll be out in a minute.
Why isn't
anyone talking about the fact
that all these infected attacks
started happening at the exact
same time, all over the world?
It's like the infected
are communicating
on some secret network
that only they can hear.
Now there are reports
of these gatherings of infected,
and these nests
across the country.
What I'd like to know is
what the hell are they up to
and why isn't the government
doing anything...
You had any contact
with an infected person?
No.
Banished are
the sounds of children playing,
as the uninfected cower
in their homes.
Civilian military
stretched too thin.
A crude symbol,
increasingly prevalent,
indicates which homes
have been cleared
and those which still
need to be inspected.
Streets so quiet...
I keep getting his voicemail.
Mom's, too.
...the uninfected
cowering at home.
An innocuous letter... an
uppercase "I"... holds the key
-to the fate
-Hey, are you okay?
Of the families within.
The number on the left
indicates the number
of infected.
The number on the right
indicates the members
of the household
who have been removed.
It's him.
Hey, Dad.
Girls, listen to me
very carefully.
Lock every window
and every door in that house.
Nobody in, nobody out.
Do you understand?
Stacey?
I'm here.
Do you remember where my gun is?
-Yeah.
-I want you to find it
and keep it on you at all times.
Do you understand?
Do you un...
Dad?
There's no reception.
Try him again.
Dad, are you there?
24 hours ago,
military personnel
-Well, try again.
-evacuated the uninfected,
-Dad, hello?
-and just moments ago,
-Are you there?
-Iaunched an air raid,
-Dad?
-obliterating...
-What's going on?
-I don't know.
The land line's out, too.
Power still works.
There's no Wi-Fi.
This is not a test.
This emergency alert
has been issued by
the Center for Disease Control,
in conjunction with the
Department of Public Health.
The president
of the United States
has declared martial law.
All law enforcement
and emergency personnel
will be federalized,
effective immediately...
I know it's somewhere in here.
Can you please help me look?
What? It's a ring.
It's Mom's wedding ring...
that she never takes off.
She probably showered
and forgot to put it back on.
Will you please tell me
what's going on?
-Nothing is going on.
-Stacey, Mom and Dad...
There's nothing to talk about,
so let's drop it.
Fine.
Where did you learn
how to do that?
Dad used to take me
to the range.
Come on, come on.
Hey! Over here!
Sir, stay where you are.
What was that?
I don't know.
Stay back.
Stay right there.
-Get back.
-It's Mrs. Toomey.
Get down on the ground.
Get down on the ground now!
Get down!
Hold it!
Hold it! Hold it!
Turn around! Turn around!
-That's not a question!
-Don't move!
That's not a question!
We have to get out of here.
Evan!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
This is a restricted
quarantine zone.
Turn your vehicle
around immediately.
Stacey, we gotta turn around.
-Stay here.
-Turn around.
-Stacey, what are you doing?
-Ma'am...
-Get back in the car! Stacey!
-Get back in your vehicle, now.
-Sir, we're just trying to see our dad.
-Stop, now!
-Go right there...
-Ma'am, get back in your vehicle!
-Please, sir. We're not infected.
-What part of "get back in your vehicle"
-Please.
-do you not understand?
-Sir, it's just right there.
-Get back in your vehicle now!
-Ma'am! Ma'am, right now!
-Please, we're just
-trying to get right there.
-Right now!
-Stacey!
-Get back in your vehicle now...
Shit.
My God.
...you are required
to stay in your home.
By executive order,
it is now a felony
to harbor an infected
individual.
Please report any suspected
infection immediately.
You are required
to stay in your home.
By executive order,
it is now a felony
to harbor an infected
individual.
Please report any suspected
infection immediately.
You are required
to stay in your homes.
By executive order,
it is now a felony to harbor...
I need to tell you something.
Okay.
What?
Dad cheated on Mom.
Last semester,
when I went to visit him
at work,
I walked in on him
with one of his grad students.
And I freaked out.
So I told Mom
and Mom freaked out.
Well, why didn't
anyone tell me?
They didn't think
that you could handle it.
And they begged me
not to say anything.
That's why we moved out here;
to start over.
Looks like that
didn't go so well.
You should've told me sooner.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know what to do.
And that's why
I've been such a bitch,
I've just been so pissed.
And you could've handled it.
I can handle it, Stacey.
Stacey?
Emma!
Open the door!
-Open the door!
-Emma, don't...
-It's Evan, Stacey!
-You don't know if's infected or not!
Emma, don't...
What's wrong?
-He's infected.
-Who?
I'm gonna get the masks.
Is gone?
Emma... don't.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Get the lights.
It doesn't matter;
can't see anything anymore.
Don't move.
Put your masks on.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
's right out there.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Are you...?
You're okay. You're okay.
It didn't get on you,
it didn't get on you.
You're okay.
Stacey, my God.
Stacey...
Stacey?
Stacey!
Emma!
This isn't gonna work.
What?
No, I won't feed her.
You said it only grew
when ate.
Maybe you can slow it down,
but you can't stop this thing.
It takes over your body, and it
turns you into something else.
Emma!
Look...
you can go, if you want to.
-It's okay.
-Emma!
I'm not gonna leave her.
How are we gonna make sure they
don't check the house again?
What if they thought
we were already gone?
Coordinates. This
is UF-6 entering sector five.
North 47-52-0-6 east...
Looks like there's no one here.
Emma!
Emma, please!
I'm hungry, please!
Yeah, Stace, it's me.
I'm so hungry.
So hungry.
I know you are.
I can feel
it inside of me,
behind my eyes,
telling me to do things.
You've got to fight it, Stace.
You have to leave.
Emma, please leave.
Leave.
No.
You remember,
when we were little,
and I came home
from school crying
because Katie Moore cut off
one of my pigtails?
Remember?
Yeah.
And the next day...
you made her eat her boogers
in front of everyone.
It seemed like an appropriate
punishment at the time.
That-that's what we do.
We protect each other.
'Cause... 'cause Dad's
gonna come home soon.
Okay?
Okay.
Hey. Anything?
How are you holding up?
Haven't seen anybody around
in a while.
I'm never gonna
see my dad again.
My mom.
You don't know that.
Yes, I do.
I have a feeling.
You know...
I lost my mom
a couple years ago.
She had cancer.
I watched her
turn into something
that I didn't even recognize,
you know?
It was like I was the parent
and she was the kid.
And Bill... checked out, so...
it was just me there.
Every day and every night.
And,
sometimes...
I wish I could see her...
Remember her...
More for what she was
instead of what she became.
You know?
I'm so sorry.
I can't leave her.
I know.
She's the only thing
that I have left now.
I can't leave her.
Please don't make me.
-Please.
-I won't.
Hello?
Yo!
Stacey?
Stacey!
The Army split.
A bunch of us
are getting out of town.
Stacey!
Help.
Stacey?
The...
What... what happened?
They're infected.
They locked me in here.
-Why?
-I don't know.
Please help me.
Please, I need you.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
-I'm so scared.
-I'll get you out of here.
Please, please.
Please.
You really hurt me, CJ.
Baby, I know.
I'm sorry. That's why I came.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I'm sorry.
It made me do it.
I can't stop it
from changing me. Please.
Please. Please.
Your sister's keeping me busy.
Emma, this is nuts.
It's a multicellular
parasite, Evan.
That means it can be removed.
Em, trust me,
somebody already tried this.
It won't work.
You're gonna kill her.
She's already dead.
I'm gonna save her.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Thank you.
Take my hand.
No, it's gonna
make me hurt you.
You wouldn't hurt me, Stacey.
Take it.
Em, promise me something.
Anything.
If I don't make it,
you find Dad.
And tell him I'm sorry.
And I love him.
Listen to me.
You are gonna see him.
And you can tell him yourself.
29, sir. Sector 76.
I have a setting
for reference one-zero.
She's asleep.
How much did you give her?
It can't breathe.
God!
No...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Stacey?
Stacey, it's okay.
Listen to me, it's gone.
Stacey?
It's gone.
Hey, it's okay.
It's gone, it's gone.
By order
of the Governor of California,
Shadow Canyon is under
a mandatory evacuation order.
Any remaining residents
must evacuate their homes
and report
to military personnel
-in the next 24 hours...
-They want us to report.
We can't. They'll take her.
...of the
Governor of California,
Shadow Canyon is under
a mandatory evacuation order.
Hey, bitch.
Come on.
All right. Got some
really gross soup for you.
What is this? MRE shit?
It's all we've got. Sorry.
-Looks like piss.
-Yeah, well...
I'm sure it tastes
like it, too.
God,
it looks so much better.
Are you sure it's okay to eat?
Yeah. It's gone.
You guys do it yet?
-What?
-You and Evan?
We've been
a little preoccupied.
No, haven't really had time
to get naked.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I couldn't have done
what you did.
You're my big sister.
Two residences in Sector 14
showing nest activity.
Request permission to go hot.
Emma, come here!
What?
Everything is gone.
Stacey!
Stacey, wait!
-Emma!
-Stacey!
Emma, she's gone!
Stacey?
Please don't go in there.
I can't leave without her.
My God.
God...
Emma. Emma.
No.
Stacey?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Run!
Come on!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
This way!
Come on!
Shit.
Come on. In here.
Shoot him!
Stacey?
Stacey.
I can hear them,
telling me what they want
to do to you.
To everyone.
-I can't make it stop.
-Emma. Emma!
Please make it stop.
I can't.
-Emma, please!
-Emma.
-Stacey, I can't!
-Emma, kill me, please!
I can't hold them.
-Emma, please.
-No!
-Please.
-Emma.
Please, I don't want
to hurt you. Please.
-Emma, I need you to help me.
-Stacey...
Emma!
Stacey.
Stacey, stop...
I can't hold it!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
No.
Not Stacey.
Emma, let's go!
Stand up!
Come on.
Climb out. Climb out!
-Emma...
-I can't...
-She's gone. Come on. Let's go.
-I can't!
Get up! This...
Up, up, up, up.
We gotta go.
Emma!
Jump! Now! Get down here!
Gotta jump. One...
two...
three!
Where is that?
In Washington State.
Let's do it.
Hey.
Thanks.
For what?
Just for being here.
Of course.