http://filocker.com
Free Watch Online & Download Movies
(English & Indonesian Subtitled)
original subtitle by kanga6us
resynced by filocker.com
- David?
- Hey...hey...
Ohh...
Yeah, I know. Shh! Lie still.
We need a doctor!
-David, what happened?
No, no, it's alright.
You were in a car accident.
There was another car.
What happened to the other car?
Oh, David... Oh, David!
Eveleigh? Eveleigh?
Sweetie, you're OK. I'm here.
No, David, it's not OK.
There was a baby
in the other car.
-What happened to it?
-No, no, no...
Yeah, something
really bad happened!
Eveleigh, it wasn't your fault.
Try and go to sleep.
Oh...
Aww.
But you gotta be careful
with the potassium...
Uh-oh. Here she is.
-Hi, sweetheart.
-Hello.
-I'm Emilio.
-Evey.
-Nice to meet you.
-You showing David the ropes?
-Yes, he's a fast learner.
This is like getting
a master's degree in agriculture
in a one-month crash course.
Would you mind looking
over that for me? Thanks.
Come here.
You're like
a mountain man out here.
Thank you.
Eveleigh's Vineyard?
Are you really calling it that?
-You don't like it?
-I love it.
I love it. Thank you.
I know it doesn't
look like much right now,
but in September we'll be
seeing our first harvest.
And you just walked past
an acre of cabernet,
a hillside of pinot gris
and then over here...
Are we crazy for doing this
right now, David?
Come here.
I don't know about you,
but I'm definitely crazy.
Seriously, I think this
is gonna be good for you.
I need you to be happy, Evey.
Well, you're very needy
that way.
There's only one thing
I want you to be thinking about
and that's having us
a healthy baby.
Ahh...
Victor. Hors d'oeuvre?
Oh, no, no, no.
I'm going to make a toast first.
Here. Here.
Thank you.
I'd like to make a toast.
When I first heard that
there was a young couple
from Los Angeles, no less,
who were thinking about
reopening the winery,
I have to admit
that my first thought
was, "You have
got to be kidding."
But now that I've met David
and his lovely wife...
-Evey.
..I am struck by their passion
and their dedication
and these are good
qualities to have
because as we all know
this valley has
a bit of a reputation.
It's a hard place - crops that
fail and rains that never come.
But the vines that
do survive are stronger
because they seem
to thrive on this adversity.
It gives them character, just
like those of us who live here.
Now, the wine you're drinking
is a Folgore '89.
And I'm not talking about 1989.
That's 1889.
It's one of the first wines
that was made in this valley
and it was made right here.
I thought we'd have it tonight
in honour of this young couple
and to welcome them
to our very special club.
- Salud.
-Thank you.
-Salud.
Hey. Thank you for coming.
-I know it's a superlong drive.
-Long? It was an eternity!
But look at all
the eligible bachelors
you get to meet tonight.
You know how much
I love a man in overalls.
He's actually not wearing
anything underneath those.
Oh, please help me
suck up to these wine people.
I feel like I'm doing
a terrible job.
You mean like that old guy
who gave us the old wine?
That is Victor Napoli.
He's kind of like
the godfather of this region,
so we're very lucky he's here.
Hey, what's going on?
Helena Knoll!
-Hi.
No more wine
unless you're Uber'ing it.
I can't believe she came.
Who is it? Who is it?
Helena Knoll,
top distributor in the valley.
Basically, if we get our debut
wine on her list, we're in.
Very nice to see you. Goodnight.
Mmm, goodnight.
-Bacon date?
-I beg your pardon?
They're bacon dates.
They're quite delicious.
-I know they look weird.
-Hmph, yeah.
-You must be Eveleigh.
-Yes. Hi.
-Helena.
-Thank you for coming, Helena.
-You're welcome.
-Nice to meet you.
You know what?
Let's go sit down.
I want to get
a good look at you.
OK.
So did you know the Porters,
the family that
lived here before?
Oh, no. I know of them.
They left before we...
They were in
way over their heads.
Yeah, well, David's wanted
to do this his whole life,
ever since I've known him, so...
It must be a very exciting time
for you and your husband,
what with a baby on the way.
Where are your facilities?
Facilities?
Yes, the restroom, darling,
unless you want me
to go au naturel.
Just right back there.
Stay strong for the baby...
Helena, are you OK?
It's just
us mommies now.
It's just us mommies now.
Ohh! Don't touch me!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Are you OK?
Of...of course I am.
Jesus, of course I am.
What was that?
Honestly, it was like
she was possessed.
I've never seen
anything like it.
It was terrifying.
Well, chalk it up to another
mystery of the valley, I guess.
-I'm serious, honey.
-I am too.
If there was one person I wanted
to impress tonight, it was her.
Was she drunk or something?
No, I don't think so.
And she knew I was pregnant.
I mean, how does she know that?
It's not like
we're Facebook friends.
That is weird.
I didn't tell anybody.
I mean, am I showing?
You want me to take a look?
-Oh, you'd love that.
-What? Uhh!
OK, the claw will take the look.
I made the bacon dates tonight.
I've done my fair share.
- I'll show you bacon dates.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
Oh...
Arggh! Oh!
--What is it?
Oh, it's nothing.
Ohh...
Mmm...
- Shit!
Looks like everything
in here is going fine.
So exciting.
How are you feeling otherwise?
You have any pain
around your temples?
Oh, I'm good.
I mean, I'm still
having nightmares
and I'm still afraid to drive,
but other than that I'm fine.
That doesn't sound fine
to me, Evey.
Have you been in contact
with your psychiatrist
since you got off the meds?
You may be still be suffering
from lingering PTSD symptoms
from the accident.
I know where this is headed.
I'm not gonna take any meds.
Sorry, but I'm not gonna
do anything to hurt the baby.
I understand.
What about exercise?
There's a prenatal yoga class
here in town.
I hear great things.
Before we begin our asanas,
let us welcome Eveleigh
into our prenatal yoga Class.
Let us gather around and place
our hands on her manipura.
Using the breath of fire,
let us transfer love
and vitality into the child.
Now close your eyes...
..and breathe our life chant
into the child within.
It's not very Zen
getting groped by strangers.
Oh, I burst out laughing
when they did it to me.
-I'm Sadie.
-Hey, I'm Evey.
Hi.
-How far along are you?
-Three months. You?
-Three.
So I'm craving
all these salty things,
which makes me think I'm having
a little boy, but I don't know.
There's a part of me that just
knows we're having a girl.
Aw. I'm craving everything.
The other night
I took a chocolate bar
and just stuck it in the middle
of a bowl of ice-cream.
I didn't cut it up or anything.
It was like planting
a chocolate flag.
Sometimes I feel like
I'm losing my mind
completely during
this pregnancy.
Pregnancy is nuts!
You can either let it
drive you crazy or just
relax and enjoy the ride.
Give in to the morning sickness
and the stretch marks?
-Can you spare some change?
-Uhh...
No. I'm sorry, we're all out.
So sorry.
OK.
- Meth heads.
- Is that a problem around here?
Oh, it's like a plague.
Sorry, I...I just
don't feel comfortable
with you riding this bike.
-Oh, I'll be fine, Mom.
-Alright, I'm sure you are.
There's just so many
drunk drivers and meth heads...
-Am I gonna see you on Tuesday?
-Yes!
Please don't leave me alone
with those crazy women.
You don't wanna
get groped again?
I will see you then, Evey!
Buenas.
-Bueno.
What were you
even doing spying on him?
People come to the country
to be left alone.
What if they're cooking crystal
meth right next door, David?
How is that safe for us
or safe for the baby?
Evey, you don't know
what you saw, OK?
It could've been anything.
-Where's my knife?
-So what? We do nothing?
Yes, exactly.
It's none of our business.
On my way there, I saw
the ruins of the old house.
Yeah, Emilio said he was gonna
hire some guys to bulldoze it.
But we haven't had time. Why?
No reason.
OK.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
David? David!
-Oh, God!
-What? What?
David, there's
someone out there.
Honey, there's
someone out there. Yeah.
There's a man in a hood.
He's just out there.
There's nobody out here.
I saw someone.
OK, if he comes back
I'll be on him.
-OK?
-Wait. You don't believe me?
I didn't say that. No, it's...
Look, it's a new house.
Middle of nowhere,
it's creepy outside.
You're expecting...
We're expecting.
And, you know...
..you went off those meds.
That's what happens.
Come on. It was nothing.
Come to bed.
You are not crazy.
Think of all the tweakers
running around this area.
It just... It felt so real.
You have to listen
to your intuition.
And who knows? Maybe it could
be your mommy sense kicking in.
Oh, mommy sense?
Is that like Spidey sense?
- Kind of.
Once when I was a baby,
my sister was giving me a bath
and left me there
with the water running
and my mom was downstairs
running the vacuum,
obviously couldn't
hear anything,
but she just got
this feeling, you know?
She ran upstairs and there
I was, underwater drowning.
She just knew. Mommy sense.
Yeah, it's mommy sense or
it's something more than that.
I was in a car accident
about a year ago.
They said it wasn't my fault,
but there was a mother and
a baby in the other car and...
..the baby didn't make it.
I'm so sorry.
That's so awful. Jesus Christ.
I tried to reach out
to the other family,
but they didn't take my calls
and I can't say I blame them.
Anyway, then David put me on
an antidepressant because...
Well, I felt like
I was losing my mind.
Obviously, that stopped
once I found out I was pregnant.
Yes. Good. I'm glad.
You shouldn't be putting those
chemicals into your body anyway.
I know.
You can't keep
punishing yourself
over something
that is not your fault.
Thank you for being a friend.
How about I get you
a chocolate mousse, huh?
I'd have a cookie.
David?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Who's there?
Who is it? Who's there?!
Oh, David...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
--Ohh!
-Evey?
-Oh, David, David...
-Whoa, whoa. What's going on?
-The wine bottles just exploded!
What?
What're you talking about?
They just...
But they...
And there was a gun over there.
David, there was
a goddamn gun there!
- Hey.
- Hey, David.
Come on in.
Honey, this is Leo Cottrell.
-He lives down the road.
-Hello.
When we talked
the other day,
I realised I was way overdue
to stop by and say hello.
Yeah, Leo runs
a artisanal olive oil business.
-Right?
-Yeah. We were talking about it.
I just don't want
any misunderstandings.
You guys should come by
and check it out.
OK. Thanks for stopping by.
Appreciate it.
Yeah, yeah.
I'll see you guys around.
-Yeah.
-Alright.
I know what I saw.
I know.
This isn't
just seeing things.
These are major hallucinations
we're talking about.
The hooded guy, a gun...
This is what
we discussed, Eveleigh.
Your pregnant body is basically
a cocktail
of competing hormones.
I'm not taking any drugs.
But you were on medication
for nearly half a year
after the accident
and it could help you
deal with your symptoms.
And I felt like a zombie
and I wasn't pregnant.
There are very few
side effects with this.
You don't need
to worry about that.
This is a very common
antidepressant.
But I'm not depressed
and we don't know for sure
there are zero side effects -
nobody knows.
Evey, we can't live like this.
I can't live like this.
I want you to promise me
that if you have
one more hallucination
you go back on your medication.
David, we have to put
the baby first now.
I'll give
this a minute to open up.
I'm not sure I ever drank
anything that needed to open up.
'Drunk'. Whatever.
We're on more of a
Two Buck Chuck budget ourselves.
That's alright.
So when are you gonna
get this winery up and running?
We're close. The problem
out here, though, is rain.
The vines really should
have shoots by now,
but I've been bringing in
two water trucks a week
since we took over.
Water trucks? That sucks.
Isn't this supposed to be, like,
the worst drought in decades?
OK, maybe
don't rub it in, Ben.
- I'm just saying!
- It's OK.
What about you, Eveleigh?
How do you like the place?
Evey.
-Sorry. What?
She's been a little
out of it recently, so...
Well, imagine how out of it I'll
be when I'm medicated, David.
Sorry. I didn't mean
to ruin the vibe.
But you can't take medication.
You're pregnant.
Thank you.
Ben, why don't I show you
the winery?
I think the ladies
have had enough of us.
Yeah, yeah.
-I'm sorry.
-Don't wander off too far.
We don't want to send
a search party for you.
-Yes, Your Majesty.
-I'm sorry I just did that.
-Ugh!
-No.
Ben seems sweet.
Yeah, I think he's a keeper.
Sorry, I don't mean to pry,
but what is this about
putting you on medication?
Antidepressants.
No, you can't let them
do that to you.
Dr Mathison says it's safe.
What do you think?
I think there
is something wrong here
and I don't think
I'm imagining it.
That's your mommy sense.
Right now,
your protective instincts,
they're at an all-time high,
so if something
happened in this house
you're way more receptive to it.
What do you mean?
I mean...I think this house
might be haunted.
Well, I'm disappointed
that the house
isn't living up
to your expectations.
That's the understatement
of the year.
Sorry, Glenn,
I just need to know
everything there is
to know about the vineyard.
Mm-hm. Yeah, I did
every search I could think of -
police logs,
real estate disclosures -
and there is nothing,
no history of violence,
natural disasters,
agricultural accidents
or any event
that might be at the root
of your paranormal activity.
I'm actually surprised
to hear you complain.
Most people would
love to be able to say
that their house was haunted
by the spirits
of the old winemakers.
Da-da-da, blah, blah, blah...
It adds to the romance.
What about the ruins
behind the house?
It looked like there used
to be a big old house there.
Going back 80 years,
nothing that I could see, no.
It's been zoned for agriculture
the entire time
until the Porters
got their building permit
to convert the stable
into a house.
Try looking them up.
That would be my recommendation.
It's been a pleasure, ladies,
and you let me know
if I can do any more
ghostbusting for you.
Hello, Eveleigh.
It's so nice to finally
meet you...meet you...
No, no!
Don't! No!
No, no, no...
Oh, oh, no!
No! No! Ohh!
- Why are you here?
- No!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
No! No! Ohh!
- Why are you here?
- No!
-Arggh!
Honestly, Eileen,
I wish you'd been there.
It was terrifying.
Maybe it was
a TV in a neighbour's house.
Sometimes your eyes and ears
can play tricks on you
when you're alone
for too long.
Look, I just think
you have to consider
the most reasonable
explanations first.
Sweetheart?
-David's home. I've gotta go.
Have a wonderful time in Paris.
Alright, I'm gonna miss you.
Take care
and focus on your work.
I'll see you in a few months.
Oh, tell David what happened!
Yeah, right. Alright, fly safe.
'Bye, love.
Hey, honey. How was today?
We replaced all the posts
on the north slope.
I had to chase off some more
of those raccoons too.
What are you up to?
I just spoke to Eileen
and she's off to Paris.
Ohh.
How much do you know
about the Porters?
Not much.
The guy's in prison. Why?
Don't you think
it's weird we don't know
anything about the people
that lived here before us?
-What might have happened here?
-Not really. What's going on?
What if what I'm feeling
is not PTSD
and it's not hormonal
and it's something...else?
Like what?
Something...supernatural.
I don't know. Sweetheart,
let's not even go there.
That's the last thing
you need right now.
David, what if something
terrible happened
back in the days
of the old house?
So, like, what? It's a ghost
that only you can see?
Maybe because of my pregnancy.
Maybe I'm getting,
I don't know, a sixth sense.
Look. Listen to me for a second.
You went through something
really tragic last year
and that would be traumatic
for anyone, sweetheart,
and you have nothing
to feel guilty about.
OK, come here. Come on.
Ohh...
Everything's gonna
be OK, alright?
-You promise?
-Yeah, yeah. Listen.
As soon as the baby gets here
this is all gonna
seem like a bad dream, OK?
Hey.
No, no.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
OK.
- What the hell?!
-What did you just do?
-What? Do what?
Do what?!
God, Evey!
This isn't right.
If I can't make you see that,
I don't know what else to say.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Evey...
Evey? Sweetheart?
What happened? Are you OK?
-What happened?
-Ohh...
No, I don't think
there's been any concussion.
But the lacerations to her face,
they're not good.
I understand. Yeah, I'm here
with the husband right now.
Yeah, we're both
on the same page.
The baby's gonna be
just fine, alright?
I promise.
OK...
Morning.
The amniotic fluid
level looks great.
Nothing to worry about there.
And the due date
is gonna be spot on.
Thanks.
-Sadie! Hi!
-Hi!
So good to see you.
And I'm so sorry that
I didn't text you back.
I felt stupid. I called you,
like, a hundred times.
It's not you.
What's going on?
Everyone said I did the right
thing by taking the meds.
And they're probably right.
I mean, I'm not seeing things
anymore, which...
It's a good thing, right?
I don't know what to say.
Well, you don't know
what it was like.
I felt like
I was losing my mind.
Yeah, but how do you feel now?
I don't feel completely myself.
It's an inhibitor. It stops
my brain from going to extremes.
When I was having visions,
Dr Mathison said
my cortisone levels
were through the roof.
It's not his body,
and it's not David's body.
You know who's the one person
who benefits from you taking
these pills right now?
It's your husband.
David?
-Hey.
What are you doing in there?
Just looking for you.
Oh. I, uh, had to go
down to Edna Valley
and meet with a couple of
big distributors down there.
Oh, really?
-How did it go?
-It was good.
Hello?
-Oh, hi.
-Is this Jane Porter?
-Who is this?
You don't know me.
It's Evey Maddox.
I live in your old house
in Paso Robles.
Yes?
Well, I actually opened
a letter addressed to you
from the library.
-You opened my mail?
-Yes, I'm so sorry.
I wouldn't normally do this.
But I saw you checked out
all these books on ghosts
and the supernatural
and I just wondered whether
it had anything to do with
your experience
here at the house.
Oh, please, Ms Porter, I know
this sounds completely crazy
but, um, I've been seeing things
and hearing things,
and, well, nobody believes me
because I'm pregnant.
And then Helena Knoll
mentioned you...
-You know Helena?
-Yes.
At first...I thought
I was losing my mind.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Hello, Eveleigh.
Come in.
Helena?
I'm sorry for interrupting.
Eveleigh Maddox.
What can I do for you?
Do you remember when
you came to our party,
and I found you in our bedroom
and you seemed...
..upset?
I don't remember being upset.
What is it?
What are you here for?
Are you hoping for
an apology or something?
Oh, my gosh!
No, I don't want an apology.
I've spoken to Jane Porter.
I'm seeing it too.
And I'm scared for my baby.
Come here. I'm gonna help you.
-Don't you worry.
-Will you help me?
Don't worry.
I have what I'd like
to call a sensitive soul.
I can see and feel
a lot more than some people.
Makes for
a wonderful palate.
When I drink wine I can...
..feel the grapes and soil
and the weather.
But sometimes...
Sometimes it goes
deeper than that.
I get connected to
a person or a place.
It comes out of nowhere.
It wraps its fingers around
your heart and won't let go.
Did you see something
at the house?
Yeah. Yeah, I did.
But it was a feeling
of rage, anger, fear -
just all swirling up together.
This is the place.
Right here.
Oh, yes.
There's something here.
Give me your hands.
-Uh...
-Give me your hands.
You want to understand it,
right?
We have to connect,
we have to gather our energy,
be open to
the presence out there.
They want to be seen.
They want to be invited.
Understand?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What was that?
Something happened
on this property.
Something so terrible
it stained the land.
I knew
I wasn't going crazy.
I knew it was real.
Certain acts of
psychic violence,
the truly evil ones...
..echo throughout time...
..like ripples
spreading across a pond.
Yes? No, I am glad
to hear from you.
Just a minute.
-It's my daughter. Do you mind?
-Oh, no, no. Go right ahead.
Your friends wanna
help you regain control.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Helena?
- What?
--Helena?
Helena! Helena, are you OK?
Shh. No, no, don't talk.
I'm gonna get you help.
--Shh.
911.
What's your emergency?
Hey, I have a friend
who's having a heart attack.
-Can you send an ambulance?
-OK.
Can you confirm your address,
6425 Denmar Street?
Yes, yes!
It's not what you think!
It's you!
Oh, God! Helena!
No, Helena! No!
Oh, my God! Oh, no!
Oh, my God!
What is that?
Protection.
Protection from what?
El maligno. The evil one.
It get much stronger
since you come.
Evey?
-What is this?
-It's nothing.
What are you doing?
Why do you have this,
and what the hell is
this doing in our house?
Calm down for one second, OK?
Let me explain.
The workers, OK?
Emilio's people.
They keep giving me
this fertility cult shit,
leaving it all over the place.
-Why wouldn't you tell me?
-It's just something farmers do.
It's nothing.
I didn't wanna tell you
because I didn't wanna
fill your head with
these crazy stories.
-I was worried that...
-Worried that what?
That you'd start acting
exactly like you are right now.
Helena and I saw something
in the ruins, baby,
and it killed her.
-We saw it!
-No, her heart killed her.
She had a pre-existing
heart condition.
OK. Whatever you want
to think is fine.
Just come with me. Let's
just leave the house, please!
We've sunk everything
we have into this!
I'm sorry.
This is our dream.
This is not a dream.
This is a nightmare!
There is something wrong
in this house.
-I'm gonna prove it to you.
-Evey...
No, I'm not coming back here
ever again!
Hey, it's Sadie.
Leave me a message.
Oh, hey. This is Evey.
You were right about everything.
About the drugs, about David.
I'm leaving for L.A.
I just gotta do one thing first.
But I'm so sorry that we fought
the last time I saw you,
and call me back.
OK. 'Bye.
I'm sorry to hear about Helena.
Yeah.
I didn't realise until
I looked at the bottle
that your family
used to live on our land.
Oh, yes, but that was
over a hundred years ago.
Um, there's one with
a good label here.
Here we go.
"Folgore."
You can
see the house clearly.
It was the best estate
in the valley.
Did anything strange
ever happen to your family
when they were living there?
Uh, well, um...
My great-grandfather
built the place in 1881.
Family lore has it that...
..soon after they moved in,
they began experiencing
these strange events -
these whistling sounds
and pounding on doors,
things they couldn't explain.
Did they ever find out
why it was happening?
Oh, I don't know.
All this was told to me
when I was a little boy
by my grandmother.
In any case, um...
They eventually moved out
and my great-grandmother
lit the place on fire.
If she couldn't live there,
she didn't want anybody else
to live there either.
You know, there's something that
perhaps you would like to see.
Let me go and get that.
My great-grandmother
was a tough cookie
and she wasn't gonna let go
of the house easily.
So she hired a medium
to cleanse the place.
Now, the story goes that
the medium went into a trance
to try to contact the spirits
that were trapped in the house.
And these are some of
the sketches she did.
David!
That's David!
David, it's us.
A medium saw us
living in the house.
-What are you talking about?
-I've got her drawings!
-Don't get hysterical.
-I'm not hysterical.
-I've got proof.
-Calm down.
Honey, you have to come and meet
me and get out of the house.
But you have to come and
pick me up. You have my car.
I'm not going back
inside the house.
Give me some time to pack
and give Emilio instructions
while we're gone.
Call me when you get here and
I'll come out. I love you.
Pick up.
Pick up!
David?
-David?
-Yeah.
Eileen?
-What are you...
-It's OK, sweetheart.
Everything's OK.
What's everybody doing here?
We're here 'cause we love you.
David asked us
to come over tonight
just to help you get through
this tough time.
A goddamn intervention, David?
Think of it as a support system.
Who's she? I saw you
with her outside the cafe.
This is Victoria Lambert.
She's a family therapist.
And we asked her here tonight
just because we think
she can help you.
Hello, Eveleigh.
So nice to finally meet you.
Oh...
Listen, I just want everything
to be OK for you and the baby.
Your friends wanna
help you regain control.
OK, shut up. We need to leave
and we need to leave right now!
Victoria's actually
offered to let you
stay at her ranch
until the due date.
You can just relax
the rest of the term.
I don't wanna stay at the ranch,
David! We have to go and now!
- Just calm down.
What?
Sorry. I was making some tea.
It's tonight!
Uh, yeah,
she's a little panicky
but I think she knows
it's for her own good.
No, we should be there
in about two hours.
Yes, David's agreed.
It's tonight!
-What's wrong, sweetheart?
-We were wrong, we were wrong!
It's tonight.
It's tonight, David!
-What are you talking about?
-David, it's happening.
It's happening tonight!
We need to leave!
-OK, just calm down.
-Everybody, we need to leave!
- We have to leave now!
-No, don't answer the door!
-Just stop!
Just stop.
David...
We were driving to the hospital.
My water broke.
And I don't think I can
make it to the hospital.
-Come on in.
-Come on, come on, it's OK.
-No, no, no!
-I'm a doctor.
No, no, no, no!
I'm calling the police!
Give it to me!
David, listen.
You don't understand.
There is no ghost.
I was having premonitions.
You're not making any sense
right now, OK?
No, don't you see?
Helena figured it out.
When something
truly terrible happens,
it causes ripples in time,
but they can go both ways!
The Napolis, the Porters,
they were all having
premonitions of one night -
and it's this night,
David, don't you see?
We are the haunting!
Sadie...what are you doing up?
You alright?
Is everything OK?
Not really, no.
Sadie...
I need you to put
that phone down, David.
Put down the phone.
OK. It's alright.
Come on, follow me
back in the living room.
-What? What...
-Come on.
Come on, faster.
Give me your phone.
Give me your phone!
-Please... Please don't do this.
-Sit down!
-Evey.
-Why are you doing this?
You haven't figured it out
by now, Evey?
You are so stupid.
You alright? Come on. Come on!
Shit! I got her!
Give me that phone!
Sadie!
-David! David!
-Run.
-David!
-Get help.
-OK.
-Go!
No! No!
-Why are you here?
-No! No!
-You shouldn't have come here.
-Eileen.
--Whoa! Whoa!
-Shh! What's wrong?
-Leo!
No, no, we've gotta go!
We have to go!
-OK, calm down.
-You don't understand!
I got her. I got her, I got her.
No, no, no, no. I need you
to keep still for the baby.
--It's gonna be OK.
I should've figured
it out sooner.
It WAS your mommy
sense kicking in.
But it's OK now, because
she's gonna live with us
and she's gonna have
such a nice life.
I'm gonna make it alright now.
Because you,
YOU stole my baby from me!
That's right, it was me.
Yes, that's right.
They said I couldn't
have a child.
They said I couldn't conceive,
but I did.
And he was such
a beautiful little boy.
He was my whole life.
He was my hero.
He was my little miracle baby.
And then you came along
and you took him from me!
You did, you killed my baby!
And then I went online and I saw
what a perfect life you had.
And then I saw you were
pregnant, and then I knew.
I knew it was the universe
putting it all
back together again,
because I'm gonna give her such
a wonderful, beautiful home,
and it's all gonna be OK.
I need the bag now, OK?
I need you to be
brave for the baby.
I need you to stay
calm for the baby.
- Stay strong for the baby, OK?
Don't worry, Eveleigh!
No, no, no! For the baby!
I need you to stay calm
for the baby, OK?
Shh. Give me the scalpel.
Come on, come on, come on.
OK, OK, OK. Shh.
Uh...
-Shh.
Oh, Jesus.
--Yes. Shh.
Wait, uh...
I don't know if I can...
It's OK. It's OK.
I don't need you.
We don't need him, do we?
It's just us mommies now.
I can do this.
Hi, baby. Hi, baby.
I just need you to stay
really still right now.
Just be really quiet.
And it's all gonna be OK.
- Alright?
OK. Here we start.
I can do this, OK?
- Sadie?
Sadie! Baby?
What did you do?
We were gonna start a family!
Ah!
David!
Oh, honey, you need help.
I called an ambulance.
It was under the table...
..right where
you said it would be.
I think you're
gonna be glad
you came all the way out here.
It's a one-of-a-kind property.
See, these floorboards here
are vintage oak.
You have floor-to-ceiling
views here.
Oh, and you mentioned
that your husband is
a fan of ghost stories, yeah?
It's funny that
that's brought up,
because this house has
a very interesting reputation.