"It is with love that I do this.
God's will be done." Alyce Parker.
Please God, watch
over my babies.
Please just come home again.
- Hey.
- How's it goin'?
This way.
Put it down over here.
Can I help you, Mrs. Parker?
Mrs. Parker? Mrs. Parker?
Mrs. Parker, can I help you?
- You okay? - It's the
dampness, it, uh...
gets in my head.
It's gonna get a lot worse
before it gets better.
- Snap Pops! - Sorry,
buddy, no Snap Pops.
- Snap Pops. - It's the first day
with abstinence. You know the rules.
- Snap Pops.
- Milk or tea.
Sorry, honey, it's only
till after Sunday.
- Why? - Because it's the fast,
which means that we can't eat.
No flesh, no fruit, no grain.
Drink your milk,
it'll fill you up.
Now, don't chug it, it's
gonna give you a belly ache.
I don't know what she was thinking,
leaving those clothes out like that.
Her headaches have
been getting worse.
I wish Daddy would let
her see a doctor.
You know how he
feels about that.
Mr Parker? Mr Parker.
Stay here.
Daddy!
Spit it out.
- Hey.
- Hi, Doc.
I'm so sorry I'm late.
The roads are a mess.
I'm Doc Barrow.
We know. You delivered our baby
brother, Rory, up at the house.
- Oh yeah, Rory, little Rory. How
is he? - He's, um... getting big.
Good. Where is your father?
He couldn't make it.
He's still grieving.
Well I can understand that,
sweetie. It's tough.
- They said that she drowned.
- Well, I won't
know, hon, until I do
a full examination.
You mean autopsy.
Yes, an autopsy. It's the law.
You know, I'm so sorry,
it's been a long time, and
you've grown so much, I just
can't remember your name.
- Iris.
- Iris. And you?
- Rose.
- Iris and Rose.
Well, I only need one of you
to make the identification.
I'll do it.
- I'll do it. - Okay.
- This way, sweetie.
Rose, we'll be right back.
Mr Parker?
Mr. Parker, it's wet out here.
She's in a better
place, Mr. Parker.
We say that. Do we believe it?
Emma Parker. 47 years old.
Liver healthy. Moderate calcification
on the left ventricular arteries.
Sign of pill rolling.
Atrophy of right
vastus lateralis
- suggesting early
onset of Parkinson's.
What about Lamb's Day, Daddy?
We do it the way that
we've always done it.
Two days, and we will carry on.
But Mama's gone.
What?
- Mama's gone. - It's what
we do, Rose. We continue.
Iris is the eldest daughter.
It's her responsibility now.
Tree's down. Creek's
washed out.
Fetch some candles, Rose.
I'll let them know what's going
on down at the trailer park.
You're not a'scared, are you?
Are you scared?
Don't be scared.
♪ Jesus gonna be here ♪
♪ Oh, He gonna be here soon ♪
♪ He gonna be here soon ♪
- When is Jesus gonna be here?
- Soon.
Yeah, He's gonna be here soon.
That's my boy.
Sing it.
- Shhh.
- Sing it.
Daddy's home.
What is it, boy?
Huh.
Come on, come on.
Mr. and Mrs. Kimble, uh... in these
situations, 99 times out of a hundred
the missing person is safe, just
can't get to a working phone.
Your daughter's probably at
somebody's house, a friend's
house, just as worried about
you as you are about her.
But, uh, she's our only child, and
she never hasn't come home before.
I understand that, but I got... I got
roads closed, lines down, bridges out.
Let's give it 24 hours. If
she doesn't make contact
by then, we'll, uh, we'll
put out an alert. Okay?
Emily!
I need you to make copies
of that photo, and
put out an MPR on a Valerie
Kimble, all right?
I'm on it.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, I know it's a
bad time for you, but...
uh, I'm finished with
this place, uh...
There's no work, and now this damn
storm washed half the town away,
so, we're gonna head down-state to my
brother's and see if we can start over.
I think that's everything.
Good luck, Mr. Parker.
I'm hungry.
Snap pops.
It's for you.
- I don't underst... - A
token to... for last night.
"Kindness shall be
met with kindness."
- Is that in the Bible?
- It's in mine.
- Thank you. - The funeral
is this afternoon.
- So soon?
- It's our way.
I don't like to ask, I was wonderin' if you
wouldn't mind watchin' my boy for a spell.
- Too young for these things.
- Of course I wouldn't mind.
I'd be happy to, Mr. Parker.
This is Sheriff Meeks. I'm not
here right now, please leave
a message and I'll get back
to you as soon as possible.
Hey, Bob. Doc Barrow here.
I found something strange
this morning, my dog
actually dug it up, I'd
like to show it to you.
I can stop by your place today, if it's
okay. Let me know, please. Thanks.
Where are you, Pumpkin?
You're gonna have to take care
of them now. You ready for that?
I'm the eldest. That's the way it
works. The way it's always worked.
It just... doesn't seem fair.
None of it.
That's for me to worry
about, not you.
What if we refused to do it?
We just... we just stopped?
- He would make us, wouldn't he?
- I just wanna get this over with.
And then we have a whole year
to figure something out.
- I just wish we were like
everyone else. - Well, we're not.
- What are you doing? You
know you ain't allowed
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
down here! - I seen
the monster, Daddy.
One day, I'll teach you how not to be
afraid of the dark. How'd that be?
- Good. - Until
then, you stay out.
Don't go where you don't belong.
Okay?
- You always need a watchful eye. - I'm
sorry, Daddy. Rose said he was sleeping.
Rose isn't in charge. You are.
All we have is each other.
We need to stick together now.
You understand?
"And the seed shall become the
tree, which bears the fruit."
- "And feeds the
kindred. Amen." - Amen.
When the Earth has claimed our limbs,
then shall we come home to walk with Him.
To the better place He calls us,
free from want, and hungry
desires of this Earth.
But should some urgent
fate, untimely lot,
bring you to meet your fate,
nameless out the haunt that the lone
regions where has drawed no foot of man,
commend myself to God.
Behold, the Lamb of God, who
taketh away the sins of the world.
- Amen.
He hasn't eaten... since Mama...
Take him home, put him to
bed, let him get some rest.
If he wants something to eat, give him
something light, like soup or something.
- I'll call you tomorrow.
- I'm sorry, Iris.
Thank you for coming, Anders.
It was really sweet of you.
No, no hon... she didn't
suffer at all, no.
We're home, Daddy.
She was the first. Now
it belongs to you.
December 24th, 1781.
Papa has found our new home.
It is a peaceful place, high on a
mountain overlooking the valley below.
The forest is rich with serenity. The
land, it knows not the industry of men.
Our harvest dwindles as
winter approaches early.
Mother has forgone her rations,
so that the children may eat.
Father and Uncle Burnett left
yesterday in search of game.
We pray for their safe
return, as I fear we have
not yet seen the whole
of nature's cruelty.
- Hi.
- Hey.
I hope I'm not bothering
you, but uh...
I wanted to say that
when my dad died...
it was really hard on our
family. Especially my mom.
Where have you been? I
haven't seen you all summer.
Academy training? Down-state?
Yeah, this is my first
official week on the job.
- They made you cut your hair,
huh? - Yeah, academy regulation.
- You wanna come in? - Um...
- No, it's, uh...
it's just... do you
remember a Valerie Kimble?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, well, uh, have
you seen her lately?
Hmm-mm.
Not since school let out.
She's pretty.
Yeah, well, um, well she's gone missing.
And, uh, it was just before the storm,
so I thought that maybe, since she had to
come by this way on her way home everyday,
that maybe someone had seen her.
Well, you could check
up at the trailer park.
Only the new girl left,
business has been slow.
Yeah, it's been
slow for everybody.
All right, well um, well
I'll go ask her then.
I hope this doesn't come off the wrong way,
you know... I thought that maybe, um...
maybe after everything calmed
down... uh, we could, you
know, we could go to a movie
or somethin' sometime?
- A movie?
- Yeah.
Or... or a restaurant, we could go eat,
you know, whatever you want to do.
- Ask me again some other time, and
we'll see. Okay? - Yeah, of course.
All right. I will... I will...
I'll see you around? I hope.
Not if I see you first.
That's the boy from school
that you liked, isn't it?
He's okay.
Nice haircut.
I don't know what's
keepin' you here, Doc.
What you need is a good long
vacation, someplace warm.
Shit, if I was you, I'd retire and
stay there. She can stay here.
- So what do you think? - Well, it's
been floodin' up at the cemetery.
Hell, but Bob, the cemetery
is downstream from me,
and you know very well
nothing flows upstream.
- How sure are you, Doc?
- I'm not.
We'd have to send it to
Albany, be tested positive.
That's not gonna happen,
not with the flood.
What are we gonna do?
I got a state of emergency here,
I can't start an investigation
based on a piece
of bone, I'm not even
sure that its human.
- I'm not asking that, Bob.
- I know that.
- Come on, Jim, you know
what this is. - What?
- I'm sorry, man. - Aw, it's all
right. - You're probably right.
I'm probably
clutching at straws.
Believe me, when Kimmy disappeared,
we did everything we could.
She was just gone. It happens.
I wish to God it
didn't, but it does.
Yeah...
and the monster lived
happily ever after.
No, he didn't.
- What? - The monster's
not happy. He's crying.
- What do you mean? - I heard him in
the basement, behind the locked door.
He's in there and he's sad.
You hush now, go to sleep, okay?
Good night.
We lost Mrs. Burnett last night.
Mother is weakening by the hour, and I
fear that she will not last the winter.
Father returned to us this morning
with supplies of fresh meat.
Uncle Burnett continued further east
in hope of reaching the outpost.
He has not returned, and I
believe now that he never will.
Father says all is forgiven
in the eyes of the Lord.
Daddy.
What if we were different?
If we weren't like we are?
What?
Come here, honey.
What are we like?
It was God chose
us to be this way.
If we don't do as he asks,
we get sick from the poison.
One by one we'd die. You can't hide
a doubtful mind from him, honey.
He knows all, sees all.
You're stronger than
you know, girl.
I know, Daddy. One more day.
- I love you so much. I love
you so much. - I love you too.
Oh! Excuse me.
- Hey, Doc.
- Mr. Anders.
What kind of bone
you think that is?
- Where'd you find this? - In a
washed-out creek, behind my house.
Definitely not a deer. My dad would've
known, he was real good with bones.
In my humble opinion, I
believe it's human remains.
Well... in that case I take your
word for it, you're a doctor.
Well, I'm here because I
went by to see Meeks, and
told him. He just thinks I'm
some kind of a nut-case,
and he may be right. But...
there's been three
people missing from this
town in the last 20 years,
- one of which was my daughter. - I know,
I remember. I was on the search party.
Yeah, I know.
But... if you extend the
radius including the towns
within 50 miles, there are
30 people or more missing,
- none of which have been
found. - I'm just a deputy.
Oh, I know, I'm just trying to help out. I
thought, maybe it'd be useful information.
Boy, there are good folk
in this town. Nice people.
Those girls just put their
mother down, just died recently,
and down here to help out.
The father is a bit of a
whacko, if you ask me.
Hey guys, on the house. We got the power
back up, but one of our fridges won't start
so we have to eat everything
up before it spoils.
- Could I have a cup of
coffee, sweetie? - Sure.
I'll tell you what, Doc,
how about I come over
tomorrow and you can show
me where you found this.
- He woke up sick and
then got all hot. - Oh,
he just has a fever.
Children get fevers.
- Do you have any aspirin?
- Yes.
Can you crush one up in a
glass of milk, please?
- Oh, and make sure you crush it
really good. - Is he gonna be okay?
Oh yeah, he'll be fine. We just gotta
get him out of these wet clothes.
Sweetheart, do you have
some fresh things for him?
Uh, yeah, I think.
You poor little thing.
You're so sweet.
Ow!
I'm hungry.
What's goin' on?
- Eh... he's got a fever. - It's
a wonder we ain't all sick.
All this damn rain
gets in the bones.
You a good neighbor, Marge.
I'll see you out.
- Listen, maybe you oughta take him to see
a doctor? - That costs money we ain't got.
We ain't used to sickness in this
house. He'll burn it off, be fine.
- Good day, Marge.
- You're bleeding.
Well, look at that. It must be dried
out from the stove in the shed.
It's the Maker,
tellin' us it's time.
Mama has gone to the Lord. Now
it is just the three of us.
Father has changed greatly
these past few weeks.
He keeps to himself in
a back chamber of the
cave, quoting scripture
and weeping at night.
I suspect I know the great
secret father has kept from us.
As father's mind unravels, our
survival has now become my burden.
It is with love that I do this.
God's will be done.
Alyce Parker.
Lamb's Day, 1782.
We're gonna have to
call the Kimbles.
Hold this.
Help me.
- Help me. - I can't do this!
- I can't...
- We have no choice now. - You're
gonna leave me for that police boy.
Nothing comes between this
family. Okay? Nothing!
I need you. I can
not do this alone.
Please help me, Rose.
Go, please help me!
I'm sorry, Mrs. Stratton. I promise
you're going to a better place.
Get off me!
Iris, make it stop. Make it stop! Would
you please make it stop. Please!
Please, Iris! Please,
please, please...
- Did you kill the monster?
- Yeah, yeah. Yes I did. Yes.
Tell Daddy supper is ready.
Are you okay?
I didn't know it was
gonna be like that.
I won't do that again.
He can't make me.
Nobody can, not even God.
- Hi! I came by to see how the little
man is doing. - He's fine. Better.
I brought you some lasagna. Have to
use it before it goes bad, so...
It's vegetarian.
- Sweet of you. - I heard somebody
down in the shed earlier.
It must've been Daddy. He's the
only one allowed down there. Ever.
Well, it sounded
like a girl, crying.
I don't know what you think you
heard, but you must be mistaken.
Thanks. Good night.
Good night.
Thank you for the
sustenance we receive.
Blessed are the lamb, for
they are his offering. Amen.
Amen.
It's good.
Your mother would be proud.
- Eat your food, Rose.
- Yes, Daddy. It's just hot.
Blow on it.
It takes more than a flood to
bring this family to its knees.
- It looks like pot glow.
- And what is pot glow?
Means it's been boiled.
Listen, you find anything
else you give me a
call. I'll be at my
office at the morgue.
- Fuckin' "pot glow."
- Thanks!
Iris! Iris, wake up!
Get up.
You should call a girl when
you're gonna make a visit.
Morning, Iris.
- What are you doing in my creek, Anders?
- Wastin' my time, gettin' my feet wet.
I don't mind so much now
that you're around.
- I can get you a pair of my
daddy's socks. - You think so?
I know so. Come on up.
So... what are you looking for?
I, uh... I probably shouldn't
say, it's nothing.
You can tell me. Hell, you were
the first boy I ever kissed.
- You prob'ly don't remember though,
do you? - No, no... I remember.
So, you can tell me...
what are you looking for?
The storm just washed some
things way down creek.
- Well, what kind of things?
- Bones.
We been findin' bones 'round here since I
was a little girl. Deer and 'coons, mostly.
- No, but Doc Barrow thinks that these
are human. - You're just funnin' me.
No, I swear to God,
that's what he thinks.
But the sheriff, he's not buyin'
it, so... so I don't know.
Let me get you those socks.
Hey, uh... Hey Iris, could
I get a glass of water?
Iris?
- Jesus! - What are you doing
here, Anders? - Something wrong?
No. No, uh, I just
got my socks wet.
- Iris was gettin' me a dry pair
from upstairs. - What is that?
It looks like some
sort of old tooth or
something. I found it out
in the creek. Thanks.
So, how old are you now, Rose?
- Fourteen.
- Fourteen...
- You're growin' up.
- It happens.
Yes, it does.
Catch.
Ah, thank you.
- What's this? - Some kind of
bone, I found it out back.
My Daddy would know,
he's good with bones.
So was mine.
You know, there's an old family
cemetery up the creek a bit.
We used to go there
when we were little.
- There are even some
stones left. - How far?
- Not far. Just below the falls.
- Maybe, uh, maybe I should take a look.
This could be from one
of our relatives.
- I'll show you where it is.
- Okay, I'd appreciate that.
You're growin' up really pretty,
Rose. Just like your sister.
I'll see you later.
See you.
I think your sister's worried
that I'm gonna steal you away.
Are you?
Listen.
What?
My daddy called them heat bugs.
Means summer is coming.
Oh...
Damn it.
What?
Nothing. Come on,
we're almost there.
Some have signs of scorching,
and Y-shaped patterns,
indicating a serrated blade.
T-structured incisions,
indicating a flat blade,
for scraping or fileting
tissue from bone.
- This is all your dad's
land, huh? - Mm-hmm.
Don't.
Why? It's just a flower.
I'm not worth it, Anders. I'm
not what you think I am.
I don't think you're
anything but a pretty girl,
who I like a lot.
- I'm not pretty.
- Yes, you are.
- Not inside. - Maybe I
should just take you home.
You're filth. Rory's alone.
I don't know where your
sister's made off to. You
get your ass home and
look after your brother.
Now!
Get out of my sight.
Both of you.
Hi, you've reached Deputy Anders.
Sorry, I can't get to the...
This is Sheriff Meeks. I'm
not here right now...
We'll take the truck
once he's asleep. Then
we'll head to the city
and just start all over.
Just stop, okay?
Everything's gonna be okay.
You're so beautiful.
Okay?
You're gonna be fine.
We're gonna be... fine.
Shh... It's okay.
Daddy's mad.
The Lord is my shepherd. I shall not want.
He ​​maketh me lie down in green pastures.
He leadeth me in paths of
righteousness for His name's sake.
Yea, though I walk through the valley
of the shadow of death, I fear no evil.
For He is with me. His rod and
His staff, they comfort me.
Surely goodness and mercy...
- Hi, Emily.
- Hey, Doc.
- Is Anders in? - Ah,
nope, just me.
I've been tryin' to
call him all afternoon.
There's a new storm
comin', bad reception.
He might be over
at the fireworks.
- Is Meeks in? - He's out
on call, accident on 28.
Listen hon, would you... would you
mind watchin' my dog for a bit?
Ah! Oh my goodness!
He's so cute!
- I left something in
Meeks' office, can I get
it? - Oh, yeah, door's unlocked.
Help yourself.
- Okay, thanks. You be a good dog,
Zip. - Did you get what you needed?
- Yes, I did. Thank you
so much. - Oh good.
- Have you seen Deputy Anders?
- No, not today.
You haven't seen Deputy
Anders, have you?
Emma, I have seen the signs.
We're comin' home to you now.
Comin' home to you now.
Comin' home to you now, sweetie.
- Is Meeks around? - I
haven't seen Meeks in...
Father, we have kept our
tradition in its purity,
we seek our reward
in the hereafter.
Oh, come on, Kidd. Come
on, buddy, let's go.
Come on, let's go. Good boy.
Pretty, isn't it?
Honey, listen to me. You're gonna
have to be a brave boy, okay?
You're gonna have to listen to me, and do
what I say when I say it. Can you do that?
All right? That's a
good little man.
Get ready for supper.
Good boy, Kidd.
Iris.
Father, lift us from this
world of goatishness,
together, as one
and raise us to righteousness
and heavenly laity.
We have kept our
tradition in its purity,
and seek our reward in
the hereafter. Amen.
We were lost, like the lambs.
But have found the light
that will lead us home.
Let us eat.
Iris.
- Yes?
- Get the door.
- I need to see your father.
- Come in.
- Dr. Barrow.
- Mr. Parker.
You hungry, Doc?
We have plenty.
- No thank you.
- What's on your mind?
- Well, it's rather indelicate. - Leave
me and the doctor have some privacy.
Let there be light.
Mind if I smoke, Doc?
How long have you had that
hand tremor, Mr. Parker?
You didn't come here to discuss
my health, did you, Doc?
- No, I didn't.
- What then?
- Have you seen Anders?
- Who?
The Deputy. Anders.
Oh. Yeah, yeah.
- Was he here?
- This morning.
But he left.
- Is there anything else?
- Yes, matter of fact.
Your wife suffered from a rare
disorder of prion disease.
It's usually found in the
native tribes of New Guinea.
And it comes from
eating human flesh.
Did you kill my daughter?
Mmm... what?
Your daughter's
wearing a hair clasp,
that was a gift to my
girl when she turned 16.
Did you eat my daughter?
I been meanin' to ask you, um...
are you a religious man, Doc?
Tell me about my daughter.
It's not too popular
these days, is it?
Tell me about my daughter.
Tell me about my daughter!
Daddy! No!
Son of a bitch!
Come here, sweetie.
You're gonna be okay.
Don't you move,
you're gonna be all right.
Don't you go anywhere.
I'm sorry, honey. I love you.
I'm gonna go get your... your
brother and your sister.
Get in.
Come on, let's go.
Get out, get out!
Marge! Marge! Marge! Marge!
Please open up!
Marge! Please open up!
Open up!
Marge! Please!
What the fuck is happening?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Rory.
Come on.
Come on. It's all right.
It's okay.
I'm sorry. Rory,
Please, come on. You don't have to be
afraid of the dark. I'll teach you.
I'll teach you. I'll teach you.
- Rose.
- No.
- It's okay.
- Come home now.
- No. No.
Iris needs you. Iris
needs you, now come on.
- Iris?
- Iris needs you.
Yeah, she's safe. Come on.
Come on. It's okay.
Come on. Yeah, that'a girl.
It's okay.
I'll take care of you.
All is forgiven, in
the eyes of the Lord.
You look just like your mother.
Shhh... shhh...
No reason to cry.
Shhh...
- I love you, Daddy. - I
love you too, Rose.