More blood!
Great. Keep coming.
Chuck, Terry, pump away.
Don't be stingy.
Watch that arm.
I can see that fake arm.
Chase, keep that claw
really moving.
Jeffrey, jam it on there
just like Freddy would.
Good, good. And cut!
Print that, Gretchen.
Chase, you're a genius.
This makes his old claw look
like Mother Teresa's mitten.
You better thank them.
They're very sensitive.
Chuck, Terry, great blood.
- Thank you very much.
- Some of our best work.
Hey, monkey man,
want to see some neat stuff?
Come on.
It's only make-Believe.
Marianne, I gotta go.
Low bridge.
Let's see if we can
scare the P.J.'S off Mommy.
Hey, Heather.
You hungry, Dylan?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Gotcha.
It should have flexed more.
I think the servos
got shorted out with blood.
Well, take it apart,
pull it out...
and insulate them
with some styro.
The thing wasn't meant to be
submerged, for Pete's sake.
I don't like that thing.
That thing puts bread
on our table.
Is it alive, Daddy?
Heather,
you're in the next shot.
State-Of-The-Art animatronics
with bio-Organic grafting.
Bull tendons, nerve bundles
from a live Doberman.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Must've have picked up a signal
from an eighties walkie-talkie.
- Sure it's off?
- It's off.
Funny, it's warm...
just like a real hand.
Oh, God.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
What the hell's going on here?
Cut the effects!
Terry, where is it? Terry!
Chuck, get off me!
Heather, where is it?
Chase, where the hell is it?
Come on.
What the fuck?!
Earthquake. Come on.
Mommy!
What is that?
Car alarms.
You OK?
You OK, chief?
Honey, do you have a fever?
Just another earthquake, Dylan.
Getting kind of fun, huh?
Daddy. Blood.
It's nothing, guys.
It's a scratch. Really.
Where did you get that?
I don't know. Picture, I guess.
When it fell. It's no big deal.
Put a bandage on it.
Don't worry about it.
Geologists at Cal Tech...
have confirmed
this morning's aftershock...
Do we have to watch that?
...five-point-three
on the Richter scale.
Thought you turned it on.
It was strong enough
to cause further collapse...
of the already badly damaged
parking structure...
I'll turn it off.
Officials say
that this is normal...
following a quake
of last week's magnitude...
now thought to be a massive 6.8.
Dylan, this is breakfast,
not arts and crafts.
What?
Did you get any sleep
last night?
More or less.
OK, time to get dressed.
I'm late.
You going away?
Just for a few hours.
Julie will be with you.
Is there anything other than
the obvious bothering you?
I think five earthquakes
in three weeks is enough.
Hasn't been another phone call,
has there?
Good sign.
Two full weeks without him.
Maybe he got hit by a truck.
He's closer, if anything.
It's giving me nightmares,
Chase.
Did you have one last night?
It's just the earthquakes,
Heather.
Maybe.
Maybe I shouldn't do
this interview today.
No. You gotta get back
on the horse sometime.
Look, you had a nut case
making harassing phone calls.
I know how scary that's been.
No, you don't.
OK, I don't.
But it doesn't mean
that it can't be over.
But what if it isn't over?
Maybe you should
tell me your dream.
It was nothing. I was...
you and I were working on
this movie, together for once...
and one of your special effects
went really wrong.
And Chuck and Terry got hurt...
and...
well, your fingers were cut.
Right here?
Heather, you were
probably half awake...
and saw my fingers get nicked
when the mirror fell.
Dreams are like that.
Look, if you don't want me
to go on this job, I won't.
Just be careful, OK?
I think I can survive
two days in Palm Springs...
supplying soap bubbles
for a detergent commercial.
I guess so.
You guess so?
Come here.
Forty-eight hours.
I'll be back in no time.
I gotta go.
I love what you've done
with the place.
Knock 'em dead.
Dylan, I gotta go.
Take care of Mommy.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Nancy.
Dylan, I don't want you
watching this.
Dylan, what's wrong?
What's wrong?!
What's happening to you?
One, two...
Freddy's coming for you!
Someone's coming.
What?
Are you OK, honey?
Is everything OK?
It's just these quakes.
Did you feel one just now?
No. A big truck went by
before you opened the door.
It's life on the fault line.
- Hey, tiger.
- Hi, Julie.
Does he feel warm to you?
He had a fever this morning.
No, he seems OK.
Are you sure
that's all that's wrong?
Leave us alone,
you son of a bitch!
L.A. Limousine, ma'am.
Just wanted you to know
I'm out front.
I'm sorry.
Can you hang on a minute?
What is it?
I don't know.
I just have
this weird feeling today.
Mommy? Stay home, then.
This damn caller.
He's started again?
Sick fuck.
Sorry.
Dylan doesn't seem
to have a fever.
It's probably just your nerves.
Nerves?
I just meant from the shaker
this morning.
Everybody's freaked out about
how many we've been having.
And then these phone calls.
Don't answer it.
Excuse me, ma'am,
but we are going to be late.
Dylan, I gotta go. Forgive me?
Bye.
I'll call the cops for you.
You've got the number
on the fridge, right?
Give them
the time they called...
and they're keeping this list,
supposedly.
Julie, I'm really sorry.
My nerves are
a little raw these days.
It's OK.
Yeah. I gotta go.
- Morning.
- Good morning.
You played that girl.
In that movie.
With the guy with the...
Yeah, sure. That's you.
That's what I love
about this job.
I get to meet the stars.
I'm hardly a star.
What, are you kidding?
I love your stuff.
The first was the best.
Where the girlfriend's cut open
and dragged across the ceiling.
It was awesome.
And when all that blood comes
out of your boyfriend's bed?
I thought I'd shit.
But they never should
have killed off Freddy.
Heather, look, we gotta go.
Cutting it close, aren't you?
You trying to get me fired?
OK! We're coming!
So, Heather, we're approaching
the tenth anniversary...
of this whole
"Nightmare on Elm Street" thing.
I mean, the original,
five very popular sequels.
How has all the success
affected you personally?
I don't know
if it really has, Sam.
God. With the exception
of One and Three...
I pretty much stayed out of it.
Well, I'm doing a lot more
television now...
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
so those hours
let me spend a lot more time...
with my husband
and my little boy.
You have a little boy.
What's his name?
Dylan.
With Dylan,
does that change your feeling...
your perspective
about horror movies?
No, not really.
Would you let him
see one of your movies?
My son? No.
I'm sure people ask you this
all the time...
Is there going
to be another sequel...
and what's more,
is Freddy really dead?
Of course he is.
Freddy's dead and gone.
And how about your co-Star
in the original...
would you trust him
alone with Dylan?
Robert? I don't know.
Why don't we ask him
how he'd feel about it?
We've got a big surprise for you
and for our audience.
Let's bring him out.
He is the best of the bad.
Let's say hello
to Robert Englund.
Love ya, babe!
We'll do lunch!
I'm alive once again!
Freddy's back! Give it up
for your Uncle Freddy!
Just when you thought it was
safe to get back into bed!
Give me five!
I'm back,
and I'm badder than ever!
You are all my children now!
I got to go, Robert.
Just a second. I'll walk you.
There you go, kids.
- Thank you.
- Bye-Bye.
- You OK?
- I'm fine.
Well, everything went great,
I thought.
We really got you, didn't we?
I don't know why
you didn't tell me.
Come on. They loved
the expression on your face.
I think they'd like
to see us together again.
In what, a romantic comedy?
Just because
it's a love story...
doesn't mean you can't
have a decapitation or two.
- There's a call for you.
- For me?
I'll talk to you later.
Heather, it's Sara Risher
over at New Line Cinema.
How are you?
This is a voice from the past.
It sure is.
Listen, Heather,
I won't take but a minute.
It's just that we have
something to propose to you...
and I wonder
if you'd stop by the offices.
Bob would love to talk to you.
Sure. When?
No time like the present.
The car will bring you over.
- Now?
-Just take a minute.
You'll be glad you did, I bet.
Bye.
- Can I help you?
- I'm here to see Bob Shaye.
Was Bob expecting you?
Sara. How are you?
- I'm fine. How are you?
- Great to see you.
- You look great.
- Thank you.
Bob is dying to see you.
Can I get you something?
- Coffee would be fine.
- Black?
- Black's fine.
- Could you get us some coffee?
- Sure.
- Thanks.
I think the guy
is a little bit of a jerk...
but we won't know
until we've read the script.
Anyhow, I'll give you a call
when I...
Listen, man, I got to go.
Call me
when you get to Milan...
and don't forget...
risotto con tartufi.
It's fantastico!
Take care, man.
I'll talk to you later. Bye.
Boy, do you look great, Heather.
- How are you?
- Great. I'm fine.
And I don't have to ask
how you're doing.
Well, so far so good.
Which is why we asked you
to come by today.
- Thanks, Kim.
- Sure.
Look, Heather,
let me cut to the chase.
How would you like to join us
in the definitive "Nightmare"?
I thought you killed Freddy off.
Well, we did, but the fans...
God bless them,
they're clamouring for more.
I guess evil never dies, right?
Anyhow, a few weeks ago,
I got a call from Wes...
and he pitched me
this really ex citing idea...
and I started thinking...
"who better to resurrect
Freddy than his creator?"
I thought Wes stopped
doing horror movies.
He actually told me he hadn't
called in the last ten years...
because he hadn't had
any really scary nightmares.
They're his inspiration
for this thing.
Anyhow, he's right
in the middle of the script.
Which means
he's having nightmares again.
He's very excited about it.
- The nightmares?
- No, the script.
And you should be, too,
because you're the star.
I don't know, Bob.
I'm flattered, really,
but I have a kid now.
Well, so?
So I'm not sure
about doing horror.
Come on, Heather.
Kids love horror.
Thank you so much, Bob.
I have other things happening.
Look, we'll match any offer
that's on the table for you.
No, it's not that.
Look, I have a fan.
Heather, you got plenty of fans.
We've been doing
marketing research on you.
You are rating right up there.
We've got Chase working on
a prototype for the new glove.
What?
We asked him to kind of
keep it as a surprise...
until you and I could have
this conversation.
How long has Wes been
working on this script?
I don't know.
A couple of months. Why?
And since you've been
thinking of making it...
has anything funny happened?
What do you mean?
Like weird phone calls.
Or nightmares.
Why don't you answer
your phone, Bob?
That's what we got people
we pay around here for.
Will someone pick up
the damn phone?
- Thanks a lot.
- You're welcome.
What the...
Never sleep again.
What is going on?
You didn't let him watch
the movie on TV, did you?
Movie? He didn't watch
anything on TV.
He was taking his nap,
and I heard him screaming.
Honey, are you OK?
Rex saved me.
He did?
Is Rex going to die?
Rex is not going to die.
I promise you, sweetie.
Do you know where the sewing
stuff is in the kitchen?
Sure.
We'll do an operation, OK?
Come on.
Dr Dylan and Dr Julie.
Fix him up good as new, OK?
Hey, Chase. You've got a call.
It's your wife.
Chase, you better come home.
Heather, I'm stuck here.
Neither Chuck or Terry
came in today.
Why? What's the matter?
- Chase, it's Dylan.
- What?
Hold on.
The phone's breaking up.
What's going on with Dylan?
He's had some sort
of an episode.
What?
What kind of episode?
He was just acting
very strangely.
Like somebody was after him.
It's scary. It scared me.
He was acting like...
Like what?
Like Freddy.
Heather, has there been
another phone call?
Why didn't you tell me
you were working on a new glove?
And why aren't Chuck and Terry
at work today?
Forget those clowns. Answer me.
Has there been another
phone call today or not?
I'm coming home.
I'll be there in three hours.
- Danny, I got to go.
- What's up?
My kid's sick. I got to fly.
"As soon as the sun was up...
"the witch made Gretel fetch
the wood and kindle a fire.
"'We will bake cookies first,'
she said.
"'I've heated the oven
and kneaded the dough.
"'Crawl in and see if the fire
is blazing high enough now.'
"And she pushed Gretel
toward the oven.
"The witch went to shut the door
and bake her inside."
This is so violent.
I don't know why you like
these stupid old fairy tales.
Finish, please.
- They'll give you nightmares.
- I like this story.
"But Gretel guessed what
the witch was planning.
"'I don't know how to
get in,' Gretel said.
"'How am I to manage it?'
"'Stupid girl,' shouted
the witch, rushing to the oven.
"'The opening is big enough.
See? I can fit myself. '
"Quickly, Gretel came behind
and pushed with all her might...
"plunging the wicked old woman
headlong into the flames...
"banging the door shut
and bolting it tight.
"The witch howled..."
That's enough.
"The witch howled
like a scalded cat...
"but Gretel ran and left her
there to perish nonetheless.
"She ran to her brother
as fast as she could...
"flung open the door.
'Hansel! Hansel,' she cried.
"We're saved!
The witch is dead."
Time for sleep.
Say how they find
their way back home.
- Tomorrow night.
- No. Tonight.
It's important.
Dylan, you know as well as I do.
They followed the trail of
breadcrumbs back to their house.
And then their father
covered them with kisses...
and they were safe.
They were safe,
and they could sleep.
- What is that?
- Rex.
Come on.
Rex keeps him down there.
Who?
The mean old man with the claws.
He wants to come up
while we sleep.
I keep my feet up here.
Rex keeps him down there.
He's my guard.
You should have a guard, too.
There's nothing down there.
Come here.
Look. See?
It's different when you're gone.
Come on.
On, please.
OK, sweetie.
Night-Night. Sleep tight.
Don't let the bedbugs bite.
- Daddy coming home?
- He's on his way.
He can follow
the breadcrumbs, right?
Right.
If the birds
don't eat them first.
Perfect, perfect, perfect!
Come on, come on, come on.
That's me in the corner
That's me in the spot
Light
Losin' my
Religion
Mommy's scared?
Dylan, Mommy's fine.
It was just a bad dream.
What are you doing out of bed?
Rex woke me up.
He was fighting.
Dylan, go back to sleep, honey.
I'm not sleepy.
Police, ma'am.
Will you open the door?
Heather Langenkamp?
Is Chase Porter your husband?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
There was an accident.
It appears he fell asleep
while driving, ma'am.
Is he... I mean...
Is he hurt?
I'm afraid
it's worse than that, ma'am.
Is he dead?
Yes, ma'am.
Are you sure it's him?
We have his effects.
You can confirm from that.
I want to see his body.
No, you don't, ma'am.
It's not necessary.
I want to see it for myself.
- Can you hand me that?
- Sure.
Excuse me.
- Could I help you?
- Porter.
Chase Porter.
It's back here.
You said Chase?
I'm sorry.
Just sign here at the bottom.
That's all we need.
I'd like to see once again.
I'm sorry?
Could you lift
the sheet again, please?
More, please.
What is that?
It was a bad wreck, ma'am.
The head's gonna be all right
for the funeral, but...
Hey, lady. You OK?
You sure?
Oh, God. What did that?
They said the truck
was tore up something awful...
so you can imagine him
not being in...
well, exactly top shape.
It looks like he was clawed.
That's why we don't lift
the sheet past the face, ma'am.
Sometimes it's what we don't see
that gets us through the night.
So, if you'll just sign...
God is our hope and strength...
a very present help in trouble.
Therefore, we will not fear...
though the earth be moved...
and though the hills
be carried...
into the midst of the sea...
though the waters thereof
rage and swell...
and though
the mountains shake...
at the tempest of the same.
-Julie, where's Dylan?
- I don't know.
Dylan, grab Mommy's hand.
Grab it!
Oh, my God!
Hurry!
Let go of me!
Stay with me.
Stay with me, Heather.
- Where's Dylan?
- He's all right.
He's right here.
- What happened?
- Earthquake.
You got knocked off your feet.
You got a pretty good bump,
actually.
May he rest in peace, children.
And may you all get home safely.
Amen.
If there's anything
I can do, Heather... anything.
Thank you, Robert.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Sweetie.
Tina?
Who are you?
Baby, wake up.
Honey. Dylan.
Dylan, get over here!
Honey! Honey!
Come on.
OK, sugar, we're gonna
go back to bed now.
No, Mommy, I can't sleep there.
Honey, you have to sleep.
One, two,
Freddy's coming for you!
Where did you hear that?
Did you hear that on that movie?
Did you answer the phone?
Dylan,
where did you hear that song?
In my bed.
In your bed?
Under my covers. Kids singing.
Way down there with the man.
The mean man.
What is that man doing?
Trying to get up.
Trying to get up into our world.
Where's Daddy now?
Daddy's in heaven.
He's with God now.
Do you have to die to see God?
I don't think so.
I think you have to pray.
And reach out.
Why does God let there
be bad things?
I honestly don't know, honey.
Please try to get some sleep.
Can you come with me
in my dreams?
I think that only
happens in the movies.
But I'll always, always...
be right here when you get back.
And I'll make sure
that nobody gets your toes.
I know his behaviour
is bizarre...
but he's usually so normal
and well adjusted, John...
I can't believe it's him...
and not something outside
influencing him.
Or is that how denial works?
It is denial.
I don't think
that's the case here.
If you're really worried
about Dylan...
have a doctor check him out.
You'll see. Everything's fine.
You're not just saying that
to help a crazy friend cope?
Everything about Dylan's
behaviour is understandable...
for a kid
who just lost his father.
How does a child
process a thing like that?
I don't know.
I've not been able
to process it very well myself.
And you're not crazy,
by the way.
Seeing Freddy in that grave
and then jumping in...
you didn't jump in.
That's my memory.
It seemed absolutely real.
"Seemed," not "was."
It's in my family, you know.
What is?
A very close relative
died in an institution.
Really? If having a screwy
family made a person crazy...
the whole world
would be one big loony bin.
You have a crazed fan after you.
That's what's making you crazy.
Probably Dylan, too.
I never mentioned that to him.
Kids know when something's
bugging the parent.
You have no idea
who this is calling?
- Freddy, for all I know.
- Come on.
He's a man.
Or a boy
with a deep Freddy voice.
Six weeks, and you're surprised
you got Freddy in your dreams?
Hell, Sonny Bono,
after a while...
began seeing his stalker
everywhere, even at Mass.
Really?
How many times
did Letterman call the cops...
thinking that woman
was down in the kitchen again?
Really gets under your skin
if you let it.
You really think Dylan's OK?
Dylan's fine. You're fine.
You're hurting,
but you're fine...
and you're definitely not crazy.
My worst fear...
that whatever madness
is in my family I have...
and I've passed it onto Dylan.
- Make sure he's OK, John.
- Are you all right?
Are you OK? Are you sure?
Does anything hurt?
Dylan, are you all right?
Honey, are you all right?
Are you sure?
God wouldn't take me.
Oh, my God. Oh, honey.
It's unbelievable.
- You doing all right?
- Hanging in there.
You know the guy that was
calling me all the time?
He started again...
and he's putting stuff
in my mail again.
Listen, the S.O.B. Probably
read about the funeral...
in the papers or something.
Sick mother.
That's the last thing
you need right now, I'm sure.
Actually, it's been giving me
Freddy nightmares.
Wait a second.
Now, let me get this straight.
You're having nightmares
about Freddy? As in me?
No. It isn't you. He's scarier.
He's...
Darker?
More evil?
Yeah. How did you know?
Call it a guess.
Pretty damn good guess.
Anyway
what I was calling about was...
have you seen any of the script
by any chance?
No. Wes won't show it
until he's finished.
At least that's what he told me.
When is it gonna be done?
The way he's writing, who knows?
It's so weird.
I asked him how far
he was at the funeral.
What did he say? Oh, yeah.
"As far as Dylan
trying to reach God."
Whatever that means. Weird, huh?
Putting your kid in the script.
Robert...
have you been having nightmares?
Look, we need to talk,
but not over the phone.
Can I come over?
Actually, Heather...
today's no good.
There's something
I have to finish.
Tomorrow maybe, huh?
OK, tomorrow.
But early in the morning.
And meanwhile, Robert,
take care, OK?
Yeah. Sure.
Damn it!
One, two,
Freddy's coming for you!
Three, four,
better lock your door
Five, six, grab your crucifix
Seven, eight,
better stay up late
Dylan, don't sing that song.
Nine, ten, never sleep again!
Dylan! Stop it!
No! Don't!
Never sleep again
I touched him.
Any history of epilepsy
in your family?
Diabetes?
Was there a trigger event,
trauma, shock?
You haven't shown him
the films you've made, have you?
The horror stuff?
His father just passed away.
I'm sorry.
But I'm convinced
those films can tip...
an unstable child over the edge.
Unstable?
Dylan's not unstable.
He's just upset.
We'll run a battery of tests
and know in a few days.
Does he have to stay overnight?
Absolutely.
Anything more happen
we need to know about?
Like what?
Sometimes what a child
says or fantasizes...
will give a clue
to what ails him.
Did he say anything
while he was still lucid?
What do we have here?
Too soon to know for sure.
The early symptoms point
to childhood schizophrenia.
Dylan, can you hear me?
Dylan, you have to fight it,
whatever is after you...
and you got to come back to me.
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
You can't make it alone.
Do you hear?
If you can hear me, tell me
what you need to feel safe.
Rex? Is that what you want?
Well, Rex is at home,
and that's where you should be.
But you got to get better before
they'll let you come home.
Do you understand?
Home.
Home. Home, that's right.
That's where I want you,
sweetie.
And, you know,
we're not that far away.
Look right out there.
Past the freeway is our home.
But to get there, you have to
come out from where you are...
so that they'll let you
come home to Rex.
And to me.
Time for your medicine, cowboy.
- Here you go.
- What is that?
Something to help him sleep.
There you go. It looks good.
There you go.
Good. Good. Attaboy.
Come on,
lie down and take a little nap.
You should get some rest, too.
He's going to be fine.
We're gonna do some tests...
and then
you can come back later.
Can you get
that other side, please?
I grabbed his things.
These are
his favourite pyjamas here.
Honey, I've got to go.
I love you, Dylan.
Remember what I said.
We'll take care of everything.
Wake up, lady!
Don't lose it now!
Seismologists at Cal Tech...
have counted
over 300 temblors so far.
Though most were too faint
for us to feel...
seven have shaken our community
in the last few weeks...
and now scientists
are speculating...
there might be an unknown fault
running beneath Los Angeles...
a fault that could...
Hi. You've reached
the Englund residence.
We're out of town.
You can leave a message
if you wish, but...
we'll be gone for some time.
I wish I could tell you
where the script was going.
The fact is I don't know.
I dream a scene at night,
I write it down in the morning.
Beyond that, your guess is as
good as mine where it's going.
At least tell me
what it's about so far.
- Coffee.
- Thanks.
I can tell you what
the nightmare's about so far.
It's about this entity...
whatever you want to call it.
It's old. It's very old.
It's existed in different forms
in different times.
The only thing that stays
the same is what it lives for.
What is that?
The murder of innocents.
This is still a script
we're talking about, right, Wes?
I sort of think of it
as a nightmare in progress.
In this nightmare in progress...
does this thing
have any weaknesses?
It can be captured sometimes.
Captured? How?
By storytellers, of all things.
Every so often, they imagine
a story good enough...
to sort of catch its essence.
Then, for a while,
it's held prisoner in the story.
- Like the genie in the bottle.
- Exactly.
But the problem comes
when the story dies.
And that can happen
in a lot of ways.
It can get too familiar...
or somebody waters it down
to make it an easier sell...
or maybe it's so upsetting
that it's banned outright.
However it happens,
when the story dies...
the evil is set free.
You're saying Freddy
is this ancient thing?
Right. The current version.
And for ten years, he's been
held captive as Freddy...
in the "Nightmare on Elm Street"
series, but...
now that the films have ended,
the genie's out of the bottle.
That's what the nightmares
are telling me and I'm writing.
If Freddy's loose in
your script, where's he going?
Another age? Another form?
No, that's not what
the dreams have him doing.
What is he doing?
He's sort of gotten used
to being Freddy now...
and he likes
our time and space...
so he's decided to cross over
out of films into our reality.
Isn't there somebody
who can stop him?
Actually there is a person
in the dream...
sort of a gatekeeper,
so to speak.
Somebody Freddy has to get by...
before he can
come into our world.
That person's you, Heather.
It's me?
Why me?
Dramatically speaking,
it makes perfect sense.
You played Nancy, after all.
You were the first
to humiliate him, defeat him.
That was Nancy. Not me.
But you gave Nancy her strength.
So in order to get out,
he's got to come through you.
He's gonna try to do that
at your most vulnerable points.
Oh, my God, Wes.
Did you know?
It was a script.
It was a dream.
I didn't know.
You know damn well
it's more than that now.
How can we stop him?
The only way
is to make another movie.
I swear, I'm gonna stay
by this computer...
and keep writing until I finish
the script, but...
when that time comes,
you'll have to make a choice.
Choice?
What kind of choice?
Whether or not you're willing
to play Nancy one last time.
"Many of the symptoms
of childhood schizophrenia...
"are duplicated in children...
"suffering
from sleep deprivation."
"Sleep deprivation can produce
trance-Like states...
"mechanical behaviour.
"The child might..."
Rex woke me up.
He was fighting the mean old man
with the claws.
You have no idea
who this is calling?
Freddy, for all I know.
As in me?
No, it isn't you. He's scarier.
Darker, more evil?
How did you know?
He's decided to cross over,
out of films, into our reality.
Never sleep again.
The world of horror films
suffered its own terror today...
as two of Hollywood's best known
special-Effects technicians...
were found dead
in a vacant field.
Terrance Feinstein
and Charles Wilson...
two special-effects artists...
reputedly working
on a top-Secret project...
for the makers of
the Freddy Krueger films...
were found brutally slashed
to death early this morning.
Freddy's glove was missing...
and police are speculating
the murders were the result...
of a botched theft...
which apparently took place
two days ago.
At this point,
the murder weapon has not...
Oh, God.
Miss me?
Nancy.
There are no visiting hours
this late.
You must understand.
No, I don't understand.
I told you I'm his baby-sitter.
I'm a close friend
of the family, damn it.
I just need to see him
for a minute.
Sixty seconds. Come on.
You have to understand.
You can't see him.
What are you doing here?
I don't know.
I had this really terrible dream
about Dylan.
I had to come and see him.
You must think I'm crazy.
No, I don't.
Is he all right?
I don't know.
They wouldn't let me in.
There are no evening visiting
hours in intensive care.
Is he all right?
Dylan? He's holding well.
Earlier he had some problems.
- He's in an oxygen tent now.
- Oh, my God.
Seems we've had an accident,
Miss Langenkamp. May I?
Those are nasty cuts.
How did you get them?
It happened in the earthquake.
I fell.
I need to see Dylan.
In a moment.
First let's see about you.
If these had been a few inches
nearer the wrist...
what did you say
you cut yourself on?
It was the earthquake.
It was dark. I have no idea.
But these look quite fresh.
They are. It happened
in tonight's earthquake.
It happened just 15 minutes ago.
You must have felt it.
Guess we lucked out over here.
Your son...
Upcoming jump scare (Major)
is apparently
terrified of a man...
someone he thinks
is going to come out of his bed.
One of the nurses heard him
talking to himself.
Do you have any idea
who that man is?
I forgot to bring
his dinosaur Rex.
He keeps Freddy
from coming up out of his...
bed.
The man from your films?
Freddy Krueger?
With the claws?
Is that who he's afraid of?
You have let your child
see your films, haven't you?
Every kid knows who Freddy is.
He's like Santa Claus...
or King Kong or...
well, interesting talking
with you, Miss Langenkamp.
I hope you understand.
My concerns are simply
for the welfare of your son.
How's he doing?
Honey.
- You shouldn't do that.
- Too late.
I'm almost there, Heather.
Almost there.
Daddy!
- Doctor!
- Keep her right there.
We can't hold him much longer.
Get the full anaesthetic, stat.
We don't have that here.
No anaesthetic, you say?
Screw it. I'm going in.
Little booger's full of
something I don't like.
Let's get him open,
good and proper.
Cut this evil out of him.
- Gloria!
- He's got my baby!
- Who?
- Freddy!
Who?
Freddy Krueger or something?
- What the hell's going on?
- My baby!
Freddy's got my baby.
He's got my Dylan.
I suggest you go home
and get some rest.
Your son is fine.
He's downstairs
for further testing.
But he was just here.
He was here, you fell asleep,
we took him.
You looked so exhausted...
frankly,
we didn't want to wake you.
Besides, the young woman
Julie is with him.
That's his baby-Sitter, right?
Believe me. Everything is fine.
Everything's not fine.
Damn!
Call security.
Security, code yellow.
Pediatric testing.
This is a restricted area.
Do you have a pass?
Screw your pass.
It's all right.
Where is he?
Just stay calm.
How's her little boy doing?
He's fine, actually.
He came around
about ten minutes ago.
He seems to be suffering
from acute sleep deprivation.
I don't think
she ever lets him sleep.
What are you saying?
Where is he?
I've got someone here
who wants to see you.
Are you OK, champ?
Can we go get Rex now?
The bad man's getting
awful close.
I know he is.
We're gonna go get Rex
right now.
I'm afraid Dylan should
stay here until we know...
what's causing these episodes.
I'm sure you understand.
Good.
I'll tell you what.
I'm gonna go home
and get Rex right now.
You know that home
isn't far from here, right?
Right across the freeway.
That's right.
I won't be gone long...
and Julie's gonna stay here
with you.
Yeah, you bet.
Hurry up, please. I'm sleepy.
I promise. Cross my heart.
But, Dylan...
until Mommy gets back...
whatever you do...
don't fall asleep.
Julie, don't let him
out of your sight.
What's going on?
Your hair's turning grey.
Julie, keep him awake.
Understand?
Excuse me, miss.
Would you come with us?
What? Hey!
What the hell
do you think you're doing?
Get your hands off me!
Do you mind?
What the hell is this?
Just a quick word...
for Dylan's sake.
We've had an ex citing day,
haven't we?
This one?
Right there.
One, two, three.
You won.
Would you mind stepping outside
for one moment?
As a matter of fact, I would.
What are you doing?
It's just a little shot
to see that he sleeps.
No. His mother
specifically said...
- I said no.
- Do it.
All done.
He'll be asleep soon.
- Would you let go of my arm?
- You bitch!
Hey, you can't do that!
I know what's in that one.
Do you know what's in this one?
Or what's gonna happen to you
when I stick you with it?
And I will.
I want you to stay awake, OK?
Keep your eyes open for me.
Come on.
Has there been any use
of recreational drugs...
in your family?
Or any history
of mental disturbance?
What are you asking?
Please, don't take it wrong.
If there was,
there's a good chance...
Dylan could be suffering from
something passed down to him.
Have you been suffering
from any delusional events?
This man from your films...
Freddy Krueger.
Have you been seeing him?
Would you get those keys
down here?
I want you to stay awake.
Keep your eyes open for me.
Where's Mommy?
She'll be back. Now stay awake.
There are drugs and treatments,
Miss Langenkamp.
We could...
put Dylan in foster care
for a short while.
Just long enough to run
some tests on you.
Keep your eyes open.
Do that for me, OK?
Come on. You can stay awake.
Stay awake for me.
I want you to stay awake.
Keep your eyes open.
Dylan, what's the matter?
Julie, behind you.
There's nothing there.
Dylan, what's wrong?
Dylan, stop it.
You're scaring me.
I want my son out of here
right now.
Very well.
As soon as we can gather
the appropriate papers.
You don't understand.
If Dylan falls asleep, then...
I got it.
Dylan, get out of here!
Ever play skin the cat?
Come on.
Help me.
Mom!
Rex!
What the hell's going on?
You can't go in there. No.
Wait, wait.
Code yellow
to paediatric testing.
Where's my son?!
Where is he?!
Have you seen my son?
He was just here.
The boy.
No way he's going anywhere.
He's been heavily sedated.
He doesn't have to be awake
to be on his feet.
- What?
- He sleepwalks, you idiot.
He's fully capable of walking
out of this hospital.
Oh, shit.
John, it's Heather.
I need your help.
Why? What happened?
Dylan's run away
from the hospital.
I don't know if he's wandering
or headed for the house...
but I think Freddy's after him.
I know that sounds crazy, but...
you're right. That sounds crazy.
Oh, my God.
You know that home
isn't far from here, right?
Right across the freeway.
Krueger, you bastard!
Take me!
Are you OK?
You OK?
My son is out here!
Let me go! Dylan!
I'm sorry. What happened to you?
Are you all right?
I'm fine. Have you seen Dylan?
Take it easy, take it easy.
Relax. He's right there.
What happened?
Oh, God.
What's going on, Heather?
What in the world happened?
I know how Chase really died.
- What do you mean?
- Fred Krueger did it.
Yeah. Sure.
You saw him, didn't you?
Coming for you
Nancy, let's go outside.
He'll be all right.
I'll be right back.
What the hell is going on,
Nancy?
Why are you calling me Nancy,
John?
Why are you calling me John?
Nancy, pull yourself together...
before you make yourself
and that kid nuts.
Would you call Robert?
Robert Englund.
- The guy who plays Freddy.
- Freddy who?
Freddy Krueger.
Nancy, Freddy's dead.
Don't start losing it
like your mother did.
I love you, sweetheart.
Don't forget that.
I love you, too...
Daddy.
Get yourself some rest,
Nancy, please.
One, two,
Freddy's coming for you!
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Who's there?
Listen, Daddy.
I've got a proposition for you.
I'm gonna get the guy
who did it...
and I want you to arrest him
when I bring him out, OK?
Nancy, just tell me who did it.
I'll go get him, baby.
Fred Krueger did it, Daddy.
Yeah, sure.
Dylan's sleeping pills.
Say how they find
their way back home.
It's important.
Breadcrumbs.
Too late, Heather.
Too late.
Join you.
You've given me a way
to join you.
Almost there.
"The more she read,
the more she realized...
"what she had in her hands
was nothing more or less...
"than her life itself.
"That everything she had
experienced and thought...
"was bound within these pages."
"There was no movie.
"There was only... her life."
It's just me.
Are you OK? Are you all right?
Where's the man?
I don't know.
He had me,
but then he let me go.
Meet your maker.
Pick a pet for the rugrat,
bitch.
Fuck you!
Get over there, Dylan!
Take this!
Come here, my piggy.
I got some gingerbread for you.
Gotcha!
Where's your mommy,
piglet, huh, huh?
One, two,
Freddy's coming for you!
Come to papa.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Gonna eat you up.
Leave him alone!
Dylan, get out of there!
Push!
Run!
Are you OK?
Honey, honey.
Oh, my God.
We're saved. The witch is dead.
And his mother covered him
with kisses, and they were safe.
"Heather...
"thanks for having the guts
to play Nancy one last time.
"At last Freddy's back
where he belongs.
"Regards, Wes."
Is it a story?
Yeah. It's a story.
Read me some.
"We open on an old wooden bench.
"There's fire and tools...
"and a man's grimy hands...
"building what soon is revealed
as a gleaming set of claws.
"And the claws are moving now...
"as if awakening
from a long and unwanted sleep.
"Then the man lays one trembling
hand flat upon the table...
"and with his other
picks up a thick, sharp blade.
"Behind the lights,
faces watch from the darkness...
"ready to laugh
or scream in terror."