Let's get outta here!
Get out! Get out! Go!
Just leave the damn thing!
Come on!
Freeze!
Just leave it!
Go, go, go, go!
Stay back! Stay down!
Let's go!
Come on. Let's go!
Now! Move it!
Go! Go!
Stop! Right there!
Morgana!
Oh, God. Are you okay?
- Yeah, I think so.
- Easy, easy, easy.
- Oh, God!
- What?
This stopped the bullet.
Oh, my God.
- Where'd you get that?
- It was inside the statue.
What happened?
It burned me!
Drop it!
- No!
- Watch out!
No!
Don't die. Don't die.
You're scaring me.
Get out of here.
- No.
- I love you, Morgana.
Go!
Get outta here.
Jesus.
Eric.
I can help you.
Fuck off.
I can give you life everlastingly,
if you wish it.
I can end your pain
if you wish that.
I wished I'd never been born.
As you wish.
Done.
- Cover the back.
- Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Freeze!
Did I hear you say "freeze"?
Yeah. Yeah, you're goddamn right.
I said, "freeze!"
Done.
The time is come.
Fulfill the prophecy.
Hold it right there.
Now, put your hands up.
Now slowly turn around.
Open up your hands.
Slowly.
You wanna explain this to me?
He needed to chill out.
Cuff him.
Get him outta here.
Why?
You say you acted alone.
You say you shot and killed
two private security guards
in the commission of a robbery.
That is correct.
- Where's the gun?
- I said I don't know.
It just disappeared.
What about the six paintings
you cut out of their frames?
Did they disappear too?
Look. Nathaniel.
I know you're not the shooter,
so who are you trying
to protect? A girlfriend?
Is that it?
She must be a real good fuck.
I mean, you're willing to take
the injection for her.
Hmm?
You got a boyfriend?
You got a boyfriend, you sly devil.
You little faggot, you.
Actually, I don't have any friends.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
What the fuck are you
tryin' to pull here?
Why don't you just tell me what you'd like,
and I'll be happy to oblige.
The fuck you will,
you lyin' sack of shit!
You give me nothin' but horseshit!
I'm the one that asks
the questions here, not you!
Understood?
Yes.
Questions. Answers.
As intelligent a man as you are,
don't you wish your job
were a little more exciting?
Willet!
Yes, sir.
Get this asshole outta my face.
Let's go.
Guy gives me the willies.
In a case that continues
to baffle police officials,
Nathaniel Demarest pleaded
guilty this morning
to charges that he robbed
the Sarom Art Gallery
- and murdered two security guards.
- This is bullshit.
Judge Edward Lavwitz remanded Demarest
to county prison pending sentencing.
But questions still remain as to how
Demarest committed these crimes,
since a weapon was never found
nor have police discovered the whereabouts
the missing works of art.
As for the 3,000-year-old statue
damaged in the robbery,
experts are confident
it can be restored.
Called Ahura Mazda, it depicted
an ancient Persian deity of that name.
- I don't believe this.
- Meanwhile,
the family of slain security guard
Arnell Dawkins remain in seclusion.
Funeral arrangements
for the father of two
will be held along
with the other security guard.
Police Chief Howard said that there
will be a special ceremony
at City Hall to honor the officers.
- Reporting live from City Hall...
- shut up!
What's the matter in there?
- Is there something you'd like?
- Yeah!
How about your tight
little yuppie ass?
Oh, I'm no yuppie-
Don't fuck with me, bitch!
I'll fuck up your life, you cocksucker.
You understand what I'm saying?
I believe you mean you'll do me
great bodily harm if I'm deceiving you.
Believe me, I'm not.
Make a wish.
- Any wish you like.
- Uh-huh?
All right. Uh, those are nice shoes.
What, are they some kind of English shit?
I don't know.
Take 'em off.
- Take the fuckin' shoes off, or...
- I like you.
You're a powerful man.
But you waste your power.
I'm giving you the chance
to wish for anything you like.
Anything in the world.
You can do better than a pair of shoes.
Whoa! Whoa!
You're a fuckin' genie!
Hey, fucking guy.
He's a fuckin' genie!
We got a fuckin' genie in our cell!
Hell, you're a genie, huh?
- Yes.
- All right. Okay. Fine.
Fine, because I'm gonna
make a wish.
If the wish don't come true,
I'm gonna own your lily white, yuppie,
motherfuckin', golf-playin' ass.
If the wish comes true,
I own you.
The fuckin' state owns me!
- Jesus Christ.
- All right.
Okay. Fine. Great.
You see the bars there?
I wanna walk right through the bars, man,
and walk right on outta the jail.
Come on. Come on, genie.
Done.
You woke me.
Fulfill the prophecy.
It's been a long time, Morgana.
Hello, Gregory.
Father.
You shouldn't be here.
It's still a church.
It's where I live.
I'm sorry to bother you, all right?
I just needed to talk,
and you're the only one...
Look, something's going on.
There's always something
going on with you, Morgana.
No.
No. This is different.
You know, this isn't the first time
I've been here since...
What is it you want
to talk to me about?
Do you...
Do you believe in the devil?
I believe in God.
Yeah. So if, um,
if God exists,
then Satan has to exist too, right?
Is there a point to this?
I don't even know.
Eric's dead.
Is that what you came here
to tell me?
Not really, no.
You know, you could
just say "I'm sorry."
I'm sorry.
But he wasn't
the right man for you.
I loved him.
- Do you really know what love is?
- Do you?
You couldn't love me,
and so you came here.
I'll tell you what real love is.
God so loved the world
that He gave His only begotten son...
I don't need a sermon, Gregory,
all right?
What do you need, Morgana?
I need answers.
I just don't know the questions yet.
Goodbye.
Yo, check this out.
I'm getting it on
with my sister-in-law, right.
Next thing I know the bitch
drops fucking dime on me.
Attempted rape.
I got this loser for a fuckin' P.D.,
and it's my third fuckin' hit.
That's fucked up, man.
Check this out, man.
I get stopped at a light.
They check in the trunk.
I get busted for a bogus search.
My lawyer plea-bargains three-to-five
when I should have fucking walked.
Punk-ass motherfucker
should go fuck himself.
- You're absolutely right.
- Who's the fuck is this guy?
Who you talkin' to,
you fuckin' faggot?
I'm talking to someone
who doesn't belong here.
I'm gonna do you a big favor because
you're new and you're ignorant,
and not rip the fuckin' tongue
out of your mouth for talkin' to me.
I'm going to do you a favor,
because you're an unjustly
imprisoned man.
You'd like to see your lawyer
paid for all the pain and suffering
he's put you through. Yes?
- Yo, man, are you tripping?
- Yes.
- Who the fuck are you?
- I'm the Wishmaster.
I make wishes come true.
Oh, yeah? Well, you better wish
for some fuckin' sense real quick.
I believe you said you'd like to see
your lawyer go fuck himself.
I could arrange that.
Yo, man, you ain't playin' for real,
my boy here's...
I only play for real.
- What's in it for you?
- Your soul.
- Fuck it, man. Make it happen.
- Freeze.
Let's go, man.
Your lawyer's here.
- He wants to see you.
- Tell your friends.
Come on.
I said come on!
Get him outta here, man!
Well, well, well.
What do we have here, boys?
Wishmaster.
I like to flatter myself.
Flatter this, motherfucker.
Fuck off.
Now...
You wouldn't be tryin' to do any
business here, would you, bro?
Just trying to be helpful.
Is there something
I can help you with, brother?
I'm sure there is.
I'll be watchin' you.
Wishmaster.
Tinker Bell-lookin' motherfucker.
Hello, Robert. How's it goin'?
- You tell me.
- Well, actually, very well.
Oh, yeah.
Have a seat, please.
I think that I may have
some good news for ya.
Something about your case
didn't sit right with me.
It was the search.
It wasn't handled properly.
I did some digging.
And I uncovered
a procedural screwup
that's potentially very damaging
to the D.A.'s office.
I think that, uh, I can get all the charges
against you dropped.
Back up, man, back up.
What are you tellin' me?
You can get
all the charges dropped?
- That's right.
- What are you sayin', man? That I can go free?
That's right, Robert, and of course, you know,
with my connections at the police department
and the D.A.'s office, well,
you know, I can...
Goddamn, what was that?
- Are you okay, man?
- Yeah. Whoo!
Excuse me. Um, okay. Uh.
All right, yeah. We were... Ooh!
You okay?
Oh, God. Okay. We were talking...
Mister... Guard!
- Guard!
- Ohh!
Guard!
Yo, man, he's sick, man, he's sick!
Augh!
What the fuck?
What the fuck
are you doing, man?
What about my case, man?
Done.
Fulfill the prophecy.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Who are you?
Who the fuck are you!
God, this is bullshit.
Ahura Mazda.
"The deity of light in pre-Islamic Persia.
"His shadow was said to contain
all that was dark.
He thus came to symbolize
the duality of good and evil."
- Who is it?
- It's Gregory.
Come on up.
"Ahura Mazda was also known as
Keeper of the Stone
of the Secret Fire."
Never seen a girl
without her makeup before?
Father Dmitri told me you were outside
the church the other day.
Yeah. Um...
I was walking by,
and I decided to, uh...
Did you want to talk to me?
Not really, no.
You all right?
Yeah. I'm fine.
Only because Father Dmitri said
you seemed ill or...
I haven't been
sleeping well lately.
Still trying to find
the answers, huh?
The questions keep piling up.
I keep having these nightmares
and things.
People dying. A voice keeps saying,
"Fulfill the prophecy."
"Fulfill the prophecy"?
I keep thinking it has something
to do with Eric's death, you know?
Whatever.
Yeah. Actually, that's
why I wanted to come by.
I wanted to say I was sorry.
I was wrong, what I said to you
the other day about Eric.
My heart is truly with you.
I know.
The weird thing is
I'm not even sure he's dead.
I mean, there's been no reports.
Nothing on the news.
W-Wait a minute.
Maybe he's just missing.
Why do you presume he's dead?
Because I saw him shot.
What? Have you been to the police?
It was during a robbery.
I was part of it.
Oh, my God.
I killed the man
who shot him.
He left a wife and two kids.
And then I hear about this
Nathaniel Demarest guy,
arrested at the scene.
Confessing to everything.
I mean, the murders, everything!
W-Wait. You have to confess.
He's an innocent man.
I don't know what he is.
I thought at first maybe he was
a police plant or something.
But he keeps showing up
in my dreams!
Or whatever they are.
Listen to me.
You have to confess.
It's your only way to find peace.
All I know is
I gotta find out who this guy is
and get him outta my life.
I need to see some I.D.
Holmes, we need detergent.
Mr. Demarest.
Yes?
I'm Osip Krutchkov.
How do you do?
I do very well, Mr. Krutchkov.
And you?
Oh, call me Osip.
I'm as well as I can be
in this fucking shit hole.
You'd like to be out of here, of course.
Who wants to be in prison
when he can be a free man?
Perhaps I could help.
So I am told.
Really?
What were you told?
That you are the devil.
That you take men's souls.
Did you believe them?
I don't give a shit
if you're devil or not.
As long as you will give me
what I need on this earth.
It is truly a pleasure to do business
with an enlightened man, Mr. Krutchkov.
Now, what can I do for you?
First, obviously,
I want to get out of here.
- Only one wish to a customer.
- Oh, Mr. Demarest.
I am not usual customer.
Maybe not, but there are rules.
Rules are meant to be broken.
Help me, and I help you.
- Now, why would I need help?
- Everybody needs help.
Even the devil.
- What are you doin'?
- Oh, yes, sir. Just talking a little bit.
Demarest.
Let's go.
I'll catch you later, baby.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
You're gonna have a hearing
in about two weeks.
We meet again, Morgana.
How do you know my name?
I've been expecting you.
Where, exactly,
do you think we met?
In the art gallery.
That's bullshit.
I've never been there.
Why did you confess
to the robbery?
So you wouldn't have to, my dear.
- I don't follow you.
- Oh, I think you do.
We wouldn't want to talk about it too
loudly in here, now, would we?
You were there?
Indeed.
Hiding?
"Hidden," I think, is a better word.
Look, you're talking in circles.
I can't follow you.
You're right.
Why don't you ask me a question?
- What happened to Eric?
- The young man who was shot?
He had a regressive experience.
No. No riddles.
I'm sorry.
He's no longer with us.
Look, why would you take the rap
instead of me?
Access.
How could you have access to anybody?
You're in prison!
You're here.
Besides, this is only temporary,
and I've managed to gather up
a few like-minded souls.
Everybody wants something.
I love that part!
What does
"Fulfill the prophecy" mean?
You'll learn that
when the time is right.
What prophecy? And why me?
What is it about me?
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
You set me free.
Are you all right, miss?
Yes, I'm fine.
Come on, asshole.
Come on.
Go ahead and put it over there.
There's this guy. Jackie T.
Plays it off like he's my boy.
Be sharin' stuff, talk shit about
what we're gonna do when we get out.
I tell him about my stash,
I tell him about my girl.
He gets out.
Next thing I know this fuckin' Sancho
is runnin' around with my bitch.
- And I don't know what else.
- That's no good.
No.
We really must do
something about that.
- What's it gonna take?
- Your soul.
And a pack of cigarettes.
Just take care of business, all right?
Done.
Hello, bro.
See you been spreadin' your hustle
around my house.
- Yes.
- That's good.
'Cause I'm here for my rent.
- Your rent?
- My rent.
My piece, my slice, my vig.
You just got a new partner,
motherfucker.
Not.
I prefer to work alone.
I don't think so.
I am prepared to offer you
something else, however.
You don't offer me shit!
I take, and I take, and I take!
Yes, of course.
What I meant to say was,
you can take anything you wish.
Is there something you'd
trade your soul for?
- My soul?
- Man, Butz don't have no soul.
Shut up!
Oh, yes, he does.
What'll it be, brother?
Power? Money?
Sex?
One more word outta you,
and I'm gonna shove my fist
so far down your fuckin' throat
you're gonna shit knuckles!
Nobody does business
in my fuckin' house
unless I get my rent.
Very well.
What else you got?
Hmm.
Hmm?
Don't you know these'll kill ya?
Your drugs!
I want your drugs.
Exactly which drugs would you like?
I don't give a damn.
I just wanna get wasted.
- Wasted?
- Wasted.
Fucked up.
Tore up from the floor up.
Stomped right into the ground.
- Wasted.
- Mmm.
What the hell's the matter with you?
I don't know what the hell happened!
Wanna show me what you got,
motherfuckers?
Come on! Let's rock!
Careful what you wish for, brother.
That's how hard you can hit me?
Pow, pow!
Get outta here!
Can't take care of yourself?
Got to give your
a little butt a Tampax.
Mmm.
Damn.
Every time I have trouble
in my house,
I see your ugly face.
Now, what the hell
happened here?
Bad drugs.
Oh, you're a funny guy, huh?
Let's see how funny you are
with a week in the hole!
A week?
Is that the best you've got?
You want more? You got it, mister.
I was in a hole once for 3,000 years.
This should be a breeze.
You're a fuckin' nut case.
I'm gonna take care of you.
Now, get his ass outta here!
Stuff his ass in the hole!
"According to legend,
an all-powerful Djinn
"laid waste to the court of Persia.
"As he prepared to scourge the earth
"and usurp the world for his own,
the king's alchemist created
the Stone of the Secret Fire."
"By incantation, the alchemist
imprisoned the Djinn
within the fire-red opal."
Fire-red opal.
"Lest the Djinn escape
again and bring on the apocalypse,
the god Ahura Mazda was enlisted
to guard the stone."
Oh, man.
"Guard the stone and keep the Djinn trapped
within the space between the worlds."
I mean, I feel like
lam losing my mind.
I mean, the article on the Net says
there's this Stone of the Secret Fire
with this, Genie... this Djinn thing
locked inside it.
And it's guarded by this god,
Ahura Mazda.
Okay, well, I found the jewel
inside a statue of Ahura Mazda.
The jewel broke on my body.
Is that what Demarest meant
when he said I woke him?
I mean, from what?
From inside some stone?
And when I asked Demarest
who he was,
I got this... this flash...
of this hell
and this... this thing,
this Djinn, staring at me.
I mean, either this whole thing
is some kind of weird delusion,
in which case
I'm not sure I'm standing here,
or this guy is for real.
Well, in this flash,
how do you know this thing
you saw was a Djinn?
Because it looked just like
the thing in the article.
The one pictured in the article you read?
- No, wait a minute, Greg...
- No, no. The only reason I'm asking because
you've been under a lot of stress
since Eric's death.
No, you didn't see this guy.
You didn't sit across the table from him
and look in his eyes and see...
I don't even know
how to describe it.
Maybe if you'd...
Forget it. Forget it.
No. No.
Maybe I should.
Open three!
Time's up, Demarest.
Let's go.
Front and center.
Get him outta here.
Who are you?
Who do you think I am?
Leave her alone.
Is that your wish?
I'm not askin' you. I'm tellin' you.
Leave her alone.
Like you left her alone, Father?
I know how you feel.
I'd like to get my hands
on that cute little ass myself.
You won't succeed.
Who's gonna stop me?
God will stop you.
God has nothing to do with this.
God has everything
to do with this.
Begone, Satan!
I think you have your demons
mixed up, Father.
Gregory, I want you. Gregory.
Tell Morgana I'll be in touch.
Gregory?
Gregory, are you okay?
He's not of this world.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
"First the Djinn must gather 1,001 souls,
"this being the Assyrian number
for the apocalypse.
"He does this by the granting of a wish.
"The souls are held
in a kind of purgatory
"until the requisite number are attained,
or the Djinn fails,
"in which case the souls are freed.
"Should the Djinn succeed,
he must then find the human
"who woke him into this world
"and grant him three wishes.
"Upon the granting of the third wish,
"the Djinn may now bring forth
his race into our reality
"and overwhelm humanity,
as prophesied by the ancients."
Fulfill the prophecy.
You asked me before
if I believed in the devil.
I do now.
So you think it's true.
If it isn't, thank God.
If it is...
God help us.
You know, I couldn't figure out
why he'd want to go to prison.
Especially with all this power he has.
A lot of wishing going on in there.
He's just biding his time,
collecting his souls.
1,001 and then it's my turn.
All right.
What are we gonna do?
Hmm.
Augh!
- Okay!
- Uh... All right.
Here.
Thanks. I don't know
what I'm gonna do,
but you've got to avoid
Demarest at all costs.
Yeah, well, that...
- Okay.
- May not be possible.
Well, whatever you do,
please don't wish for anything.
All right, that should be easy.
Is there a 12-step program
for wish-aholics?
Yeah, it's called faith.
No. No, I brought him
into this world,
and I damn well
better get him out.
The book says he can only
be returned to his own realm
by someone who's...
Pure.
All right! So I got a little bit
of a problem there.
Gonna have to work on it.
Hmm.
Well, I'll tell you what.
You work on it from your end,
and I'll work on it from mine.
Purify my soul.
Forgive me, Father,
for I have sinned.
Do a couple more reps.
Why are you so quiet today,
my friend?
Running out of customers?
It appears I've exhausted
my consumer base.
Oh. So the rest of those morons
are not so stupid that they look.
On the contrary, they're more stupid
than you can imagine.
Checkmate.
Well, time to blow
this Popsicle stand.
Amazing! I woke up
with the same idea.
Shall we go, then?
Oh, yes. Sure. How?
Walk out the front gate.
Just like that?
Yes.
- All you have to do is wish it.
- You said I get two wishes. Remember?
You make a wish.
I get your soul.
After that, we'll see.
To be continued.
- Get your butt out of here.
- Sorry, sir.
You're a naughty little girl.
You hear what I'm sayin'?
And Daddy gonna teach
you some respect!
This is my house.
And ever since you been here,
there's been nothin' but trouble.
There's been four murders.
There's been an increase of contraband.
There's been a lack of discipline.
You're not foolin' me, man!
You think this shit's funny?
I got a place here called "hell"
that'll make your week in the hole
like a walk in the park.
- Been there.
- Oh, you think you're a tough guy.
When I close them doors,
I'm gonna have you cryin' for your mama
like a little bitch.
Sounds great, sir,
but I've made other plans.
You just got a month in hell.
I'm gonna keep you there till the rats
eat your damn eyes out.
Is that your wish, sir?
That's my order.
- I tell you what my wish is.
- I'm all ears.
I wish I could slow dance with you
for one minute, alone, Compton style.
Done.
Oh, my God.
Shall we dance?
Krutchkov.
Yes, sir!
Krutchkov, how badly do you
wanna leave this prison?
No, sir. I am happy here.
Yes. I am happy.
Everything is fine, you know?
American prison is the best
in the world.
ls it your
wish to blow this Popsicle stand?
Demarest?
Make your wish.
Are you fucking too much?
Yes.
Open sesame.
Morgana!
My God.
What happened to your hand?
I had to cast out my own devils first.
Look, he escaped.
What! When?
This morning. I think he has all the souls.
ls that why he got out?
I don't know, maybe he needs more
and can't find any takers.
A thousand's a pretty big number.
Yeah, well, not big enough.
You know, all the books say that
when the apocalypse is very near,
the nature of the world will change.
I haven't seen that yet.
I don't think anything
this guy does is random.
- Tell me. How did he escape?
- They don't know yet.
This guard was killed.
He was mutilated.
He left with this other guy,
this Russian man...
Wait wait wait.
- A Russian. What was his name?
- I don't know.
You know what, It's gotta be
in the papers by now.
Here it is. Osip Krutchkov.
I know that name.
Krutchkov. He murdered
two men in my parish.
Wait, what, he lives here?
I... I can't say. I just... I
used to hang out at this club...
Um, Siberia. Club Siberia.
- Wait, the place on Third.
- Yeah.
Hey! Hey!
My droog Nathaniel! Here!
Drink.
- No, thank you.
- Come on.
What the hell
kind of devil are you?
You know, he's the devil,
this son of a bitch.
He can give you
anything that you want.
Money, Pavel?
Hmm? Huh?
You want...
You want a big dick,
my little friend Misha?
Huh? You want it?
He can give it to you.
Get out of here.
Get out, I told you!
Misha, I said to get out of here!
This fuckin' son of bitch!
Get out of here!
Nothing. Just...
You speak Russian.
Why are you so afraid
of Pushkin?
Everybody is afraid of Pushkin.
He's a big boss.
I despise Pushkin!
Make me big boss.
Get rid of this fucking Pushkin.
I wish I want to be big boss.
You've already had your wish.
One more, please.
Sorry.
There are rules
not even I can break.
Come with me.
Please. Come.
Mmm.
Is this true?
Absolutely.
Just ask.
Why?
What you get from this?
The pleasure of seeing you
achieve your end.
You are the most
interesting character.
Yes, I am.
- There is nothing I need.
- Surely there's something you want.
Fame, fortune, power.
Fortune and power I already have.
Fame I don't need.
Excuse me.
Maybe a woman you couldn't get.
Some object of great value.
Perhaps you'd like an enemy
to disappear.
I don't need you for that.
You're wasting my time.
Moustafa!
I told you! Never mention his name
in my presence!
Nathaniel can get to him, really.
Somebody who's offended you.
Someone you can't touch.
Moustafaranski's gang out of Chechnya.
What could you do against Moustafa?
Anything you wish.
I want his head.
Can you do this?
Consider it done.
Moustafa!
Get out of here!
I'll kill you, motherfucker!
Take him out of here.
Moustafa! Moustafa!
I did it!
On his Wish I did it! Ha-ha!
Ah, now I am the boss,
number one!
What?
I got what I want.
You get what you want.
- And what would that be?
- One more soul.
One more soul?
I need 800 more souls,
and I'm growing impatient.
Oh, wait, wait.
Go on the street and take them.
You're powerful.
I can only act
when I'm wished to do so,
but that will change very soon.
My droog Nathaniel, wait.
You need souls.
I have such a great place for you.
Lovely to see you again, Morgana.
Did you really think
you could kill me?
Evil never dies.
Perhaps there is something else you desire.
Your dead friend Eric alive again.
No.
There will come a time, soon,
when I will call upon you
to fulfill the prophecy...
you who woke me.
Three wishes you will make.
Then my kingdom
will reign on this earth.
For now,
this wish I give you freely
so you may know its joy.
Tell me your desire, child.
I shall grant it.
No!
Souls, Krutchkov.
I need souls.
God, forgive me.
God forgives all sin.
Some sins are too great,
even for God.
No sin is too great
for his forgiveness.
I killed an innocent man.
I left two children fatherless.
I have blood on my hands
I can never wash out.
The blood of the Lamb
can cleanse all sins.
No, not mine!
I brought him into this world.
And I'm too weak.
I'm too impure to get him out.
I pray to God for forgiveness,
but I can't hear his voice.
Morgana, listen to me.
It's in God's hands.
If it's His will
that you serve him, so be it.
I saw his true face.
The face of God?
The Djinn.
I found Demarest and...
I tried to kill him.
My God.
And when I shot him,
he changed.
Those pictures of the Djinn...
there's no way to fight him.
For us, no.
For God, through us...
Hey! Come in.
It's okay.
A priest can't do you
any good, girlie.
He's gone.
Where?
I'm afraid I can't
tell you that, Father.
Why not?
What are you afraid of?
I made a pledge.
You made a pledge?
You sit before God, and you tell me
you made a pledge
with this... this evil?
I don't see God in this room.
I just see a poor priest...
and a pathetic little girl.
You want to save the world?
I show you how to save the world!
Just... Just put the gun down.
If she's dead, she can't
wish this world into hell.
- He's right.
- No! Put the gun down.
No, it's the only way to stop him.
I can't let you!
Put the gun down.
Aah!
No!
There's nothing there.
Oh, he has other plans for you.
How many souls?
How many souls does he have?
Did he say?
You made a wish, right?
You want to spend eternity
in his hell?
Then help us!
Help yourself!
He said he needs 800 more.
- That gives us some time, right?
- Yeah.
Not where he's going.
I understand
you'll be representing our
Eastern European partners
while you're out here.
Yes, indeed. Quite so.
Do you have any experience
in the, uh, gaming industry, Mr. Demarest?
Oh, yes.
- Whoo!
- Congratulations, Tex.
Thank you, partner.
Yeah, we like folks to win.
Anything that encourages
our other guests to bet is good for us.
Since the house
has the advantage,
eventually they all lose.
Now, what a wonderful business.
Yeah, we like to think so.
In fact, you might say
the casino wishes everyone
the best of luck.
The casino wishes
everyone the best of luck?
- Most assuredly.
- How nice.
Mr. and Mrs. Lee.
How are you?
How's the suite?
Gimme them bones, gimme them bones.
Baby needs a new pair of shoes.
Come on, seven. Come on, seven!
Come on, seven!
Yeah!
Ka-Ching.
Hello?
This is Osip Krutchkov.
I am so sorry. I must talk to you.
What do you want?
You must go to him
before he gets all his souls.
I have purchased you a ticket.
Please, I beg you.
You must go, now.
Yeah, right.
I also need one
for Father Gregory.
Both
tickets will be waiting at the airport.
Goodbye, Morgana, and thank you.
This is it, Gregory.
Do you really think we can do this?
Yeah.
It says here that the king's
alchemist from Persia
got the Djinn back into the gem
through an incantation.
Now, what incantation?
"And as it was prophesied, the alchemist
took the stone unto his hand,
"as a woman pure of heart takes
the light of God unto her soul,
"and spoke the words
Nib sugaroth baheim,
upon which the Djinn was again
imprisoned within the opal." there it is.
All right, so you figure if you just
say those words, um...
Nib sugaroth baheim.
Yeah, the Djinn is just
gonna disappear?
Yeah... no... well, yeah... I mean
he goes back inside the opal.
But if the king's alchemist can do it,
then so can we. Why can't we?
Because he knew
what he was doing.
At least you're pure of heart.
Look, Gregory,
the world as we know it
is about to come to an end,
and you're gonna stop the Djinn
by using a quotation
from a book you bought
at the Spell-Checker?
What else have we got?
Morgana, I really don't think
this is the way to heaven.
Don't be too sure.
Magic.
What the fuck is goin' on?
I don't know, Mr. Farralon.
All right, dealer. Let's see what you got!
Come on! Let's see what you got!
Go ahead!
Yeah!
I claim that which is owed.
Fulfill the prophecy.
Morgana, what is it?
What is it?
Aah!
It's over.
He has all the souls.
If we stay calm,
no one will get hurt.
We all wanted
something for nothing.
And that's what they got.
All right, it's showtime.
Let's go.
Three wishes, Morgana,
and I shall reign.
Come in.
I trust you didn't find the disturbance
downstairs too upsetting.
Is that what you have in mind
if your kingdom comes?
Well, you know what
they say, Father.
"What goes around comes around."
Do you like to gamble?
Depends on what's at stake.
Anything you wish.
The casino would be happy
to offer you unlimited credit
to play the game of your choice.
I have a feeling
you'll do very well.
I can feel it.
Matter of fact,
I can guarantee it.
Save your games
for the people downstairs.
Hm.
So you want me
to make a wish?
Three, to be exact.
All right.
I wish...
you were gone forever!
Poof!
Hmm.
Still here.
A wish cannot change
that which is eternal.
Please wish again.
You can do better.
I wish... I wish you back into
the Stone of the Secret Fire.
I see you've done your homework.
Unfortunately for you,
it's not that easy.
After all,
I am the Wishmaster here.
So any wishes pertaining to me
are circumscribed by the prophecy.
Nib sugaroth baheim.
So, we have done our homework.
Do not play with forces
you don't understand,
or you will suffer
the consequences.
You don't frighten us.
God's already sent you
once back to hell.
Oh, please.
Not that old story again.
Hell is your world, not mine.
In God's name, I command
you out of this world.
I wish you into hell, Demarest.
Gotcha.
Welcome to my world, Morgana.
Where's Gregory?
Where he's always wanted to be.
Behold the man.
What good is your faith now?
What have you done?
Nothing that can't be undone, child.
Just ask.
Let him go.
Let him go, please.
Is that your wish?
No.
Then watch him suffer.
Aah!
I wish you to release him.
Done.
Gregory!
Oh, God! Gregory!
Oh, God.
You said you'd release him!
And so I shall.
Gregory?
You bastard!
Two more wishes.
Go fuck yourself in hell.
Make your wishes.
Never.
You tax my patience, child.
I wish there was no evil
in the world.
Evil is the half
of a perfect sphere.
- Try again.
- Tell me how to stop you!
We've been through all that.
You're wasting my time now,
and you're pissing me off!
Make your wish!
Fulfill the prophecy.
All right. I understand.
You've had a tough day.
Hmm.
I can see how
this could get a little depressing
in here, couldn't it?
This place isn't exactly...
happy-
I know.
What we need is a more
wish-provoking environment.
Ross.
Can you believe this?
First a run on the house.
Now 200 people drop dead
all at once?
- What's next? Frogs and locusts?
- Could be.
- We're finished!
- Not yet, Ross.
What we need is some more action.
Good for business.
Come on. Don't you wish we had
some real action?
No! No, don't!
- Who's she?
- An acquaintance.
Don't listen to him.
He's the devil.
So, what do you say, Ross?
No, don't say anything.
It's a trick.
You know, Nathaniel,
I think I've had about all the action
that I can handle.
I just wish I could see this nightmare
come to an end.
No!
Hurry up! Help!
Look out!
Get out!
This place is damned!
Everyone out!
Too bad.
You just crapped out.
Ahh.
"Ooh!
Do you wish to see more?
- No.
- Then end it.
Make your wishes.
I don't even know
what to ask for.
Ask for your heart's desires.
A million dollars?
A bird's nest?
To see your lover priest
one last time?
You said, "Fulfill the prophecy."
what prophecy?
I have no more time, child.
You told me I'd know the answer
when the time was right.
It is written,
"that one who wakes the Djinn
"shall have three wishes.
"Upon granting all three,
the race of Djinn
shall inherit the earth."
And as was prophesied,
"the alchemist took the stone
unto his hand,
"as a woman pure of heart takes
the light of God unto her soul,
"and spoke the words,
Nib sugaroth baheim."
I wish the man I shot
was alive again.
Done.
- Ah.
- Daddy! Daddy!
That's good.
Nib sugaroth baheim.
Nib sugaroth baheim!
Gregory, he's gone.