You're available
to start right away?
Yes.
I'm not really seeing
a lot of restaurant experience
on the résumé.
I've always had,
um, summer jobs,
but, yeah, mostly retail.
So did you drop out
of school, or...
Why'd you come
all the way back here?
No...
Well, this is my home,
and there was an accident,
so I have to take care
of my brother.
Well, I'll tell you
what I can do...
I'll talk to the owner.
I know they were looking for,
waitstaff with experience,
but...
obviously you're smart,
so maybe they'll,
work with you, so...
Sure, that'd be...
that'd be great.
Maybe you could do...
host, if nothing else.
Oh, sure, definitely.
Okay, I mean,
I can't promise anything, but...
- Oh, no, yeah.
- Maybe.
I'll let you know
by the end of the day.
Thank you so much.
Nice to meet you.
Nice meeting you.
I can make you some eggs
if you want.
Yeah, I can make 'em too.
I'm gonna go back to the clinic
for a little while today.
Will you be okay here alone?
Something wrong?
Dr. Barden thinks that
he can help us
cut some of the costs.
How?
I... I have no idea,
but I'll find out.
So there'll probably be
some of this... yeah?
Yeah, probably.
Thank you.
Thank you both.
Dr. Barden?
The nurse said that I...
Of course, come in.
Iris, good to see you.
Hi.
Iris, Shepard Lambrick.
Iris.
Dr. Barden's told me
much about you.
Iris, please, have a seat.
Shepard.
So...
Your brother.
He's quite sick, correct?
You can help him?
Well, let's just say
that my foundation
has the ability
to improve his situation.
The Lambricks have funded
the building of clinics
all over the world,
Haiti, Afghanistan...
Schools too.
Well, my brother
doesn't need a school.
You're right.
Absolutely right.
Because we're not
talking about that today.
Not at all.
My family also believes in
creating opportunities for...
everyday people,
people who just haven't
received a fair shake in life,
people like you
and your brother.
What do we have to do?
I'm hosting a dinner party
tomorrow night,
and I'd like you to join us.
Just me?
Just you.
But there will be
other guests there,
individuals that
we'd also like to help,
and the evening will culminate
with a game of sorts,
and the winner...
will be taken care of.
Bills, school, house...
everything.
A contest.
What if I don't win?
Well, then you just don't win.
That's it.
I'm sorry, Dr. Barden, I...
no offense to Mr. Lambrick,
but is this legit?
This is for real?
Very real, Iris.
Mr. Lambrick saved my life.
Not long ago,
but before I met
you and your brother,
I was in the same position.
I'd already lost my wife.
I was on my way
to losing everything...
this practice, everything.
I had no place to turn.
I was invited to this event,
so I went.
You won?
He did, and I am proud to say
that the Lambrick Foundation
came through on its promise.
Tenfold.
You see what we might be able
to do for you.
Well, money
would definitely help,
but my brother needs
a bone marrow transplant.
So do you mind
if I think this over?
It's just...
Short notice.
It is. You're right.
Of course, yes.
Think it over.
Do that.
Well...
But RSVP by 8:00 tonight
if you do decide to join us.
And my staff will make
arrangements to pick you up.
Thank you.
When I say
that we have the ability
to dramatically improve
your brother's situation, Iris,
it's not just the money
I'm talking about.
You win the game,
and we can bypass
any waiting list
and locate a donor immediately.
I will let you know.
Thank you.
She's perfect.
This is the special du jour.
It's pasta à la vegetable...
Okay.
Iris, that's a terrible
Italian accent.
And if it's French,
"monsieur" is not pronounced
"man sewer."
- Monsieur.
- Yes.
Come on, seriously, like,
it's not gonna kill me
to have some protein
now and then.
Hello?
Speaking.
Okay, well, wait,
what about the hostess position
that you...
Okay, well, thank you.
Thanks again.
You mad at me or something?
Why would I be mad at you?
I thought I would be a match.
I feel like I let you down.
You can't always be the hero.
Sometimes you have to let go.
Like let go of you?
Get down! Get down!
Give me cover!
Killing lots of aliens?
Nope, terrorists.
Killing lots of terrorists?
Straight up murderin'
these terrorists, yo.
What's up?
So, I'm gonna go out tonight.
With who?
I... I ran into a couple
friends from high school,
and I thought, you know what?
I should go and unwind.
Yeah, let your hair down
and shit.
Yeah, just go crazy.
Yeah, cool.
So you're gonna be okay here
alone for the night?
Yeah.
Got my meds, emergency contact.
I'll just play video games
or whatever.
I could really use the quiet.
Great.
Cool.
Love you.
Aren't you sick of this?
Taking me back and forth
to the clinic,
bills, taking care of me.
Like, don't you want a life?
No.
I mean, yeah, I...
It's hard,
but, Raleigh,
you're my brother.
This is my life.
It's gonna be fine.
We'll get through this.
This way, please.
Thank you.
Pretty.
Yes.
Does the Lambrick family
live here?
Not exactly.
Property's owned
by the foundation.
It's used for holidays
and special events like this.
Dinner will begin shortly.
You can wait in here
with all the other guests,
and please help yourself to any
of the provided refreshments.
Our eighth and final guest.
Lucky number eight.
Did everyone get
an introduction like that?
Oh, yeah.
It's been very formal.
It's nice to meet you guys.
I'm Iris.
Lucas, and this is...
Cal. How you doin'?
Hi.
Have you guys been here long?
Not long.
Couple minutes for some.
Hour or two for the rest of us.
Are you both from the area too?
No, they flew me in
from Seattle.
Iowa.
Would you like
a little something to drink?
No, I'm okay. Not yet.
So what do you know
about the others?
Anything?
A little.
As you can see,
they're not exactly gregarious.
Big guy over there is Peter.
Supposed to be some sort of
high-stakes gambler from Vegas.
Not that any of us
have actually heard of him.
That's the way
he made it sound.
Yeah.
Lady in the wheelchair
is Linda.
She barely speaks.
Kid in the corner is Travis.
He's an Iraq vet.
And he's got
that thousand-yard stare.
What about the girl?
Her name is Amy,
and, yeah,
she's a real charmer.
And the older gentleman?
I don't think
I'd call him that.
"Older"?
"Gentleman."
Why?
Conway's a bit of a sourpuss.
Yeah, he's...
he has some conspiracy theories
about the Lambrick Foundation.
Don't get him started.
Maybe I will have a drink.
Good.
My very own specialty: BLT.
Thank you.
To the Lambrick Foundation.
Salud.
She's perfect.
Case?
I'm not sure
she's right for this.
What?
She couldn't be more perfect.
She's fighting for her brother,
herself.
She has no relatives,
no family,
no one to ask questions.
Shep, she is not right.
Let's just say
I've appreciated your discretion
over the last couple of years.
Should I be concerned
about this moment of weakness
on your part?
Of course not.
I'm fine.
Bevans has informed me
that the last guest has arrived.
We ought to get downstairs soon.
Do we have to sit through
an entire dinner?
Why can't we just
get it over with?
Julian...
That's not the way it works,
as you know.
There is a process involved.
Of course.
I trust that you will be
on your best behavior tonight.
I'm not even drinking.
I'm serious.
The integrity of the game
requires minimal participation
on our part.
You must remain
an objective observer,
even if one of these people
is eliminated.
Do you understand?
And if one of them
has to be removed from the game,
Bevans will be the one
to handle it.
Your job, as a Lambrick,
is simply to observe.
You can engage these people
with questions and conversation,
but you will
not so much as touch
any of these people tonight.
I know.
Julian,
look, I appreciate
that you've taken an interest
in the foundation.
I do.
But what happened last year
was unacceptable.
For the last time,
I understand.
Okay, okay, okay.
I won't bring it up again.
And you're underdressed again.
We have one small matter
to clear up before we begin.
In the interest of discretion
and eliminating distraction
and unfair advantage,
we ask that you leave
all possessions here
during the game...
phones, keys, et cetera.
I don't like this.
I don't like it.
I assure you they will be safe.
These are the rules.
Right.
If you're ready,
I'll escort you
through to the dining room.
This way.
Please, take a seat.
Place cards have been provided.
Thank you.
Of course.
And good evening, everyone.
I apologize
if I've kept anyone waiting.
Welcome to the Lambrick house.
This is my son, Julian.
Hello.
Now, you've all met
our butler, Bevans,
and his staff, yes?
Bevans...
Let's start with some wine,
shall we?
Dinner tonight
is seared foie gras
and rib eye steak
with a red wine reduction
served with asparagus
and garlic leek mashed potato.
Enjoy.
Haven't had a meal like this
in so long.
Never had a meal like this.
You kidding me?
Yes?
I probably should have
mentioned this before.
I'm a vegetarian.
Well, this is interesting.
We don't have anything else
in the kitchen, Iris.
Okay.
I...I don't mean to be a bother.
The potatoes are fine.
I'll be fine.
So have you always
been a vegetarian?
Most of my life, yes.
Long time.
- I just can't imagine eating...
- I think...
That we have just found
our first opportunity
to award some money tonight.
Iris.
I would like for you to eat
the steak and the foie gras.
I really would.
I can't do that.
You can...
but you won't...
yet.
No, I really... I can't do it.
I'm not trying to be rude.
I just...I won't do it.
Listen, I understand
that it's not going to be easy,
but I refuse to accept...
that you don't have a price.
$5,000 to eat the steak
and this decadent foie gras.
Make it $10,000.
$10,000.
What could you do with that?
You should eat it.
Just close your eyes.
It's a lot of money.
Eat it with some of the liver.
I can't believe I'm doing this.
Yeah, for $10,000, though.
A lifetime of discipline
and commitment to cause
wiped away by a mere $10,000.
Well...
That is nothing
compared to what's
really at stake tonight.
I can assure you of that.
You don't like the wine?
Well, no, it's not that.
We can get you something else.
We have some wonderful scotch.
No. No, thanks. I don't drink.
Oh, I see.
You're a recovering alcoholic.
Aren't you?
That's not your business.
On the contrary.
You are here essentially
begging me for money.
How is that not my business?
How long has it been?
It's been 16 years,
and I turned everything
in my life around.
But you haven't.
Look at you.
You're still mired in a pit
of poor health
and crippling debt.
I'd hate to see what
you looked like 16 years ago.
I mean, really.
What's the point?
Please.
Why are you doing this?
Because I want to help you.
Look...
It's safe to say that drinking
is what ruined your life
in the first place, isn't it?
So what if
drinking again
could help you save it?
What?
I will give you $10,000
if you drink
that glass of wine.
No.
No. No way. No.
You don't understand.
You have no idea
how hard I've worked.
But Iris here,
she just devoured
a pile of meat,
and she's a devout vegetarian,
and you won't drink
a little wine?
It's totally different.
Why are you doing this to me?
$50,000.
If you will drink...
This decanter
of the finest scotch
that money can buy
right now.
$50,000.
This is what, a test?
This is not real.
Oh, no...
I am deadly serious, Conway,
and you know that I am.
The glass of wine
or the whole damn decanter.
Now, it seems to me
that the wine,
that's pretty simple,
isn't it?
But the scotch...
Well, we could consider that...
A momentary lapse to...
Change your life.
I'm sorry.
So what would you rather do?
That's a good man.
Hey.
Bevans.
That was brilliant, as usual.
My compliments to Marcel.
Regarding tonight's game,
please allow me to alleviate
any concerns you have.
We haven't already
been playing?
Oh, no, the game has yet
to officially begin.
What exactly is the game?
Well, it is not a quiz
or a trivia contest,
nor is it a test of
brute strength or athleticism.
At its core,
it's just a children's game,
and I would wager
that some of you
here this evening
have played "Would You Rather?"
at some point.
So how do we play?
In each round, each player
will be given a choice
between A or B,
and usually,
neither choice
is very attractive.
Let's see if I can
give you an example.
Travis.
Travis, would you rather...
kiss Iris
or...
Peter?
- Guess I'd kiss Iris.
- Very good.
Now, this is where our version
of the game is different.
Whatever you choose,
you must act upon.
So in this case,
Travis, you must walk over
and kiss Iris.
You're gonna make us
kiss each other?
No, no, no.
Nothing like that, my dear.
No, that was just
off the top of my head.
Now, as the game continues
with one dilemma after another,
eliminating players as we go
until we have a winner.
And how are players eliminated?
Well, if a player
is no longer capable
of continuing,
for whatever reason,
then they are eliminated.
What if someone refuses
to make a choice?
Like, if Travis didn't want
to kiss either of us?
If you refuse to choose.
Well, I am afraid
that that would be grounds
for elimination.
And one more thing.
The dilemmas are timed.
And you must make your decision
in 15 seconds,
or you will be eliminated.
Hold up. Is all this necessary?
I mean, couldn't you
help all of us?
Why does this have to be
a game?
Because,
as simple as the game is,
it's all about decision making
in its rawest form.
And there's no better window
into a person's character
than the decisions
that they make
and how they make them
and how one applies
rationale and ethics and reason
while under duress.
Tonight...
Will test your limits
and ultimately prove...
whether you deserve our help.
If anyone no longer
wishes to play,
now is your opportunity
to leave.
We have cars waiting outside.
Anyone?
All right.
We have a full house.
And so...
Here...
we...
go.
Our man Bevans,
ladies and gentlemen.
Did you know he was formerly
an agent with MI5?
Many years ago.
An interrogator.
Is this one of your old toys,
Bevans?
It is, sir.
Car batteries with some
aftermarket configurations.
What... what the hell is this?
Oh, no.
I see where this is going.
Conway?
I knew this was too good
to be true.
This is a joke.
You just want to hurt us.
You people,
are you gonna sit here,
and you're gonna let this sick,
perverted son of a bitch
debase you?
Be my guest.
Someone's had
a little too much to drink.
That's right!
That's right,
and I'm going home.
No, you've already
been given that chance.
I don't care!
I'm done with this!
You were warned.
You go to hell,
you sick motherfucker!
I would like to go home.
Well, obviously,
participation
is no longer voluntary.
I believe we just made that
perfectly clear.
Bevans, shall we?
What's this?
What are we doing?
Cal, you're up first.
So, Cal,
would you rather...
electrocute yourself,
or would you rather
electrocute Amy?
The blue button is for you.
Press the red button
if you'd rather zap Amy.
And you have...
15 seconds to decide,
beginning now.
- W-wait.
- Wait.
- Stop, stop, don't push it.
- Wait, Bevans...
Okay, wait, wait, stop.
Don't push the button.
Moving on.
You're not serious.
No! Oh, no!
- Oh, come on!
- Blue is for Linda.
No, no, no, no, no, please!
Amy.
You're next.
Would you rather
electrocute yourself or...
Wait...
Take it easy!
We're competing, right?
No timer needed.
Linda.
Linda!
Bevans, is she ready?
Linda.
Can you hear me?
Your turn.
I can't do this.
Well, you have to do it, Linda.
You must make a decision.
It's the game.
Red is for Peter.
I don't think
I can do this either.
All right.
What was that?
Christ.
Would you rather
electrocute yourself,
again,
or shock Peter?
15 seconds.
Fuck!
Well done, both of you.
Next.
Are you okay?
Stall 'em.
- Are you okay?
- I can do one more.
- What?
- Just stall 'em.
I'm not gonna shock you.
Iris.
What have you seen
in the last ten minutes
that leads you to believe
you don't have to perform
in this round?
Keep... still.
Much better.
Red is for Iris.
Now, Lucas,
what would you rather do?
Red is for Cal.
Iris, would you rather
electrocute yourself
or Cal for the second time?
You do what you got to do.
Go.
That's an interesting choice.
Right.
Well done, everyone.
Very well done.
Now...
I'm gonna give you a moment,
all,
to compose yourselves
while we prepare
for the next round.
Listen, we just need a moment,
some kind of distraction.
If we all move at once,
we can overpower 'em.
It seems like
they're all packing,
so that's not much of a plan.
If we can disarm one,
I can shoot.
That'll even the odds
pretty fucking quick.
What about the doors?
They have us locked in.
I saw a couple of 'em
with sets of keys.
Here comes another set
right now.
Hi, everyone.
The game's getting pretty
intense already, right?
Why are you doing this?
"Why are you doing this?"
You're fucking crazy.
You know...
you agreed to be here.
You're basically asking
my family for a handout.
The least you could do, pig,
is show a little
fucking respect.
Psycho little bitch.
Excuse me, what?
You heard me, bitch.
I'm sorry, we didn't get
formally introduced.
Well, now we have.
How about you show us
a little respect?
Stop.
What's your name?
Name, pig! What's your name?
- Travis Schulke!
- Okay, Travis.
Travis,
you're the soldier, right?
Well, allow me to thank you
for your bravery
and your service.
Really.
But yeah, that said...
Opening your mouth
was a big mistake.
Easy, easy.
So...
Cover the walls and the...
area around the table.
Wait. What are you guys doing?
That was incredibly stupid,
Travis.
I will fuck that guy up
if I get the chance.
But you won't.
Cool it.
They want us
to turn on each other.
If we stay logical,
we can turn the tables on 'em.
She's on her own.
Look around you.
Yeah, we're fucked.
And so we begin again.
Does anyone need to use
the restroom or anything?
I'm just joking.
I know you're probably all
just as eager
to keep playing as we are.
Now, in this round,
you will each get 30 seconds
in order to make your decision,
all right?
So let's begin with...
Iris.
Iris, would you rather...
Stab Cal in the thigh
with an ice pick...
What?
Or...
strike Travis three times
with this
African whipping staff,
a sjambok?
Oh, my God.
They're gonna kill us!
Look, Iris,
three whacks from that,
I'll be okay.
If I stab him,
I could kill him, right?
And it's only three.
It's gonna hurt, though, man.
I know.
Let's just get it over with.
The clock is ticking.
Sjambok it is.
Now, Iris,
you have to put
your back into this?
There's no just tapping him.
That doesn't count.
And Travis,
this is going to hurt,
so make yourself comfortable.
Like this, ma'am.
Across the back.
Travis?
Go ahead, Iris.
No. No, no, no, no, no.
That won't count.
Fuck.
All right.
That looked like it hurt,
Travis.
Well, it did.
Are you okay?
I've been through worse.
Lucas.
You're next.
Would you rather
stab Iris in the thigh...
Or...
Give Travis three more strikes?
Oh, come on!
Look, it's a really dangerous
place to stab somebody.
There's a major artery there.
You know what I'm saying?
I do.
Let's just get it over with.
The sjambok again.
Sorry, man.
Travis...
You're probably relieved
to find out
that it's your turn.
Something like that.
All right, then.
Let's get it over with.
Travis...
Would you rather...
Stab Lucas,
the man who just whipped you,
or...
drumroll, please...
Take three more lashes,
this time
administered by Bevans?
Ser...seriously, man.
I can't...
I can't do this anymore.
I wonder why
you're being singled out.
What the fuck is the matter
with you people?
What did I ever do to you,
What?
That's... that's what I thought.
Travis, we need a decision.
Yeah.
Yeah, fucking whip.
I'm not stabbing anybody.
We have to stop this.
We have to.
Yeah, wait.
Wait, stop...stop.
Travis, just stab me
in the thigh, okay?
We can't watch this go on.
I'm not stabbing anybody.
Travis, come on.
Lucas, this is admirable,
but it's against the rules.
But I'm okay with it.
He can't go back.
His first choice is final.
Just hold on a second.
I said I'm okay with it!
It's okay.
Come on.
- Lucas.
- It's okay.
This is all very admirable.
His decision.
It's okay.
It's just like life, isn't it?
There's no do-overs.
Travis, Travis, Travis, Travis.
Hey, hey, hey.
He's in trouble.
He needs medical attention.
Peter...
I'm awfully sorry,
but I'm afraid it's your turn.
You know the drill by now.
The pick
or give Travis three more.
If I do the pick,
who does it have to be?
I'm sure you've already
worked the angles on that one,
haven't you?
Well...
I don't want to stab a lady.
I'm not Mr. Manners
or anything,
but I think there's some common
decency considerations here.
30 seconds.
On the other hand,
Travis is in real bad shape.
We can't really hit him anymore,
can we?
Honestly, Linda,
you're paralyzed, right?
Your leg wouldn't feel this
anyway.
No, please.
If I whip him with this thing,
he's going to die.
And haven't we all
been saying this whole time
that we have to work together?
Well, unfortunately,
you're gonna have to take one
for the team, Linda.
I'm sorry.
You're gonna be okay,
I promise.
Just close your eyes.
In and then out, okay?
Don't push it too far.
Fuck.
- Oh, shit.
- Holy crap.
I think I hit that artery.
Do you have a belt?
Tie it. Tie it. Hurry.
What happened?
You're okay. You're okay.
Can we not take her to
a hospital or something here?
This isn't good.
People, we're playing a game.
Linda, it's your turn.
Now, would you rather
whip Travis
or give your neighbor Amy
down there
the old in and out?
What?
Can we not give her a sec?
Peter, what's going on, man?
Is the tourniquet supposed
to go above or below the wound?
- Above, above!
- Okay, okay.
My God, tighten it!
- I got it. I got it.
- Tighter!
Linda has not
made a decision yet.
Linda!
Travis or...
Bitch!
You fucking scratched me.
Linda.
Stupendous.
But then, come to think of it,
she didn't have another choice.
She couldn't whip Travis
even if she wanted to.
She can't walk.
So let's...
change things up
a little bit here.
Amy...
Would you rather
whip Travis or...
Stab any player
of your choosing?
In case any of y'all
haven't figured this out yet,
this game isn't about
helpin' each other.
It's about eliminating
the rest of you.
Bevans...
This one's probably gonna
bleed to death.
You're okay.
Duck.
Goose.
Hey, hold on a second.
Okay, okay.
She's made her decision.
Don't do this.
Please don't do this.
Can I stab her anywhere?
Well, that's a new one.
Just from the shoulders down.
No!
Let me see. Let me see.
Can you breathe?
I think she missed the lung.
Put some pressure on it.
Can you breathe?
Tighter.
Tight.
Travis?
Bevans.
Still breathing, sir.
Remarkable.
Guys, she hasn't moved
for a while.
Stabbed an old woman, Peter.
Linda.
See, she's unconscious.
She's not unconscious.
She's dead.
You guys saw what happened,
right?
I tried to help her.
Oh, yes, Peter,
we all saw what happened.
You made a decision.
There was a consequence.
And now...
Cal is the one
to make a choice.
Finish off Travis here or...
stab Lucas.
Stab Lucas like the others?
Like Linda,
that's what you're saying?
30 seconds.
Okay, come on.
Let's get it over with.
Maybe Amy is right.
Eliminate a player.
That's what this is about.
No, Cal, Amy's crazy.
Well, maybe he wants
to end it too.
That's not your choice
to make, man.
But it is.
They're making it my choice.
Cal, come on, I'm giving you
an opening here!
Time.
Okay, I choose...
God, no, Cal. Don't do this.
- Don't do that.
- You can't do this.
No.
It's murder.
Don't look.
Oh, Jesus.
Nicely done.
And now...
On to the next round.
It had to be done, right?
Right?
You didn't have to do that.
So how long would you say?
He may live for several
more hours, days even.
I don't know.
But he's in no shape
to continue play.
That much is certain.
All right, let's move him out.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I regret to inform you
that Travis is unable
to continue playing.
Aww...
Do not do that.
Keep your sarcasm to yourself.
I'm thinking...
We don't have much time here
with these delays.
We have 21/2 hours left.
Is that enough for us to...
Can you run?
Now!
Iris, run.
Get back!
All right,
everyone back to the table.
Get up. Everyone, get up.
Julian, get up on your...
Back to your seats.
Well...
That was some unexpected
excitement, wasn't it?
Everyone sit down.
Where's Iris?
- What?
- Iris!
Bevans!
The door was unlocked?
Stay here! Keep an eye on them!
Bring her back to the game!
I should help him.
Fine, go, go.
Remember what we spoke about.
I believe I said sit down.
Little pig tried to run away,
didn't she?
What? You gonna go tell on us?
Well, no one
is gonna believe you, okay?
No one.
Iris.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
Get back.
I'm getting you out of here.
I made a mistake.
I should've just told...
Shoot her, Bevans!
She attacked me!
Your father
will be disappointed.
After all she did,
she doesn't get punished?
I need to take her back
to the game.
Take him upstairs
and leave him there.
I'll inform his father.
I'm sorry, Iris,
but we're not through playing.
Welcome back, Iris.
Bevans, what took so long?
Where's Julian?
Your son tried to rape Iris.
- She...
- What?
Stabbed him in the thigh.
He's been taken upstairs, sir.
Let me handle that.
Excuse me for a moment,
everyone.
Lock that behind me.
Where's Cal?
They shot him.
You gonna be okay, Iris?
Iris, talk to me.
How far did you get?
Is there a way out?
Do you all get it now?
They're not gonna let us
just leave.
She's right.
She's absolutely right.
Iris...
I am dreadfully sorry
for what took place
in the basement.
Since the loss of his mother,
my son lacks...
Restraint.
Well, please.
My apologies.
All right.
Let's continue.
That's it?
Why is this bitch allowed
to stay in the game?
You're lucky
you didn't get us all killed.
Crazy girl has a point.
This is my game.
I make the decisions here.
Keep your petulant mouth shut.
She will play.
The game will continue.
Final.
Now...
My son, Julian,
is unable to continue.
What a shame.
Excuse me?
Thank you.
So on to the next round.
Now,
when all of you were deciding
whether or not to accept
our invitation to play the game,
you were, in essence,
making a choice
between the known
and the unknown.
You could continue to deal
with your problems, the known,
or possibly solve your problems
in the unknown,
our game.
This round
uses that same concept.
What's this for?
Are you gonna let us clean up?
No, Peter. I'm sorry.
The barrel of water
is for the next round.
Envelopes are being placed
randomly in front of you.
They each contain a card
with a punishment on them...
some of them quite harsh,
others relatively harmless.
You must decide between
what lies inside the envelope
or the barrel.
The known or the unknown.
What's with the barrel?
Two minutes.
Two minutes held underwater.
That's the barrel.
And you will have 30 seconds
in this round
to make your decision.
Let's begin, shall we?
Peter.
Fuck.
We will begin with you.
So what will it be?
The barrel
or what is in that envelope?
Well, I already know
what I'm choosing.
Do you? Really?
Do tell.
This is gambling 101
right here.
You just got to look
for the patterns.
It's all patterns.
It's psychology.
And drowning
does sound pretty bad.
So I'm guessing you think
I'm gonna choose the envelope
to avoid Duggins
holding me underwater
for two minutes and drowning.
Is that it?
Bevans.
Whatever.
If you were facing
a normal player,
that's exactly what you'd do...
put something really shitty
in that envelope
so all the other players
think twice.
But I know you.
You've looked into my past.
So you know all about
my gambling experience.
So you probably
have anticipated
that I was gonna
figure this out.
Come on, come on, come on.
Make a decision.
Your time is running out.
The envelope.
Obviously.
And the envelope says?
What is this?
You have to light off
a firecracker in your hand.
That's it.
Good.
See?
Gambling 101.
Why are you
pointing a gun in my face?
I'm agreeing to this.
What the hell is this?
You have to light it, Peter.
It's what the envelope says.
But it's not a firecracker.
That's a quarter stick.
You know, you're right.
Maybe you ought to move away
from the table.
You're gonna make an awful mess.
Let it go before it goes off.
Don't hold it too tight.
No, he must hold it tight.
Bevans?
Secure it to his hand,
if you would, please.
Oh, fuck.
You know, Peter,
maybe it's a dud.
Did you think about that?
Did you consider that?
But, of course,
we won't know that
until you light the fuse.
Use the lighter!
And light the fuse!
Now!
If this is a dud,
do I have to go again?
Nah.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
- Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
That was loud.
We're lucky
we didn't break any windows.
Let's see what we have.
I think he's having
a heart attack, sir.
Really?
Peter?
- Peter?
- Peter.
Now he's dead.
Oh, well.
Lucas.
It's your turn.
So what is it,
the barrel or the card?
What would you rather do?
Two minutes held underwater.
I don't think I can do that.
I don't think I can.
We're running out of time here.
No.
I'll take my chances
with the card.
Okay.
What do we have?
What is it?
- Oh, well, that's...
- What...what is it?
This...this is...
Is very interesting.
You must...
Slit open your eye.
You can use this mirror,
if it helps.
No.
- That's it.
- That's it?
No, that's not it.
No, I can't do this.
- Lucas.
- I can't.
You made your decision.
This is how the game is played.
Pick up the razor blade.
Please.
- Pick it up.
- Please don't.
You sick fuck!
I will give you...
30 seconds to do this.
I can't do that!
30 seconds.
I can't do it!
- 30 seconds to do it...
- I can't do it.
- Or Bevans...
- I can't do it!
Will dispatch you.
Do you understand?
And by the way, you can pick
whichever eye you want.
It's completely up to you.
Go.
20 seconds.
Fuck!
I can't do it.
10 seconds.
Listen, Lucas,
he will eliminate you,
I am telling you.
Five, four, three,
two, one.
There.
All done.
Iris.
Are you interested in seeing
what's in your envelope?
No.
Oh, of course.
You're not the gambling type,
are you?
Oh, no, no, no.
No, you prefer the sure thing.
Thank you.
Lovely.
So...
Two minutes, yes?
Go.
I keep having this dream
that I'm on a boat.
Suddenly, the boat
tips over and throws me
into the water.
You and all these people
are pinned under it...
And you're drowning.
Come on, come on.
And I keep trying
to pull myself up,
but the more and more I do...
The more the boat
comes down with me.
And you are trying
to grab my hand,
trying to help me,
but we're sinking faster
and faster and faster until...
I just finally...
Yes!
Two minutes!
Iris!
Very impressive.
You know,
this is designed
to actually drown people.
What was in her card?
I have no idea.
Find out.
Set of lungs.
That was a close call, Iris.
All your teeth extracted.
Sorry, Bevans, maybe next year.
Is Amy ready?
So how long
can you hold your breath, Amy?
How long did it
take your husband
to hold your little girl
while he drowned her?
What is this?
It's another barrel,
with a four.
And that four stands for...
Four minutes.
That isn't possible.
No, technically,
it is possible.
Not even close to
the world record, by the way.
Well, I guess...
beggars can't be choosers.
I guess so.
Four minutes.
Ready, Bevans?
Go.
She wasn't ready!
At the beginning of the night,
I would have pegged her
as the odds-on favorite to win.
You never know, sir.
And then there were two.
Iris, I would like for you
to sit across from Lucas,
if you would, please.
Thank you.
We're in the final stretch now.
Now...
Before we begin
the final round,
I'd like to say a few words,
if I may.
I know that this evening
has been difficult.
For all of us, really.
But it has also been one
for the books.
And I speak not only for myself
but for Bevans and his staff
and the entire Lambrick family
when I say,
well played, both of you.
Personally, I'd be happy
if either one of you won.
Truly.
To the final round, then.
Now, in all likelihood,
the game will end
with the very first question
in this round.
We have found
that the player who goes first
in the final round
has a decided advantage.
Therefore, we will flip a coin.
Bevans.
Heads, Iris.
Tails, Lucas.
Bevans, if you would, please.
Heads it is.
Iris...
you're up.
The final question.
Would you rather,
A...
end the game right now,
you and Lucas free to leave,
empty-handed
but alive.
Or B...
With this dueling pistol
with a single round
in its chamber...
Eliminate Lucas,
claim victory
and salvation for your brother.
Which?
Iris.
It's over.
We're done. We can...
We can go home.
Iris,
I never told you why
I came here tonight.
I think you should hear it,
okay?
I think we have
some things in common.
You're here for someone else,
right?
Your brother.
Upcoming jump scare (Minor)
I'll bet you'd do anything
for him.
I know exactly how you feel.
I have three sisters...
We have a winner.
Brava!
Bravo!
This is yours.
There should be enough in there
to cover any debts
that your parents
left behind you,
plus enough for you
to go back to school.
We had previously located
a suitable donor in Romania.
Arrangements are already
being made as we speak,
and your brother will be
undergoing the procedure
before the week is out.
You see?
We keep our word.
I believe a "thank you"
is in order.
Thank you, Mr. Lambrick.
Oh, please.
No, no, no, call me Shep.
Raleigh.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
What did you do?
Oh, my God.